♪♪
[clattering]
Happy Hearth's Warming Eve!
[crash]
[giggle]
Shucks, Twilight, y'all done
it up nice and cozy in here.
We're about to hang our
Hearth's Warming Dolls,
if you want to join us.
Well, that's mighty
sweet of you,
but we're just stopping
in to wish y'all
a happy Hearth's
Warming before we go.
I think it's sweet
that your families
are spending the
holiday together.
Picture the most funtacular
thing you can think of.
Now multiply that times
infinity! IT'S GONNA BE GREAT!
[train whistle]
That's us! See you later!
Now can we open presents?
But tonight is
Hearth's Warming Eve.
Everypony knows you don't
open presents till tomorrow.
When Spike and I spent our first
Hearth's Warming Eve together,
he couldn't wait all night
to open his presents.
Ever since then, we've always
opened them the night before.
It's kinda like...
our tradition.
That's not how our
family does it.
And I reckon it can't be how
Pinkie's does it, is it?
No, sir-eee!
To each their own, I suppose.
[train whistle]
AH! GOTTA GO! BYE!
[grunts]
Just what I always
wanted! A book!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Chancellor Puddinghead Puddings?
How about a
Windigo-frosted snow cone?
It's so exciting. Related or
not, it's gonna be a hoot
havin' our families
together under one roof.
Apples and Pies, together again
for the first time, maybe,
unless we're related,
which maybe we're not.
I think I just
confused myself.
Friends or family, this
here's about togetherness.
Have you tried the
Equestria Flag Crepes?
The blue is BLUEBERRY!
And don't tell Granny I saw, but
her trunk is full of presents!
Applejack: Now hang
on, Sugarcube.
You know Hearth's
Warming isn't just about
candy and presents, right?
Uh oh. That's your boring
sisterly lecture voice.
'Fraid so. Ahem. A long
time ago, the Earth Ponies,
Pegasus Ponies,and Unicorn
Ponies weren't friends.
"I don't like you!"
"I don't like
you either!"
But then the icy
chill of the Windigos
almost iced up everything.
So the ponies decided
to work together
and their friendship drove
them nasty critters away.
"Beat it, Windigos!"
Triumphant, they raised
a new flag to celebrate
all three tribes, and
Equestria was born.
[chomp]
Uh, what happened
to the flag...?
[munching]
I don't know.
[gulp] [slurp]
Is that why we celebrate
with a flag-raising tomorrow?
Mm-hm. And tonight we'll
have the traditional
Hearth's Warming Eve Dinner
to remember the shared
bounties of our ancestors.
We do that, too!
Then we'll hang our
Hearth's Warming Dolls
over the fireplace, to remind
us of the warmth shared
on that fateful night.
That's what our family does too!
And tomorrow, we open presents.
WE DO THAT TOO!
It sounds like the
Apples and the Pies
do everything the same way.
Of course! We might be related!
Hey, I was going to say that!
Stop saying what I'm saying!
You stop it first!
[laughter]
[train whistle blows]
[squeaking wheels and brakes]
[train whistle]
I'm so happy I need to make up
a new word for how happy I am.
What about, "Rooftastic!"?
Rooftastic?
As in: I gotta get on the
roof and yell to everypony
HOW ROOFTASTIC THIS IS!
[crash]
What if our families
don't like each other?
We are friends,
Applejack.
And after tonight, our families
are going to be friends too!
Do you know what
that means?
Number of Apples times
number of Pies is 24
minus my pre-existing
friendships plus 1 for Maud
and you makes 5 from 24 is--
[big breath]
Nineteen new friendships!
Maud!
[monotone voice]
I'm so excited to see you,
Pinkie Pie. You too, Applejack.
I hope you had fun
sledding yesterday.
How'd you know that?
Isn't it obvious?
There's specks of Extrusive
Andesite on your hoof.
It's a mountain rock.
Oh... she's good.
How's school going?
If you thought Quartz was high
on the Mohs Hardness Scale,
wait'll I tell you
about Corundum.
I missed you so much!
♪♪
This place looks amazing!
C'mon everypony, meet my
super-mega-funderful family!
♪♪
Everypony... meet... everypony!
Surely thy name is
not but Granny Smith.
I am called Igneous Rock Pie,
son of Feldspar Granite Pie.
Thou shalt know me
as Cloudy Quartz.
May providence favor thee
well and to thou comfort
our humble homestead bring.
Y'all gabbin' with
words real funny-like.
What'd ya say them names were:
"Iggy?" And I'm just gonna
call you, "Big Mama Q."
Gaze into the eyes
of Limestone Pie.
Ma and Pa may own this rock
farm, but I keep it running.
Cross me and--
--Aye aye, Captain Grumpy!
No one's gonna mess
with your precious mine.
Or Holder's Boulder!
[sigh]
Everypony stay away
from Holder's Boulder.
There, you happy now?
And you must be...
This is Marble
Pie, my baby sister
who's only a few
minutes younger than me
but she'll always be a baby
to me, isn't that right?
She's so excited
to meet everypony!
Oh, and she wishes you all
a happy Hearth's Warming!
Mmm-hmm.
Guess Pinkie Pie always
did the talkin' for her.
[giggle]
[beckoning whistle]
ATTENTION!
What'd I say about the boulder?
I'll just be a second!
Everypony, get settled in.
There's plenty of room upstairs,
and then it's time for
Hearth's Warming Eve Dinner!
So far, so good "cousin!"
Hee Hee!
I can't wait to taste
their fresh sweet rolls.
They're my favorite part of
Hearth's Warming Eve Dinner.
I'm more of a six-layer
bean dip filly, myself.
I love that too! Oh, Applejack,
do you think theirs will
be even better than ours?
Oh, that's a mighty tall order,
but it wouldn't surprise
me in the least.
Are you excited for dinner
time because guess who is?
Spoiler alert: it's ME!
[clunk]
♪♪
What about hot rolls? And mulled
cider? And double-baked pot-pie?
What about 6-layer bean dip?
We have rock soup.
Potato, po-tah-to!
Double-baked-pot-pie, rock soup!
Dinner is dinner, Am
I right or am I right?
Yeah, um... you know what?
This is what we were
expecting, right everypony?
[mumbles]
Heh heh.
[slurp]
Is everything all
right, Applejack?
Of course. I'm just
bein' a rusty fiddle.
Tune me up and let's
get back to dinner!
[slurping]
[choke]
More rock, please!
Eat up, so we can get to
our Hearth's Warming dolls!
Now that's somethin'
I know all about.
Who wants a Hearth's
Warming doll?
Are you sayin' that rock
is a Hearth's Warming Doll?
Don't be silly, silly.
[crack]
Our dolls are these
little pieces!
Isn't that right, Marble Pie?
Mm-hm.
[clinking]
Our dolls... are rocks?
[crack]
Y'all don't have
traditional crocheted dolls
passed down in your family?
Ohhhh, you're just
a frown factory
because you got a weird rock.
Cheer up! I'm sure
you'll do great in the
Flag-Finding Mission.
What-findin' what-now?
Limestone Pie, you're the judge.
Big Mac? Marble
Pie? You're team 1.
Apple Bloom and
Maud? You're team 2.
Ma? Pa? You're gonna
be with Granny Smith.
Don't think of it as "team old,"
think of it as team three.
And I'm with
Applejack, of course!
Since we might be cousins!
So now that we're all split up,
mind tellin' us
what we're doing?
As everypony knows--
STAY OFF HOLDER'S BOULDER!
Sheesh.
When the three tribes
united to form Equestria,
the first flag was
sewn by Nimble Thimble.
It's tradition to raise a
flag on Hearth's Warming
to celebrate that famous day.
[agreement]
But who gets to put the
flag on Holder's Bolder?
You mean on the flagpole?
No, silly!
It goes on the highest point.
And who's the lucky pony?
Traditionally, it's
the youngest...
ON YOUR MARK, GET SET, GO!
Pinkie Pie, will you please
tell us what's going on?
I'll explain on the way!
Oh!
I still don't understand.
Earlier today, Limestone
Pie hid an obsidian stone.
Whoever finds it gets
to raise the flag!
It's all just so...
complicated. And "rock-based."
Well, how else would we do it?
I don't know.
I sure hope everypony else
is havin' a better time.
Mmm-hmm.
Eyup.
Mmmmmmm-hmm.
Eyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyup.
So, how'd ya meet
this Iggy fella?
We were chosen by
the pairing stone
and betrothed
within a fortnight.
The choosing stone decreed
"thou shalt love one another,"
and lo, it was so.
Hoo-wee. I gotsta look into this
oldfangled choosin' stone thing.
Do you reckon it knows
any Apple farmin' hunks?
Indeed so.
What does the rock look like?
It looks like
something that formed
when volcanic lava
cooled quickly.
Oh.
Have you ever wished you
could turn into a rock?
I had a dream once
I was an apple.
We have a lot in common
when it comes to thinking
about turning into things.
Pinkie: FOUND IT!
FOUND IT! FOUND IT!
A picture? I been lookin'
for a real stone, Pinkie Pie.
Um, that would be weird. Do
you know what this means?
I get to raise the flag! And now
it's time to hide the presents!
Y'all hide your presents?
Of course! What's more fun
than getting a present?
FINDING A PRESENT!
Although most years
nopony finds one.
So nopony gets presents?
Not usually.
So let me get all this straight.
You're only allowed to
eat Rock Soup for dinner.
Then, the pony who finds this
rock gets to raise the flag,
but not really cause you
don't got no flag pole.
And to top it off, you
don't even get presents?
Well, it doesn't sound very
fun when you say it THAT way.
Well, how about
you picture this:
both our families, opening
presents, raising the flag...
Picturing it, loving it!
Goodnight, everypony!
Goodnight, Pinkie Pie!
We gotta do something, y'all.
Pinkie Pie's family's never
had a real Hearth's Warming.
Is that really what she said?
Well, I'm sure it's
what she meant.
These are their traditions.
Eyup.
I know they have their
traditions and we have ours,
but I just want them to see how
much better theirs could be.
[rooster crows]
Hearth's Warming!
Hearth's Wa-
Oh, my, oh my.
What. Happened. To. My. Farm.
It's Hearth's
Warming, Apple style!
We've been doing
everything your way.
I thought we could
mix it up a bit.
Marble Pie, you could raise the
Equestria flag up this pole,
because you're the youngest Pie.
Ma and Pa Pie, we'll cook you up
a meal you'll never forget.
And look, we all get presents
without having to find 'em!
Yeah! This is going to be great!
All the stuff she
said. Right, everypony?
Pinkamina Diane Pie, truly thou
do not favor this madness?
Well, I want to
be one big family.
But what about
what we usually do?
I, um, well? I don't know!
Don't make me choose!
I didn't mean to cause a fuss.
Why don't we just open
presents around the flagpole.
It'll be fun, you'll see.
Excuse me. You planted
your pole on a fault line.
[crackling]
[crash]
NOOOOOOOO!
[smash]
[sigh] Oh boy.
You didn't have to
ask them to leave.
They wanted to go.
We don't need anypony forcing
their way into our family.
This was all a
misunderstanding, everypony.
I know Applejack,
and she'd never do
anything bad to anypony.
Look around, Pinkie Pie.
It's gonna take me ages to get
this rock farm back on track.
And how're we gonna
lift Holder's Boulder?
This is all her fault.
Then it's my fault too.
Probably best if we head
back to Sweet Apple Acres.
Maybe in time we'll
be friends again.
But for the now it's best if
we give them a little space.
I wish we didn't have
to. I really like Maud.
She's sweet once you get
to know her. They all are.
Worst Hearth's Warming ever.
Has anypony seen Applejack?
[sobbing]
I really cracked
the corn this time.
I really popped the
piñata this time.
Pinkie Pie?
Ah! What are you
doing here?
What are you
I came here to think.
You did? So did I!
[laughing]
I'm too ashamed to
go back up there.
Your family, my family?
They all must think
I'm such a nincompoop.
Aw, no one thinks that.
Pushy, aggressive, mean.
Oh I'm not helping, sorry.
I'm sorry I forced my
traditions over yours.
I don't want you to have to
choose between the family
you were born into, and the
friends who love you like one.
I really hoped we could be
one big family. I guess not.
Don't say that!
[train whistle]
I wish I could stay but
I have a train to catch.
Hap... hap... happy
Hearth's Warming.
You, too.
[rattling train wheels]
You wanna know why Holder's
Boulder's so dangit important?
Well, now, their great great
great great great grandfather,
Holder Cobblestone, he found
that boulder in a Dragon's nest,
older than time itself.
He built the family
farm around it,
even though it was just
an ordinary rock.
It's always brought
them good luck.
Crickets! That is important.
I got so caught up in the
things they were doin',
I never asked why they did 'em.
[clatter]
"To Applejack, from Pinkie
Pie. ...cousins forever."
You just found your first Pie
Hearth's Warming present ever!
Only Pinkie Pie could hide a
present on a moving train.
What a great tradition!
STOP THE TRAIN!
♪♪
[grunts and groans]
C'mon, you boulder, c'mon!
I'm pushing as
hard as I can, too.
[grunts and groans]
Oh, it's hopeless.
Applejack: Need a
little help?
Pinkie: [gasp] Apples!
What do you want?
I wasn't trying to take
your traditions away;
I was trying to share ours.
I was so focused on us
bein' one big happy family,
I thought we needed the
same traditions right away.
What I shoulda done
is learn about yours
and teach you about ours.
And over time, we'd make
new traditions together.
I'm sorry, y'all.
Well, don't just stand there.
We got a boulder
to move!
♪ [bells] ♪
And I'm in charge!
[grunts and groans]
I think we just invented our
first combined tradition!
Pushing Holder's Boulder
out of the Quarry!
I can't wait for
Applejack to knock it over
next Hearth's Warming!
[laughter]
♪♪
Marble Pie, you want to wish Big
Mac a happy Hearth's Warming,
don't you? And you
too, right, Big Mac?
Mm-hm.
Eyup.
Uh, let me see here.
"If thou asketh me...
Thou two art OK-eth in my book."
"Yee...haw?"
♪♪
Happy Hearth's Warming.
Happy Hearth's
Warming, Pinkie Pie.
Attention, everypony!
Maud wants to sing some Hearth's
Warming carols that she wrote!
[excited chatter]
The first one is about rocks.
They're all about rocks.
♪♪
Hearth's Warming is great,
like Calcium Silicate.
What a wonderful day,
as good as Mica or Clay...