♪♪
Phew! Thanks
for helping me
get them so fresh
and clean, Twilight.
No problem!
Happy to do it.
You probably can't wait to
get back to your castle
and take your
own bath, huh?
Aren't there more animals
that need cleaning?
I think you and I are
the only ones left.
And I can't wait to get
the mud out of my mane!
[splash]
Oh no! Angel
got dirty!
I'd better stay longer to
help give him a bath, too.
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪ ♪
Fluttershy: Thank you ever
so much for staying
to give Angel a bath, too...
But um, I think
he's dry.
Goodness! It's
gotten late.
You really didn't
have to stay all day.
Not that we don't
appreciate it.
Isn't that right?
I for one am exhausted.
[exaggerated yawn]
Plus, I really
need to rest up
for that big pancake
breakfast tomorrow!
And I'm sure you have to
get the castle ready--
No! The castle's...fine.
[brightening]
But maybe I'd better see if
Pinkie Pie needs help
with the pancakes!
[slam]
Um...Angel?
[munching]
[appreciative murmurs]
These are delicious,
Pinkie Pie!
[slurp] [gulp]
Thanks! Twilight spent all night
helping me pick the flavor.
I kept thinking we'd
found the right one,
but she insisted I
make even more to try.
And more. And more.
And more. And more. And more!
It was like she
never wanted to--
--leave?
Exactly!
[munch]
Eventually we ran out of
time so we just went with
Everyberry Anychip Surprise.
The surprise is I lost a
measuring spoon in the batter.
Somepony's gonna get a
very special pancake.
Rainbow: Up all night, huh?
Is that why she's so...
uh... out of it?
[snoring]
Um, I don't mean to
sound unappreciative,
but has anypony else noticed
that Twilight's been
a little too helpful lately?
Now that you mention it,
she was lendin' a hoof
at Sweet Apple
Acres the other day
and stuck around
till near midnight.
Dug up fifty tree-plantin' holes
when all I needed was ten.
Rarity: She spent an entire
afternoon rearranging
a single gem drawer
at the boutique.
An entire afternoon!
Rainbow: You think that's weird?
She raced me, like, a hundred
times the other day
and lost every time.
She just kept going!
Best out of ten.
Best out of twenty.
Best out of a hundred!
I mean, I know hanging
out with me is awesome
but it was like she'd
rather keep losing than--
--leave?
Yeah.
Who does that?
[snoring]
[splat]
Somepony who's avoiding
something, that's who.
Soon as she wakes up,
we're gonna find out what.
[cough]
I WIN!
[gasp]
I'm pancake!
I mean, awake!
Uh, Twilight, is there
something you want to tell us?
You know how much we
appreciate all you do for us,
and we simply adore
having you around.
But we worry you might be...
avoiding something else?
Oh, has it been
that obvious?
I've been...
The thing is...
I know it's silly but I...
I've been avoiding...this place.
[gasp] Why in Equestria
would you want to avoid
such a gorgeous castle?
Yeah, this place
has everything!
Big tall ceilings that
make you feel tiny.
Shiny new floors that
are cold to the touch.
BRR!
And it even has long
empty hallways... [echoes]
...hallways... hallways.
OK, I get it.
The castle is amazing.
But it just...
[sigh]
It doesn't feel like home.
[laughing]
Is that all?
Why you simply need
to decorate, darling.
Make this space your own!
It's just so daunting.
Look how big it is.
I don't even know
where to start.
You can start by letting
us do it for you!
We will make this the
castle of your dreams
while you go the
Ponyville spa
for some much needed
rest and relaxation.
I'm saying this
with love, but...
have you looked in
a mirror lately?
I've never seen you look this...
Frazzled?
Yes, that is absolutely the
word I was going to use.
I guess I do need a little
help, and so does my castle.
And I just know
you'll do a great job
because nopony knows
me better than you!
We'll make this place feel
cozier than hot cider
on a rainy day.
There's gonna be cider?
Uh...I mean, let's decorate!
Spike: Oh no, did I
miss the pancakes?
I sleep like a baby under
that cold, cavernous ceiling.
Spike, I'm so
glad you're here!
Really?
Yes. You're taking
Twilight to the spa.
Great! I've been meaning
to get my claws done.
[munch]
Oh. You mean now.
♪♪
Come on y'all, we've
got work to do!
♪ [orchestra with mandolin] ♪
♪ Let's all work together,
To make this castle shine. ♪
♪ Once we add some sparkle, ♪
♪ It'll feel, It'll feel,
♪ It'll feel ♪
♪ It'll feel divine! ♪
♪ Crates of apples
and bales of hay, ♪
♪ Just makes you feel at home! ♪
♪ Furry friends and
some popinjays, ♪
♪ So she won't be alone! ♪
♪ And we'll make, and we'll
make, and we'll make ♪
♪ this castle a home! ♪
♪♪
♪ There's nothing like
balloons and confetti, ♪
♪ To greet you every time
you walk through the door! ♪
♪ She'll need this and those
posters up of my heroes, ♪
♪ how could anypony awesome
ever ask for more! ♪
♪ And we'll make, and we'll
make, and we'll make ♪
♪ a home she'll adore! ♪
♪♪
♪ Bright curtains of
flowing silk and lace! ♪
♪ This picture of
me winning a race! ♪
♪ Party cannons to
give her a surprise! ♪
♪ Hoes and rakes and some
more garden supplies! ♪
♪ Getting hugs from this
nice big friendly bear! ♪
♪ Decorate with some
gemstones bright and rare! ♪
♪ More of this and that! ♪
♪ Don't forget the party hats! ♪
♪ How could anypony awesome
ask for more than that! ♪
♪♪
Let's all work together
To show that we have shown
Princess Twilight Sparkle
♪ How we make,
how we make, ♪
♪ how we make this
castle a home! ♪
♪ How we make,
how we make, ♪
♪ this castle a home! ♪
♪ How we make,
how we make, ♪
♪ this castle a home! ♪
♪♪
[bird squawks]
[squirrel chitters]
♪♪
Applejack: Wow, girls.
[unsure] We did a great job.
Together!
Heh heh.
Yeah, that sure is something.
We sure did.
[chirps]
Fluttershy, I love that you
brought so many animals.
Are these your trophies?
I prefer to think of them
as everypony's trophies.
But with my name permanently
etched onto them.
My my, Applejack.
Bringing the outdoors
inside, it's...earthy.
What a lovely touch.
[sniff sniff]
Are these quilts vintage?
Nope. Just old.
Unlike your sparkly window
doohickeys, which are...
why, they're just swell.
No one said anything about
my hidden confetti cannons!
Oh right. They're hidden.
[giggle]
Hey guys, how do my claws
look? SWEET CELESTIA!
Oh! Spike! Are you and
Twilight done already?
Don't worry, I ordered her the
super-deluxe mane blowout.
She'll be a while.
Man, this place looks terrible!
[relieved sighs]
Thank goodness somepony
said something.
It's pretty bad, right?
This place looks like a
mishmash of knickknacks.
Hmmm, I suppose it is
a little cluttered.
What are you guys talking about?
I think it looks super fun!
[pow]
[animal sounds]
[crash]
[growl]
Whee!
Oh no!
Please don't do that.
If we could all just take a
deep breath and calm down...
[crash]
[chitters]
No! That bunting is
embroidered by hoof!
Don't you move one more paw!
[rip]
EVERYPONY STOP!
[tire screech]
[clatter]
OK, now it's a mess.
[pow]
What are we gonna do?
I don't know, but Twilight's
blowout won't take that long!
If she was avoiding
the castle before,
she'll never set
hoof in here now!
Come on, guys!
We've gotta do something!
Twilight's counting on us!
Spike, you've got to get back
to that spa and stall her!
Whatever you do, don't
let her come home!
Like forever?
But we live here.
Uh...yes.
Well uh, maybe you
could manage until...
...sunsetish?
Anything for you, Rarity!
OK, we all agree the castle
is too cluttered, right?
So why doesn't everypony take
one of their own decorations out
and we'll see how it looks?
Uh huh!
Spike, you're back!
How do I look?
Great!
And more importantly,
how does the castle look?
Great!
I can't wait to go
home and see it!
Great!
I mean, NO!
I mean, uh, I'm not
quite ready to go yet.
Why don't we have a massage?
I was really hoping to
get uh, this thingy!
The extra strength hot
stone deep tissue massage?
[gulp]
Yep.
I think I'll just have
a traditional massage,
but you go for it.
Did somepony order massages?
[crash]
YEAH!
Let's DO this, little dragon!
[crash]
Oh, I hate it when
he does that.
Come with me, Princess.
Come on, Rarity.
Everypony has taken
somethin' out except you.
I know!
I simply can't decide.
How about this?
No! Not that!
Anything but that!
How about these?
But those brighten
up the whole room!
They're my favorite accent!
Then let's lose the curtains.
The room wouldn't
need brightening
if they weren't
making it so dark!
Not them!
They're my favorite, too!
They can't all be
your favorite!
OK, I'm taking
down the portrait.
We already know
what we look like.
The room still looks a little
bit cluttered, doesn't it?
Perhaps I'll take
down a poster or two.
Only to be helpful, of course!
OK, everypony calm down.
I'm sure we can find a way
to remove the clutter...
together!
You're absolutely
right, dear.
Hey! Those are my
warmin' quilts!
Together!
[popping]
Fluttershy, tell your birds to
stop pecking at my balloons!
I guess they must not like being
scared out of their wits
by exploding confetti
cannons or something.
But we can't get
rid of the cannons!
I don't remember
where I hid 'em!
[pop]
Allow me to help you!
Applejack: Oh no,
I'll help you!
Rainbow: NOT IF I
HELP YOU FIRST!
Ah. Great
suggestion, Spike.
I feel totally relaxed.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow!
You wanna hop on?
Maybe I can get us
to the castle faster.
OW!
I mean, how...
nice is this day?
I was hoping we could
take the scenic way back.
I don't know.
Come on.
Walking is good for
post-massage circulation.
Really?
I've never heard
that theory.
[sigh] I really miss
this place, Spike.
We had so many wonderful
memories here.
We did, didn't we?
Oh Spike, I'm so sorry.
Of course losing the Golden Oak
Library was hard for you too.
I've got an idea!
Why don't we have the
girls add some things
to make the castle feel more
like your home as well?
Really?
Hop on!
[thud]
Ow!
What are you doing?
I, um, I just thought
of what I want.
Oh. OK. What is it?
It's a...
Well, I want a...
it's - I kinda need a...
A bed.
I thought you said you sleep
like a baby in the castle.
Pfft! Everypony knows babies
are terrible sleepers.
Let's go!
There! Now nothing is
cluttering the castle!
You're right.
There is literally NOTHING
cluttering this castle!
What do we do now?
I hate to be the bearer
of more bad news,
but it's almost sunset.
If we don't figure
this out soon,
it's going to look like we
didn't lift a hoof to help her.
Why is this so hard?
We're Twilight's best friends.
This should be easy for us!
She said it herself: if
anypony should be able
to make her feel comfortable
in her new home, it's us.
If we can't do it...
...then Twilight will be
stuck living in a castle
that just makes her
feel sad...
[echoes]
...sad...sad.
Wow, Fluttershy, I
didn't know you could be
loud enough to echo.
[muttering to
herself]
What do we do?
If Twilight comes home
now she'll be like
"What did you guys do?"
And we'll have to
be like "NOTHING!"
And then she'll be like
"I was counting on you!
Some friends you are!"
and we'll be like "AAAHHH!"
[blubbering]
Calm down, Pinkie.
We just need to figure
out what we did wrong
so we can make it right.
Rarity: Well, I didn't
do anything wrong.
I did exactly what I would
do if this were my home.
But it's not your home;
it's Twilight's home!
Where she keeps all her
Rainbow Dash trophies?
Touché.
Fluttershy: Maybe we're
all a little guilty
of making ourselves feel at
home instead of Twilight.
Come on, y'all, we just need
to think about Twilight!
What was it she
loved about living
in the Golden Oak Library?
Oh, everything!
The books, the
smell of books,
the joy she felt from
organizing books.
Remember that time I crashed
into all those books
attempting my Sonic Rainboom
after you guys just cleaned up?
[sigh] That was good times.
Yeah, for YOU, maybe.
Rarity: Oh and Applejack,
remember when we were stuck
having a sleepover there?
That turned out
to be so much fun!
Remember the time it got
blown up to smithereens?
Wait, no. That
was the worst!
We had a lot of good
memories there, though.
That's what made the
Golden Oak Library home.
[all agree]
[gasp] That's it!
How's that one?
Too soft?
Too hard?
Too lumpy?
Ummm...
Just right! I'll take it!
Oh, thank goodness.
I thought you'd never
find one you liked.
Let's find a salespony
and get out of here.
Sounds good to me!
I mean, uh...
Do you hear that?
[imitates a squeak]
Too squeaky.
Better keep looking.
[growl]
Applejack: [sigh]
Maybe my plan won't
work after all.
Of course it will,
darling! I can see it!
You and Fluttershy stay here.
Rainbow Dash and Pinkie
Pie, you come with me!
We're going shopping!
We'll meet back at the castle!
♪ [mandolin and orchestra] ♪
♪ It's not the things
that you gather round. ♪
♪ It's not how much you own. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The things that hold the
meaning in your life, ♪
♪ are the memories
you've sown. ♪
♪ So we make, so we make, so
we make this castle a home! ♪
we make this castle a HOME! ♪
♪♪
Hello? We're home!
All: Welcome home!
Oh. I, uh, love what you've
done with the place!
You did such a good job of...
preserving the integrity
of the original design.
Spike: Oh, come on!
It looks exactly the same!
Do you know how hard it was to
keep her from coming back here?
I never want to see another
dust ruffle as long as I live!
Twilight: Wait.
Keep me from coming back here?
It took a teensy bit
longer than we thought.
What really makes home feel like
home isn't what it looks like,
it's the memories you
make when you're there.
So we made something that
celebrates the memories
we've made with you since
you moved to Ponyville.
♪♪
The ornaments on the chandelier
are reminders of all the fun
we've had together.
That one shows your party at
the Golden Oak Library
welcoming you to Ponyville.
The time we shared donuts after
the Grand Galloping Gala.
We were hoping that being able
to look at your beautiful
old memories would inspire
you to make new ones.
And the best part of it is
it's made from the roots
of the Golden Oak Library.
So you'll never forget
where you came from.
♪♪
It's exactly what
the castle needed.
And I am ready to make
new memories here!
Then let's start right now
with a new memory cake!
Seven Layer What's-That-Flavor
Mystery Surprise!
These might be chocolate chips
or they might be super
spicy black beans.
Let's go to the dining room!
It's a little sparse
but at least there's a
table and chairs.
Whoa! What
happened in here?
Last I checked this
place was empty!
I couldn't help myself.
It was just begging
for the personal touch.
Truth be told, I
couldn't either.
Your kitchen might have some
rustic farm decor, Twilight.
And there may or may not be
some Derring Do posters
up in your library.
And some stuffed
animals in your bedroom.
[pop and cheers]
What was that?
One of Pinkie Pie's
confetti cannons.
What! It's not my fault
I hid them so well!
[sigh] Ah, Pinkie!
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ friends ♪