♪♪
OK, Crusaders!
Back to the business of
earnin' our Cutie Marks.
Any suggestions?
No! We've tried everything!
We've run out of ideas.
Are you kiddin' me, Crusaders?
We can do better than that!
♪♪
♪ We've been searching
for our cutie marks ♪
♪ for a while now ♪
♪ trying to find out
how we fit in ♪
♪ so many ways we've
tried before ♪
♪ but we keep on
trying more ♪
♪ Cause the Cutie Mark
Crusaders don't give in! ♪
♪ We'll make our mark!
One way or another ♪
♪ We'll make our mark on
the day that we discover ♪
♪ the ultimate reward
of our cutie marks! ♪
Now that's more like it!
Cutie Mark Crusaders! HELP!
What's wrong, Pip Squeak?
I'm running for
Student Pony President!
I was hoping you three would
be my campaign managers.
We've never tried getting our
Cutie Marks in campaign managing
What do you say, Crusaders?
YEAH! HA!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
So, Pip? How would
you help the school
if you were elected
Student Pony President?
Our playground equipment
took quite a beating
during Twilight's
battle with Tirek!
If I'm voted in as
Student Pony President,
I'll go to the School
Board and right this wrong!
(cheers)
Well, I think that's a
ridiculous waste of money.
It's just like when Twist
proposed to repair the window
that Discord destroyed.
She just wanted
to repair it
like a plain old
schoolhouse window!
But you all know voting
for me was the best choice
because I convinced
the School Board
to give that window
visual appeal!
'Course it doesn't hurt that
her mother, Spoiled Rich,
is President of
the School Board!
Exactly! Which is why when
Diamond Tiara is voted
Student Pony President,
the school will be
putting a statue of her
in the center of our schoolyard!
Silver Spoon! That was my big
announcement for when I won!
I was only
trying to help.
I don't need that
kind of help.
Haven't we all had
enough of Diamond Tiara?
Do we really need a
big statue of her?
Especially where our playground
equipment should be?
[chattering]
A vote for Pip is a
vote for the playground!
A vote for Diamond Tiara is a
Vote for MORE Diamond Tiara!
♪ It's time to make a change
This is our chance! ♪
♪ Don't be afraid to do what's
right! He's it, vote for pip! ♪
♪ We've got an opportunity
To have fun again! ♪
♪ A vote for Pip and you
can join the fight! ♪
♪ It's time for a new leader
It's time to make a change ♪
♪ We're here to fight for what
we believe Vote for Pip! ♪
♪ It's finally time we beat
her and play a better game ♪
♪ Cause when we vote together, ♪
♪ there's nothing that
we can't achieve! ♪
♪♪
♪ I don't believe
what I am hearing! ♪
♪ I'm the only one you
should be cheering! ♪
♪ Pip Squeak, try Pip's
weak, don't you think? ♪
♪ But a diamond is perfection.
it's natural selection ♪
♪ So your vote better be for
me, not the weakest link! ♪
♪ We'll let the voting decide! ♪
♪ Everypony has their little
secrets (I know you do) ♪
♪ A vote for me will help
you keep them safe! ♪
Like your creepy super strength
Or your mane extension, a
little thing I won't mention!
♪ Or those freakish large
teeth in your face! ♪
Come on now, Ponies,
don't listen to her!
♪ You got to vote for change!
It's time for a new leader ♪
♪ End all the tyranny, vote
now and we can beat her! ♪
♪ It's now another day and we
believe in what's right! ♪
♪ Vote for Pip, vote for Pip!
Our Victory is in sight! ♪
Stop! Everypony who
hasn't voted, listen up!
♪ Pip makes promises he can't
keep, but I can do more! ♪
♪ You could really
use a new book bag ♪
♪ Cause I'll make
things happen ♪
♪ that none of you here can
afford to do, like ever! ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like a
little something sweet? ♪
♪ Here's a parasol to
hide you from the heat! ♪
♪ Who says that I
can't be nice? ♪
♪ But first there's one thing
an itsy-bitsy little string ♪
♪ And voting for me
is the price! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I've a tiny suggestion!
That you should be aware ♪
♪ You could probably
win this election ♪
♪ If you SHOW THEM
ALL YOU REALLY-- ♪
I don't recall
asking you to speak!
[gasp]
Well, if that's how you
treat your best friend,
then I choose Pip Squeak!
♪ Vote! ♪
♪ Stand strong and
don't be afraid! ♪
♪ Vote Pip! ♪
♪ Ponies! Let's free
ourselves from the past ♪
♪ Vote! He's it,
vote for Pip! Vote! ♪
♪ Let honour win out
against the tyranny! ♪
♪ And Make a change
that will last! ♪
♪ Vote for Pip! ♪
♪ It's time for a new leader
It's time to make a change ♪
♪ We're here to fight
for what we believe! ♪
♪ Vote for Pip! ♪
♪ It's finally time we beat
her and play a better game ♪
♪ Cause when we vote together, ♪
♪ there's nothing that
we can't achieve! ♪
♪ Vote for Pip! ♪
The votes have been counted.
The Student Pony President
is...Pip Squeak!
Huh?
[cheer]
Oh, my gosh, Crusaders! Pip won!
I couldn't have won
without the hard work
of my campaign managers,
the Cutie Mark Crusaders!
Campaign Manager Cutie Marks!
Guess you're not as good as
you thought, Blank Flanks!
In fact, I demand a recount!
Trust me, Diamond
Tiara. Pip won.
I'll be the judge of
that, Miss Cheerilee!
WHAAAAAAAAT??!
ONE VOTE?
SILVER SPOON? YOU
didn't vote for me?
No, I didn't!
But you're my best friend!
Am I? Cause I tried
to help by mentioning
your "surprise statue"
and suddenly I wasn't
even allowed to speak!
You could have actually
won this election
if you'd just listened to
me. You wanna know how?
Sorry. I'm not
allowed to speak.
[shriek]
What? I don't have to
follow her drama anymore.
I know Diamond Tiara's
been pretty awful,
but we should probably
make sure she's OK.
Just 'cause she's never cared
about anypony else's feelings
doesn't mean we shouldn't
care about hers.
♪♪
Diamond Tiara, why are
you making that face?
That is not the
face of a winner.
Because I didn't win.
What? You mean I hefted
all these party supplies
to celebrate nothing?
Sorry, Mother.
It's bad enough you lost to that
transplant from Trottingham.
But imagine if you'd lost to
one of those Blank Flanks!
As a rich pony, you must always
think of your social standing!
That starts here in Ponyville
and reaches all over Equestria.
Don't ever forget that,
Diamond Tiara! Ever!
♪♪
♪ If I'm a diamond, then
why do I feel so rough? ♪
♪ I'm as strong as a stone,
even that's not enough ♪
♪ There's something jagged in me
and I've made such mistakes ♪
♪ I thought that
diamonds were hard, ♪
♪ though I feel I could break. ♪
♪ Would you believe, ♪
♪ that I've always wished
I could be somepony else ♪
♪ Yet I can't see,
what I need to do ♪
♪ to be the pony I want to be. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I've been told my whole life,
what to do, what to say ♪
♪ Nopony showed me that there
might be some better way ♪
♪ And now I feel like I'm
lost, I don't know what to do ♪
♪ The ground is sinking away,
I'm about to fall through ♪
♪ Would you believe, ♪
♪ that I've always wished
I could be somepony else ♪
♪ Yet I can't see,
what I need to do ♪
♪ to be the pony I want to be. ♪
♪♪
♪ To be the pony I want to be ♪
Is it weird that I
feel bad for her?
If it is, then
I'm weird too.
She wants to change, but
she doesn't know how.
Seems like she could
use a friend or two
to help her figure it out.
[bell rings]
[chatter]
Hey, Diamond Tiara! Wait up!
What do you three want? To
gloat? Rub in my defeat?
Actually, we wanted to
invite you to our clubhouse
to hang out.
Really?
Yeah. For real.
Well, thanks to you all,
I don't have any important Class
President business to attend to
or anything. So,
I might as well.
That sounds like a yes.
So, do you three just sit around
here plotting out different ways
to try and get your Cutie Marks?
Actually, yeah.
You three are...really lucky.
We are?
Yeah. You get to explore
all these options,
learning who you really are
before you're stuck with
something you don't understand.
But you've done that, right?
Yeah! Cause I have
my Cutie Mark!
And I'm not struggling
at all to figure out
who I'm supposed to be and
what I'm supposed to be doing
with this mark that's
already on my flank.
Uh, are you sure about that?
That's a weird question.
Not really since we kind of
overheard you yesterday.
Were you trying to get
your Cutie Mark in spying?
Is that on your little chart?
No! We were just worried about
you when you lost the election
and then you lost your friend
and then your mom yelled at you.
We know you wanna change
and we think we can...
HEEEEELP!
Cutie Mark Crusaders!
I was at the School Board
Meeting and they didn't approve
my request for the new
playground equipment.
Why not?
There's no money in the budget!
So I checked my Peggy Bank
to see if I had enough bits,
but my little Peggy wasn't
nearly full enough.
Don't worry, Pip!
We'll meet you back at school!
And help you find a solution!
Thanks, Cutie Mark Crusaders!
Oh, I already
have a solution.
Our new Student
Pony President
is going to be kicked out of
office and I'll be reinstated!
Where is she going?
Where do you think!
C'mon, after her!
Wait, I'm coming too!
♪ Cutie Mark Crusaders,
get out of my way! ♪
♪ Those ponies need
to know the truth ♪
♪ and they'll hear it from me! ♪
♪♪
♪ Stop! Diamond Tiara,
this is not the way! ♪
♪♪
♪ We know you're better
than this hostility. ♪
♪♪
♪ You don't even know
me at all ♪
♪ Don't understand the
meaning of my fault ♪
♪ What the family would think
if I ever fail at anything! ♪
♪♪
♪ I'm a diamond
that means you never break! ♪
♪ No matter what the cost
of the path I take! ♪
♪ Whatever I have to
do to win in the end! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Stop! This is not
the answer! ♪
♪ Wait! And it's plainly seen! ♪
♪ Listen! You can redeem
yourself, ♪
♪ but by something other,
not by being mean! ♪
♪ We know you want
friends who admire you! ♪
♪ You want to be the star
with all the power too! ♪
♪ But there's a better way!
There's a better way! ♪
♪ There's so much more still
left to learn about yourself! ♪
♪ See the light that
shines in you! ♪
♪ We know you can
be somepony else! ♪
♪♪
♪ You can stop right now
and try another start! ♪
♪ You'll finallly free
yourself from the dark! ♪
♪ And see the light, and see
the light of your cutie mark! ♪
♪♪
Everypony! I have
an announcement!
♪♪
Diamond Tiara!
Think hard about the choice
your makin' right now!
You can be a
better pony!
Diamond Tiara!
I just happen to be here
for the School Board Meeting
and this is what I see when
we adjourn? My daughter
associating with confused,
insignificant, low-lifes?
Socializing with their
kind is not how you move up
in Equestria! Come,
Diamond Tiara!
No, Mother!
Excuse me?
You've spent your life
acting like a high horse
and raised me to follow
in your hoofprints.
At first, I thought
this was fine,
but then I finally realized I
wanted something you don't have,
FRIENDS!
[gasps]
That's enough,
Diamond Tiara!
Step away from
those BLANK FLANKS!
These are the Cutie
Mark Crusaders
and they are my friends!
You need to stop calling them
such mean and hurtful names.
They are working harder
to get their Cutie Marks
than anypony I've ever seen.
And they will get them
exactly when they discover
their true talent, which I
guarantee will be amazing!
Now, will you please
deliver this to Father?
Yes, of course, dear.
I have to thank
you, Crusaders.
Obviously, I've known
since I got my Cutie Mark
that my talent is getting other
ponies to do what I want.
I just asked my father if
he could donate the money
for the new
playground equipment.
[excited chatter]
I know you were worried
for a second there, weren't you?
Huh, well, I think it's all
going to work out just fine,
Mr. President!
♪ We'll build a playground
for all of us to enjoy! ♪
♪ So full of games, there's
enough for each girl and boy! ♪
♪ I wanna help and do
everything that I can! ♪
♪ I'm here to show you a change.
Listen up, here's the plan! ♪
Bring it in. That's
right, keep it coming!
Hey there, you with
the amazing strength?
Can you help them move that
merry-go-round across the lawn?
Thank you so much!
And you with the Super Teeth...
We need you to help
with that teeter-totter!
You got it! That's the spirit!
♪♪
♪ There's so much I can
do to help everypony else! ♪
♪ I see the light
that shines in me! ♪
♪ I know I can be my
better self ♪
♪♪
♪ I can free the past! Cause now
the future's bright for me! ♪
♪ My cutie mark has
set me free! ♪
♪ To do what's right and
be the pony I want to be! ♪
♪♪
♪ And be the pony I want be! ♪
I've been thinkin', Crusaders.
We spend an awful lot of
time fussin' and frettin',
tryin' to discover
our true talent.
But when we take
a little time off,
we end up helpin' other ponies
figure out their true talent.
Yeah, and I think that's
way more important
than worrying about our
Cutie Marks, don't you?
Absolutely! I don't care
if I ever get my Cutie Mark
as long as I get to hang
out with my best friends.
So, whaddaya say, Crusaders?
Wanna just focus on helping
others find their Cutie Marks?
YEAH!
♪♪
[whoosh]
Whoa!
What happened!
What's going on?
It's your Cutie Marks!
They're amazing!
WE ALL GOT THE SAME CUTIE MARK!
CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS FOREVER!
♪ We were searching for our
cutie marks for a while there ♪
♪ trying to find out
how we fit in ♪
♪ So many ways
we've tried before ♪
♪ but we kept on trying more ♪
♪ cause the Cutie Mark
Crusaders don't give in! ♪
♪♪
♪ Now we know what
it took all along! ♪
♪ And our journey here
is never really done! ♪
♪ For it is more than
just a mark, ♪
♪ it's a place for
us to start! ♪
♪ An adventure that
has only just begun! ♪
♪ We'll make our mark! Show
the world what we can do! ♪
♪ We'll make our mark, helping
fillies to break through! ♪
♪ To the ultimate reward
of a cutie mark! ♪
All right, everypony!
Get ready for the biggest
Cuteciñera celebration ever!
[celebratory shouts]
Oh, sugar cube, if
Mom and Dad were here,
they'd be so
proud of you.
Oh! Thanks, Applejack!
Now go on and party
with yer pals!
♪ I'm so proud of
you, little buddy! ♪
♪ You've taught me
a thing or two! ♪
♪ You've inspired
everypony around you ♪
♪ And you've inspired me too! ♪
♪ You've made your mark! And
done Equestria so proud! ♪
♪ You've made your mark and
we're here to sing it loud! ♪
♪ For the ultimate reward
of your cutie mark! ♪
Well, what do you
think, Crusaders?
Were these Cutie Marks totally
worth waiting for or what?
Yeah! I can't wait to see who
we're going to help next!
♪ We started out just three! ♪
♪ Crusaders driven to see ♪
♪ What we find in our hearts!
Discover our destiny! ♪
♪ And here we are, best friends
About to start it again ♪
♪ An adventure that
never will end! ♪
♪ We'll make our mark! Helping
fillies most in need! ♪
♪ We'll make our mark! ♪
♪ So each one of
them succeeds! ♪
♪ Cause the ultimate reward,
is a CUTIE MARK! ♪