♪♪
[groan]
[raspberry]
[sigh]
[groan]
[loud sigh]
I'm bored.
But you're reading.
I've read all these
books already.
And?
And I'm bored! I
want to do something!
Things have been so
slow around here and-
Rarity: Twilight? Twilight?
Oh, Twilight, darling! Oh, thank
goodness! It seems that my-
Whew! Got here as fast as I-
[gasp]
♪♪
Yes! Finally! We've
been summoned.
I wonder where the
map wants us to-
Uh, Twilight?
[groan]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Where do you think--?
[delighted squeals]
Manehattan! We've been
called to Manehattan!
Oh, I've simply been dying
to go back for a visit.
And now, I return...
...with a purpose.
Hmm. It looks like
you've been summoned
to this particular
neighborhood here.
We're off to solve
a friendship problem
in one of the busiest
and most vibrant cities
in all of Equestria!
Isn't this exciting?
Seems a hair odd
though, don't it?
Map callin' me to a big
city like Manehattan?
You may be more of a country
pony at heart, Applejack,
but the map picked you two
because you're the best ponies
to tackle this
particular mission.
But how will we even know what
our mission is supposed to be?
That "neighborhood" probably
has twice as many ponies
as all of Ponyville.
[scoff] More like three times!
Why it's not only home to
the haypacking district,
it's also home to
the fashion district!
Hmm. Shame you weren't called
as well, though, darling.
You did end up quite a fan
of the hustle and bustle
of Manehattan on our last visit.
It's such an exciting city.
And there's still so much
I'd like to do there.
So many museums and historical
landmarks to visit,
not to mention
all the libraries.
But this is your mission.
Don't worry about me.
I've got plenty of...
books to keep me busy.
Pah!
Mm hm!
[gasp] I just
remembered something.
The Sisterhooves Social.
We'll have to miss it.
No tellin' how long
we'll be in Manehattan.
I sure hope Applebloom and
Sweetie Belle aren't too upset.
♪♪
Oh, Manehattan!
What you do to me!
[rumbling hooves]
[gulp]
Darling, are you all right?
Ponies move so fast here,
not at all like back home.
Eyes peeled. Ears open.
[tweet]
♪♪
Remember, Applejack, you're in
the big city now. No moseying.
You've got to walk with
speed and confidence.
[tweet]
♪♪
Yoo-hoo!
Move it!
Sorry 'bout that!
Oh, get out of my way!
Sorry!
Watch it!
Oh, dear.
Butter my biscuits, I can barely
cross the street in this town.
How am I supposed
to help solve a--
[gasp] There!
Yes, I think this is the one--
No! No!
Excuse me?
That hat clashes
with your mane.
Not to mention
it's far too large
and will undoubtedly
obstruct your vision.
Oh, dear. None of these will do.
Oh, Applejack,
what good timing!
♪ [humming] ♪
Here! This will do splendidly.
Oh, it's lovely! How much
would you like for it?
Oh, no, no, no!
Please, please keep it!
I can always make another.
Thank you!
And you thought we wouldn't
discover our purpose here.
Yeah, I'm pretty
sure that wasn't it.
What? I just saved that
poor pony from committing
a terrible crime of fashion!
She could've been
meeting a friend
who would have
laughed at her new hat
and then their friendship
could've been ruined forever.
It's possible.
Did your Cutie Mark glow
signifyin' a job well done?
No, I suppose it didn't.
Still, a disaster was averted.
Averted? You just lost
me a paying customer!
Oh, my! Oh, I-I-I'm so, so
sorry, I never meant to-
Beat it!
Please accept my
sincerest apologizes
for the misunderstanding.
And might I add, what a lovely
establishment you have here.
[nervous laughter]
You're right, Applejack.
The search continues.
♪♪
Applejack: Uh, 'Scuse me.
I was just wonderin'...
Friendship problem, anypony?
See we've been sent here to--
A map summoned us and uh--
If you could just
take a moment to--
Rarity: Friendship advice!
Anypony looking for
friendship advice?
Good grief! This isn't working.
I'm not sure what we're
supposed to do. To be honest,
I'm still not even sure what
the Map called me here for.
Oh, try not to worry, Applejack.
The Map picked us for a reason.
Although, how we're supposed
to uncover that reason,
I haven't a clue.
We can't possibly approach
every single pony in town
until we find out what
we're meant to do.
"Please help us restore our long
lost, but beloved tradition,
the Midsummer Theater Revival!
With a guest performance
by local theater troupe,
'The Method Mares'
as well as games, food,
and much, much, more,
this event promises to bring
our Bronclyn neighbors together
and restore our
sense of community.
But there's so much to
do and we need your help!"
[gasp]
Darling, this is it! The contact
on the flyer is Coco Pommel!
Oh, right. She's the
one you got a job
makin' costumes for that
designer friend of yours.
Don't you see! This must be
why the map called us here!
Oh, and you were so worried.
Well, I suppose it's at
least worth lookin' into.
That is, if we can ever
get off this street corner.
♪♪
I can't believe
you found my flyer.
Quite a coincidence,
don't you think?
Applejack and I were
specifically summoned here
to be of service.
And you, my dear friend,
are in need of help.
It's no coincidence,
darling. It's fate!
This "Midsummer Theater
Revival". What is it exactly?
An outdoor play held
at the community park.
Many moons ago, local theater
troupes would perform
and ponies in the neighborhood
would help make the costumes
and design set pieces,
prepare food to share
during the performance.
Y'all do look like you're
enjoying each other's company.
Kind of reminds
me of Ponyville.
It sounds
lovely, darling!
It was, up until
several moons ago.
What happened?
That's Charity Kindheart.
She was a well-known costume
designer on Bridleway.
She started the Midsummer
Theater Revival as a way
to share her passion for
theater with the neighborhood.
No matter how busy she was,
she always made time
for the Revival.
But when she moved away to be
closer to her grand-fillies,
the neighborhood lost the
special tradition she'd started,
and worse, the sense of
community it fostered.
[tire screech]
Hey! I'm trottin' here!
Nopony else stepped up
to take over for Charity?
I've been trying to,
but I've just gotten
a last-minute request
to alter costumes for the
cast of My Fair Filly,
and I'm afraid I haven't
made much progress.
There's just so much to do to
bring back the Midsummer Revival
and my flyers haven't
attracted a single volunteer!
Say no more! You finish up your
work and by this time tomorrow
you'll be up to your mane in
ponies who want to lend a hoof.
Applejack and I will
make sure of it.
You will?
You bet your
boots we will!
Oh, I don't
wear boots.
I find they chafe my
calves when I walk.
It's just an
expression.
So you see, the Method Mares are
only available on this one day,
and we need all the help we
can get with preparations.
Yeah, not a good
time right now.
What am I saying? It's
never a good time.
Ahem! Well, what
do you think?
I got my own problems.
You think I got hours to
dedicate to somepony else's?
Ah, yes, Charity's Midsummer
Theater Revival...
such wonderful memories.
So you'll help us?
[laugh] Don't be ridiculous.
I run a very important oat and
hay import/export business.
I can't spare even a
moment for such things.
♪♪
This is a nightmare.
Oh, not at all, darling.
It's quite lovely.
I think she was talkin' about
the Midsummer Theater Revival.
I've finished the alterations
for My Fair Filly,
but have barely started the
costumes for the Revival,
and The Method Mares are
coming to the park tomorrow
for a costume-fitting
and rehearsal.
Well, I could help
you with the costumes.
But what are we going
to do about the rest?
The park is in desperate
need of repairs,
and the sets still
need to be built.
I know a thing or two about
buildin' and fixin' things.
It's kinda,
well, my thing.
Could be the reason
the Map called me here.
You see, dear? We went out
looking for volunteers
when all the help you
need is right here.
Uh-huh.
The map wouldn't have chosen
just Applejack and me
if it was more than
we could handle.
Everything is going
to be just fine.
Perhaps I spoke too soon.
♪ [sombre music] ♪
Oh, dear, you're right.
Are you sure you can
manage this by yourself?
Well, there's a lot to
do, but Rarity's right.
The Map wouldn't
have called us here
if we weren't up
for the challenge.
You two go on and take
care of the costumes.
I'll see you at the
dress rehearsal.
[gulp]
♪♪
[snap]
[crash]
[rustling]
[creak]
[crash]
♪♪
[thud]
I know it looks bad, but I'm
movin' as fast as I can.
[splash]
Don't worry. We've still
got plenty of time.
Everything's going to be fi-
Umm, excuse me, is this where
the Midsummer Theater Revival
is supposed to be, par chance?
We're here for the
dress rehearsal.
Oh, yes!
We've just put the finishing
touches on the costumes.
At least those
look professional.
We'll do a dry run of the play
first and then the fitting.
No! Wait! I haven't
gotten a chance to--
Agh!
[crash]
...reinforce the stage yet.
♪♪
[sigh] I just wanted to live
up to Charity's example,
to bring my neighborhood
together again.
But the park is still a mess.
We haven't even thought about
what refreshments to serve
during the performance.
And even if we had,
we don't have a stage
for the Method
Mares to perform on.
It's hopeless. Just hopeless.
I don't understand.
The Map summoned us here to
solve a friendship problem.
We've clearly found it
but why did it send the two
of us? Why not Twilight?
I'm sure she could
have used her magic
to transform this
park in an instant.
I've been thinkin'
the same thing.
I mean, I can at least
see why you're here:
Coco's your friend and you have
an eye for costumes and all.
But me?
I was never gonna be able to
finish a project this big.
We'll return to
Ponyville as failures.
Why must this be, Applejack?
Why? Why? Why!
Now hold on there.
I'm not suggestin' we
pack up and go home.
[indiscernible]
Then what are
you suggesting?
I'm suggestin' we stop worryin'
about what we can't do
and start doin'
what we can!
I think I've got a plan.
It won't be anything big or
fancy, but it'll be somethin'.
And somethin's gotta be
better than nothin'. Right?
I suppose so.
That's the spirit!
Sorta.
[hammering]
All right, y'all. It's ready.
Should we go ahead and start?
Excuse me? I'm
Charity Kindheart.
I'm here about the
open design position.
I brought some
samples of my work.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I had the hardest time
finding my way here.
I just moved here and
I keep getting mixed up
by the street names.
I had a map, but I
dropped it in a puddle...
which only made the street
names harder to read!
I see.
What is that?
I don't know, Sugar. Looks
like some kind of play.
Well, can we stay and watch it
please? Please? Can we? Can we?
Oh, all right, I suppose we
could stay for a minute.
Excuse me, but your next
appointment is here.
All right, send him in.
I'm sorry, but based
on these samples,
I just don't think this
is the place for you.
[gasping inhale]
Don't get me wrong;
these clothes are all
exquisite and well-made,
but more theatrical
than avant-garde.
Have you considered
costume design?
I have a contact on Bridleway.
If you're interested, I can
put you in touch with him.
And scene.
[murmuring]
Charity, dear, is that you?
Hello, Mrs. Pearblossom!
I didn't see-
Oops!
Oh, let me help you, dear.
Are these the costumes
you've been working on?
Yes. I was supposed
to be finished by now,
but there's just so much to do!
And I still have a few last
minute alterations to make
before opening night.
I'm sorry I couldn't get
enough tickets for everypony
in the neighborhood.
I hope Mr. Pearblossom
wasn't too disappointed.
I know Trotter on the Roof
is one of his favorites.
Oh, my dear filly,
don't worry about that!
We're so proud of you; we
shall be with you in spirit!
Thank you. You've all made
me feel so welcome here
and have become
like family to me.
I just wish I could
share this experience
with you and the others.
What's going on?
It's the Midsummer
Theater Revival.
The Method Mares are performing.
The Revival. Yeah. My
pop used to bring me.
It's so nice of you to put on
this play for the neighborhood.
I couldn't have done it
without everypony's help.
I know it's not Bridleway, but -
Oh, pish-tosh!
It's perfect, dear.
♪♪
Oh, you're such a dear,
thank you. This is so nice.
Haven't seen the
neighborhood this friendly
since Charity moved away.
♪♪
[cheers]
Thank you, fillies
and gentlecolts.
Please give a warm welcome
to the one who made this
entire event possible...
our neighbor, Coco Pommel!
[cheers]
Ahem. Thank you all
so much for coming.
The Midsummer Theater
Revival was always something
that meant so much to me
and it seems it means quite
a lot to all of you as well.
I really can't take
all the credit, though.
My dear friends,
Rarity and Applejack
helped me ever so much.
[cheers]
Oh, darling please, it
was just a few costumes.
Aw, shucks, I just happen to
be good with a hammer is all.
To be honest, we had much
bigger plans to start.
When those fell through,
we decided to simplify.
This here was the result.
Oh, don't be so modest.
Coco and I
were lost.
You bet your
boots we were!
♪♪
[crowd chatting]
We just wanted to say
how much we enjoyed
the Midsummer Theater Revival
and how much it inspired us.
Oh, yeah?
I used to think that
to help my community,
I had to do something
big. And let's face it,
in this day and age, who has
the time for such a commitment?
But here, you did something as
simple as building a stage
and putting on a play.
And look at how it's
brought everypony together.
I saw Coco's flyers for
volunteers, but didn't think
anything I'd have time to
do would be that useful.
Now I wish I'd offered to help,
even if it was just
pulling a few weeds
or planting a few flowers.
Not sure if you've
noticed but the park
is far from bein' fixed up. I
imagine if you look around,
you'll find there's lots
of little ways for you
to get involved in changin'
this place for the better!
And I will.
And I don't think
we'll be alone.
♪♪
Yahoo! We did it!
[gasp] I understand now!
It all makes perfect sense!
Huh?
I know why the Map
called you here!
You do?
If Twilight had used her
magic to fix the park,
it wouldn't have fixed
the real problem,
which is that these
Manehattan ponies
didn't think they had time to do
something for their community.
But by building that stage and
making sure the play went on,
you showed them that just
by doing something small,
you can make a big difference.
Well, I'll be!
Seems you have more in common
with the Manehattan ponies
than you thought.
But all the same, I'd sure
like to head back to Ponyville
on the next train.
I want to check
in with Applebloom
and find out how the
Sisterhooves Social turned out.
Oh, absolutely, my dear.
Just as soon as I stop that
pony in the shop over there
from purchasing that
dreadfully hideous scarf.
Stop! You're making
a terrible mistake!
[groan]