Does every animal have their
copy of "Wuthering Hooves"?
Hooray! I love Furry
Friends Book Club.
Now let's discuss
the theme of nature
as it applies to
Hoofcliff's love--
Did somepony leave a light on?
Oh, It's me.
OH! It's me!
We'll continue this
discussion when I get back!
[door clicks closed]
[chittering]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
You're here!
[poof]
Isn't this exciting!
Oh, you were called
too! Thank goodness.
I feel so much better
going with a friend.
I was about to come and get
you but then I got distracted.
Oh.
Ever since the
map called us,
I've been doing a
ton of research.
[zap]
Testing out potential
friendship problems,
diversifying my
solution portfolio...
[pop]
"Ever since the map called us"?
But that happened
five minutes ago.
I know, but I want to be one
hundred percent prepared.
I mean, I'm the
Princess of Friendship.
How would it look if I couldn't
solve a friendship problem?
Oh, I'm so lucky I'm
being sent with you.
Speaking of which,
where are we going?
The Smokey Mountains!
Oh, I've never
been there before.
Neither have I. And there isn't
a lot of information on them.
All I could find was this.
"The Smokey Mountains harbor
the most beautiful valley
in all of Equestria between its
two majestic mountain peaks."
That's gorgeous.
And where there's nature,
there's a ton of animal friends!
I can't wait to
get started.
I'm a little nervous, since
that's all I could find.
I usually like to be
a bit more prepared.
You seem pretty
prepared to me.
Are those...for us?
Yup! I've prepared our things:
Snacks, books, blankets, books.
You said books twice.
There are a lot of books.
Oof!
What do you think our friendship
problem's going to be?
[struggling]
I don't know. But I'm
sure we'll figure it out.
Do you think it'll be
a problem about lying?
I'm sure we'll find
out when we get there.
You're right.
Ooh! Could it be about when two
friends just randomly decide
to do something together
but they forget to invite
the third friend and the
third friend feels left out?
Or where one friend tells
another friend's secret
after they ask them not to?
We'll know very, very soon,
since we're almost there.
Here, let me get that.
Oh, thank you.
Sorry I've been a little
scidilly-bopty-boo.
I just can't believe this
is finally happening!
[whoosh]
Whoa!
Whoa. What in
Equestria is happening?
It's nothing like your
book said it would be.
Oh, boy, I'm feeling
very unprepared.
Where do we even start?
[whoosh]
Maybe by figuring out where the
flying pumpkins are coming from?
Ready?
♪ [banjo picking] ♪
Aim.
♪♪
Fire!
[boom]
Um, hi, hello. Excuse us,
but... what are you doing?
We're pumpkining our neighbors!
Yes. But, umm, why are you
pumpkining your neighbors?
Well, because the McColts
are just plain rotten.
Hey, wait a tick.
Who are you two?
You're not spies for
the McColts are Yeah?
I am Twilight Sparkle, the
Princess of Friendship.
And I am here to solve
your friendship problem.
I'm Fluttershy. And
um, I'm here, too.
Ma Hooffield.
Pleased to meet you, but
you're wasting your time.
We don't have a
friendship problem;
we have a McColt problem.
And there's absolutely
no friendship there.
Well, maybe there could be if we
figure out what the McColts did
to make you so mad.
Oh, well they've
done so many things!
Why just today, they shot
pebbles at our farmhouse
and wrecked it!
See, we're not very
good at building
so all it took was a
little pebble. But still.
♪♪
[squeaks]
Oh, no!
I know what to do. We're
gonna talk with these McColts
and hear their
side of the story.
Once we have all the facts,
we can put an end to this,
using reason and rationale.
Good plan!
That's why she's the Princess.
In the meantime, could you
please call off the pumpkining?
Oh, all right.
Thanks. Come on, Fluttershy.
[knock knock]
State your business.
Don't even bother.
They're probably spies
for the Hooffields.
Hey wait, you're an Alicorn.
I thought just the three
princesses were Alicorns.
There are four Alicorn
princesses in Equestria now.
I am Twilight Sparkle, The
Princess of Friendship!
And I'm Fluttershy.
We have a new princess?
When did that happen?
And, and how did the Hooffields
come by a princess spy?
We are not spies! Why does
everypony assume we're spies?
[rattling wood]
Because we don't get a lot of
visitors. I'm Big Daddy McColt.
You caught us at a weird time.
We're in the middle
of a giant feud
with our terrible neighbors!
[echo]
[crash]
Well, actually,
that's why we're here.
To solve your problem
with the Hooffields.
So you're here to help
us get rid of them?
[whooping cheers]
No, that's not what
I meant at all!
Well, if you ain't for
us, you're against us.
Twilight: We are not
on anypony's side.
We're here to help you
become friends again.
Well, that's gonna be hard.
I don't believe we've ever been
friends with the Hooffields.
But you could be.
They're just really upset
you ruined their farmhouse--
Wait a hog-wogglin'
minute! We only did that
because the Hooffields pulled
the pin out of our wagon wheel.
[clunk]
A whole week's worth of food
rollin' down the mountain!
Us McColts are
mighty fine builders
but we don't know the
first thing about farming.
We have to travel a ways
away to buy our food.
And now, we'll be stuck
eating the pumpkins
the Hooffields launched at us!
Pumpkin bread, pumpkin
soup, pumpkin quesadillas,
pumpkin paella, pumpkin cheese,
pumpkin pie, pumpkin fri-ta-tas.
Actually that all sounds
pretty good, but it'll get old.
♪♪
Have you tried meeting
at a neutral location,
talking about your problems, and
really listening to each other?
What? No. They'd sooner
launch their dinners at us
than listen to us.
Well, they'll listen to me.
I'm an impartial third party.
♪♪
[amplified] Attention,
Hooffields and McColts!
I'm not on anypony's side, but I
can see you're both wasting time
and resources on being
mean to each other.
Ponies are supposed to help
each other and be kind.
So, let's stop this
senseless fighting.
There. That should do it.
Ready to go home, Fluttershy?
I'd love to, but if we've
solved the problem already,
shouldn't our cutie
marks be glowing again?
Oh, yeah. They should be
glowing any minute now.
[splat]
Or not.
[panicked shouts]
So much for potential friendship
solution number twenty-eight.
I guess we should find
out why the Hooffields
are launching tomatoes now.
One at a time, Greenhoof.
If you smush them
tomaters in the slingshot,
they won't break on the McColts!
What are you doing? I
asked you to stop fighting!
Oh, is that what you
were hollerin' about?
We thought the McColts
rubbed you the wrong way,
so we tomatered them
for ya. My mistake.
Stop the tomater slingshots!
[thud]
Reload the tomater slingshots!
We're gonna paint
their mountaintop red!
Well, that didn't work.
I was so sure it would.
♪♪
[crashes]
[galloping hooves]
[gasp]
It was a good plan, but we
need to think of another one.
And soon.
This fight is really affecting
the animals around here.
Not to worry. I'll just...find
the root of the problem
and work from there!
[crash]
Pardon us, Ma, but do you
remember what started
this whole feud in
the first place?
They know what they did.
I'm starting to think
neither of you know
what either of you have done.
Sure we do. Them Hooffields
did us a grave injustice
some time ago for some reason.
Hear, hear!
O-kay, backup plan
to the backup plan.
Maybe we can find some common
ground that you can bond over.
What do you do when
you're not fighting?
That's easy. Getting
ready to fight.
What do you hope to
get out of fighting?
The satisfaction of winning.
Of winning what?
The fight, of course. To
prove our family is the best!
The best at what?
Winning! Haven't
you been listenin'?
So the only thing they have in
common is that they both want
to win a fight and neither
of them know what it's over.
How can I end this feud if I
don't know what it's about?
Ooh. Maybe somepony just
needs to say they're sorry.
That's a good idea.
And friendship solution
#48, but we can move it up.
I'm so glad you
agreed to do this!
This apology cake
will go a long way
to making amends
between you two.
Which part of my argument
changed your mind?
The part where I said the
benefits of friendship
outweigh the cost of war?
Or the part where I said
forgiveness is an
investment in happiness?
Yeah, yeah, all of it.
Wait, are you even
listening to me?
Who goes there?
It's Ma Hooffield--
Hooffield alert! Arm the canons!
--with an apology cake.
Did you say...cake? As in, cake?
Consider it a gesture of
good will, from us to you.
I haven't had cake in ages.
Open the gates!
It's such a beautiful cake.
Think of this as more
than just a cake.
It's the first step in the
long road to forgiveness.
Nothing says let's be friends
like a cake that says
"let's be friends".
I wrote that in
icing on the top.
For glory!
♪♪
[scream]
McColts! Assume delta
force formation!
[battle cries]
Ready?
Aim!
Fire!
Ma Hooffield! You planted
ponies in that cake?
Yeah. Wait, were you
serious about apologizing?
Why in Equestria
would we do that?
We didn't do anything wrong!
What are you talkin' about?
You've done so
many things wrong!
Not as many as you!
Take that, Hooffields!
You started it!
No, you did!
[shouting continues]
[angry shouting]
If you could just
not yell so much,
or maybe stop saying
words altogether...
[screaming]
Agh!
Twilight?
♪ [sad music] ♪
[sigh]
Um, Twilight? We should
probably get back there.
I mean, if you need
a break, that's fine
but I really can't
do this without you.
I don't know if we
can do this at all.
Even if I make things right,
they're just going
to fight again.
[chittering]
Hey, little fellas. That's
OK. You can come out.
[chirping and chittering]
[growl]
What was that?
[growling tummies]
Oh, you poor things! There
isn't enough food here for you.
Brr! And you're freezing! I'm
gonna take you all home with me
and get you all hot cocoas. How
do you feel about book clubs?
Twilight: I don't get it.
This was supposed to be
the most beautiful valley
in all of Equestria.
What happened?
[chittering]
What's that?
Oh.
Uh huh.
Twilight! They know what
happened here!
What?
[shouts]
Stop! You have to listen to me!
[splat]
EVERYPONY FREEZE!
[echo]
[whoosh]
[silence]
Fluttershy, you
have to tell them!
It's a lot harder to
freeze an army of ponies
than just six of them.
[straining]
Before you keep fighting, there
is something you should know.
Long ago, there were
two best friends...
...Grub Hooffield
and Piles McColt.
When they found the valley
between the Smokey Mountains,
they knew it was
something special.
So they made a promise to each
other to protect and preserve
the valley for all its
adorable furry inhabitants.
But, they disagreed
on how to go about it.
Grub wanted to start
by planting crops
so that everypony would
have something to eat.
But Piles thought it
would be better to start
by building a shelter to protect
them against the cold and wind.
The two ponies were unable
to come to an understanding.
So Piles went ahead and
built a shelter anyway,
exactly where Grub was
going to start his farm.
♪♪
Grub was upset, so he
tore down Piles' shelter
so he could plant his crops.
They kept fighting,
back and forth,
until it turned into a feud.
♪♪
The valley suffered from
the constant destruction
until finally the
Hooffields and McColts moved
to separate mountains.
Even then, the valley and
all the animals in it
continued to be caught
in the crossfire.
You see, by fighting, you're
destroying the very thing
that brought you here
in the first place.
So it's time you both put
your differences aside
and come together, if
not for yourselves,
then for the sake of these
cute and cuddly guys.
[grunts]
Aw, shucks. We never meant
to hurt you little critters.
Yeah, we're sorry.
[chitter]
They say they
accept your apology!
Um, Princess? You
can unfreeze us now.
[grunt]
Oh, right.
Ma Hooffield? We promise we
won't fight you no more.
Us too. Except we
promise not to fight you.
I suppose it doesn't matter
who's right. We're both wrong.
That's one thing
we can agree on.
[spit]
This is wonderful!
I am so proud of you two.
Thanks, Princess.
Though I would just
like to point out
that I was the first
to admit I was wrong.
That may be, but I promised
not to fight first.
That counts for more.
Oh, yeah?
[urgent chirping & chittering]
Oh, all right. We don't
have to speak animal
to know what y'all
are sayin'. Truce?
Truce.
♪♪
Hoo-wee, ain't that
a pretty sight!
Sure is.
The McColts are going to
help us rebuild our homes --
good ones this time.
And the Hooffields are going
to help us grow some crops.
Not pumpkins!
Thanks for teaching us that
friendship is so much better
than winning a silly argument.
Yay! I told you
we'd figure it out.
We did. And we didn't need my
friendship portfolio to do it.
We just needed each other.
[poof]
So what do you think
will happen next?
We've all been called
by the map now.
I'm sure we'll find
out when we get home.
What if it summons all six
of us to another place?
Or another pony we
weren't expecting? [gasp]
What if it wants us to solve
other kinds of problems like
quantum physics or why the apple
doesn't fall far from the tree?