♪♪
Granny: Aw, snickerdoodle!
Where is the darn thing?
I wish for once I'd remember
to label these boxes.
Big Mac, be a dear and
help me move those.
Maybe it's in that
one on the bottom.
♪♪
Oh, dagnabbit, it's
not in there either.
[giggling from outside]
You can't catch me! Hey!
OK! Ha ha ha! You trickster!
Sisterhooves Social is
right around the corner.
Thought it'd be nice to award
the winner of the big race
a ribbon from when we hosted
the very first Social.
If of course I can
find the darn thing.
♪♪
Awww, would ya lookie here?
My, how Apple Bloom used
to love watching you
make that thing fly. It's like
she thought you were magic.
All right, enough
reminiscin'.
Gotta find that ribbon.
If you would just
help me [grunts]
then maybe I can ...
Uh, Big Mac?
[thud]
[grunts]
Found 'er!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
S-I-S-T-E-R-S! Which two
sisters are the best? We are!
Apple Bloom and Applejack
forever. Yeeee-hewww!
We are gonna win
every competition
at the Sisterhooves
Social!
Those other fillies aren't
gonna know what hit 'em.
Oh, hey there, Big Mac.
Did you want something?
Eyup.
Hold that thought.
Applejack, you are the
most awesome sister ever.
Aw, gee whiz. Heh.
Well, I think it's sweet that
you hold that opinion, but--
It's not opinion.
It's objective fact.
You've saved Equestria
like a gazillion times.
You're smart. Funny. Strong.
Why you're the best
sister of all time!
Probably the best Apple of
all time! Right, Big Mac?
Eyup.
And with you by my
side, I am guaranteed
to taste sweet, sweet
Sisterhooves Social victory!
Go Apples. Go,
go, go Apples, go!
Uh, Apple Bloom? I think
Big Mac's got something
he wants to show you.
Oh, hey! Is that the toy we used
to play with when I was little?
Eyup.
Neat. All right then! Let's
get back to practicin'!
One more run-through of
our juggling routine,
make sure our harmonies
are tight on our song,
and see if we can't beat
our best pie-eatin' time.
Hold on, sugar cube. I need a
minute to talk with Big Mac.
Mind if I go ahead and
start eating this pie?
[splat]
[clanging]
Hey Big Mac, you all right?
Eyup.
You sure? You seemed a
little down back there.
[scoff] Nope.
Come on, you can tell me. You
feelin' a little left out?
Apple Bloom and I have been
spendin' a lot of time together
gettin' ready for the Social.
What in the--?
Your Cutie Mark!
You're being summoned,
Applejack! This is so cool!
Eyup.
Wonder where you're
being called to?
Wonder what you're supposed
to do when you get there?
Obviously it is something
awesome because you're awesome!
But if you're being summoned
to solve a friendship problem,
that means you'll have to
miss the Sisterhooves Social.
And if you have to
miss the Social,
then I'll have to
which means I won't be able to
taste sweet, sweet victory!
Now calm down. Let me just
go over to Twilight's castle
and see what's what.
Maybe it's just a false alarm.
But you said it
was a false alarm!
I said "maybe"
it's a false alarm.
Well, it's not. Rarity and
I have to go to Manehattan.
Can't you just tell that map
it'll have to wait
a couple days?
No can do, sugar cube.
When duty calls, I
gotta answer right away.
What kind of an example would I
be settin' for my little sister
if I didn't?
This. Can't. Be. Happening!
Your extreme awesomeness
is backfiring on me!
[sigh] I'm sorry,
Apple Bloom.
Try and cheer her
up, won't Yeah?
Eyup.
[clanging bell]
Breakfast! Come an' git it!
♪ [sad music] ♪
Oh, it's no use, Big Mac.
If I know my Apple Bloom,
she won't come out
of a funk this funky
till her big sister gets back.
[knock at door]
Hey Apple Bloom, the Social is
going to start in a few hours.
Thought you might
wanna go with us.
Since Rarity and
Applejack are out of town,
you and Sweetie Belle can cheer
on me and Rainbow Dash instead.
Pretty great they're
letting you participate,
even though you're not
technically sisters.
Social's always had a
pretty loose definition
of what consti-ma-tutes
a sister.
Long as you share a bond
that represents the spirit
of the Social, you're in.
So...what do you say?
You coming?
Why not? I got
nothin' better to do.
Let me wash up and I'll
meet you in a little bit.
Oh, such a shame we
don't live closer
to all your second cousins.
You could maybe do the Social
with one of them instead.
What is it, Big Mac?
Y'all got an idea?
Eyup.
What? What is it?
♪♪
Today's our big day!
We have so got this!
I'm gonna go sign us in.
I guess I'm just
a little jealous
you two get to
compete and I don't.
But at least I get to be
here and cheer you on.
I thought Apple Bloom was
going to be here, too.
Guess she changed her mind.
Hey! There you are.
You ready to cheer on me and
Rainbow Dash to victory?
Uh, not exactly.
Seems I'm gonna get to
participate after all.
Applejack is back from
Manehattan already?
That must mean
Rarity is back, too!
No. Our sisters are still gone.
But it, uh, turns out my long
lost cousin Orchard Blossom
was able to make it last minute.
[weak chuckle]
Your cousin whowhatnow?
[southern belle voice] Well, I
do declare it's hotter today
than the business end of
a corn cob pipe. [giggle]
♪♪
Oh my, I am so delighted to
meet your little friends,
Apple Bloom.
Would these be your dear and
beloved Cutie Mark Crusaders?
[sigh] Sweetie
Belle and Scootaloo,
Cousin Orchard Blossom.
It is my extraordinary pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
That's Big Mac in a dress.
"Big Mac?" Why as charmed
as I am that you find me
in the slightest resemblance to
such a fine and noble product
of the Apple clan, I'm
astonished in equal measure.
However, I shall take this
startling observation
under advisement, given that
it's from such an astute
and perceptive filly as
yourself, Sweetie Belle.
That's awful nice of you to
say, Cousin Orchard Blossom.
I've been told before
I'm pretty observant.
I haven't the slightest doubt.
Pardon me,
my dearest cousin Applejack is
regrettably unable to be here
as planned, so I, her
Cousin Orchard Blossom,
will accompany Apple
Bloom in her stead.
I trust that's acceptable
to all concerned?
Cousin Orchard Blossom, huh?
I know Applejack has
a lot of relatives,
but I feel like she
would have mentioned you.
Why, you must be Rainbow Dash!
You're Scootaloo's... how
are y'all related again?
Why don't I just let
you finish signing in?
But don't think me and Scootaloo
are gonna take it easy on you
just 'cause you're a stallion.
Now where were we?
[crash]
Um, excuse me, I have
to... go to the bathroom.
You mean "powder your
muzzle," don't you, dear?
Such a more feminine-like
reference to nature's call,
don't you agree?
Have they called your
brother's bluff yet?
No, but they're about to.
I can't bear to watch.
Yoo hoo, Apple Bloom!
They've approved us
as a pair! [giggle]
Hurry along now, precious.
I can't believe they bought it.
It's sweet he wants to help you
out like this. Weird. But sweet.
♪♪
Bravo. Bravo! Weren't
those two sisters great?
Now where are our
next competitors?
Here we are!
This one please.
Excellent choice... ma'am.
You sure you know all the words?
cause it took Applejack a pretty
long time to get it down.
Did it now?
♪♪
♪ We all love our brothers ♪
♪ and our fathers and mothers ♪
♪ We honour them like
every family should ♪
♪ But there's something
that's quite unique ♪
♪ When my sister's
there with me ♪
♪ And we share that special
bond of sisterhood ♪
♪ Sisterhood...
[Sisterhooooood] ♪
♪ Is a special kind of friend ♪
♪ Sisterhood...
[Sisterhooooood] ♪
♪ Is a bond that never ends ♪
♪ It's not always perfect ♪
♪ You might fight or
be misunderstood ♪
♪ But together
you'll always have ♪
♪ Sisterhood ♪
♪ Sisterhood...... ♪
♪ [low voice]
Sisterhooooooood.... ♪
[surprised chatter]
Heh heh! Are you OK,
Cousin Orchard Blossom?
You sounded like you
were catching a cold
or something else
that would make your voice
sound totally different
right at the end
of the song.
Just a frog in
my throat, dear.
Probably just need to
get a sip of water.
If you'll excuse us,
we've another event in
which to participate.
Oh, my, that certainly
didn't go as I had planned.
But don't you worry.
We'll get you a blue
ribbon, yet, Apple Bloom.
You sure about that?
As sure as my name is
Cousin Orchard Blossom.
But that isn't your name.
C-O-U-S-I-N-S!
Which two sisters, er,
cousins, are the best? We are!
Apple Bloom and Applejack,
I mean Orchard Jack,
Blossom forever. Yay!
Yay.
♪♪
Oh, I don't know
why I didn't choose
to wear something more casual.
Why I knew that juggling routine
like the back of my hoof.
But never you mind, there is
still the race to be run.
I really appreciate
all the effort Big Ma--
Cousin Orchard Blossom,
but maybe we just skip
the whole obstacle course
thing and call it a day.
Why, Apple Bloom, I
wouldn't hear of it.
Your Cousin Orchard
Blossom may be many things,
but she is not a quitter.
I'm sure she's not. But,
it's like Applejack said,
there'll be more Sisterhooves
Socials down the line.
I'm sure she'll help me get a
blue ribbon next time around.
But you wanted to win at
this Sisterhooves Social.
And no matter what, I am
going to get you that win.
Why I simply have to.
♪♪
All right, Scootaloo,
remember the parts where
teamwork really comes into play.
How could I forget? We've
been training all week.
OK, hot stuff. What's our
move on the grape squish?
The alley oop.
Apple Toss?
Flip flop.
Egg carry?
Flutter bomb.
Yeah!
Oh, dear.
Granny: Competisisters,
take your positions.
♪♪
And ready. And set. Go!
Nice jump, Scoot!
♪♪
[crash]
Woohoo!
♪♪
[burp]
[crash]
♪♪
[splash]
Yikes! You almost squished ME!
♪♪
Pick up those
hooves, Apple Bloom!
Why you're barely
moving at a mosey!
♪♪
Come on, junebug;
it's like you've never
carried an egg before.
I'm goin' as fast as I can!
♪♪
Hey!
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
♪♪
[low voice] Woo-hoo!
[silence]
I mean, [high] victory is
ours, sweet Apple Bloom!
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, indeed.
Ugh. I should have known
you'd eventually get busted
for being a stallion.
Oh, no. We've
known all along.
The Sisterhooves Social has
always had a loose policy
when it comes to what
counts as a "sister".
But we do have a strict policy
when it comes to sportsponyship.
In your "sister's" desperation
to win, he used brute strength
to physically take
out the competitors.
That kind of behavior is not
just unbecoming of a lady,
but, quite frankly, of anypony.
And for that, you two
are hereby disqualified.
Looks like we win, squirt.
Woo-hoo!
[cheers]
I told you I should have just
waited until the next social
to win with Applejack.
♪♪
You know, I'm not
mad, right?
Eyup.
I mean, let's face it,
you dressing up as my
Cousin Orchard Blossom
was a pretty crazy idea
in the first place.
Eyup.
And it's not like you got me
disqualified from the Social
forever or anything.
I can participate next time with
Applejack. Everything's fine.
Eyup.
I just don't understand
why you went so crazy there
at the end of the race.
I mean, I know you like
to win and all, but...
You wanna tell me
what's going on?
Nope.
All right. Well, it's
getting late. You coming?
Nope.
OK. See you
later, I guess.
Apple Bloom?
Yeah?
When you were little, you
used to look up to me.
Thought I was the best
thing since zap-apple jam.
Things are different now.
Applejack's the hero
of the Apple family.
Always rushin' off
to save Equestria.
And I'm just here on
the farm. Doin' chores.
Helpin' out the way I can.
Nothin' special. Nobody's hero.
I guess I just thought...
Aw, never mind. Here I am
about to start blabberin' on
about my feelings. You don't
want to hear all this.
Yes, I do.
I guess I just thought if I
could fill in for Applejack
at the Social and get
you a blue ribbon,
well, I could be somepony
you looked up to again.
Be your hero again. Even
if it was for just a day.
It was foolish.
And I'm ashamed.
Please. I just want
to be alone right now.
Yeah well, too
bad, you big goof.
'Cause I'm not
going anywhere.
And I know that you're always
gonna be here when I need you.
Heck, you'll do a whole
obstacle course in high heels
if you think it'll help
me get somethin' I want.
You're my big brother.
You've always been a hero to me,
Big Mac, and you always will be.
I'm real sorry I haven't
been lettin' you know
that's how I feel.
Guess both of us have
been holdin' back
when it comes to
expressin' ourselves, huh?
Eyup.
Granny: Big Mac! Apple Bloom!
Your sister's home! She says
she's got quite a story to tell
about her trip to Manehattan.
Be there in a bit.
I'm spending some quality
time with my big brother!
Hey, Big Mac.
Eyup.
How do you think
Cousin Orchard Blossom
would describe this sunset?
Why, dear, I do declare this
is the most beautiful sunset
my eyes have ever looked upon.
Though sittin' here
on these tree roots
is a trifle uncomfortable
for my hindquarters.
[giggling]