♪♪
As princess, I've
been chosen
to spread the magic of
friendship across Equestria.
So why would the
Tree of Harmony
want us to sit in a
castle in Ponyville?
Spike: This is incredible!
It's got all of Equestria!
♪♪
Fluttershy: Why are our
Cutie Marks over there?
Twilight: It seems like the
map wants us to find out.
An entire village with
the same Cutie Mark?
Starlight: Welcome!
Fluttersky: This must be
the most pleasant place
in Equestria!
Starlight: I'm delighted
you're interested
in our Cutie Mark vault.
Twilight: It's a trap!
Aaah!
Starlight: Now you can spend
the rest of your lives here.
Without your Cutie Marks!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪ ♪
P.A.: In sameness,
there is peace.
Exceptionalism is a lie...
Free yourself from
your Cutie Mark...
Choose equality as
your special talent...
[grunts]
[whimper]
Hey! This is pretty good!
[announcement continues]
Ugh. We've got to find
a way out of here.
I can't take much
more of that voice.
Oh, this is horrible!
There there, Rarity,
it's not so bad.
Yes it is! Look at
those drapes!
I have no idea if
they're tacky or not!
Well, I think they're nice.
So do I!
[blubbering]
[chirp]
Oh, thank goodness!
Can you help us, little birdy?
[chirping]
Go on, now. Fly away
and get us help.
[chirp]
Oh! Even tweets don't
make sense anymore.
[bang]
Agh! This door's shut
tighter than a...
summer of...
of piglets in...
Shoot, I can't even make
countryisms no more!
I don't know, maybe it'll be
super fun to be all the same!
Sort of.
More pleasant than
fun, I guess.
Something odd about
that staff.
I haven't studied Eastern
unicorns as much as I should've,
but I'm pretty sure Meadowbrook
only had eight magical items,
not nine.
And I don't remember any
of them being a staff.
Well, it looks like you'll
have plenty of time
to try to think about it.
[announcements continue]
Difference is frustration...
To excel is to fail...
Be your best by never
being your best...
Conformity will set you free...
Accept your limitations and
happiness will follow...
You're no better
than your friends...
I'VE GOT IT! I know how
we can get out!
[sigh]
Forget it, Twilight.
This door's not opening.
And I'm afraid the windows are
much too small for escape.
But there is a third way.
Pinkie: Of course!
Eventually the wind and weather
will wear down the walls
until they start to crumble!
Then all we have to do is wait
for a big enough hole to form
and we can just walk out!
It's the perfect plan!
I guess...
We don't actually
have to escape.
They'll just let us
out when they think
we've accepted
their philosophy.
But they're never gonna
believe we switched over
in just one night.
There's one of us
they might believe.
Ah! Me?
You've been saying how great
this place is since we got here!
That's because
everypony's so nice
and their village is so
pretty and...and...
Oh, you're right.
They probably would
believe me.
I hate to lie to them.
They've been so
welcoming and friendly.
Aside from locking us in here
and trying to brainwash us
into abandoning the things
that make us special.
OK. I'll do it.
WOO-HOO!
I mean, cool.
But what do I do
once I'm out?
You've got to find a way to
get our Cutie Marks back.
[gulp]
[feedback]
Oh, good morning!
I trust you had
a pleasant night.
This way, please.
There are some friends
who would like to see you.
Gather 'round,
friends, gather 'round!
We've come to ask if any of
you are ready to join us.
There are so many friends to
be made, once you realize
you don't need your
Cutie Marks
or the talents that
come with them.
We have a welcome
ceremony for new friends.
The whole village joins together
to build you your own cottage.
Not interested! You
may have them now,
but we're going to get
our Cutie Marks back!
Y'all don't understand, do ya?
You can't force
nopony to be friends!
It don't work like that!
Please, join us!
We love new friends!
It's all right, everypony, this
is a perfectly normal part
of the equalization process
for those who haven't...
quite seen the light yet.
We'll try again tomorrow,
once you've had a bit more time
to consider our philosophy.
I'd like to join!
[excited chatter]
Fluttershy?
How could you?
If giving up my Cutie
Mark means I get to stay
in this lovely village
with these lovely ponies,
then I'll do it.
We have a new
friend, everypony!
[excited chatter]
There's one more
order of business.
It seems some in
our midst might be
dissatisfied with
the village life!
[gasps]
Unfortunately, it's all
too true, my friends.
Will you kindly tell us the
names of those friends
who so desperately miss
their Cutie Marks
that they would sneak
around in the shadows
talking to
strangers about it?
Just so we can be sure your
intentions are, indeed, pure.
[gulp]
Um, I don't know
who they were.
Um. I'm sorry, I don't know
your names and faces yet.
Nonsense! Obviously these ponies
must have asked you directly.
Kindly point them out.
Male: It was me!
It was only me.
I only wanted it back
for a little while.
And you're quite
certain it was only you?
I just wanted to remember
what it was like.
And no thought to the pain
you'd cause your friends.
Such selfishness.
I'm sorry, everypony!
I never wanted to
leave the village!
I love all of--
[slam]
What was I thinking?
I can't believe I even
considered asking
for my Cutie Mark back.
Don't worry, Fluttershy will
have us out of here in no time.
Didn't you see what just
happened out there?
Your friend has
accepted our way.
You will all accept
our way.
It's only a matter
of time!
This guy's a
barrel of laughs.
Laughs don't come in barrels.
They come from inside you as
your body's response to delight.
So what are we gonna do while
Fluttershy's out there
lookin' for our Cutie Marks?
We have to stay as
positive as we can.
If Party Favor sees how much
we really do like each other,
even though we're all different,
maybe we can use him to
spread our message
to the rest
of the village.
[speaker static]
To excel is to fail...
Let's just hope they don't
convert any of us first.
Welcome!
Gosh, you really are the
nicest ponies I've ever met.
Come, all new
friends stay with me
until their cottage
is completed.
Let's get you settled
and then you can enjoy
all that our little
village has to offer.
♪♪
[slam]
[coughing]
[sigh]
Get the Cutie Marks back.
That's all you've got
to do, Fluttershy.
Just sneak through the dark
to that spooky old cave
with the scary magical staff
and get the Cutie Marks back.
OK, you're doing great.
The cave's got
to be close now.
Starlight: Excellent
work, Double Diamond.
Of course.
But I don't understand why you
wanted me to bring them here.
Fluttershy is one of us now;
surely she can be trusted.
This one belongs to a princess.
It could be very
important to our cause.
Double Diamond: But if Twilight
Sparkle becomes our friend,
then what do we care
about this old Cutie Mark?
I just want to keep
them close.
Until everything
is...settled.
You may go, Double Diamond.
Oh dear!
How am I ever going to get
the Cutie Marks back now?
[crash]
Ow!
Agh! Starlight,
you clumsy fool!
[gasp]
Oh no!
I've got a good
feeling about today!
So...do any of you have
anything you'd like to say?
Aw, a pity.
Well, let's try this
again tomorrow, shall we?
No new friends
today, I'm afraid!
Wait!
I'd like to lock them in.
Marvelous, Fluttershy,
that's the spirit!
Party Favor, will
you join us, please?
I'm sorry, Starlight!
I'm sorry, everypony!
I've seen the error of my ways!
I never want to look
at my Cutie Mark again!
It seems there's cause
for celebration after all!
[cheering]
They tried to break me!
They wouldn't stop talking
about how different they are,
and that somehow makes
their friendship stronger!
Such backwards thinking.
But I didn't listen!
I knew what they were up
to and I didn't listen!
Well done, Party Favor.
We welcome you back
with open hooves.
Fluttershy: Um, Starlight?
I think we might have one
more friend joining us today.
[gasps]
Is this true?
I...I think so.
But I just want to be sure.
If I agree to leave my
Cutie Mark in the vault,
I'll really be happier?
Just look around!
Equality has given
us more happiness
than you've ever known!
And you wouldn't let me just
live here in the village
with my old Cutie Mark?
Out of the question.
A pony with a different
Cutie Mark in our midst
would destroy our
entire philosophy.
We are all equal here!
[murmurs]
Fluttershy: Then how
do you explain THIS?
[splash]
I knew you couldn't
be trusted.
No! Get away!
[gasps]
Wha..What are you looking at?
They're the problem,
not me!
How could you?
You said Cutie
Marks were evil.
You said special talents
led to pain and heartache.
They do, don't you see?
Look at them!
Then why?
Why did you take ours
and not give up your own?
I..I had to, you fools!
How could I collect your
Cutie Marks without my magic?
But the staff has all
the magic we need!
The staff is a piece of
wood I found in the desert!
It's my magic that
makes all this possible!
You'd all still be living
your miserable lives,
thinking you're better
than everypony else,
if it weren't for my
magical abilities!
I brought you friendship!
I brought you equality!
I CREATED HARMONY!
You lied to us!
So what?
Everything else I
said is true!
The only way to be happy
is if we're all equal!
Except for you.
Twilight: Everypony has
unique talents and gifts.
And when we share them with
each other, that's how real--
QUIET!
You can't have that
Cutie Mark, Starlight.
Either we're all equal
or none of us are.
♪♪
[whoosh]
Come on, let's get
our Cutie Marks back!
Yeah!
Come on!
[pounding hooves]
Let's go get OUR
Cutie Marks!
Fluttershy: Our Cutie Marks
aren't in the vault.
They're in there...with her!
♪♪
STAND BACK, EVERYPONY!
[clang]
[crackling]
[whoosh]
♪♪
[power up]
Even without my Cutie Mark, I
can tell this is beautiful.
They think they can come to
my village and disrupt my life?
Let's see how they like spending
the rest of their lives
without their
precious Cutie Marks!
[smash]
[grunts]
[whistle]
Stand back, everypony!
[crash]
[smash]
They're gone!
They were right over there!
♪♪
Look!
She's headed for the pass!
If she makes it into those
mountains, we'll never find her.
These are amazing!
There's a whole network
of caves up there.
Your Cutie Marks
will be gone forever.
Then let's get movin', y'all!
Oh, come on!
♪♪
Are you all so willing to
give up everything
because of these... strangers?
We gave up everything for you!
Because we thought
you were our friend!
I can't believe we have to
count on these other ponies
to save our Cutie Marks!
If we hadn't come
here to help them,
they'd still be living
under her rules!
Now it's their turn to help us!
And I know they can do it!
♪♪
My newest recipe!
Snow pie!
[whoosh]
[explosion]
♪♪
She's gonna get away!
Whoa!
These are my old skis.
This is where I
first met Starlight.
Maybe you can
reminisce another time.
She's almost to the caves!
Feel like an airdrop?
♪♪
[smashing glass]
♪ [chimes] ♪
[whoosh]
♪♪
Yee-haw!
Finally, I can buck like
a five-bit snake herder
in an Appleoosa
ranch house again!
And you got your
countryisms back, too!
♪♪
[power up]
[zap]
[whoosh]
I studied that spell for years!
How can you--?
I studied magic for years, too,
but what I didn't know then
was that studying could
only take me so far.
Each of my friends has taught
me something different
about myself.
It was their unique gifts and
passions and personalities
that helped bring out the
magic inside of me.
I never would have learned that
I represent the Element of Magic
without these five.
And I certainly wouldn't
be here to stop you now.
Spare me your
sentimental nonsense.
I gave these ponies
real friendships
they never could
have had otherwise!
Double Diamond:
How do you know that?
You never even gave us a chance.
[explosion]
She's getting away!
We'll never find her in there.
We just have to hope that
when she's had a chance
to think it over,
she realizes that you all
have taught her something.
It's you who have
taught us something.
We all came to this village
because we were searching
for something missing
from our lives.
We thought Starlight had
given it to us, but now...
...now it seems it was
in front of us all along.
It's us.
Does that mean you'll
stay in the village?
It's our home.
I'm not going anywhere.
This is a chance for all of us
to get to know each other again
for the very first time.
And I finally have a
chance to bake something
besides terrible muffins!
[laughter]
[happy chatter]
Now those are real smiles.
I'll never get used to that.
I think it's divine.
Does that mean the map is
calling us somewhere else?
I have a feeling it means
our work here is done.
Applejack: Looks like you
were right, Twilight.
The map did have a reason
for sendin' us here.
We brought real friendship
to these here ponies.
Guess that's why you're the
Princess of Friendship.
But the map didn't send me.
It sent us.
You're a part of me, all of you,
and there's no doubt you're
a part of my mission
to spread friendship, too.
[happy chatter]
This feels like an ending.
It doesn't have to be
an ending yet, right?
'Cause that Sugar
Belle can bake.
Maybe we can stay a
little while longer.
Come on!