[splat]
So, Scootaloo's keeping
Petunia busy like you asked.
What did you two
want to talk about?
I'm sure you get these
questions all the time.
Oh, this is so awkward.
Uh, you're the experts, so we
thought you'd have some insight
into our daughter's
new... uh, cutie mark.
What's wrong?
Obviously, we're both very proud
of her and her cutie mark.
Despite its, um,
unsettling nature.
Unsettling?
I don't get
what you mean.
Her mark doesn't
bother you at all?
[petunia] Hey! Check
out what we found!
Look! A spiny-backed Pon-asaurus
in our own backyard!
And I found them on my
very own. How cool is that?
Oooooh. She's an
archaeologist!
Of course! What did you think
she was gonna be? A pirate?
Pirate! Pfft! Why
would we think that?
[fake laughter]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart!
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Whoo-hoo! Another successful
cutie intervention.
You know Crusaders, I don't
want to toot our own horn...
but we've helped a lot of
ponies figure out their
purpose in life.
Like Blue Note, here. Nice
saxophone, Blue Note!
♪♪
Yep. Everywhere you look,
there's a pony we've
helped find a purpose.
[tapping]
You've gotta admit, we've
had a pretty good effect
on everypony since
we discovered
our destiny.
And started helping
other ponies
discover theirs!
Could this get any
better or what?
Now, Scootaloo, you do know
there will always be challenges.
Someday, somepony might even
come to us with a problem
that even we can't
handle. Like, say...
...a griffon?
Ha! Exactly. Like a griffon.
But that's just crazy talk.
OR NOT!
♪♪
Is that really a griffon?
You're durn tootin' it is!
Whaddya think that
griffon wants?
I guess we've gotta
ask her but...
aren't Griffons supposed to
be kind of mean and cranky?
Crusaders, looks like we've
gotta step carefully!
The Cutie Mark Crusaders?
I can't believe it's
really really you!
[giggling]
This... griffon... not cranky!
How in the blooming apples
did you know who we are?
Know who you are?
KNOW WHO YOU ARE?
Why, I've heard about you
from everypony in Ponyville!
I'm so excited to meet
you, I could just EXPLODE!
I'm Gabriella, but
you can call me Gabby,
since we're friends
now. Pleased to meetcha!
[wobbly shout]
Well, howdy, um... Gabby.
OOOOOOH! I'm just
about the most excited
any griffon has ever
been about anything.
Excited? But whatever for?
What for? WHAT FOR?
Everypony in town tells me
of your amazing assistance.
How you help ponies find
their place in the world.
It's a calling. But...
And that's why I'm
here. I need help, too.
I want you to give
me a cutie mark!
Um, can a griffon
even GET a Cutie Mark?
I don't know, but I think we
should probably find out.
[nervous giggling]
So, Gabriella...
Gabby, 'kay?
'Gabby.' Why do you
even want a cutie mark?
It doesn't seem like a very
griffon-y thing to want.
Right? Right? RIIIIIGHT?
You're telling me! I don't
know if you've heard,
but griffons can be a
little bit unfriendly.
Most griffons don't pay much
attention to each other.
And if they do,
it's not, y'know...
the good kind of attention.
As for me, I'm just a little
mail-delivery griffon
who likes to spread a little
bit of griffon-y sunshine
on my rounds! Which
always made me feel
different from the
other griffons.
[slamming doors]
I'd do anything for any
ol' griffon in need.
[indignant squawks]
But it just always seemed
like the harder I tried,
the less I fit in!
It wasn't until your friends
came to Griffonstone
that I realized some
creatures actually like
helping each other.
And I saw something
so awesomely awesome!
How helping spreads from pony
to pony and griffon to griffon.
I knew then that I had find
out why I was so different
from the other griffons.
And I knew the answer just
HAD to have something to do
with those wonderful, amazing
marks on the ponies' flanks!
And I admit, I became,
maybe, a little obsessed.
So first chance I had to
deliver a letter from Gilda,
I took it so I could
find the perfect ponies
to help me understand
what those marks are.
Everypony here
told me one thing:
I just HAD to see the
cutie mark crusaders.
They've helped everypony
here get their cutie marks.
And I knew, I just knew, that
someday I'd have one, too:
a cutie mark of my very own!
That's why I flew
all the way here.
I want to find my own
place in the world
and I know you can help me
by giving me a cutie mark!
So let's make with
the cutie!
Whenever you're ready!
Did it happen yet?
Uh, not exactly.
How 'bout now? How 'bout now?
Um, Gabby, I hate
to break it to you,
but it sounds like you
mighta heard some tall tales
about what Crusaders can do.
I mean, we are kinda
awesome and all,
but nopony can just
give you a cutie mark.
It just sort of... happens.
Though I'm pretty sure it
doesn't happen to Griffons.
Or if it does, we've
never ever heard of it.
Oh. I hadn't thought of that.
Sounds like a challenge.
And who could be up to it
but the world-famous
Cutie Mark Crusaders?
Cutie marks: it's in
your name and everything,
right? Right? RIGHT?
Now I have to deliver Gilda's
letter to Rainbow Dash.
I bet by the time I get back,
you'll have it one-hundred
percent figured out!
Toodles for now.
Wheeeee! Gonna
get my Cutie Mark!
What she wants, it's
not possible, right?
I don't know. But I know
someone who just might!
I've read every
book on the subject.
And I've never read a
thing about any creature
other than a pony
getting a cutie mark!
But Twilight, Gabby flew all the
way here so we could help her.
There's gotta be
something we can do.
Say... is there some kind
of spell you can whip up
to make her mark appear?
Um, I don't know if any of
you remember, but using magic
to get a cutie mark never
really works out all that well.
Ohhhhhh... riiiiight.
Crusaders, I'm sorry. While
I can't say for certain
that it's utterly impossible,
the chances of Gabby
getting an actual mark
are... pretty slim.
Everything I've ever
learned tells me...
it's just not gonna happen.
Oh NO! Poor Gabby!
What the apples are we
ever gonna tell her?
Crusaders, this is terrible!
Gabby really believed in us, and
now we're going to let her down.
But what else can we do?
Hmmm. You know what,
Crusaders? So what.
Maybe we can't help
Gabby get a cutie mark,
but we can still do
what we're best at.
We can help her
find her purpose!
And I reckon doin' that
is the same for Griffons
as it is for ponies... or any
other creature in Equestria!
All we have to do is be extra
special clear with her.
Like, Crystal Empire clear.
Yeah!
INCOMING!
[groans]
Hiya, you wonderful,
wonderful Crusaders.
I just know you figured
out how to help me
because you're
all so incredible!
Well, Gabby, we've
talked it over
and we think we may just
be able to help you out
but not exactly in
the way you think.
See, here's the thing about
you getting a cutie mark.
I'M GETTING A Cutie
mark! Wooo-whooooo!
Wait, you didn't let me finish!
WHEEEEE!
Um, I think maybe that
could have been clearer.
Cutie mark, cutie mark,
gonna get my cutie mark!
YEAH! Woo-woo-woo-woo-woo!
She's still going! Anypony know
if Griffons ever get tired?
What do you think my mark
will be? A lightning bolt?
An erupting volcano?! I don't
care if it's a jar of marmalade.
I know I'll love
it, whatever it is!
Hold on just a hoofstep, Gabby,
there's something
we need to clear up.
We can definitely help
you find your purpose
but that mark's probably
not gonna happen.
WHAT?!
It's true. Twilight's
never heard of a creature
other than a pony
getting a cutie mark.
Oh, pfft, is that all? You
had me worried for a second.
I mean, there's a first
time for everything, right?
And she didn't say it
was impossible, right?
Well, not exactly.
Well, then if anypony can make
it happen, it's you three!
I mean, you haven't failed yet!
You know what, Gabby?
I promise, we're gonna
do everything we can
to help you get your mark!
OH! It's gonna happen! I can
feel it! Whoo hoo! Whoo hoo!
Aaaaand, she's off again.
Why in tarnation would
you promise something
that just can't be done!
I know what it's like to want
something that's out of reach.
And just because it
hasn't happened yet
doesn't mean it can't.
Maybe trying for the
impossible isn't so bad.
I guess we'll never know for
sure unless we give it a try.
All right. But where
do we even start?
Where we always do, with a good
ol' fashioned Crusaders CHART!
The first thing we gotta
do is find your purpose.
Nopony gets a mark without one.
All right! Let's do this!
What are you good at?
Do you play any sports?
Or like to dance?
Or how about singing? I just
love to sing. LA LA LA LAAAAAAA!
Wow. I kinda wanna
just try everything.
I mean, I don't even
know what to pick!
Don't worry, that's
what we're here for!
♪ [military snare drum beat] ♪
♪♪
♪ Like a racer at
the starting line ♪
♪You're chomping at the bit ♪
♪ You are here to
find your purpose ♪
♪ And the place
you really fit ♪
♪ And until you find your
place in life you're
never gonna quit ♪
♪ We can help you find the
purpose in your life! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ A griffon mixes
lion's strength ♪
♪ With wingéd eagle's might ♪
♪ When I finally find my purpose
then my cutie mark's in sight ♪
♪ Crusaders, I won't
let you down ♪
♪ I've just begun to fight ♪
♪ You're gonna help me find
the purpose in my life! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Got a job that's
just no fun? ♪
♪ Call on me,
I'll get it done ♪
♪ Cauldron's stuck
and needs a mix? ♪
♪ I'm the one who's
got the fix ♪
♪ Help you teach pre-calculus ♪
♪ Scrub the floors,
won't make a fuss ♪
♪ Clearing kelp?
Just give a yelp! ♪
♪ Rarin' to go, ready to help ♪
♪ That's the spirit, you ought
to see what you do best ♪
♪ Try it all, pick your fave
and leave behind the rest ♪
♪ I'll try anything to
get my cutie mark ♪
♪ Keep up with me crusaders
we're just getting our start ♪
♪ Rock your little
ones to sleep ♪
♪ While hanging up the sheets ♪
♪ I can help you with
your heavy load ♪
♪ Walk granny cross
the street ♪
♪ I'll run you around the bases
fast, it's really no big feat ♪
♪ Can we help her find
the purpose in her life? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Cheer you if you're
feeling low ♪
♪ Plant your garden
make it grow ♪
♪ Write a piece for your quartet
filling in on clarinet ♪
♪ Bake that cake as
fast as lightning ♪
♪ She's so good at things
it's frightening ♪
♪ Cutie Mark Crusaders, I
think we've got a problem ♪
♪ Build a boat and sail
it out across the sea ♪
♪ Need some help, you know
that you can count on me ♪
♪ CMCs you're going to
help me find my purpose ♪
♪ The purpose in my life! ♪
♪ In my life! ♪
Now how we gonna do THIS?
[song ends]
Gabby's special purpose
can't be everything, right?
It may as well be.
I don't know how we find
what she's supposed to do
when she can do it all.
And if finding her
purpose seems impossible,
we can just forget about
the whole Griffon-getting
-a-cutie-mark thing which
is actually impossible.
I never should have
gotten her hopes up.
I Did. It. All! So? Lay
it on me, Crusaders.
What's my purpose?
And how do we get a mark
on these here haunches?
Gabby, we... we don't.
Wait! What are you saying?
We're saying that since
you can do everything
so amazingly well...
we just can't figure out what
one thing you're supposed to do.
Gabby. We can't help you.
But-but you're the world-famous
Cutie Mark Crusaders!
I can't believe it. I-- I--
I WON'T believe it.
Gabby! Wait!
We're sorry! We're so, so sorry!
This is just awful!
For the first time ever,
the Cutie Mark Crusaders
are cutie mark... failures!
♪ [dramatic flourish] ♪
I'm sorry, Crusaders. I really
thought we could help Gabby.
I thought we could help anypony.
Maybe that's just it. Maybe
we can only help ponies.
Or maybe we just plain failed.
Failed? Then what
do you call THIS?
A CUTIE MARK!?
WHAT? You got your
mark after all!
Even though we couldn't
find your purpose?
But - whaaaa? Huh? HOW?
An' what does it
mean? A cauldron?
Um, I don't know. Maybe
it means my purpose is uh,
helping uh, Zecora with potions.
That's the first thing I tried.
I guess it just took some time
to appear but here it is!
This. Is. AWESOME!
We're not failures.
Whatever we did WORKED!
I had a feeling we could
help you and we did!
Ooh, we've gotta go see
Twilight right away!
She'll want to know about this.
Correction: she NEEDS
to know about this.
I bet she'll want to
write a whole book
about the very first Griffon to
get a cutie mark of her own!
Oh, totally. Um, but you
know Rainbow Dash asked me
to pick up her answer
to Gilda's letter.
I better take care of
that before I forget.
Here's an idea: uh,
you head to the castle,
I'll meet you there, cutie
mark and all. Um.... toodles!
Wow, can you believe it?
We were able to help her
get her mark after all!
Come on, Crusaders;
let's tell Twilight!
Gabby? You just missed her!
She was in such a hurry
she didn't even come in.
Just dropped this
letter and zoomed away.
Dear Crusaders: I'll
never forget you!
You really are every bit
as awesome as I heard.
I'm heading home to
tell all the griffons
how you did the impossible
by getting me my
cutie mark. Toodles!
[crash]
Wait a second, CUTIE MARK?
You actually got a
griffon a cutie mark
for the first time
in recorded history?
You know what this calls for?
A full-scale research project!
This makes no sense.
Gabby didn't come in
and show you her mark?
You have GOT to get Gabby
back here right away.
I have so many
questions!
I hope I have
enough ink and parchment
to document EVERYTHING!
SPIKE! Guess what just happened!
Weird. Gabby didn't
show Twilight her mark,
like she said she
was gonna do?
Something in this here
applesauce smells kinda fishy.
We better find her and
find out what's going on!
Come on, Crusaders.
Keep your eyes on
the skies, ponies.
Gabby can't have gone far.
She's not in the air,
she's right THERE!
Gabby! Hold up, we're a-comin'!
Um, sorry, no time to chat.
I just stopped to help
this pony get out of the muck
and then I really gotta fly!
OK, HEAVE-HOHHHH!
Gabby, we're your friends!
Why in Equestria you
running away from us?
Running away? Oh,
I'm not running away.
I'm just, um, excited to
show my lovely new cutie mark
to everyone in Griffonstone.
You mean the cutie mark that's
runnin' right off your flank?
Yup. That's the one.
I guess the one thing I'm
really not that good at...
is faking things.
Wow, Gabby, painting
on a fake cutie mark
to make yourself feel better?
You must have been REALLY upset.
Sure, I was disappointed
but I didn't do it to
make myself feel better.
I wanted to make
you feel better!
[gasp]
I couldn't bear you three
thinking you failed
after you tried so
hard to help.
That's why I had to leave before
you or Twilight found out
the truth. [sigh]. I'm sorry
I wasn't honest with you.
I'll just wing my way
back to Griffonstone.
Thanks for trying.
You don't need to
apologize for caring about
how other ponies are feelin'!
I'm just sorry we couldn't
come through for you.
Hmmm... maybe we can.
Gabby, clean up and meet us
at the Crusaders clubhouse!
I know you all tried
your very best,
but I guess griffons and
cutie marks just don't mix.
Maybe I don't even
have a special purpose.
Hang on a second! We
were wracking our brains
trying to figure out your
destiny until we remembered
how every time you
did something new,
you tried to help
everypony around you.
Even us! How did it feel
when you showed up
with that fake mark
and the three of us thought
we'd actually helped you?
Well... I was really glad
I helped you feel happier!
So maybe helping is
your thing.
You might even say
it's your purpose.
But helping just feels good. It
couldn't have anything to do
with what I'm supposed to
do with my life, right?
Gabby, finding your special
purpose doesn't have to be
about being good at something,
it's about feeling good
about something inside.
And it looks like your destiny
is a whole lot like ours:
helping others.
And you don't need a symbol
on your flank to know that!
But since we ARE the
Cutie Mark Crusaders,
we made you one
anyway! Behold!
Your very own cutie mark!
TA DA!
We carved it to mark the
moment we all figured out
what you should
do with your life!
But they look just like
yours? You can't mean...
You bet we do! You're one of us
now! Gabby, today we dub thee...
the very first Griffon member
of the Cutie Mark Crusaders!
WOOHOO!
You may not be able
to get a cutie mark...
...but you're selflessly
dedicatin' your life
to helpin' others anyhow!
I can't think of anything
more Crusadery than that!
AWESOME! My very own cutecinera!
Landsakes, you sure
have earned it!
And so have we. Scootaloo,
you're pretty amazing.
Even though things
looked bleak,
you still found a way to
help Gabby in the end.
'Course! Helping's
what we do, right?
Ooooo, I am SOOOOO grateful!
I'm gonna go home and
do my very very best
to bring Cutie Mark Crusader
values to Griffonstone,
I promise!
Promise us one other thing, too?
COME BACK SOON!
After all, you're a Crusader
now. Crusaders forever?
Crusaders forever!
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ friends ♪