[Rarity] I'm so sorry I lost
track of time on our picnic.
I didn't mean for us to get
caught out here after dark,
but there's really
nothing to be afraid of.
The forest at night is the same
as the forest during the day...
[whistling wind]
...only darker.
[thud]
[teeth chattering]
Still, maybe we should
hurry back to the cottage.
[whoosh]
Nothing to worry
about. No reason to...
[rustling]
[scary moaning]
RUN!
AAAHHHH!
[fearful whimpering]
[scary moaning]
[thunderclap]
[roar]
[scream]
Haw! Haw! Haw!
Got ya! Ha ha ha!
[gasping]
That wasn't funny.
You really scared me.
I hope you're happy.
[low snarl]
Nope. You're too easy.
You're scared of everything.
That's not true!
Boo.
AAAHHHH!
[chattering teeth]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure!
Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart!
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness
it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
I mean, how could you
not appreciate that?
Because I don't think
being scared is very fun.
I do! Your heart
gets all racey!
Your hooves get all tingly.
Your mouth gets all dry-y.
Actually, I don't like that
part, but the rest is great!
See? Everypony likes a good
prank. They're just jokes.
[Rarity] Now, Rainbow Dash,
I don't think Fluttershy
would have called us all here
to talk about this if she
thought it was funny.
Everypony has things they
like and things they don't.
And scaring Fluttershy
is just lazy.
LAZY?
A prank isn't
very good
if you're the only
pony laughing.
But what if it's really,
really, really, really,
really, really funny?
And I can do funny.
I know you can. I guess
the trick is making sure
that your idea of funny
matches the pony you're
pranking. That way-
[fart sound]
[laugh]
[giggles]
[screaming laughter]
Good one, Rainbow! You have
to admit. That was funny.
Not really.
Yeah. A whoopee cushion
is like a joke shortcut.
WHAT!?
[Rainbow] Honestly, Rainbow
Dash,
if you are not willing
to put forth the effort
required to pull a prank
that everypony can enjoy,
you may as well not
pull one at all.
Fine. If you ponies
want effort,
then that's just
what you'll get.
I'm not sure she
understood what we meant.
I know you're excited about
the Filly Guide cookie drive,
but I still have to do
a few finishing touches
on your uniform.
Mmmm. Not bad.
Hmm. "You asked for it."
What does it mean?
Hmm. I assume this is
Dash's idea of a prank.
Which can only mean she's
rigged some kind of booby trap
to your Filly Guide
uniform up there.
So... how do we
get it down?
We don't. If Dash thinks
I'm going to fall
for whatever she's
got in mind,
she's got another
thing coming.
There's more uniforms
where that one came from.
Mmm. The sewing machine
cake is actually better
than the cake cake!
RAINBOW DASH!
[laughing] GOTCHA! Ha ha!
How's that for effort?
[clang]
What's all this, Applejack?
I thought you were
gonna help me get ready
for the Filly
Guide Cookie drive.
Uh, yeah. Sorry about that,
but Rainbow Dash has been
on a pranking tear and you
can never be too careful.
Do you really think Dash
is gonna try to prank you
in your sleep?
Not if I have anything
to say about it.
[click]
See you in the
morning, sugar cube.
[grunt]
Huh?
[crowing]
Whooooaa.
[splash]
[clang]
Ha! Still think I'm
lazy? Gotcha! Ha ha!
[grunt] RAINBOW DASH!
[splash]
[oinking laugh]
♪ [square dance
accordion music] ♪
♪♪
Ha ha! Got ya!
[crash]
Got ya!
[clang]
[laughing]
Got ya!
Pinkie, we need
your help.
OK!
For what?
Are you honestly going to
stand there and tell us
you know nothing about all
the pranking Rainbow Dash
has been doing?
Oh, no. She's been
pranking up a storm!
Did she get you, too?
[laughs] Oh, yeah.
She and Gummy both...
Boo.
AHH-HAHAHA!
They got me good.
Well, she needs to stop.
Stop? But pranks
are so much fun.
Not for everypony and it
doesn't seem like Dash
is taking the time to
find out who enjoys them
and who doesn't.
Uh, since you and Dash
share such an... affinity
for pranking, we thought you
might be able to get her to,
um... quit it.
Hey, Rainbow Dash!
I have something very
important to tell you.
Pinkie! Hey.
I actually have something
totally important to tell you!
You do? Oh.
You go first!
OK, you know how I've
been pranking everypony?
Yeah. It's been
pretty funny.
I-I mean, actually,
that's what I have
to talk to you about.
Here, have a cookie.
Oooh. Thanks.
So I got to thinking,
why waste my time
pranking every
pony one at a time,
when I could prank
everypony at once!?
Wow. Everypony at
once? That sounds amazing.
Uh. Wait. I mean,
it's not...
You don't even know
what it is yet.
Pinkie, this is going to
be the best prank ever!
I special ordered
these joke cookies
so the colors would
match my mane.
And...?
And I'm gonna switch them
with the Filly Guide Cookies.
When Scootaloo and
her friends sell them,
everypony in town's gonna
get a rainbow mouth,
courtesy of Rainbow Dash, ha
ha! It's gonna be so awesome.
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, it doesn't really
seem all that funny.
WHAT!?
Maybe this is a good time to
stop pranking for a while.
The other ponies
in town have--
STOP!? No way! This prank
is happening, Pinkie.
And it's going to
be hilarious!
[munch]
Pinkie! What's the deal? I
told you I needed your help
switching out all the
Filly Guide Cookies
for the joke cookies.
But when you didn't show, I
had to do it all by myself!
Uh, Pinkie?
[cough]
Wow. Your face is
still pretty rainbowed.
Yeah. I haven't really [cough]
[cough] been feeling well,
and these joke cookies
are the only thing
that makes me feel better.
You don't have any
more, do you?
Uh, no. I just told you. I
used them all for the prank.
Oh.
Pretty soon, the CMCs
will start selling them
to every pony in town.
Ponies will open their
boxes and start eating.
Then all of their teeth
will turn rainbow-colored
and they'll know it was me.
It's gonna be so awesome! Come
on. You don't want to miss it.
Actually, [cough] I don't
think I can even stand up...
UNLESS YOU'VE GOT
MORE COOKIES!
Agh! On second thought, maybe
you better stay here and rest.
[sigh] Yeah. You're right.
Sorry to miss out. I'm sure
it's going to be hilarious.
♪ [upbeat banjo] ♪
All right, who's ready
to sell some cookies?
All: ME!
Look, here, Rainbow Dash.
I know you promised
Scootaloo you'd help out,
but I don't want
none of your pranks
ruinin' these
fillies' night.
Look, I'll be with
you the whole night
so you can totally
keep an eye on me.
Come on, Applejack,
let's get started.
Yeah! We've got a lot
of ground to cover.
We wanna hit every
house in Ponyville!
♪♪
Come on! You heard her.
Every house in Ponyville.
Heh heh heh.
♪♪
[knock knock]
[growl]
[scream]
[knock knock]
[laughing]
Applejack: I think you
three should be real proud.
Y'all did a mighty impressive
job for your first go-round.
You took the words right
out of my mouth, Applejack.
Isn't that right,
Rainbow Dash?
Any minute now.
Uh... any minute now, what?
Huh? Oh. Uh, nothing.
Have you guys noticed
how quiet it's gotten?
I mean, it's still
early, right?
Of course it's quiet.
Ponies can't talk
while they're eating
those fabulous cookies!
You think?!
Of course.
They're probably all in
a cookie coma right now.
Huh. Maybe you're
right. I'll go check.
What is going on?
OK, definite
cookie-eating happening.
But where is everypony?
They must have seen their
rainbow mouths by now.
They should all be running
out into the streets.
Unless everypony
went to bed early.
Pinkie?
♪ [mysterious] ♪
The whole town
got the cookies
and now everypony is
shut up in their houses!
You don't think there's
something wrong
with the joke
cookies, do you?
[clatter]
[crashing tins]
Mrs. Cake! Whew.
Have you seen Pinkie?
I was thinking I might
have something to do
with her not feeling great.
Uh, Mrs. Cake?
[munching]
Cooookies! Cooooookies!
Uhhhhh... I can see you're
busy. I'll come back.
[crash]
COOOOKIEEEES!
[scream]
More coookies.
COOOOKIEEEES...
More coookies
♪ [horror music] ♪
More cookies!
♪♪
[zombie noises]
[panting]
♪♪
Twilight! You've gotta come
with me to Sugarcube Corner.
Something's going
on with the Cakes.
Well, not something, exactly.
I mean, it may have something
to do with these joke cookies.
COOOKIEEEEES...
Oh no.
COOOOKIEEEEES...
[whimper]
Fluttershy?
COOOOKIEEEEES...
[growls]
[slam]
[panting]
COOOOKIEEEEES...
♪ horror sting ♪
[crash]
COOOOKIEEEEES...
You sure you don't mind
us all coming over?
Oh, of course not.
I think the girls have
earned a little celebration
for all of their hard work.
And I have plenty of sewing
machine cake left over.
Unless, anypony
wants a cookie.
Don't touch those!
Oh! There is certainly
no call for that.
There is plenty
for everypony.
Come on! We've got
to get out of here.
What in tarnation are
you going on about?
There's no time! You
have to follow me!
Oh, Rainbow Dash, if you
want all those cookies,
you will have to buy them,
just like everypony else.
I don't want the cookies-
[zombie noises]
...but they do.
Whhh-what's happening?
I'll explain later! Come on!
COOOOOOOKIEEEEEEESSSSS!
We need to find
somewhere to hide!
[zombie noises]
Cooooookies.
This way!
[zombie noises]
[hammering]
Did we lose them?
Why are we running from
the ponies of Ponyville?
What happened to
all of our friends?
I think it's something
in the cookies.
Uh, that's ridiculous.
Filly Guide Cookies
haven't changed for years.
It's not like there's a new
ingredient that's turning
the whole town into
cookie-craving zombies.
Unless there is.
What are you saying?
What did you do?
COOKIEEEES...
Cover the windows!
COOOOOOKIIEEEEEEEES!
♪ [dramatic] ♪
OK. So, I may have switched
all the Filly Guide Cookies
for joke cookies that
were supposed to make
ponies' mouths rainbow, but
somehow turned everypony
into mindless cookie-eating
zombies instead.
I figure we just hide out here
until the effects wear off
and as long as nopony
else eats the cookies,
we'll be fine
That's lovely, darling,
except for one thing...
We've already eaten them.
[zombie noises]
Looks like your prank
up and backfired.
[scream]
COOOOKIEEEES!
[gasp]
Cooooookies...
More... Cookies...
No. Stay away. They're
making you sick!
You don't want these.
But we dooo. We want COOKIES.
Please. Stop! I never
meant for this to happen.
It was just a harmless prank.
It was supposed to be funny.
But this isn't funny at all!
Pinkie (normal voice)
Exactly!
What?
Wait. What's happening?
Just delighting in
pranking the prankster.
He-heh, yeah.
How does it feel to get
some of your own medicine?
So, you're not sick?
None of you are?
Of course not, silly.
[Everyone] GOTCHA!
This... was all... a PRANK?
Yep. And you can
thank Pinkie Pie.
After you told her about your
plan to prank the whole town,
she got everypony together
and came up with a way
to turn the tables on you.
Aw, shucks. It was nothing.
Just a little something
I threw together.
Uh...
Wow. You should
see your face.
Ha ha! Talk about funny!
Well, I don't think
it's very funny!
And I'm the one that got
pranked. I was really scared.
I thought I made everypony sick.
You can't just go around...
Pranking whoever
you feel like?
Without thinking about how
it might make them feel?
Or if they'd even enjoy it?
Or think it's funny?
Yeah! Oh. I see
what you did there.
Pranks can be a lot
of fun when everypony
has a good time. I thought
you just needed to see
what it's like
when they don't.
I guess I did. I'm
sorry, everypony.
I haven't really been thinking
about how other ponies feel.
Well, I hope you
learned your lesson.
Totally! You ponies pulled
off an amazing prank.
I'll have to work
extra hard to top it.
[crickets]
Gotcha!
[laughter]