♪♪
[Starlight] It's the ponies
from my old village.
[laughing]
Oh! It's only a dream.
With my past, I should never
be in charge of anything.
THEY'VE TAKEN MY SISTER AND I!
IT'S WORSE THAN LAST TIME!
Chrysalis and the
Changelings are back.
They've ponynapped all of
the most powerful ponies
in Equestria.
This is Thorax. He's
a reformed Changeling.
They took Fluttershy?
I think I have a pretty good
idea where she might be.
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
♪ [scary music] ♪
Oh, this is so strange.
We're here and that's there
and I clearly meant for us
to be there and not here.
Oh, I can probably
explain that.
Oh well, if at first
you don't succeed.
Maybe we should come
up with a plan first?
A what?
You know, figuring out the
best way to do something
before you actually do it?
[laughing] Oh,
that's adorable.
But, you see, unlike
you I can do anything.
Actually--
That's all very nice, but
really a waste of time.
We have me.
And what else could
we possibly need?
A draconequis with magic AND
half a brain might help.
Why are you here
again?
I mean, it's not like you're
going to stop the Changelings
by pulling a rabbit
out of the hat.
At least my magic
can do something.
The thing about
magic here is--
Like this!
For Fluttershy!
Eeyah!
[oinking]
I've been trying to tell you.
Nothing other than
Changeling magic works here!
Chrysalis' throne is carved
from an ancient dark stone
that soaks up outside magic
the same way Changelings
soak up love. It's how
she keeps the hive safe.
[chimes]
So... What kind of
plan were you thinking?
Without magic I have no idea.
But nopony else is coming,
so somepony better
come up with something.
Anypony?
Anything?
Hmmm.
This throne. If we get into
the hive and destroy it,
can we get our magic back?
Uh-huh.
Well, that's a terrible plan.
How are we even supposed
to get to the hive?
We walk?
I haven't walked that
far in millennia.
Ugh.
Ugh. I don't know how any
of you manage not being able
to disappear and reappear
whenever you want.
Well, I for one definitely miss
you being able to disappear.
Give Discord a break.
None of us knew we weren't
going to be able to use magic.
I did.
If we get separated, it might
make sense to have a way
to make sure we are
who we say we are.
Ooo. Like a secret code.
How about if I say "We are"
you say "Doomed?" Or you say
"Rescue" and I say "I'm--
[crash]
How about if we say "Klutzy"
and you say "Draconequis?"
Klutzy draconequis.
Works for me.
I'll definitely
remember it.
[whistling wind]
[Trixie] OK. I am
definitely glad you came.
I don't think we'd be able
to find our way without you.
You definitely wouldn't.
[rumble and slam]
Um... Where's the way out?
It's a Changeling Hive. It
shifts and changes like we do
and we're the only ones
who can navigate it.
It's total chaos to
non-Changelings.
Well, it's decent chaos. I don't
know if I'd call it total.
Discord: Are we sure that
I'll get my magic back
when we destroy
this throne-thingy?
If Thorax is
right, then yes.
Well, that's reassuring.
And how are we supposed
to destroy the throne
when we find it?
I... don't know.
That's reassuring.
I don't suppose you brought
any throne-destroying tools
along with these
useless side show props?
Asks the "lord of chaos"
who can't go for a walk
without whining non-stop.
Yes, but when the
throne is destroyed,
I'LL be able to rip the
very fabric of reality
to save our friends
while YOU'LL still be
a self-absorbed,
below-average illusionist.
SELF-ABSORBED?! Why you--
CUT! IT! OUT!
I'm just barely
keeping it together
and it would be WONDERFUL if you
two could actually try to help
instead of bickering like foals.
OK.
How can we help?
Don't ask me! I couldn't
even handle giving advice
at the Sunset Festival
and I HAD magic then!
And the three of us
are as good as useless.
At least Thorax knows
where we're going.
[Thorax] Um... guys?
I think we're lost.
[Trixie] Aww, great!
We might as well just
sit here and wait
for the Changelings to
soak up all of our love
or whatever gross thing
it is that they do.
How often do you
all get hungry?
Actually, I haven't
been since I met Spike.
And Changelings
are always hungry.
We can never get
enough love.
Well, that's just super.
But you aren't
hungry at all now?
Once I made a few friends,
I guess I just sort of...
forgot about the
whole feeding thing.
Is that about the same
time your wings changed?
I guess so.
[Discord
yawns]
While I would love to
sit around chit-chatting
about feeding and
not feeding.
I have a FLUTTERSHY to save!
[Echo: to save,
to save, to save]
Can you please lower your voice?
You're going to get
us all captured!
Oh! You keep saying
that, but I haven't seen
an actual Changeling since
we got into this hive.
[buzzing]
What's that!?
A CHANGELING PATROL!
♪ [scary music] ♪
♪♪
[gasping]
This seems like one of those
moments where we need a plan.
What kind of plan?
We have no magic
and it's not like my illusions
are going to save us.
Do you have any of
your smoke bombs?
Are you kidding?
Looking for somepony?
[whoosh]
[snarl]
Is that the best
you've got? Hahaha!
[whoosh]
[explosion]
[zoom]
♪♪
Not exactly Great and
Powerful, but effective.
I'll take it.
Klutzy...
Draconequis.
[whoosh]
I really think we
need a new code word.
That was a pretty
good plan.
But we still don't
know where we're going.
[Trixie] Actually, we might.
Two of the Changelings
didn't go with the rest.
Oh! With an intruder
in the hive,
they went to
protect the Queen.
Good thinking,
Starlight!
[nervous laugh]
[buzzing]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪♪
Now what?
We go in.
Even if I wanted to, there's
no way past the guards.
We'll be spotted for sure.
We need some kind
of distraction.
I'm fresh out of
smoke bombs.
Normally I'm the most
distracting thing
I can think of, but
without magic...
You shouldn't
underestimate yourself.
[slam]
[stomp]
[tap tap tap]
Hello, Changelings and
Changelettes, believe me;
I was just as surprised
as you are that I'm here.
When I heard that I'd be playing
for a bunch of Changelings,
I was beside myself. Then I
realized it was just one of you.
♪ [snare drum rim shot] ♪
[chuckle]
But seriously, this
isn't the toughest crowd
I've ever been in front of,
but it's definitely
the easiest to bug.
♪ [drum shot with cymbal] ♪
To bug...
Is this thing on?
[tap tap]
[angry hissing]
Well, if you think that
you can do any better,
be my guest!
♪♪
It is absolutely ridiculous
that that worked.
It is certainly a pleasure
to have such dedicated fans.
I'll have to come back
with some new material
after I rescue Fluttershy.
Please... Help...
Fluttershy!
Discord! I'm stuck!
You certainly are.
And I should probably
help you get free, but...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
But what?
But you are obviously
not Fluttershy.
Oh.
I mean, I'm separated
from the group
and just happen to come across
the one pony I care most about?
I can smell this
set-up a mile away.
[sobbing]
No. You're right.
There's no way you
should trust me.
Just go find the
others. I understand.
Oh, come on.
[loud sobbing]
We're probably
all Changelings.
You shouldn't
rescue any of us.
Unless you think maybe one of us
might be the real Fluttershy.
That certainly would be a nasty
Changeling trick, wouldn't it?
I'm the real one.
I'm the real
Fluttershy.
[snivelling]
We can't wait for Discord.
Between seeing him and Trixie,
the castle will be
crawling with guards soon.
But if we do manage to
destroy Chrysalis' throne,
we'll need him.
He could take on the
entire Changeling army
by sneezing if he
wanted to.
He's probably already
been captured.
Hello? Fellow rescuers?
We can't stay here. We've
got to find the throne!
Oooh! I heard some
of the Changelings
who were chasing me say
that they know where it is.
Klutzy...
Hmmmm? Oh, yeah haha. I can
be klutzy. Now, follow me!
You know that's
not Discord, right?
Obviously.
This way! We're
almost there!
I know this trick. If
he says to go left,
we should definitely go right.
He's leading us to a
swarm waiting to attack.
[sigh]
OK, I'll handle it.
You two just get ready to
run into the other tunnel.
Wait, what!? Trixie
you can't.
I won't know what to do.
We've already lost Discord.
I can't lose you too.
Without magic I--
Starlight, you got us this
far with just my illusions
and Discord's
annoying personality.
You don't need magic to
figure out what to do next.
I know you're afraid
to be in charge,
but you're really good at it.
Listen to your best friend.
Hey, Discord? Wanna see the new
trick I've been working on?
I call it, "The
Changeling Catcher!"
Run!
[whoosh]
♪♪
♪ [weak] Ta-daaa... ♪
[panting]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪ [music quiets] ♪
♪♪
[splat]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪♪
[evil laugh] One little
pony all by herself.
Oh, how will I ever
prevent this daring rescue?
[hissing and snarling]
Well, well, well. The Princess
of Friendship's sole pupil.
Honestly, I didn't think
you were worth replacing
with one of my drones.
You won't get away with this!
I already have. Nopony
is coming to save you.
Your little squad was it,
and now there's just you.
Thorax is still out there.
Don't mention that traitor's
name in my Kingdom!
He was a fool to leave and
even more a fool to return.
When I find him he'll
learn just what happens
to those who betray the hive.
[whimper]
And it seems I don't
have far to look, do I.
[zap]
Thorax!
[hiss]
[clanking]
Very clever. And clearly Thorax
revealed to you the secret
of my throne. I can't
have powerful ponies
using their
abilities against me.
Even with your
rather embarrassing
little rescue attempt,
everything has gone
according to MY plan.
What plan? Why did
you do all this?
So I could feed, of course!
By replacing the most beloved
figures in Equestria,
my drones will be able to store
all the love meant for them
and return it here... to me.
Everypony will do as I
command and my subjects
and I will feed on their love
for generations! [evil laugh!]
What if you
didn't have to?
Ridiculous!
The hunger of Changelings
can never be satisfied.
Exactly. Thorax left the
hive and made a friend.
He shared love and now
he doesn't need to feed!
You don't have to live your
lives starving all the time!
You know nothing
of the Changelings
or what it takes
to be their Queen!
I decide what is best for my
subjects, not some mewling grub!
I know what it's like to lead
by fear and intimidation.
And I know
what it's like
to want everypony
to do what you say.
But I was wrong. A real leader
doesn't force her subjects
to deny who they are.
She celebrates what
makes them unique...
and listens when one of
them finds a better way.
The only thing
Thorax has found,
is what happens to those who
turn their back on the hive!
[zap]
No! Stop!
Just as soon as I drain every
last ounce of love from him
and show my subjects
what a real leader is.
I can feel the love
inside me slipping away.
I can't hold onto
it much longer.
Then don't!
Sharing love is what made
you different to begin with.
You should share
yours with Chrysalis.
Give her all of it.
[whoosh]
[zapping]
This is what happens
when you give love freely
instead of taking it.
♪♪
[rumbling and cracking]
[explosion]
♪ [soft music] ♪
♪♪
Fluttershy?
It's, um, good to see you too.
Starlight?
What happened?
We defeated the Changelings
with no magic at all;
they found a new leader...
and they're all
kinda good now.
Well done, Starlight Glimmer.
It seems as though you've
learned a great deal
since we last spoke.
[cracking]
[shriek]
♪♪
When Twilight and her
friends defeated me,
I chose to run away and seek
revenge. You don't have to.
You can be the leader
your subjects deserve.
There is no revenge you
could ever conceive of
that will come close to
what I will exact upon you
one day, Starlight Glimmer!
Thorax, as the new leader
of the Changelings,
I look forward to discussing how
we can improve our relationship
in the future.
However, for the moment,
perhaps it is best
that we leave the Changeling
Kingdom to the Changelings.
[poof]
Splendid idea!
Now who's ready
for some celebratory
tea at Fluttershy's?
Oh. Um. Everypony?
Actually, now that you
can snap your claws
and send us absolutely
anywhere again,
I think I have a
better option.
Uh.. Hey Starlight.
What are you doing here?
You left in such
a hurry before,
we kinda thought you
didn't want to come.
Yeah. I guess after the way I
used my magic on all of you,
I wasn't sure I was somepony
who should even be in charge
of a baking contest. I was
afraid I might go back
to being the pony I
used to be. But...
I realized that sometimes
you don't have a choice.
You have to step up. And I
HAVE changed. I can handle it.
Whether than means saving
Equestria OR helping friends
with a sunset festival.
Speaking of which...
I know the festival is almost
over, but I kinda invited
a few of my
friends to join.
Hope that's OK.
Are you kidding? Of course!
Great. Now, where's
that baking contest?
This pony needs a cupcake!
So I'm able to rip the very
fabric of reality again.
Yeah, yeah and I'm
still a self-absorbed,
below-average
illusionist. Right?
Actually, I was going to say
a COUPLE of those illusions
were slightly above average.
If you ever need a little chaos
in your act, let me know.
Ha! When pigs fly!
Your wish is my command!
[snap]
[squeal]
Whoa-whoaaaa!
Somepony is really gonna have to
catch us up on what we missed.