Spring training was awesome, but
I can't wait to see my friends!
I'm gonna catch up on some
Daring Do with Twilight,
help Applejack make
my favorite cider,
and have a sleepover
with Pinkie!
We get it, you have
a fun week planned.
Meanwhile I'm stuck here running
trials week at the Academy.
But you love yelling and
blowing your whistle.
Yeah. I do.
See you gals later!
[whoosh]
Heh heh heh.
[sigh]
[alarm beeping]
Huh? Oh, the map!
Hey Twilight! So
where am I going?
The Crystal Mountains?
Vanhoover? Here?
Please say here.
Well, the good news is we
both got called by the map.
Awesome! Does that
mean there's bad news?
No! Well, not exactly.
Aww, I was just there!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Ahem.
All right newbies,
welcome to trials week
for the Wonderbolt Academy!
You'll be judged on your
speed, strength, agility
and technique, culminating
in a final evaluation.
Will it be hard? Yes.
Will you cry? Maybe.
Will you fly so much
your wings fall off?
That has only happened once.
She's just exaggerating
to make a point, right?
I mean, wings can't
really fall off, can they?
You think you've got what it
takes to be an elite flyer?
Yes, ma'am!
Well, let me tell
you, you don't.
I remember when she
said that to me.
[excited hero-worship chatter]
You don't think Rainbow
Dash is the pony
whose wings fell
off, do you?
[whistle blast]
Quit yer whisperin' and give me
five hundred laps! Go go go!
Um... I just wanted you to know.
You two are my favorite
ponies in all of Equestria.
Well, isn't that sweet. Now
get going on those laps!
Welcome, Princess
Twilight!
What are you doing
back so soon?
Official Friendship business.
Have you noticed anypony having
a hard time with their friends?
Not really. But it's
not my job to worry
about their relationships. I'm
here to make them elite fliers.
Adorable. They're so full
of hope and competition.
Their technique could
use some work, though.
You should tell them.
I'm sure they'd appreciate
any notes from you.
Nah. I wouldn't want to
mess with their confidence.
But they'll never get better if
they don't know what to work on.
Sloppy wing placement.
Crooked lines.
I'm gonna have to drill
them on basic technique
in the classroom portion.
Classroom portion?
Yeah. It's everypony's least
favorite part of trial week,
but it has to be done.
Maybe we can help.
We can?
Absolutely.
Between your flying skills
and my teaching expertise,
they could learn a lot!
Plus, once they get to know us,
they'll be more comfortable
coming to us with their
friendship problems.
Count us in.
Great!
[tweet]
You have your work
cut out for you.
Thank goodness I had time
to whip up a few charts
on flight patterns
and wing symmetry!
It's fresh in my mind from
when I learned to fly.
This is so exciting!
Maybe for you. I
practically fell asleep
when I went through
this. Tell ya what.
I'll leave the
teaching stuff to you
and I'll just make
sure they stay awake.
[blast]
I'm pretty sure their thirst
for knowledge will keep them
bright-eyed and bushy tailed.
[laugh] Good
one, Twilight.
[blast]
Wake up, newbies!
Class is in session.
Hello, students!
I'm Twilight Sparkle and
this is Rainbow Dash.
But you can call us T-Sparks
and the Dashinator!
[Twilight] Ahem!
Heh heh. Just kidding.
And we're here to go over
basic flying technique.
[Kid] Uggggggh.
Who said that?
Me. I mean, we're here because
we're amazingly awesome
crazy good flyers. We're
waaaaay past basics.
What's your name?
Sky Stinger. You've
never heard of me?
He set the record
for the fastest
vertical acceleration rate.
500 feet in two seconds.
That's pretty impressive.
It's amazing.
Ahem. It is.
And we can talk personal
records after class, Ms...?
Vapor Trail. She's my wingpony.
I never fly without her.
But you'll have to
in the solo trials.
There are solo trials?
Yup. It's a part of
your final evaluation.
We'll ace that test with our
wings tied behind our flanks.
My picture will go
right up there,
next to yours.
That's a mighty big claim
considering everypony here is an
"amazingly awesome
crazy good flyer."
I know.
[ahem] OK! Let's
get back on track.
Now, who can tell me
the best wing angle
to achieve minimal
air resistance?
[snoring ]
[blast]
Wake up, newbies!
Class is in session.
[chattering]
Well, there were a
few hiccups,
but overall that
went pretty well.
[noisy yawn]
Yeah. Nopony fell asleep.
What? I'm not
a student!
Hey, teach!
Me? Or Twilight?
Probably Twilight.
Uh, both. About
the solo test,
I'm actually kinda
worried about it.
Aw. That's all right.
We all have moments
where we doubt ourselves.
No. No. I have absolutely
zero doubts about myself.
I'm a strong flyer, like
really, really, really strong.
But this isn't about me.
I'm worried for Vapor.
Oh. Well... that is
very... kind? Of you.
Tell you what. It's almost
time for freestyle training.
Why don't you grab her and
show us what you've got?
Yes! Prepare to be
impressed. By me.
Like I said, Vapor
still needs work.
Well, he may be full of
himself but I have to admit,
Sky's an excellent flyer. He
must've shot up 200 feet!
But did you see Vapor Trail?
Her wing was under his.
I think she gave him a boost.
I guess I didn't
even notice Vapor.
I was too busy
watching Sky.
Twilight: [gasp] I
think you're right!
Vapor just created a gust of
wind that caught Sky's wing
at a 45 degree angle, propelling
him into a flipping loop.
Somepony paid
attention in class!
Sky obviously has no
idea he's not actually
"amazingly awesome".
And Vapor's so busy making
her friend look good,
she's not focused on
her own flying at all.
This must be our
friendship problem,
and there's only
one thing to do.
Fix it without
telling them!
Tell them
the truth!
You don't want
to tell them?
Of course not. Flying
is like 30 percent skill
and 70 percent confidence.
You can't mess with
a flier's confidence.
But you can't improve if you
don't think you have to!
Besides, Vapor's keeping a
pretty big secret from Sky
and that can lead
to trouble.
Yeah, but if we tell
them that they've been
holding each other back,
that could be trouble too!
I nailed that
flipping loop.
I'm actually surprised
you're still here;
I thought I blew
you away.
You were [PANT]
great, Sky. [PANT]
Come on, Vapor Trail.
You're going to have to
build up your endurance
if you want a shot
at the Academy.
Wonderbolts don't
get winded.
Angel Wings! You call
that cloud busting?
That cloud barely
knew you were there!
I love my job.
We'll keep working
and who knows?
One day you might come close
to being almost as good as me.
Oh, I don't think so.
You were voted Stratusberg's
Most Promising Flier.
I was voted
Best Sneeze.
Achoo!
You do have a
really great sneeze.
Thanks, Sky. But I don't
think I can sneeze my way
into the Academy.
[sigh] I'm pretty beat.
I'm gonna hit the showers.
You have to help her.
Actually, she's
not the one--
Will do!
♪♪
Hey, you did great. You're
a really strong flyer.
Me?
Vapor Trail, we know
what you've been doing.
You've been doing... great!
You've been helping Sky.
Uh. I don't know what
you're talking about.
Sky doesn't need anypony's
help. He's amazing.
Not without you. And it's
gonna be pretty obvious
during the solo trials when
he can't get enough air
to do a flipping loop.
Oh no. I can't let
that happen.
I mean...aww, sugarcubes!
Why are you doing
this for him?
[sigh] It started when we were
kids. You have to understand...
Sky grew up with a lot
of siblings. It was tough.
He was always trying to
get his parents' attention.
Meanwhile, I was an only child
who hated all the attention
I got from mine.
[Mom] Vapor Trail! Where are
you? Do you need a snack?
Do you want to do homework?
[Dad] Or we can just spend
some time together!
All day is never enough!
Mom! Dad! Up here! Look, look,
look, look, look, look, hey!
Mom! Dad! Can you see?
[sigh]
That was amazing!
Flying together gave
us both what we wanted.
But I never told Sky how
much I was helping him.
It started with a
small boost here
or a little gust of
wind there.
But I didn't think my help could
actually hurt his chances!
I understand. But now
you're both in trouble.
You need to work
on your tricks.
And Sky needs to be able to fly
without you or he won't make it.
Oh, but he has to! Flying
with the Wonderbolts
has been Sky's dream
ever since he was a colt!
What about you?
I-I guess I haven't
thought about it.
I just want to be
with my best friend.
Then we have to find a
way to help both of you.
Starting with telling
Sky the truth.
No! You can't. Sky
will be crushed.
And without his confidence
he won't fly as well.
[sigh] Then I guess we'll
give Dash's method a shot.
Yes! I love being right.
OK. Here's what we do.
Sky needs to build his strength.
Air drills, wing lifts...
all that boring,
methodical stuff.
Sounds like my
cup of oats.
But how will we
get him to do that?
He doesn't think
he needs practice.
We'll just tell Sky that he
should practice with Twilight
so you won't feel so
self-conscious about getting
special training from me.
With you? Really?
You'd do that for me?
Ha. You say that like
it's not gonna be a blast.
♪♪
Whoa!
Agh!
♪♪
You were awesome!
Really? Thanks! I can't
believe I was able to keep up!
That's the first nice thing I've
heard you say about yourself.
Hey!
Can we switch now? I want to
do tricks with Rainbow Dash!
You can't. I mean... uh
you're already so good
at the fancy stuff.
And the basic stuff.
You're right. I don't
need to practice at all.
Um. Maybe, Sky,
you should...
I'm already the best and
everypony's gonna know it
when I'm asked to join
the Academy tomorrow.
But not if you
don't practice.
I wouldn't be surprised if they
asked me to become a Wonderbolt
straight out of the trials!
Boom. Dream achieved.
SKY YOU'RE NOT AS GOOD
AS YOU THINK YOU ARE!
What did you say?
Sky. I want you to get
in as much as anypony,
and you're amazing, but...
But what?
I've been... helping you.
Please. I don't need
your help. Watch.
[grunts and groans]
[panting]
How could you do this
to me? Did you all know?
Oh great. So everypony
but me knows I'm a joke.
Was this your plan the whole
time? To embarrass me?
What? No! Don't
you know me at all?
I guess not since it took
me this long to find out
you're a terrible wingpony!
I can't believe you!
I can't believe I
was ever your friend!
[zoom]
Thanks a lot.
Do you think
they're still mad?
Yeah, they're still mad.
This is all my fault. If we
had just done things your way,
maybe we could've
avoided this whole mess.
No, it's my fault.
It hit me when I was
watching Sky train with you.
He wasn't even trying.
Oh no. He's lost
his confidence.
Do you want to tell me why one
of my most promising students
is flying like a balloon
with a hole in it?
Uh, it's a long story,
but we'll fix it.
Yes you will!
[tweet!]
[sigh] We really messed up, huh?
I have a plan.
Hey, Sky. I thought I
might find you here.
Well, apparently I
need a lot of practice.
Guess I'm not the
natural I thought I was.
No, you're not.
Thanks. Good pep talk.
I wasn't a natural
at friendship.
But with some practice and
some help from my friends,
I got better. And now? I'm
the Princess of Friendship.
So you're saying I can be
the Princess of Flying?
You know, you're really good.
You're lead pony material.
That's sweet of you, but no.
I couldn't handle
all the attention.
But you'll never
become a Wonderbolt
if you're too afraid to shine.
That is what you want, right?
Not at first. I just
wanted to be with Sky.
But learning to do all
those fun tricks with you?
It made me realize this is
something I want for myself.
I was hoping you'd say
that. Come with me.
What's she doing here?
Sky, Vapor was never trying
to steal your spotlight.
She thought she
was helping you.
And Vapor, you shouldn't
have been so content
to take a back seat.
Now you can either stay
mad, or help each other
and become two of
the greatest fliers
the Wonderbolt
Academy has ever seen!
Please pick the second option.
I don't want Spitfire
to be mad at me.
[whoosh]
♪♪
You've got this, Sky!
Focus on a cloud
when you spin!
It'll help you fly straight
when you come out of it.
Uh-huh!
♪♪
[whoosh]
Woo-hoo!
♪♪
Woo! Yeah! Ha ha ha!
[hoofs screech]
Oh yeah, way to go! Woo-hoo!
[cheering]
Congratulations.
You've both made it into
the Wonderbolt Academy.
Whatever you
did, it worked.
These two have a
lot of potential.
Who knows? They might even
be better than you, Crash.
[nervous laugh] OK, let's
not get carried away.
Um, I just wanted
you to know.
You two are my new favorite
ponies in all of Equestria.
[Rainbow Dash] Hey! I
heard that!
I can't believe
we did it!
You were great! Even
though you can out-fly me,
you can be my
wingpony anytime.
[laugh] And you
can be mine.
♪♪
[crash]
Phew! It's good to be home.
You're telling me. Now
we can finally catch up
on some Daring Do; I can
make cider with Applejack...
[knock at door]
Dash! I've been looking
all over for you.
Wonderbolt emergency!
We gotta get back to HQ!
You've got to be kidding
me! I was JUST there! [sigh]
[giggle]