♪ [eerie music] ♪
♪♪
[slurp]
The last time I was here,
I woke them and ended up
with a mane full of bats!
[sigh] Thanks for being
my basket holder, Spike.
Basket holder? I thought
I was your bodyguard.
What? Oh yes, yes.
That of course, too.
Oh for once I wish
unicorn magic wasn't so...
luminescent.
Spike, you'll wake the
bats! Turn that off!
I can't! Oooh!
[gasp]
[squeaks]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure!
Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart!
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness
it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Twilight: I'm so glad
you two could come.
Of course. We so
rarely get a chance
to relax and just visit.
There's usually some crisis
we have to deal with.
Somepony always needs
our help. But today--
HELP! Twilight! There's
something wrong with Spike!
Twilight: What's wrong?
I don't know! [grunt]
All of the sudden
my scales just started
glowing and burning.
Little is known
about dragon culture,
but this is a phenomenon
we've seen before.
It is the Call of
The Dragon Lord.
Dragons glow whenever
the Dragon Lord
has need of them
in the Dragonlands.
Great! [groan] How
do I make it stop?
The only way to end the
summons is to answer it.
You must journey
to the Dragonlands
and see what is
expected of you.
But the Dragonlands
are full of... dragons!
And they're
ghastly creatures!
Oh-oh not you of
course, Spikey Wikey.
But remember that
rotten Garble?
[gulp] How could
I forget?
He would have burnt us to a
crisp if you weren't there.
If I have to go to
the Dragonlands,
would you two come with me?
Oooh! Oh my goodness! I'd
love to! We are sadly lacking
any information on dragon
culture and customs.
I could research them, maybe
even write an article!
This could be my chance to
make a great contribution
to the knowledge of Equestria!
And be there for
Spike, of course.
Be very careful.
The Dragonlands are
particularly dangerous
for ponies. It would
be wise to be discreet.
Oh, I'm sure I still have
the dragon costume we used
the last time we snuck into
the Dragonlands! [giggle]
I think we might
want something
a little more
practical this time.
[chattering teeth]
Rarity: Well, it may
be practical,
but this disguise isn't
flattering in the slightest!
Twilight: It's not supposed
to be flattering;
it's supposed to blend in!
SHHHH!
[snarl]
Hey, look. It's our old
friend, Sparkle Warkle.
It's Spike.
Are you sure your pony friends
didn't give you a pony name?
It's nice to see
you too, Garble!
I didn't say it was nice
to see you. It's not.
I don't like you.
Was I not clear about that?
[sneeze]
Hey! That's my rock.
Oh really? Then why
aren't you sitting on it?
[mean laughter]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪♪
Dragons of Equestria! Hear me!
I have been Dragon
Lord for longer
than many of you
can remember.
And my reign has
been extraordinary.
AGREE WITH ME!
[All agreeing at once]
Torch! Torch! Torch!
Who is that?
It's Dragon Lord Torch, dummy.
No, next to him.
That's his daughter,
Princess Ember.
I wouldn't even look
at her if I were you.
Unless you want
Torch to eat you.
[gulp]
This is fascinating! Dragons
are notoriously reckless,
but they do whatever
the Dragon Lord says.
Unfortunately,
according to dragon law,
it is time for me to
step down. Sad, I know.
BE SAD!
[all groaning]
This is why I have
summoned you.
To compete for the throne
in the Gauntlet of Fire!
[excited shouts]
[teeth chattering]
Whomever has the
strength and fortitude
to retrieve this
Bloodstone Scepter
from the heart of
the Flamecano
will be crowned Lord
of the Dragons!
[explosion]
[whoosh]
When the scepter disappeared,
the dragons stopped glowing!
We are learning so much!
Ah ah ah ....
choo!
Uh, Excuse me.
Ugh. You even
sneeze like a pony.
The Gauntlet is dangerous,
for I designed it myself.
Only dragons with my ferocity,
strength and determination
will be able to finish.
We will gather at the cliff
when the sun is at its peak!
[cheers]
I don't want to be Dragon
Lord or dragon toast
and I stopped glowing so
let's sneak out of here!
Where do you think you're
going, little dragon?
Oh, uh, hi Your Lordship.
I was just going home.
You don't get to leave
unless I say you can.
Dad, look at him!
He's just a runt.
Besides, he doesn't even
want to compete. Let him go.
He is rather tiny. I could
squish him with my pinky claw.
[weak laugh]
That wasn't a joke;
it was a fact.
When I want you to laugh
I will say "BE AMUSED"!
Of course, Your Lordship.
I guess I don't understand
dragon customs.
Another reason why
I shouldn't compete.
Very well, little
dragon. I release you.
Thank you!
And thank you.
Where do you think you're going?
To prepare for the gauntlet.
No, you're not. You're not
much bigger than that runt
I just sent home.
But I'm smarter than most
of these boulderheads
and you know it.
Being smart won't help
you win this gauntlet.
It was designed for a
big strong dragon to win
because it takes a big
strong dragon to lead.
Besides, I SAID NO!
I hate when he does that!
[chattering]
When I become Dragon Lord,
I will make burps an
official greeting.
Ha, you? Please.
When I win, I will
pillage Equestria
for all their pillows!
Why should these
ponies be comfortable
while we sleep on rocks?
That's nothing.
When I'm in charge,
the first thing I'll do is get
revenge on those puny ponies!
They'll regret they
ever crossed Garble!
We'll take whatever
we want from Equestria
and burn the rest.
Rarity: Oh my gosh. I can't
believe I'm saying this,
but I hope that
burping dragon wins.
Spike: None of them can win!
Equestria is in big trouble
if any of them are in charge!
Twilight: But what
can we do?
There's only one thing to
do and only I can do it.
I have to win the
Gauntlet of Fire!
[whimper]
What do you mean you
have to win the Gauntlet?
It's the only way to protect
Equestria from the dragons!
You heard them. They have
horrible plans for ponies
if they win! So somehow,
I have to do it.
There has to be another way!
It's too dangerous.
Besides, if you win,
you'd have to stay here!
I know. But there's no other
way to keep my friends safe.
Well, if you're
staying to compete,
then we're staying
to cheer you on.
♪♪
I thought I released
you, Tiny One.
I decided to compete. I
am a dragon, after all.
Are you sure? You
can't even fly!
[mocking laughter]
All dragons are
welcome to compete,
for they do so at
their own peril.
Flying to Flamecano Island is
the first of many challenges
you will face in your quest to
find the Bloodstone Scepter!
[roar]
Good luck. Just kidding,
I hope you lose.
Aaaaah!
[splash]
Thanks, Garble, I was
planning on swimming anyway!
You can do it, Spike!
[screeches]
[splash]
He's gonna drown!
SPIKE!
Hey, are you OK?
[coughing]
[gasping]
Princess Ember!
What do you think you're doing?
Rarity: Only saving your
ungrateful scales!
Did that seaweed just talk?
Ponies? What are
they doing here?
They're my friends!
Friends? Dragons
don't do friends.
Well, this dragon does!
Whatever. I don't care as long
as none of you get in my way.
I have a gauntlet to win.
But I thought your dad said--
I don't care what my dad said!
I'll show him and
everydragon who thinks
I'm just a little "Princess"
there are better things
than being big and strong!
Aaah!
[thud]
Don't leave me here, Spike!
[grunt]
Ha ha! I knew you'd do it.
Your pony friends made you soft.
[splat]
Uh-huh. You're welcome.
For what? I didn't
say thank you.
[sniff]
Wow, you even smell like ponies.
[sniffing]
Or is it coming from over there?
[deep voice] Uh, that's just me.
I uh, robbed some ponies
on my way over here.
I like your style.
Have I met you before?
You kinda look like--
My uh, old neighbor,
uh, Sandy Rockbeach!
Stupid slingtails
knocked me down.
But I've wasted enough time
making small talk. Get it?
Because you're too small
to win this. I'm funny.
Why did you cover for me?
You could have had
one less competitor.
I could ask you the same thing.
You could have told
Garble about my friends.
Yikes. That looks rough.
But that's what
makes it a challenge.
Are you kidding? Those
boulders are huge!
Hey, what if we
work together?
You fly me up there and
I'll help you look out
for boulders like a
second set of eyes!
Rarity: PSSST!
Spike!
Are you sure it's a good
idea to team up with Ember?
You don't know her too well.
I do know she could have
told Garble about you,
but she didn't. I
think we can trust her.
Her behavior does seem
contradictory to everything
I've noted about
dragons so far.
Hey! You. Little fella.
I've thought about it and your
plan makes sense. Let's do it.
Really? Great! It's a deal.
Just so you know, this doesn't
mean we're gonna pick flowers
or exchange necklaces or
whatever pony friends do.
Good luck. We'll
meet you at the top.
♪♪
Pull up, there's
one on your tail!
♪♪
Go left!
So, what do we do now?
I think we go through there.
[whoosh]
Rarity: Ah! Oh,
that looks scary!
I mean, you can do it!
Listen, Spike, I wouldn't have
made it this far without you.
So I guess, if you want to, we
could keep working together.
I mean, just until we
get through that tunnel.
OK.
We'll be right behind you.
♪♪
[slam slam slam]
[grunt]
[groan]
[gasp]
Agh!
[groan]
[thud]
Rarity: Oh, you made it!
Oh, we were so worried.
About us? Pssh. That
tunnel was cake.
Wait, how did you
two get through?
[rumbling]
[screams]
Rarity!
♪♪
Oh thanks, Spike!
It was nothing.
Nothing? You just risked
everything to save her.
And they're putting themselves
in danger just to support you.
That's just what friends do.
Don't you have anyone
who looks out for you?
Not really. Unless
I count you...
which I don't because we
were only helping each other
get through the tunnel and now
we're through the tunnel so,
that's it.
Wait. What do you mean?
Well, there's only one
winner, one scepter
and one Dragon Lord.
So I guess it's every
dragon for themselves.
Oh. So we aren't
really friends?
Maybe if we were in ponyland
but like I said, dragons
don't do friendship.
♪♪
I can't believe
Ember ditched me.
Oh you're better off. She was
only looking out for herself.
She's just like all
the other dragons.
She's not, though. I know it.
She saved me, even when
she didn't have to.
I don't care what she says.
That makes us friends.
Twilight: Is it just me or
have we seen this crevice
three times already?
It's kind of hard to tell.
They all look the same.
Except for this one! Look!
We made it!
I can't believe I'm the only
dragon to make it this far.
You're not!
And I'm not losing to a puny
pony-loving dragon like you!
[gasp] We have to
do something!
Look!
[shouts]
Ember! I thought it was
every dragon for themselves.
Why did you save me?
That's what friends do.
And I am. I mean we are.
I never should have
left you back there.
Ugh, please don't make me
talk about my feelings.
What the--?
Spike! Get the scepter!
♪♪
[shouts]
Aaaaagh!
I'm sick and tired of you
two helping each other!
Dragons don't do helping!
These dragons do!
Whoa!
[whoosh]
[zap]
Spike: Leave her alone!
What? You? You have the scepter?
But that means that you're...
The Dragon Lord.
Dragon Lord Spike.
Aw. Dragon Lord Spike.
That's right. Uh,now go start
your long journey home.
And give every dragon
you see on the way a hug.
Don't tell them why.
Aw, but that'll be
super embarrassing!
I command you to do it!
Ugh. I can't believe this.
"Dragon Lord Spike." Hmm,
has a nice ring to it.
Dragon Lord Ember
sounds a lot better.
What? No. You're
the Dragon Lord now.
The Dragon Lord is whoever
brings the scepter back
to your father.
Besides, you'll
make a great leader.
I was just doing this
to protect the ponies,
but I know you'll protect them
just as well as I would have.
Are you sure about this?
Absolutely. My home is in
Equestria with my friends.
Well, you'll have at least
one friend here, too.
What are you doing?
It's called a hug.
Oh. I don't know if
I like it, but OK.
Aw.
Ember? You?
I know you didn't think
I could do it, but I did.
I expressly told you NOT TO
DO IT! Because you're not--
I'm not big and strong!
I know! But you know what?
I won anyway. So, maybe it
takes more than just being
big and strong to be
a good Dragon Lord.
I was wrong, Ember.
You might not be big, but
you are strong. And smart.
And perhaps that counts
for more than I thought.
And you will make
an excellent leader.
Thanks, Dad.
AGREE WITH HIM!
Just kidding. That's
not gonna be my thing.
[laughter]
Dragons, hear me!
I present to you our new
Dragon Lord... Ember!
[cheers]
♪ [trumpet fanfare] ♪
What is the meaning of this?
I can't tell you!
[laugh]
You did well, Spike. With
Ember as Dragon Lord,
the ponies will be safe
and you've gained us
a powerful ally.
And a new friend.
Plus, Ember said I could
write to her any time
I had questions
about dragon culture!
With this much information,
I'll be able to write a
whole book on dragons!!
And I gained tons of
ideas for a new line
of camouflage clothing! I
think I'll call it camo-mod.
[laughter]
♪♪