[rooster crows]
♪♪
[yawn]
I've prepared a
full day of spells.
You've been doing great,
but now it's time
for a real challenge.
Oh, it is on. Where
do we begin?
Teleportation. Multiple
locations. Try to keep up.
Transfiguration!
[zapping]
SHIELDS!
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[crashing and zapping]
Whoo! I am on FIRE!
What's next?
Maybe there is such a
thing as too much studying.
[crash]
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
As you know, speed spells
like Accelero are not easy.
But if done correctly,
they can allow you to be
much more efficient
with your day.
[whooshing]
Spike: Way to
go, Starlight!
Oh, I'm not finished. I've
discovered a very old spell,
Similo Duplexus.
When combined with Accelero
in just the right way...
[whoosh]
...you can literally be
in two places at once!
[sigh]
NOW I'm finished.
I have to admit, your skills
with magic really are
nothing short of amazing.
I'm very impressed.
I've always been
something of a natural.
However, it doesn't
look like you've tackled
any friendship lessons
since you met Trixie.
Are you sure? I
could have sworn
there were a couple
in there somewhere.
I'm sure.
I see. Well, I'm really
quite busy this week...
so many commitments! I'll try
and find some time in my --
No time like
the present!
Spike and I are
headed to Canterlot.
Princess Celestia wanted
me to give her students
a quick overview
on the history
of enchanted objects
in Equestria.
We'll be back after the
presentation, which should be-
20 moons from now?
Tonight. It's a
quick presentation.
Sure. Keep tellin'
yourself that.
You can tackle a
friendship lesson today
and we can review
your progress
when I get back
later this evening.
Of course! No problem.
Friendship lesson. On it!
Great! Can't wait!
Now Spike, help me
color code these cards
according to time,
place and object.
[Spike groans]
[knock at door]
Huh? Oh.
♪ [nonchalant humming] ♪
Hey! Twilight and I are
about to head to Canterlot.
Just checking to see if you
need anything before we left.
Nope! Not at all!
I'm good here. Not
good. Great.
Not a problem in
the world.
Uh-huh.
So... what are
you doing exactly?
I was... just trying to decide
which friendship lesson
I was going to tackle while
you two were in Canterlot!
Oh, yup. Right here. Where I
just left them a second ago!
Bake a cake with Pinkie Pie,
scrapbook with Applejack,
sew with Rarity...
Uh.
Help an animal with Fluttershy,
chillax with Rainbow
Dash? What is chillaxing?
No idea.
You know, uh, if
you're nervous about
your friendship lessons,
it's totally okay to say so.
NERVOUS?! ME!
HAHAHA. Oh Spike.
You really are hilarious.
You think I'm nervous
that I'm going to
fail something
as simple as baking
a cake?
Well, if you were,
it would be--
Silly! Twilight just said
how impressed she was
that I combined a speed spell
and a duplication spell.
THAT was a challenge.
These? Ha!
I could combine all five
of these at the same time
without breaking a sweat!
I think maybe you're missing--
An opportunity to
really impress Twilight?
Great idea, Spike! I'm gonna
get right on that. Good talk!
And I thought Twilight was
the master of the freakout.
So, with your help,
I figure
these should be
done in no time!
Are you sure this is what
Twilight would want?
Seems like you might
wanna take your time
with each of these.
But by working as a team,
we can get them done faster.
And isn't teamwork a key
factor in friendship?
I guess.
Super! Pinkie Pie,
since we're baking,
you will be in
the kitchen.
[gasp]
Rarity, Applejack you two
can set up in the library.
Oh, I don't know that
the dusty old library
has the proper lighting.
Perhaps we can stay
out here in the foyer?
I thought that Fluttershy and
I could work with the animals
right here in the foyer.
Oh, um, whatever
you think is best.
Great. Now, Rainbow Dash--
[Fluttershy] But it might
depend on the animal.
For instance, this poor little
eagle with a sprained wing
might be better off up
in one of the towers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah sure.
And these adorable chipmunks
might prefer a nook somewhere.
Maybe if you spent
some time getting to--
In a minute, Fluttershy.
Uh, I don't know if we
can chillax properly
in the castle. We need
very specific conditions
for optimal chillaxing.
Oh. I just assumed chillaxing
could happen anywhere.
Ha. Shows what you know
about chillaxing.
Let me do some
location scouting.
[zoom]
O-kay. Uh, it seemed
more efficient to
start with the scrapbooking
so we could just--
Oh! Oh! oh!
Can we start with me?
We're gonna need time for the
cake to bake! After all...
♪ It's a piece of cake
to bake a pretty cake-- ♪
Uh, we're on a schedule.
No time for a song.
We can start with
baking. THEN--
But we can't design dresses
after you've been baking
with Pinkie. She
can be a bit messy.
Fine. We can start with
the dresses and THEN--
While y'all figure that out,
I'm gonna start layin out
the pictures for scrapbooking.
We've got a whole
lot of time to cover.
How much is a whole lot?
We've got at least 80
moons worth of memories
to go through!
80 moons!?
Ugh!
There is NOwhere to
chillax in this castle.
We're gonna have to
set up somewhere else!
[voices talking
over each other]
Could you all excuse
me for one second?
[zoom]
Wow. That pony really
needs to chillax.
[deep breathing]
OK, Starlight.
You've got this.
A handful of friendship
lessons is nothing
compared to the spells
you've mastered.
Maybe if I cast a little
spell to help things along.
Something simple and
safe. Fiducia Compelus?
That's not bad. They
would barely notice it.
But is it enough?
Maybe Cogeria so they are
more open to suggestion?
Or maybe Cogeria combined
with Fiducia Compelus!
Yes... that could work nicely.
Oh, with a hint of Persuadere
to be sure it sticks.
[explosion]
Everypony will
probably thank me
for getting it all
done so quickly.
And Twilight will
be thrilled
I've completed so many
lessons. Everypony wins!
[explosion]
Congratulations Starlight,
you're a genius.
[gasp]
♪ [mysterious music] ♪
Maybe the congratulations
were a little premature.
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪♪
Cogeria...
Persuadere...Fiducia...
Oh, of course! Fiducia
Compelus needs a trigger!
PONIES! HEAR MY
VOICE AND LISTEN.
Pinkie, kitchen. Rarity,
Applejack, library.
Fluttershy, stay here.
Rainbow Dash, find
somewhere INSIDE the castle
and set up a place
where we can chillax.
[agreement]
♪♪
Let's get to work, Pinkie!
Okie-Dokie. What would
you like to do first?
Uh. What are we
supposed to do first?
Whatever you want to do
first, Starlight Glimmer.
In a medium-sized
mixing bowl,
beat together eggs, sugar and
two teaspoons of vanilla...
Mix in flour...
Add baking soda,
salt and cinnamon.
I think you can
take it from here.
Take what from where?
The baking. Just keep
following the instructions
in the book until I get back.
Absotively! Instruction
following starting... NOW!
Baking a cake, check!
Now on to sewing.
What did you have
in mind, Rarity?
Whatever you want me to have
in my mind, Starlight Glimmer.
♪♪
Can you make a dress
exactly like that one?
JUST like this one?
Just like it.
Absolutely! It will
look perfectly divine!
♪♪
That's a whole
lot of photos.
How do you usually
organize them?
However you want me to
organize them, Starlight.
Ok. Tell me
about this one.
Sweet Apple Acres.
20 moons ago.
Granny Smith was looking
for her favorite pie tin.
She looked in the kitchen,
but it wasn't there.
She looked in the barn,
I don't need every
little detail.
Just sum up the story
in one sentence.
Huh. Turns out Granny
Smith didn't know
HOW to make a pig
do the backstroke.
Uh-huh. Why don't you
keep putting these photos
in chronological order
and when I come back
you can give me
more highlights.
Sure thing,
Starlight Glimmer.
Fluttershy? Where
are all the animals?
They ran away.
And why didn't
you stop them?
Because you
didn't ask me to.
Obviously I wanted
you to... never mind.
Can you please round up all
the animals in the castle
and bring them back
here to the foyer.
All the animals. Got it.
Did you find a place to
chillax, Rainbow Dash?
Sure thing,
Starlight Glimmer.
Great. Let me know
when it's ready.
Yes, Starlight Glimmer!
Granny Smith knew she was
gonna need a bigger boat.
So Goldie Delicious says, "If
you can't say anything nice
about anypony...
come sit by me!"
Big Mac knew if he just
covered himself in mud,
the creature wouldn't
be able to see him.
Fluttershy: Starlight Glimmer!
I have finished the dress!
Isn't it gorgeous?
What is that?
You wanted me
to make a dress
exactly like the
one in the book.
Go make a REAL
dress out of fabric
exactly like the
one in the book.
Ahhhh. I see. Yes, of
course, Starlight Glimmer.
Rarity! Make it BIGGER
than the one in the book.
Of course, darling.
Bigger it is.
[questioning squeak]
She was just a pony, standing
in front of another pony,
asking him to love her.
[crash]
Pinkie, what are you doing?!
Following all of the
instructions in the cookbook
in order, Starlight Glimmer!
I meant just the ONE cake! I
was only gone a few minutes!
How in Equestria did you get
all of this done so fast?
First I combined
three eggs, then...
[muffled speaking]
I think the baking
lesson is done.
[growling]
Oh, what now?
[crackling flames]
They can take our farm, but
they can't take our freedom!
[gasp] What's going on?
[growl]
I've gathered all of the
animals like you asked,
Starlight Glimmer.
Oh yes, this will do
nicely. A MUCH bigger dress!
[Applejack] It was
the best of apples;
it was the worst
of apples.
I can handle this. It's just
magic and I know magic.
What's that?
[muffled speech]
What did you say?
The cakes are burning!
You left the ovens on!
We need water!
Yes, Starlight Glimmer.
[thunder]
Storm clouds?!
[cracks of thunder]
♪ [tense music] ♪
[whoosh]
Big Mac told me, with
a whole lotta power
comes a heckuva lot
of responsibility.
This can't get any worse.
WHAT IS GOING ON!?
I had no idea we had
spiders in the castle.
I'm never sleeping again.
Maybe if I had reversed the
Fiducia Compelus and Cogeria.
Or maybe I added
too much Persuadere.
What?
You're really missing
the point here.
I finally untangled
that mess of a spell
and got everypony home. It
was really powerful stuff.
They're gonna feel
that in the morning.
Now, please try to
explain to me
how in the name
of Celestia
things got this
out of control?
Well, it was the first time
I cast that particular spell
and I didn't fully
think it through.
I bet if I had reversed--
I think you might be
missing the point here.
Told ya.
What made you think
that casting a spell
on your friends
to do your bidding
was even remotely
a good idea?
Well, when you put it that
way, it sounds really bad.
That's because it
IS really bad!
Uh...
Starlight. I'm not mad at
you. But I am disappointed.
You've been doing so well.
I just don't understand
how a friendship lesson
turned into all of this?
Ugh. Fine!
I've been avoiding the
friendship lessons on purpose.
Why?
I can cast complex spells.
But baking a cake with
Pinkie Pie freaks me out.
And yes I know how
ridiculous that sounds.
That's why I didn't
say anything.
I thought if I just
kept wowing you
with my magical abilities,
you might just... not notice.
Baking a cake
freaks you out?
Yes! Baking a cake,
sewing. All of it.
What if I was
bad at it?
I didn't want to be a
disappointment to anypony
and I ended up being a
disappointment to everypony.
Starlight. Do you
think anypony cares
if you can bake a cake?
But the lesson--
Was to get to know
Pinkie Pie better
by doing something
she loves.
It was a friendship lesson,
not a baking lesson.
Oh. You know I think I might
have missed the point here.
Told ya.
So now what?
Now it's time for a pretty
advanced friendship lesson.
It's called apologizing.
[groans]
I dunno what kinda whammy
Starlight put on us,
but I feel like I got
shoved through the
super speedy cider
squeezy 6000.
Ugh! Tell me about it.
If everypony could speak in a
whisper for the next few days,
that would be delightful.
My head is thumping.
I was up all night
calming the animals down.
Fluttershy, please!
Not so loud.
Starlight's spell made me
burn perfectly good cake!
I NEVER burn cake!
[Starlight] Yeah, about that...
Things got a little
out of hand last night.
Ain't that the
understatement of the day?
Tell it to the cakes, sister!
Can we all PLEASE argue
at a lower volume?
I really messed up.
I cast the spell because I was
nervous about working with you
on the friendship lessons.
Well, here's a friendship
lesson for you.
Don't cast spells
on your friends!
Believe me; I know.
What I did was wrong and
I can't take it back.
You're right to be upset
and I hope one day,
I can make it up to you. But
all I can say is I'm sorry.
Now if you'll excuse me, I've
got to go clean the castle
covered in wet cake
batter and spiders.
That was a pretty
good apology.
It seems like she
feels really bad.
Hey, Starlight! Most of
the Apple family photos
are still laying
around in the wreckage.
I think I'll come along
and hunt 'em down.
Oh! And I feel awful for
disturbing all of those
cute little spiders and
bats. I should check on them.
Ah, yes. And I left
some lovely fabric out;
I should come move it to
that nice quiet library.
Uh, I'll come and get
those storm clouds
out of the bathroom.
Fine! Somepony has to
bake a cake to honor
all of the poor cakes that
sacrificed their batter
in last night's tragedy.
♪♪
It seems your
apology went well.
[sigh] I'm just lucky to have
such understanding friends.
But it's probably
going to be a while
before I try to tackle those
friendship lessons again.
What do you mean? You've
been doing them all day!
What are you
talking about?
I've been cleaning
up the mess I made
by totally failing
at friendship.
Really? But didn't I see
you sewing with Rarity?
Yes but--
And you and Applejack did
a great job collecting
those photos and putting
them in the book.
Helping animals with Fluttershy,
baking with Pinkie Pie.
Those sound like your
assignments to me.
In fact, I think there's just
one that you're missing.
Sun? Check. Chairs? Check.
And thanks to a simple
catadupa levitata spell,
we've got water! Is that
everything we need to chillax?
Nope.
No? What did I miss?
Quiet.
Ah. Right.
Great job, Starlight.
Looks like you've completed
another friendship lesson.
[happy sigh]
Hey! She completes the lesson
when I say she completes it.
So less learning
and more chillaxing!
So, how long do we
sit quietly?
[laughter]