♪♪
[frightened whimper]
[crashing]
[grunt]
[hiss]
Well, don't stop there! You
read; I pack. That's the deal!
I'm sorry, Rainbow Dash.
I just keep thinking about
how much fun you're
going to have
at the Daring
Do Convention.
I wish Princess Celestia
didn't need my help
with the friendship
summit in Griffonstone.
Don't worry. I'll make sure
AK Yearling signs your book.
I can't believe she's
going to be there.
She never goes
to conventions.
[sigh]
Which I guess will be cool for
all those other fan-ponies,
but since you and I know
AK Yearling personally...
and we know that she's
secretly Daring Do, herself...
It's no big deal.
This convention'll be fun,
but it's nothing to
get too excited about.
So! Excited!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
You look like a pony who'd
be up for an all-inclusive,
one-of-a-kind, adventu-cation
where you get to live
"The Daring Do Experience."
No thanks. Did
that already.
Ah!
[whoosh]
This is the awe--
Both: someest thing ever!
Now this is something that only
a true fan can appreciate.
They even put the tiles
in the right order!
Good catch. I'm Quibble Pants.
Nice to meet you.
Rainbow Dash.
Nice costume.
You too.
Thanks. The hard part was
figuring out the right--
Both: number of arrow holes.
B-because on page eighty-four
of Sapphire Stone,
it describes her dodging a quote
"score of arrows shooting forth
from holes in the
very walls," unquote,
but then on page one hundred and
seven, Daring Do says she quote
"barely made it past the trap's
barrage of arrows" unquote.
But clearly, Daring
Do is embellishing
and the correct
number of arrows is--
Both: Twenty.
[chuckling]
♪♪
I am so glad I
ran into you.
Even though I knew
the convention
would be totally awesome,
it's more fun when
you're with someone
who really knows
Daring Do.
I know what you mean.
It's so hard to find a
pony who really gets it.
That's weird. We've only done
stuff from the first trilogy.
After lunch, we should probably
start working our way back
through the other books.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. There
are no "other books."
Of course there are.
Daring Do and the Trek
of the Terrifying Tower,
Daring Do and the
Many Faces of--
Uh, please, please don't. Just
don't even mention the titles.
I'm not saying those
books don't exist.
I'm saying that I refuse
to acknowledge them.
Why?
Because they're horrible!
I mean, there isn't a single
thing after Ring of Destiny
that is even remotely in
the realm of the possible.
WHAT! I know for a
fact that everything
in every one of those books is
one hundred percent possible!
And how could you
possibly know that?
I just do.
Well, that's a
compelling argument!
Why would you even
come to this convention
if you hate Daring
Do so much?!
I don't hate Daring Do.
The first series
was smart and cool
and an amazing nod to old-time
serialized adventure books
that somehow manages to be
self-reflexive and ironic
while at the same time
celebrating the art form
without a hint of cynicism.
Which is why I came here to ask
AK Yearling, muzzle-to-muzzle,
why she sold out and dumbed
down the rest of her books
into just a series of
impossible action sequences.
OK, now I know
you're crazy.
AK Yearling is awesome and every
Daring Do book that comes out
is better than the last.
Wow. OK. Yeah. I'm-I'm sorry
but I could never be friends
with somepony who's willing
to believe impossible stuff
is possible as long
as Daring Do does it.
That's OK, because I could
never be friends with somepony
who's so focused on
things being possible
that he's willing
to turn his back
on the coolest hero
of all time!
Fine!
Look, just tell AK Yearling
that Rainbow Dash is here
and I need her help to
convince a know-it-all pony
that everything Daring Do's
ever done actually happened.
Rainbow Dash?
AK! I've got to talk to
you! It's an emergency!
Not here.
Now, tell me what's going on. Is
it Caballeron? Did you see him?
What? No.
But there is a pony downstairs
who thinks everything
you've written after the first
trilogy is totally unrealistic
and terrible and I need
you to help me prove to him
that it's all
totally possible.
I've got bigger
problems on my hoofs
than dissatisfied
fan-ponies.
Whoa!
The Amulet of Culhuacan.
And Caballeron wants it.
But the amulet's
only a key. [chuckle]
The real treasure is
hidden in a lost temple,
The Seven-Sided
Chest of Chicomoztoc.
Caballeron wants to sell it to
the highest bidder, of course,
which is why I need
to find it first.
YES! Sounds like another
awesome Daring Do Adventure!
But what are
you doing here?
Since I haven't
found the temple yet,
it's the safest place
for me and the Amulet.
It's crawling with security
and if I get into trouble,
I can just blend in with all
the Daring Do cos-players.
How can I help?
Just keep your eyes out
for anything suspicious.
Got it.
[knock at door]
Does a pony who only
likes your first trilogy
qualify as suspicious?
Just checking.
[door closes]
[sigh] I find all this fanfare
around my archenemy disturbing.
I mean, where is the
booth for Caballeron?
I do not see the likeness.
Come. Let us find Daring Do
and the Amulet of Culhuacan.
I don't want to spend any
more time in this place
than I have to.
Well, if it isn't the pony
who knows impossible things
can happen because
she just does.
Ugh. Sorry, Quibble, I've got
more important things to do
than argue with a pony
who thinks awesome
means unrealistic.
No, wait. I wanna hear more
about how you're 100% sure
that in Curse of the Jungle
Queen, Daring Do could survive
a sixty-story drop from
the top of a waterfall
after sustaining a broken
wing in a category six rapid.
Ugh.
Obviously her wing
wasn't broke--
Caballeron!
See, now THAT'S a
great character!
Solid backstory.
Good motivations.
No-no-no! Caballeron
is right there!
Of course he is.
He's also over
there, over there,
Oh-oh over there,
and over there.
Where are you going?
And we're out here because...
Daring Do told me
that Caballeron
came to this convention to
steal the Amulet of Culhuacan
and I just saw him and his
henchponies come this way.
OK. I'm gonna head back inside.
Just a little
too much crazy out here
for the both of us.
[gasp]
I do not know what
Daring Do is playing at,
but if she told you two
fanponies of my plan
to steal the Amulet,
you must work for her.
Caballeron! HA! What do you
have to say NOW, Quibble?
This was your plan to prove the
Daring Do books are realistic?
You bought a "Daring Do
Experience, Adventu-cation"?
Really?
What?! NO! Look around us!
Henchponies. Caballeron!
The jungle it took forever to
get to! This is the real deal!
Right. We're ACTUALLY being
held captive by Caballeron.
Please. This guy's accent
is all over the place.
No offense.
I....
So, what's the setup,
here? You've kidnapped us
and taken us to the middle
of nowhere because....?
The Temple of Chicomoztoc is
somewhere in this jungle!
When I find it, the Seven-Sided
Chest is as good as mine!
I just need the Amulet of
Culhuacan to unlock it!
Uh-huh. And Daring
Do has the Amulet,
so you came up with this
overcomplicated plot
to lure her into the jungle
and exchange it for us?
I wouldn't call it
overcomplicated, but yes.
OK, we're done here. Great work.
Seriously. Very believable.
[slap and shout]
Listen pal, you can keep
her money, but I'm not--
Going anywhere.
You may not approve of my plan,
but I'm the mastermind here.
Debatable.
AND I SAY you will remain
here until Daring Do
comes to rescue you. And if she
wants you back in one piece,
she will give me the
Amulet! Tie them up.
The Griffon's Lock!
You know of it!
Further proof that you
are an agent of Daring Do.
Or an avid reader.
And now I will continue
my search for the Temple.
Don't go anywhere. [evil laugh]
Listen, if I pretend to
believe this nonsense is real,
will you call off the henchpony
repertory theater over there?
They're not going to listen
to me. They abducted us BOTH!
Oh, wow. So you're going
to stick with that script?
Oh, OK fine. We're in
a Daring Do adventure.
What was that?
DARING DO! THANK
GOODNESS! WE'RE OVER HERE!
Fan out! We can't let
Daring Do rescue these two.
All four? I mean, shouldn't at
least one of them stay behind
to guard us? Oh-oh
wait, no because then
it wouldn't be a terrible
Daring Do adventure!
It doesn't matter.
We'll never solve the Griffon's
Lock before they get back.
OK, that was pretty good.
Quick! We've got to get out
of here and warn Daring Do!
No way. Just point
me to the hotel
and you can play fanpony
and hunt treasure
out here all day long.
Fine. Let's say this IS a
Daring Do Adventu-cation.
The only way to get back to the
convention is to go through it.
So just follow me and
I'll lead you out. Deal?
Ugh. Fine.
Maybe if I just leave you in
the jungle, it'll convince you.
Which would make Daring Do left-
hoofed, which we KNOW is false!
And THAT is everything
that's wrong with Daring Do
and the Trek to the
Terrifying Tower.
Now the problems with
the next book are even--
Oh, right. What Daring Do
adventure would be complete
without the precarious
rope bridge?
I'm all for making things
feel as real as possible
but are these adventu-cation
ponies sure this thing is safe?
Is it too "realistic" for you?
Wouldn't want THAT on a
Daring Do adventure, would we?
If this were really a
Daring Do adventure,
I'm sure I'd step on the wrong
plank at exactly the wrong mo--
[shout]
♪♪
Heh. Good thing this is all
just a pretend adventure.
At least we know all
of this struggling
won't make the
bridge fall apart.
[snap]
You need to get
your money back.
[snap]
[screaming]
[thud]
Ha! How's THAT for
not possible!
THAT. WAS. AWESOME!
I-I-I thought we...
And then you...
and the flying...
Wow, and I was like
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
And then you swerved!
And I was-was-was on the water!
And the-the rocks?! WOW.
Yeah. If you read
that in a book
you might even think
it was unrealistic.
OK. I'll give
you that one.
I mean we could
have been done for.
We could have been
done for!
What kind of
Adventu-cation IS this?
I mean that's just bad business!
What are these ponies thinking?
[foreign accent] Right now?
We are thinking that we should
thank you for escaping.
For you have led us directly to
the Lost Temple of Chicomoztoc!
[evil laugh]
Make sure they are
secure this time!
We can't have them
escaping again.
You'll never get
away with this.
Won't I? You've led
me to the temple.
And Daring Do is too noble to
let harm befall her companions
so the amulet is
as good as mine.
What? No witty remarks this time
about how silly my plan is?
This isn't the official
Daring Do Experience
Adventu-cation, is it?
FINALLY!
It's some cheap knock-off run by
a bunch of incompetent ponies
that have no idea how to
execute this adventure
with any level of safety!
Ugh.
What was that with the bridge!
We were in serious danger!
I'm reporting you all to...
Well, I don't know who
I'm reporting you to,
but it's gonna be
somepony important!
Oh, and this cut-rate
excuse for an "experience"
hasn't proved anything
except that I'm right.
It has all the hallmarks of
a lame Daring Do adventure.
Uh... Quibble?
No. I'M talking! Generic
jungle locations? Check.
Overly complicated
villain plot? Check.
Random coincidences
that conveniently
get us to the next
big set piece? CHECK!
Watch where you are
stepping, you fool!
Listen, buddy, I
don't take orders
from some second-rate
performer who learned acting
from the supervillain
school of bad accents.
The only thing this mess
is missing is some giant
Ahuizotl wanna be monster
and I have a feeling
that would be a bit too much
for you bargain basement
adventurers to pull off.
[roar]
Um. You're real.
This is real?
[snap]
THIS IS REAL!
I told you to warn me
of anything suspicious,
not run off on an
adventure without me.
Whoa whoa whoa. You're real.
You're-you're...
friends with her?
Uh, we'll have to do
introductions later.
Right now we have to--
Get out of here. Yes! Thank you!
Actually, no.
WHAT?
We can't leave
without the treasure.
And we should probably get
to it before our friend
gets any higher.
[splash]
Whoa!
Seven doors, Seven locks. One
of them leads to the treasure.
I'd rather not think about
what the others lead to.
Yeah, yeah. The classic
pony and the tiger bit.
All you have to do is--
Um... Maybe you should let
Daring Do figure it out?
Oh, excuse me.
[fake cough] Not that one.
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeehhhhhhh.
Is he always like this?
Yeah. But... he's
usually right.
[sigh]
Which lock do YOU think it is?
FINALLY! Look. Each door has
another door that matches.
THESE two both have earth
ponies fighting serpents.
THESE two have Pegasi
fighting Griffons.
THESE two have unicorns
fighting bears. But THIS one...
Has an alicorn on it!
It's the only one without a
match. How did I miss that?
I've been asking myself
that ever since book four.
The Seven-Sided
Chest of Chicomoztoc.
Uh, guys?
The way out is
totally covered!
How are we gonna
get out of here?
There!
Seriously, do you
ever NOT escape
out of the top of a temple?
We'll have to carry mister
adventure critic out with us.
We won't be fast enough!
We'll never make it!
Guys!
I think Rainbow Dash
and I have this covered.
♪♪
Go around! You
can't go over him!
Go over him? Are you crazy?
If Quibble says go
over him, go over him!
[scream]
You two are insane!
You SAID go over him!
I SAID go around him!
And I said be quiet!
This way! I heard them!
OK, I've got it. Let's
create a fake treasure
out of mud and rocks, give THAT
to Caballeron and then when--
Not EVERY Daring Do plan
has to be super complicated.
I swear I heard them!
[crash]
[roar]
[scream]
I'll get you Daring Doooooooo!
Uh. Not particularly original
or inspired, but it worked.
Who are you again?
He's a fan.
Uh-huh. There's some stairs on
the other side of the temple
that lead out of
the ravine.
I suggest you two take
them and head west.
What about you?
I've got to get this to a
museum. Thanks for your help.
I couldn't have done it
without you. Both of you.
So?
So. Maybe the later books
ARE slightly more realistic
than I gave them credit for.
I still don't like them.
What? How can you--
Wait! Hold on! Before
we get in another fight,
I think I finally
figured it out!
I love the Daring Do that solves
puzzles and uses her brain
to get out of tough situations.
And she did WAY more of that
in the original trilogy.
YOU love the Daring Do
that is brave and awesome
and comes out on top no
matter what the odds.
OK.
And that's OK!
We might never agree on
what makes Daring Do cool.
But YOU are definitely cool.
I mean the way you saved
me on the bridge? Wow.
And escaping from the temple!
You, Rainbow Dash, are AWESOME.
Well. I'm not the one
who can locate a treasure
in half the time Daring Do can.
You may have terrible
taste in books,
but you're pretty
awesome yourself.
In a brainy egghead puzzle-
solving kind of way.
I guess we don't have to agree
on everything to get along.
Friends?
DEFINITELY friends.
Do you think AK
Yearling would consider
letting ME write the next book?
I mean, think I could
make things way clearer.
I mean for instance, in
the second adventure
there's a side
character;
I don't want to kind
of name it right now,
because it's sort of this thing
that I've already written
a lot of fan fiction on I
don't want, you know... not
that I'm saying that you
would steal it.
But I am saying that this
would totally go along
my whole thing about
puzzle solving.
Except what if each
puzzle that was solved
unlocked a new karate move?
Think of it that way, right?
I'm kind of a Yearlite myself,
so I'm sure she'd be open to--
Rainbow Dash: Uh, Quibble?
Sorry!