♪♪
[panting] Come on! If we
hurry, we can get there
before the paper's even
delivered to Rarity's house.
Maybe she won't
read the article.
I'm pretty sure Rarity
is going to read a review
of her new boutique
in Manehattan.
I still can't believe we
all just blabbed everything
that happened to
that reporter.
I just hope it doesn't end
up being an article about
how her friends almost
ruined the opening.
I think you're all
over-reacting.
Rarity is our friend.
If any pony is going to
understand, it'll be her.
I was wondering when all of
you were going to show up.
[gasp]
Now we can all read
the review together!
Um, I have an idea. How
'bout we don't read it?
What she means is,
before you read it,
we should probably
tell you about--
No, no, darlings.
Please, no spoilers.
But--
NO SPOILERS!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure!
Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart!
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness
it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Now, is everypony ready
to hear what I'm sure
is a stellar review that
describes in stunning detail
exactly how each
of you contributed
to the successful opening
of Rarity for You?
[ahem]
"Many a pony has tried their
hoof at joining the ranks
of the elite fashion
trend-setters
currently ensconced
in the boutiques
of Manhattan's
famed Saddle Row.
[giggle] Some might say it's
the ultimate achievement
in Equestrian fashion and
never before has a reporter
been granted such unfettered
behind-the-scenes access,
until now."
I wish it had been
more fettered.
[mumbles] Ah! [mumbles]
"I sat down with [giggle]
Rarity and her friends
after the opening to
get the inside scoop.
And what a scoop it was..."
♪♪
OK, kid. You successfully
opened a shop in Manehattan
and that's no mean feat.
Most ponies might wonder
what it feels like.
Here's how it's gonna be.
I'm going to interview
you and your friends
so I can paint a picture of
how it all came together,
a word picture mind you,
not an actual picture.
Any questions?
Well, I was wondering--
Let's get started!
Ms. Rarity. You got
shops all over Equestria,
but this was your first
time trying to make it
in the big city.
What made you think you
could tackle it on your own?
Well, I wouldn't say
all over Equestria.
I just have two
other boutiques,
one in my home
town of Ponyville
and one in
Canterlot.
Uh, still, when I
decided to open this one,
I was nothing
but confident.
[ding]
Let's just say that
if I could choose,
I probably wouldn't do it
that way again. [chuckle]
Well, it wasn't the
funnest party ever.
It was a plum-puckered,
pig-pushin' disaster!
After a lifetime of
awesome, I think everypony's
allowed to mess up every
now and then, right?
Wait, are you
writing this down?
Um. It didn't go exactly
how I thought it would,
but it um, started
out all right.
Welcome to Saddle Row.
An entire street lined with
the most fashionable boutiques
in all of Equestria.
If it's supposed to be
the most fashionable
block of shops,
where's Stinky Bottom's
Discount Hat Emporium?
I suppose it didn't
make the cut.
[gasp] Here it is!
Rarity For You.
Rarity, it's lovely, but
are you sure you'll be ready
to open tonight?
[sniff] Ah-CHOO!
No need to fret over
a mere moderate amount
of preparation. My
clothes arrive soon;
my sales associate after that
and with a little dusting,
we'll be ready for the
Grand Opening tonight.
Rarity! So good to see you.
Your store, it's going to be
a very good place, I think.
Mr. Stripes owns the building.
He's a very pleasant landlord.
A-a-although he can
be pushy at times.
OK, all the time.
You've met my daughter?
The apple of my ear,
the hay in my hoof. You
will let her work with you!
It's just... I'm
dreadfully busy preparing
for tonight's grand
opening, as you can see.
There are only two things I
love more than being pushy.
One is my daughter. The other
is miniature doll furniture.
And I would sell my entire
mini-furniture collection
to make my daughter
happy. You understand?
I'm sorry, I just don't think
it's going to be possible.
Let me say another way:
hire her or I raise rent
until you no can afford.
Oh, uh, welcome aboard!
First idea! Instead of clothes,
we sell glow-in-the-dark teeth.
Like this.[clank clank] but
they'd glow in the dark!
Golly, what a splendid
idea! [chuckle]
GLOW-IN-THE-DARK TEETH!
What was she thinking?
[scream] Fluttershy!
Your assistance is required
in the stock room post-haste.
Awwwww, hello.
But what are they doing here?
Smokey made too much
noise eating garbage,
so Softpad's mother made them
move out of the trash can.
Then Smokey Junior found a
nice home in the crawl space
behind the building, but
Mr. Stripes demolished it
so they were temporarily
camped out in the back
until they found a
new place to live.
No no no, I can't have a
family of rubbish-scented
raccoons living in my boutique.
♪ [booming music] ♪
Uh, did you hear that?
Turns out there's a Club
Pony Party Palace upstairs.
Pony Party Palace upstairs!
♪ [muffled booming music] ♪
♪ [louder] ♪
I'm sorry. Could you please
ask her to turn it down?
COULD YOU ASK HER TO
TURN IT DOWN PLEASE?
OH PLEASE!
Ugh. Foals today listen
to their so-called "music"
far too loud.
I realize that makes me
sound like an old mare.
But this is business!
♪ [booming] ♪
I wish we were having
as much fun as they are.
Well, sweeping can
be fun too.
Sweep. Sweep. Sweep. Sweep.
Only Twilight could make a
dance remix about sweeping.
I mean, how lame
is that?
Yeah, it wasn't
even catchy.
Nope.
Sweep! Sweep! Sweep! Sweep!
Apparently, DJ Pon-3
has a residency
at the party
palace upstairs,
but security won't
let me speak to her!
[loud honk]
Bahh! What in the name
of Celestia was that!
You know how most stores
have a little jingle bell
when the door opens? I thought
we should have something
with a little more "pizazz."
So I installed one of
Daddy's antique horns.
[honk honk honk]
Ugh! We'll have to do
something about that.
After I think of a way
to quiet down that music.
And after I finish designing
the window display.
Ahhh!
Wait. is this my merchandise
shipment from Ponyville?
It's completely
disorganized.
Ah! Uh. [gasping]
Ah...ugh...ah...[SNEEZES]
Gesundheit! Oh! Miss Pommel!
I'm so glad to see you.
Now, as the sole sales
associate at Rarity for You,
I hate to add to your
already overflowing plate
of responsibilities, but
it looks as though we have
just a tad more to do before
tonight than I thought.
Actually, I...Ugh ah! [sneeze]
[sigh] I can't work tonight.
Oh? Why not?
[honk]
[sneeze]
Feel better, my sweet. We'll
manage without you, somehow.
And we'll manage glowing
teeth and car horns
and disorganized
clothes and dance music.
Am I forgetting anything?
[chittering]
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
Well, opening a
store in Manehattan
is a pretty big deal.
It's natural that Rarity
would be a little stressed
about how it was going...
since it wasn't going well.
Still, I think she
handled it all right.
The dream is doomed!
Doomed, I tell you! Doomed!
I know things haven't
gone perfectly so far,
but we've done this
kind of thing before.
If we all work
together--
I appreciate the offer,
but this is Manehattan.
To make it in the
fashion scene here,
everything has to be perfect.
The perfect location.
The perfect clothes.
The perfect opening.
Maybe we should
just postpone.
Postpone? Darling,
tonight is the last night
of the fall season.
If we don't open
tonight it won't be--
[sigh] Perfect.
Yes. I know what needs to be
done. I just need more of me.
Oh, how I wish I could
make copies of myself!
Yeah. Making copies of
yourself always sounds
like a great idea, but
before you know it,
you're locked in a room
with fifty Pinkie Pies
watching paint dry.
We can do this and we can
stay true to your vision.
You'd do that? Fluttershy,
you'll handle those
strong-smelling
raccoons for me?
Of course!
Leave Plaid Stripes to me.
I'll handle her and her...uh
"good" ideas.
Oh! Oh! Oh! And I can go
upstairs to that nonstop party
and have tons of fun
and eat some cake
and set up party
cannons and--
and then make
them be quiet.
I'm pretty sure I know
somepony who wouldn't mind
organizing this merchandise
shipment for you.
I'm talking about myself.
Oh PLEASE let
me organize it!
This all sounds splendid, but
I don't even have a single
employee and I'll need
the best of the best.
Leave the hiring to me.
Oh! This is it,
my dears!
If you can handle
these problems,
I'll focus on the designs for
the front window display.
We'll show Manehattan what
Rarity for You is all about.
Aww! What would
I do without you?
What would she do without
us? Huh, let me think.
"Darlings, I'm absolutely
doomed! Doomed! DOOMED!"
Ha, I sounded
just like her.
Hey, you're not writing
this down, are you?
Now for the perfect
window display. Hmmm.
♪ [thumping dance music] ♪
Ooo! I can't really
stop a super-fun party
in the middle of
mega-happy-fun times,
can I? [groan]
What would Rarity want?
Keep that party going
till the break of dawn!
Really?
Indubitably! And as for
the roof? Get jiggy!
Raise it, Pinkie!
Raise it like you've
never raised it before!
Hah! If you say so!
Oh please, Pinkie Pie!
Never in a million years
would I say such balderdash!
[groan]
Obviously DJ Pon-3 only
plays the sickest of beats.
I just wouldn't want her
to miss out on the coolest
new music straight from
the back alley underground
zip-zop party scene!
I'd play the whole
thing if I were you,
no matter what
other ponies think!
♪ [Light Latin music] ♪
Awwwwww.
Rarity for You is only
hiring the best of the best
and to me that
means the fastest.
Now...uh, before
we begin... [groan]
Am I doing this right?
What would Rarity want?
New plan.
Who can be the first one to
tell me what fabric this is?
That's organza.
Are you sure?
It's a thin, plain
weave, sheer fabric,
traditionally made
from silk, so...yeah.
I don't know the first
thing about clothes.
Pretty much all I can
do is look at something
and tell you if
it's clothes or not.
This chair? [chuckle]
Not clothes.
See if you can keep
up with me here.
What are all
clothes made of?
Uh, fabric?
Bingo! But not in this
store. Uh uh. Not anymore.
Oh no?
Two words for you:
spoon clothes.
All our clothes will
be made of spoons!
[sigh] What would
Rarity want?
You know, I like
you, Plaid Stripes.
If it were up to me, we'd
have a spoon clothes store
right next to Stinky Bottom's
Discount Hat Emporium.
But it ain't up to me.
So...the answer is no.
Personally? I think spoon
clothes ain't such a bad idea.
Useful, too. Eatin'
soup. Stirrin' gumbo.
Diggin' little holes.
There. Perfect.
Although, what
would Rarity want?
Maybe she wouldn't
like it done by color.
Guess I have to
start over!
Hello Smokey. Softpad.
Smokey Junior.
I have some,
interesting news. I...
Oh, I'd like you to all stay
here forever, but...[gasp]
What would Rarity want?
You have to move
out! [sob]
A window display is the
first thing customers see.
And if they like it,
they'll walk inside
and experience the glory
that is my boutique.
I don't know which
one of you to hire!
Just keep guessing fabrics.
Daddy! Rarity's friend
doesn't like my ideas!
Spoon clothes! Is good idea!
♪ [thumping music] ♪
Oh no! Not a shopping
music mash-up!
[gasp] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
[gasp]
[crash]
When you write the story,
could you maybe
skip over the part
where we locked Rarity in the
window display? [chuckle]
Hello? The door
appears to be stuck.
Yep! We're working on it!
Hm. Well, shouldn't let
this time go to waste.
[chattering]
How did this happen?
I shut down the party.
I told Plaid Stripes no.
I asked the raccoons to leave.
I asked a lot of
fabric questions.
...just like I thought
Rarity would want.
Rarity asked us to help
her with everything
because she knows
all of us so well.
She knows how much
you care for animals.
She'd trust you to solve
the problem your way.
Maybe we should all
do the same.
Doing this our way
is what Rarity wants.
It's not too late. Let's all
dig in and we can fix this...
...before Rarity finds
out how bad we messed up.
I'm sorry I asked
you to leave.
The place is yours,
if you want to stay.
Though I would like to ask
you all just one favor.
I'm sorry I made you play
that unfun superboring music.
But if you're up for it,
I have an idea to make
the party even better.
OK, I don't get fabric,
but I do get speed.
And I need somepony
fast enough
to help all the costumers
Rarity is going to have so...
First one to the river
and back gets the job!
IT'S A RACE! GO!
Mr. Stripes, I owe your
daughter an apology.
She's got good ideas and I
should give 'em a chance.
So here's what
I'm thinking.
Perfect!
[crash]
Wow, looks like we fixed
that door just in time!
[gasp] Ooh. What's all this?
The whole place
organized by style,
cross-referenced by size and
reverse-indexed by fabric.
She'll be able to
find anything
in three seconds
flat. [gasp]
It was some of my
best work.
Oh, I knew I could
count on you!
All right. I suppose this
is the moment of truth.
[jingle]
Rarity for You
is now open!
[excited chatter]
Oh, dear, I wasn't quite
prepared for such a crowd.
How will I handle
them all?
My name is Blue Bobbin.
I'll be your personal shopping
assistant this evening.
Right this way,
everypony
and one of our talented sales
ponies can help you out.
Honestly, they were
all pretty slow,
but they finished the race.
Plus they knew a lot more
about fabric than I did,
so I hired them all.
♪ [soft electronic music] ♪
The way I see it,
Rarity designs fashion.
DJ Pon-three designs beats.
What better combination
than a boutique dance club?
After a quick bath, they were
more than willing to help.
Ah, a blue corn reduction
with shallot confit, but...
how can I possibly
enjoy it without a--
Spoon?
[chuckle] Told ya spoon-clothes
ain't such a bad idea.
Ah! Mmm...mm!
Exquisite.
This is the most whimsical
and wonderfully fashionable
boutique I've ever seen.
[agreeing chatter]
"In the end, Rarity's
Grand Opening
was a smashing success.
True, it got off to
a rocky start...
but somehow this ragtag
group of ne'er-do-wells"--
Oo! Heavens, I
think he means you!
"...came together and created
the perfect boutique,
a vision of Rarity,
combined with the expertise
of her friends. [giggle]
This reporter, for
one, is a believer."
Why didn't you tell me there
were so many problems!
We all figured you had
enough on your mind.
And we didn't want you
to think that the opening
wasn't perfect. [chuckle]
ne'er-do-wells or not,
I know I can always
count on all of you.
And nothing could be more
perfect than that.
[slurping sound]
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ friends ♪