♪♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa ahhhhhh!
[smashing glass]
Agh!
Well, we don't all
have magical horns.
I've been meaning to
move these older books
to my "reference"
section for a while.
Gotta keep the new
books front and center!
Thank you both for
your help.
Are you kidding? After
all you've done for me?
This is the least
I can do.
Oh please, I haven't
done that much.
Nah. You just taught me
the value of friendship.
Not much at all.
I may have offered
some guidance,
but you are responsible
for the pony you've become.
I'm proud to call you my
student AND my friend.
Now, we just need to
get rid of these boxes.
Spike, can you... Spike?
What's that?
Is it a bird?
Is it a parasprite?
It's... It's... INCOMING!!
[crash]
Oh. I usually get
letters by dragon.
It IS the fastest
way to get mail.
For me? Who would be
sending me a letter?
It's the ponies
from my old village.
Are they in danger?
Are they upset with you?
No. It's worse.
They've invited me to the
annual sunset festival!
♪ My little pony ♪
♪my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[sigh]
Uh, hey there,
everypony.
Uh. Hey Starlight. What
are you doing here?
I... I was invited. To
the Sunset Festival?
Uh yeah. But we
didn't think you'd
actually show up.
You didn't think we really
wanted you here did you?
But I apologized. I thought
everything was fine.
[laughing]
PLEASE. Stop. STOP!
♪ [eerie music] ♪
What happened? Is
anypony there?
Princess Luna? What
are you doing here?
Dreams are my domain,
Starlight Glimmer.
I am here because
you need me to be.
Oh! It's only a dream.
It may only be a dream, but
the feelings in it are real.
Great. So I guess
I'm more afraid
of going back
to the village
than I thought.
What do I do now?
I have been helped
time and time again
by six very
special ponies.
They helped me
overcome my past.
You are fortunate to
have them as friends.
I suggest you share your
concerns with them.
I see much of myself in
you, Starlight Glimmer
and I can tell you from
personal experience
that things do
indeed get better.
[whoosh]
Huh?
and Princess Luna
said I should tell you all
how I was feeling.
So, there it is.
I'm afraid to go back to the
village for the celebration.
But why, darling? You went back
to apologize; they accepted.
Everypony has moved on!
But have they? They don't really
know how much I've changed.
Or even worse, maybe I
haven't changed as much
as I think I have!
TRUST ME. You are a totally
different pony now.
I mean...you were
pretty awful!
RAINBOW DASH!
WHAT?! She WAS!
It's a compliment!
I don't think they would
have sent the invitation
if they didn't want
you to come.
I'm sure they'd be
happy to see you.
And getting an invitation
to a party and NOT GOING?
That's like...
it's like...
Well, I don't know what it's
like, but it is definitely bad.
Just be honest
with them.
I'm sure they'll understand
where you're comin' from.
I understand how
hard this is for you.
Maybe if you took
a friend along,
it might
make things easier.
Somepony you trust who
would look out for you.
Thanks so much for
doing this, Trixie.
When Twilight said I
should bring a friend,
you were the first
pony I thought of.
Great idea,
Princess Twilight.
Asking me, Starlight's
BEST friend,
to help her on this
difficult journey
really shows how wise a
princess you have become.
Thanks, Trixie.
I was TALKING about me.
The festival lasts
a whole week,
but I'm sure we
won't stay that long.
Oh I don't know,
Starlight,
time really flies when
you're spending it
with your BEST FRIEND!
Bye Starlight!See
you later! Good luck!
There it is! The
town where you --
Magically stole
everypony's cutie mark,
replaced them with equal
signs and forced them all
to hide their
natural talents? Yes.
I was going say
where you came from.
But yours is a more...
emotionally traumatic answer.
[sigh]
I just want to blend in. Be
just another pony in the crowd
enjoying the Sunset
Festival with my friend.
Sounds good to me. And if
things get weird for you,
just let me know.
I've got your flank.
Is that a promise?
Not just a promise. A GREAT
and POWERFUL promise.
[pow!]
[cough]
Well, I couldn't ask
for more than that.
If we're gonna do
this, let's do it!
Ahh! STARLIGHT! YOU CAME!
[nervous giggle]
We were worried you
wouldn't be able to make it!
Are you staying
the whole week?
We have different
events planned each day!
How is it living
in a castle?
It is SO good
to see you.
Oh yeah. These ponies
are terrifying.
[giggle]
It's good to see
all of you too.
You got here
JUST in time.
We were having some debate
about these banners.
Which do you think
feels more sunsety?
Oh, you don't need
me to decide that.
Whatever you think
is probably best.
Uh well, how about
helping us with the routes
for the relay races tomorrow.
Can you take a look?
Oh, I shouldn't.
You all go ahead.
I just want to
enjoy the festival.
But you WILL be a judge for
the baking competition, right?
We had a few questions
about the order of the acts
for the talent show.
And the unicorns have a
fireworks show planned.
We could REALLY
use your help!
[Talking over each other]
NO!
[explosion]
[chattering teeth]
Huh?
The great and powerful Trixie
would like to thank you all
for being such an
amazing audience!
Sadly it is time
for us to depart!
Good night, fillies
and gentlefoals!
[explosion]
[coughing]
[all chattering]
Ugh. I was horrible
when I led that town.
I was ready for them to not
trust me, but I wasn't ready
for them to put me
in charge again!
With my past, I should never
be in charge of anything.
So you messed
up. Big deal.
Don't you ever tell
another pony I said this,
but even Trixie's made
mistakes. Ha, I know!
The trick is to just move on and
pretend they never happened!
I feel like that's
almost good advice.
Hey! Uh, Pinkie Pie!
Hey, you!
So. You're probably wondering
why I'm back so soon.
Where were you?
I went to my old village?
For the festival?
Ooo sounds fun!
How was it!
It was kind of a disaster.
I came back early
because I freaked out.
Oooh, sounds awful! Bye!
That was strange.
Isn't she always strange?
Yeah, but not like that.
Hey! I'm back early!
Ah, welcome
back.
Have you two noticed Pinkie
acting a little strange?
Pinkie Pie always
acts strange.
Told you.
Anyway, I wanted to
talk to all of you.
Things didn't go the way I
thought they were going to go
at the Sunset Festival.
What happened?
I kind of freaked out and
ran out of the village.
HA HA HA!
You freaked out and ran
away from a festival?
Ha! That's the funniest dang
thing I've heard all day!
Ha ha, Oh my! Let me guess. The
decorations were TERRIFYING!
HA HA HA!
[Whisper]
Hello ponies. We need
Rarity and Applejack.
Very important
friendship business.
I have to say I'm really not
as impressed with your friends
as the rest of
Equestria is.
I need to talk
to Twilight.
♪♪
[knock on door]
Twilight! Hello?
What do you want?
Twilight's very busy!
Spike, I really need
to speak with her.
Make an appointment! She's
a princess after all. [slam]
[knocking] What's wrong with
you? Why are you being so--
Rude? I think a certain dragon
didn't get his nap today!
Yeah right. Whatever...
Sorry, he's been acting
a little off all day.
I think he missed a
meal or something.
He's not the
only one.
Everypony is acting a
little strange today.
Yes. It's definitely been one
of those days. How are you?
Not great actually.
You're probably wondering
why I'm back from the
village so early.
I didn't want to bring it up but
yeah, it did seem strange.
Did it not go well?
The townsponies kept
asking me things,
like they expected me
to be in charge again.
But being a leader is the
last thing I should ever be.
So we left. Very suddenly.
In a literal puff of smoke.
Wow. You should DEFINITELY
never go back to that village!
What?
If you were worried about what
they thought of you before,
it's probably WAY worse
now. I'd cut my losses.
That's surprising
advice coming from you.
Trust me. I'm the
Princess of Friendship.
You don't need those ponies. You
can always make more friends.
Ah, speaking of friends,
if you'll excuse me.
Important business to attend to!
[slam]
♪ [mysterious music] ♪
Cut my losses? That
can't be right.
♪♪
Hey! I wanted to apologize
for my behavior earlier.
Party Favor? Can you hear me?
I TOLD you, you can never
speak to them again!
What are you all doing here?
Making sure you do what I said!
I'm your teacher,aren't I?
Didn't I say to
never come back here?
Yes, but that's just
doesn't seem right.
You aren't acting like
yourself. Something is wrong.
[whistling wind]
A dream! This is
another dream!
Starlight Glimmer...
Princess Luna?
Starlight Glimmer!
Princess Luna, where are you?
STARLIGHT GLIMMER!THERE IS
NO TIME! YOU MUST GET HELP!
What? What are you talking
about? This is just a dream!
NOT HERE! IN THE WAKING WORLD!
THEY'VE TAKEN MY SISTER AND I!
IT'S WORSE THAN THE LAST TIME!
YOUR DREAM CALLED TO ME AND
I WAS ABLE TO BREAK THROUGH!
YOU MUST FIND HELP!
What are you saying?
WHO'S taken you!
BE CAREFUL WHO YOU TRUST.
YOU WILL NEED ALL THE
HELP YOU CAN FIND.
THE CHANGELINGS
HAVE RETURNED AND--
Princess Luna!
[whoosh]
[gasping]
THEY'RE BACK!
[knocking]
Trixie? Trixie, it's
Starlight! Are you awake?
Of COURSE Princess Celestia,
I'd love to perform
for Peanut Butter crackers.
TRIXIE! WAKE UP!
[firecrackers explosions
and whistles]
[coughing]
Starlight? What time is it?
It's late. I think I figured out
what's wrong with my friends.
I have a whole
list of things
that are wrong
with your friends.
We can go over it
in the morning.
No! Trixie, we're in danger!
OK fine. Aside from lack of
sleep, how are we in danger?
I think the...
What did you tell me never
to tell another pony?
Starlight, if you woke me
up to play guessing games--
After we left my village!
What did you tell me to never
tell another pony you said!?
That even Trixie's
made mistakes.
Trixie, there's no time for
this. What did you say?
That even Trixie's made
mistakes, OK? Are you happy?
Yes. Sorry. I just had to make
sure you weren't one of them.
One of who?
A changeling.
I think they've taken Princess
Celestia and Princess Luna.
What? Are you sure? I
mean, what do we...
We have to tell Twilight!
If I'm right, then it's
too late for that.
[muffled conversation]
Agh!
[nasty laugh]
Is it ready?
Just one more.
[zapping]
QUEEN CHRYSALIS!
Ugh, I can't take
any of you seriously
when you look like that.
Oh. Right.
MUCH better. Now report.
Everything here is going
according to plan.
We've replaced the six
ponies and their dragon
and have taken
control of the castle.
Excellent. And I've
just received word
that the Princesses from
Canterlot have successfully
been replaced as well.
[cackling]
We thought too small last time,
ONE ponynapped
princess wasn't enough.
With ALL the most beloved ponies
of Equestria taken care of,
NOPONY can stop us.
[evil laugh]
[whoosh]
[creak]
[hiss]
[whoosh]
[sniff sniff]
[panicked whimpering]
[zap zap]
I can't deal with this.
I'm just a performer.
This is... this is
princess level stuff.
But the changeling's have all of
the princesses. We're doomed!
Maybe not. Queen Chrysalis only
said they took Luna and Celestia
and obviously Twilight
and the others,
but maybe Cadance is still safe.
Our best bet is to get
to the Crystal Empire
before the changelings
do. That way we--
There's no help coming
from the Crystal Empire.
[frantic screaming]
Thorax?
Yes.
Your wings look... different.
I guess they do.
How do I know you aren't
some other changeling
pretending to be Throax?
You were there when Spike
defended me to the ponies
of the Crystal Empire.
Princess Twilight said...
As the Princess of Friendship,
I should set an example
for all of Equestria, but today,
it was Spike who taught me--
OK! OK. I believe you. We
don't need the whole speech.
Trixie, this is Thorax.
He's a reformed changeling.
He's on our side, understand?
Hi, it's a pleasure to--
If Starlight says you're on
our side I believe her but...
maybe just stay over
there for now, OK?
What did you mean
there's no help.
Did the changelings
get Cadance too?
They took Cadance, Shining
Armor AND Flurry Heart!
Sunburst sent me here to get
Princess Twilight's help
but it sounds like it's
too late for that too.
So what should we do?
Yeah, Starlight what
are we going to do?
I... I don't know. There
has to be somepony else
who can handle this.
There is NOPONY else.
Everypony with powerful
magic is already gone!
You know, whenever ponies
talk about powerful magic,
they always leave me out.
If I weren't so evolved, I might
decide to take it personally.
Well, isn't this
QUITE the combination
of secondary characters.
Where are Twilight
and the girls?
First, how do we know
that you're really you?
[snap]
♪♪
Shall I continue?
Chrysalis and the
changelings are back.
They've ponynapped all of
the most powerful ponies
in Equestria.
Celestia, Luna, Cadance,
Shining Armor, Flurry Heart,
Twilight and her
friends. We need to--
They took Fluttershy?
Yes.
Where?
The changeling kingdom. With
you on our side, I think we --
[poof]
Odd. I was trying to take
us right to Fluttershy,
but there is no Fluttershy.
[smash]
I think I have a pretty good
idea where she might be.
♪ [dramatic] ♪
Oh. I'd hoped to never see
that place again. Now what?
♪♪