♪♪
(train chugging)
This just got real.
(excited chatter)
♪♪
Listen up, gang.
We're almost there so I've
got a few things to say.
First off, who here besides
me thinks this is the best
Equestria Games delegation
in Ponyville history?
(cheers)
(grunting roar)
And no matter what
your sport is,
we've gotta give it our best
because we've all got a genuine
shot at Ponyville gold!
(cheers)
With the possible
exception of Bulk Biceps,
Fluttershy and me.
I mean, we're good and all, but
we're up against the Wonderbolts
in the aerial relay, so
gold's kind of a stretch.
Let's not kid ourselves.
Don't feel bad, Rainbow Dash.
We have absolutely no shot
at winning gold, either!
Uh, that's because you're
carrying the flag for Ponyville
in the opening ceremony.
There are no winners.
Winners or not, we still have
the chance to be awesome!
That's the spirit.
You hear that, everypony?
Winners or not, we all still
have the chance to be awesome!
(cheers)
But uh, let's
still try to win
lots and lots of stuff too, OK?
♪ (military snare drum) ♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
(squealing brakes)
(hiss)
(grunts)
Phew! It's all in there, gang.
Leave it to Spike,
champion gear carrier,
for all your
gear-carrying needs.
And the Ponyville flag?
You sure?
And what about the flagpole?
In with the portable ramp.
Whoa! (crash)
Give it a rest,
Applebloom.
Spike: Aw she's just
nervous, that's all.
Perfectly understandable.
Whenever I'm afraid I'll forget
something and I start to panic,
I have a simple
trick: I count to ten,
and by the time I'm done,
I've calmed myself enough
to get the job done
right every time.
Easy peasy cider squeezy.
(galloping hooves)
Spike: Hey!
Put me down!
What's going on?
(galloping)
(thud)
Spike! Are you
all right?
A thousand pardons, O
Great and Honorable Spike
the Brave and Glorious.
Huh? Who the what now?
Thanks for bringing
Spike to us.
It's OK, Spike.
We'll have our hoofponies
go back for your bags.
Can they hang back a sec and
tell me what's going on first?
(munch)
(gulp)
Mm mm!
So the ponies here think
I'm some kind of hero, huh?
More of the green ones, please.
I like the green ones.
Twilight: Last time
you were here,
you got the Crystal Heart
to Princess Cadance
in time to save this entire
empire from destruction.
You are known
throughout my empire
as Great and Honorable
Spike the Brave and Glorious.
Isn't that awesome?
You're a big shot here, Spike.
See that?
That's you!
Hello, gorgeous.
This is why we all hope
you'd do us the honor
of lighting the torch at
the opening ceremony.
You'd be the very
first dragon
in the history of the
Equestria Games to do so.
Of course, I'll do it!
And bonus: I can do it
with my fire breath.
(whoosh)
(sizzle)
(giggle)
(roaring crowd)
♪ (ceremonial theme) ♪
Places for the
procession, everypony.
Two minutes!
♪♪
(crowd cheers)
(giggling)
(upper class British accent)
And you're quite certain
you also understand exactly what
you're supposed to do?
I stand where you tell me
until you give me the signal.
And then I walk over
and light the torch.
Mm. Couldn't be simpler.
(roaring cheer)
(frightened whimper)
Mr. The Dragon? Are you coming?
Honestly.
Would somepony help him walk?
Now please welcome the
delegation from Ponyville!
Ponyville forever! YAY!
Awesome!
Yeah!
(cheers)
Whoo hoo!
♪ (trumpet fanfare) ♪
(stomp stomp)
♪♪
This is the signal.
(stomp stomp)
I'm giving you the signal now.
Mr. The Dragon!
(big inhale)
(cough)
Come on, Spike.
Calm yourself.
Count to ten.
One, two, three, thousand,
fourteen thousand,
twenty thousand,
thirty thousand!
What's wrong?
(squeak)
Tell me this isn't happening.
(chattering)
Equestria, we
have a problem.
♪♪
(cough)
Mr. The Dragon, would you
light the torch already?
I don't know what it is, but I
just don't have the stuff today.
Did you bring a match?
You're a fire-breathing dragon.
(cough)
Then some cough drops, maybe?
Never mind.
I'll keep trying.
(thud)
Somepony go down and help him!
(click click)
Light! Light!
(grunt)
(grunts)
(whoosh)
(roaring cheer)
♪ (trumpet fanfare) ♪
Phew!
How did you do that?
I'm...not sure.
Ah well, better
late than never.
Let the Games begin!
(crowd roars)
♪ (trumpet fanfare) ♪
Oh! There are our
little superstars!
You were fabulous!
Made me sit up proud like
a cornstalk in August.
Ya done good, squirt.
Twilight: You three
really were wonderful.
But does anypony know what
was going on with Spike?
He sure seemed to be havin'
a tough time of it out there.
He put things right
in time, though.
Actually, it was me.
I didn't want him
to be embarrassed,
so I cast a secret spell
to light it for him.
Oh dear. Have you
told him?
No, but he might have
figured it out on his own.
You gotta tell him just in case.
I know. I'm just afraid
of how he'll take it.
I know what pride he
takes in a job well done.
Psst. Here he
comes now.
Act casual.
'Sup.
Spike! Is everything OK?
I guess. I don't know!
The weirdest thing
happened down there.
Yeah, about that. I--
I mean, there I was,
trying to light the torch,
with all of Equestria watching,
and feeling like the
hugest failure ever.
And then the thing just
lit. It was amazing!
Oh! Phew! I was afraid
you'd be upset.
Upset? Are you kidding? Why
would I be upset to discover
I can light fire with my mind?
Huh?
Look! It's the Great
and Honorable Spike
the Brave and Glorious!
Can we get your autograph?
Sure!
How you saved our empire
last time you were here
was really amazing.
Aw. You know what
else is amazing?
Watch this!
(distant birds chirping)
(straining grunt)
Don't worry. Once it bursts
into flames through brainpower,
I'll sign another one
for you. Promise.
(grunts)
(groan)
(softly) Spike, may I have
a word with you a moment?
Better be careful with that.
Might burst into flames later.
Delayed reaction.
Hey Twi, what is it?
Hold on, hold on!
Give me a second.
If I can set fire to
stuff with my mind,
mindreading must be
just around the corner,
and I predict that you
are about to ask me
to set fire to something
with my mind!
No. Because you can't.
Oh really? So how do you explain
what happened down there
in front of thousands
and thousands--
I did it, Spike. I cast a
spell to do it for you.
... in front of thousands
and thousands...
I'm sorry, Spike.
I just couldn't stand to
see you stuck like that.
You understand, don't you?
I, uh...I need to be
alone right now.
Spike?
O Great and Honorable Spike
the Brave and Glorious.
Can I get your autograph?
Sorry. You should probably
ask somebody special instead.
(cheering)
♪♪
Our next event:
the aerial relay!
That's Dash and Fluttershy!
Oh no, we can't
be late for that!
Miss, step right over here.
Unicorns will no
longer be admitted
without a disabling spell.
To prevent cheating.
And make sure you don't
even try casting a spell
or we'll know it.
Hmph!
(clang)
If Ponyville medals here
we'll have 8 medals so far,
putting us tied for the
lead with Cloudsdale.
Unless Cloudsdale
medals here, too.
(whoosh)
Ms. Harshwhinny, I know
you're really busy but--
What is it?
Maybe there's something else I
can do for the Games, you know,
something really worthy of the
Crystal Empire's admiration?
What are you talking about?
You lit the torch
for the whole thing!
Well, actually, that
wasn't really--
That wasn't "worthy"
enough for you?
For ponies' sake!
Next thing you know, you'll be
asking to put on a rock concert!
Agh! Celebrities.
Wait. That's it!
(whoosh)
(roar)
Second place!
We got silver!
Congratulations to
all our medalists.
And now, the anthem of--
And I shall do the
honor of singing!
(cheers)
Spike? What are
you doing?
You know how they always
just play the music?
Well, I know all the
words to our anthem
and will sing them for you
now, loud and proud,
to the enjoyment of all!
(cheers and applause)
And now, um, the Cloudsdale
anthem, as sung by Spike.
Wait, the Cloudsdale anthem?
They only play the anthem
for the winners, Spike.
The Wonderbolts are
from Cloudsdale!
But I don't know the words
to the Cloudsdale anthem.
I've never even heard it!
Sing for us, O Great
and Honorable Spike
the Brave and Glorious!
Ahem!
♪♪
♪ Oh we're the Wonderbolts! ♪
♪ And we're super-fast! ♪
♪ And we're from Cloudsdale
which is a part of Equestria ♪
♪ that we like best and
we're proud and we're fast ♪
♪ and we like it because it
really has nice trees ♪
♪ and we love the town
because it's so cool, ♪
♪ and we like to
fly really fast ♪
♪ and everything like that. ♪
♪ Uh, I kind of wish this was
over cause it isn't yet... ♪
♪ over.... Now...oh... ♪
♪ we're the Wonderbolts! ♪
♪ And we're super-fast! ♪
♪ And we're clear
from Cloudsdale ♪
♪ We like it there
because it's really nice ♪
♪ and the trees are cool, ♪
♪ and I hope this is over now, ♪
♪ and it keeps going on
la la la... ♪
♪ and we really love the town ♪
♪ So I wish that this
song was over now ♪
♪ Over now... ♪
♪ Over now ♪
(baby crying)
Pinkie Pie from afar:
NAILED IT!
Spike, you coming?
Nah, I got this
stuff to pack up.
But you've been moping in here
for almost the entire Games.
And tonight's the
closing ceremony.
Which means we leave tomorrow.
Ergo the packing.
And so the Games conclude
as they always do
with the Ice Archery finals.
Ice archers, take your places!
(cheers)
Too bad Ponyville doesn't have
any ice archers competing.
We don't have
anyone to root for.
It's OK.
Ponyville has 37 medals
and Cloudsdale 36,
so looks like we'll be medal
champs of the Games anyway!
Whoo hoo!
But Cloudsdale has two
ice archery finalists
down there right now.
If they both place, Cloudsdale
wins the medal count.
So you're saying it all
comes down to this one event?
Pretty much.
Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
Twilight! Come take this
extra seat next to me
and freak out over
the medal count.
I'll show you how.
Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
Actually I was
looking for Spike.
Have you seen him?
He wouldn't come.
We tried to talk him into it.
But he wouldn't listen.
You can have his
extra seat, though.
Uh...Twi?
Twilight: Spike? You here?
(splutter)
Uh, yeah. I'm super busy.
Look at all this
packing left to do.
Crazy, right?
No more hiding out.
You're coming with me.
Now.
OK, fine. I'll come. Can
I at least wear these?
♪♪
Those aren't your
average arrows.
They freeze whatever part
of the target they hit.
Whoever encases their entire
target in ice first wins.
Keep your eye on
Number 7 from Cloudsdale.
He's the favorite.
♪♪
Honestly Spike, I don't
see why you're being
so hard on yourself.
I let everypony down. Twice!
You never let anypony down
so you have no idea
what that's like.
Are you kidding? I've
totally let ponies down.
That's not the point.
The torch got lit; the aerial
relay teams got their medals.
No harm no foul.
Can we at least watch
from inside there?
I'm not sure I'm ready to face
crowds in the stands just yet.
(crackling)
(gasps)
(panicked screams)
NO!
Steer it towards the field!
Away from the crowds!
Somepony cut the
disabling spell!
There isn't time!
Dash! Fluttershy! MOVE!
(crackling and hiss)
(roaring cheer)
That was awesome!
I just wanted to
thank you personally
for saving those ponies,
and the Games,
O Great and Honorable Spike
the Brave and Glorious.
You must be very proud.
I guess.
All: You guess?
I just saw what needed
to be done and reacted.
It just so happens
I can breathe fire.
If any of you could do that,
you'd have done the same.
Forgive me for
being blunt, Spike,
but you're not makin'
a lick of sense.
It's just how I feel.
Wait a second. I
think I get it.
You keep saying you
let everypony down.
But we all keep
saying you didn't.
You know who was disappointed
in you, Spike? You.
And only you can make
it right with you again.
What would that take, Spike?
I don't know. Can
you turn back time?
Cause I'd sure like a do-over
on that opening ceremony.
We can't turn back time.
But would you do me
the great honor
of lighting fireworks
in my place
at the closing
ceremonies tonight?
Come on, Spike.
You've saved the
Crystal Empire. Twice.
I think you can
light some fireworks.
I guess I have to at
least give it a shot.
(happy chatter)
(cheering)
We did it!
Ponyville won the medal count!
And only by one medal.
Hmm. Wonder which
medal that was?
Bam!
How's it feel to have opened
the best Equestria Games
in Ponyville history, Squirt?
Probably as good as it
feels to close them.
OK, it's time.
Spike: You know,
it's kinda weird;
no matter how many times others
tell you you're great,
all the praise in
the world means nothing
if you don't feel it inside.
Sometimes, to feel
good about yourself,
you've got to let
go of the past.
That way, when the time comes
to let your greatness fly,
you'll be able to
light up the whole sky.
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ friends ♪