♪♪
Today we have two
special guests
with a very special
announcement.
Everypony, welcome the Head
of the Equestria Games,
Ms. Harshwhinny.
(door opens)
Thank you.
Now I'm sure you all
know about the Equestria Games,
where ponies from all over
the land compete for glory
in various athletic pursuits?
Well, now you littlest ones will
have the chance to compete
for a weighty responsibility
of your very own.
Rainbow Dash: Oh, c'mon!
Tell them the fun part!
(whoosh)
(Ooh and aah from the others)
That's right!
All you gotta do is show
Ms. Harshwhinny the coolest,
most spectacular,
most rockin' routine
and you're goin' to
the Games!
So, who's gonna be
the lucky ponies?
It's got to be me.
Maybe it's me.
Maybe it's us!
(crash)
Hey! It could happen!
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Rainbow Dash: So the
winning team gets to carry
the Ponyville flag at
the Equestria Games!
Oh, you are gonna LOVE this!
Ms. Harshwinny: Miss Dash!
Will you please curb
your overenthusiastic outbursts!
Now then, let me be
clear on the rules.
You ponies will form teams.
Each team will create
their own flag-carrying routine.
Everypony will be judged on
grace, style, and originality.
There's a most complicated
scoring system,
which I will elaborate
upon now. Firstly...
Aw, Get to the
nitty gritty later.
Tell them the important
stuff: like who's the coach?
(whistle blast)
That's right: ME!
And you know why I'm
qualified to coach you?
Guess who carried the
Cloudsdale flag in the Games
when she was a little filly.
ME!
I'll never forget it.
I burst into the stadium...
spreading my wings,
the flag flapping in the breeze!
I did tricks with that
flag the likes of which
no pony saw before,
and no pony's seen since!
Professionalism, Ms. Dash,
I must insist.
If you want to keep your job
as coach of these ponies,
you must maintain a
professional attitude
and keep your
emotions in check!
Am I making myself absolutely,
100% crystal clear?
Yes, Ms. Harshwhinny.
You know, professionalism
is my middle name.
Rainbow
"Professionalism" Dash.
Hmph! Well, in
three days' time,
Ms. Dash will accompany anypony
competing to the Crystal Empire
where you will demonstrate
your routines for me
and the other judges.
Who will judge you
very professionally.
Ahem! Yes, quite,
quite correct!
In the meantime, get
ready to train and train hard!
Because I know this Opening
Ceremony is the single most
important thing that will ever
happen in your young lives.
But I know you're up
for the challenge!
And so am I!
WA-WAHOOOO-(cuts short)
AHEM!
Meet me after school tomorrow
at 15-hundred hours, sharp.
And show me
your flag-carrying skills.
I am outta here!
(skid)
Professionally!
See how professionally?
(groan)
Ponies, the most
important thing is this:
your routine needs to show
what your town means to you.
So do Ponyville proud!
Work hard. Be bold. Wow me.
That is all.
(bell rings)
(excited shouts)
So what do you say we come
up with the perfect routine
and win this thing?
I'd say that's rootin'
tootin' terrific!
But there's one problem!
I bet everypony in class
is planning to compete.
Listen: somepony in our class
is gonna carry that flag.
So it might as well be us!
Crusaders, are you in,
or are you in?
Cause I'M in.
Me too!
Me three!
All right, the winning
routine needs to show
what's important about
Ponyville, right?
Both: Right!
So what's special
about Ponyville?
It's...It's...
I've got it!
It's a place where
different kinds of ponies
live together as friends.
Earth Ponies, like me!
Unicorns, like me!
And Pegasi, like me!
So somehow we gotta figure out
a way to show that in our act.
We're gonna
need a plan.
And a lotta
hard work.
And a whole bunch
of practice.
But take it from me: We
may just be little ponies,
but we have hearts as
strong as horses!
♪♪
♪ We're the toughest
little ponies in town! ♪
♪ Got the moves, got the mojo. ♪
♪ No harder-working
ponies around ♪
♪ We are a trio,
work as a team, ♪
♪ We'll be the first ponies
out on the flag-waving scene. ♪
♪♪
♪ We get going when
the going gets tough ♪
♪ We know our very best
is just never enough ♪
♪ We're kinda short,
but so what? ♪
♪ We don't get defeated. ♪
♪ We could take a little
break but we don't need it. ♪
♪ We've got hearts
as strong as horses. ♪
♪ We've got hearts ♪
♪ hearts strong as horses. ♪
♪♪
♪ When we put our minds together
we can achieve. ♪
♪ We're the Cutie Mark Crusaders
and you should believe. ♪
♪ We've got determinations
to represent the nation ♪
♪ for the win! ♪
♪ We've got hearts
as strong as horses. ♪
as strong as horses! ♪
♪ And we're playing to win
As we gallop to glory! ♪
♪ We can conquer any
challenge we're in ♪
♪ We've got hearts.... ♪
♪ Hearts strong as horses! ♪
♪♪
Whoa!
Oof!
If that's the best you've got,
we're going to win for sure!
We already have the most
divine routine planned.
It's absolutely
sure to crush everyone else.
And I mean CRUSH!
But we're winners,
and we have heaaaarts...
Sure, but you know
what you don't have?
YOUR CUTIE MARKS!
Blank Flanks! Blank Flanks!
Blank Flanks!
What does that have to
do with flag-carrying?
Having Cutie-Mark-less
ponies represent Ponyville
would be unthinkable!
And we, of course,
already HAVE our Cutie Marks.
So we know who's going
to be in the winner's circle.
Listen you two: Cutie Marks or
no Cutie Marks, you'll see:
the Crusaders are going to
carry that flag at the Games.
May the best ponies win!
GAME ON!
♪♪
Show me what you got, Cutie Mark
Crusaders. And make it good.
Don't worry, we will!
Sweetie Belle: Now, this is
just a little something
we threw together.
It's not perfect
yet. Not even close.
Let's watch the Cutie
Mark GOOF-saders
do their sad
little routine.
They're gonna be
a hot mess.
(mean giggles)
(dramatic) Since the
dawn of recorded time,
in one town of amazing
amazingness...
three types of
ponies coexist.
We are Earth Ponies...
We are Unicorns...
We are Pegasi!
And the town where friendship
reigns is our home.
Now welcome to the stadium
the flag of the place
we love best...
♪♪
(screech)
PONYVILLE FOREVER!
YAY!
It's kind of a
work in progress.
So, what did you think?
That.
Was.
AMA--
(to herself) Wait. Hold on now.
Gotta stay calm,
cool, and collected.
To give a calm,
clear analysis...
Wait: you whipped that
act together just yesterday?
That...
is...
(to herself)
Professionalism, Dash.
Keep those emotions in check.
Overall it was kinda sorta...
Overall it was OK.
Keep working hard,
who knows?
You might have a
shot. Gotta go.
Do y'all think she liked it?
I'm not really sure.
You heard her. If we
keep working hard,
we might have a shot.
So let's keep working!
Trot to it, ponies!
Did you SEE that?
I can't believe I'm saying
this. They could win!
But how do we stop them?
We already called
them Blank Flanks.
Then we need to find a new
way to get under their skin.
Or maybe, get under their WINGS.
Girls, we just wanted to say
your act is quite impressive!
Wait, what?
Um... thanks?
Oh, but of course!
As a matter of fact,
we think you're very brave.
Brave? Why?
Isn't it obvious?
It is to us.
In fact, it's obvious
to everypony.
You're showing all three
types of Ponyville ponies,
yet you have a
Pegasus Pony...
Both: who can't even fly!
What in tarnation does that
have to do with anything?
Silver Spoon: I'd say
not being able to fly
has everything to do with
everything, doesn't it?
I mean, a Pegasus
pony at your age?
You should have been
flying long ago!
So what if my wings
can't get me off the ground?
Your career as a
flag carrier
isn't getting off
the ground, either.
Ms. Harshwhinny will
never pick a Pegasus pony
who can't fly to
represent Ponyville
in front of all
of Equestria!
Ms. Harshwinny never
said anything about that!
I would've thought
that was obvious.
Diamond Tiara: Well, have
fun practicing anyway.
Even if your routine
will never...how shall I say?
"Take off."
Don't listen to them, Scootaloo.
Scootaloo?
You OK?
This routine isn't
working how it is.
We've gotta rethink
my part in the whole thing.
WHAT?
Why?
If we want to win, I'm
gonna have to fly.
Is that even possible?
And by tomorrow?
Maybe I can fly if I
work twice as hard.
See?
Oof!
Maybe three times as hard.
Apple Bloom: Golly, I
don't know, Scootaloo.
I don't think
that's the problem.
Well, I know
this for sure:
flying is the only
way we're gonna win.
So it's back to practice!
Is this a good idea?
Whooah! (thud)
I'll just work four
times as hard.
Probably not.
Guys, guys, guys!
Try it again.
(groan)
We've been rehearsing
all the livelong day!
We're getting tired.
Fine. We'll skip to my big
impressive flying entrance.
So you've done the do-si-do
to the left, then the right,
and there's the hoop.
Then I come in...
(thud)
Not quite what I had in mind.
We'll just (sigh) try
that part again.
(grunts)
I liked our routine
the way it was!
Me too. But all she cares
about now is flying.
Don't worry; I'll be
flyin' high tomorrow
at our final run-through
for Rainbow Dash.
I'm gonna get this, you'll see!
(grunts)
(thud)
Okay, Cutie Mark Crusaders,
this is your final run
before you show it at the
stadium tomorrow.
I know you're gonna
absolutely, positively,
...have a lot of fun.
OK, go! (whistle blast)
♪♪
Ponyville!
home of the um...
(whispered) Friendship!
Friendship, right!
There are four--no, three
kinds of ponies...
(yawn)
Left! LEFT!
I'm sorry!
I'm just tired.
And then I dip, and
then we turn...
Sorry!
(grunts)
(boing)
(thud)
♪ Tada! ♪
(gasping)
So? What'd you think?
That's. Y'know. Good and
all, heh heh.
I just thought maybe
possibly you might wanna
go back to, say, the first
version of the act, which was,
I don't know, what's the word?
Better.
Just do the routine
as it was.
Don't mess with
success, right?
Seriously.
Now I need to go coach
these other ponies.
And don't forget we've gotta
catch the early train
for the Crystal Empire.
See you in the morning!
What are we gonna do?
We're competing tomorrow
and I still can't fly, unless...
I'm just too tired.
I can't keep going.
Me too!
I'm tired; I'm hungry. And
now I hate this routine!
It feels like it's
all about you now.
She's right.
It's like you don't
even need us anymore.
Of course I need you!
Without you two, who's
going to hold up the hoop?
UGH! You don't
listen to yourself!
Oh, forget it.
I'm going home to
get some sleep.
So? Are you gonna
leave me too?
We've gotta catch the early
train to the Crystal Empire.
I better get some rest.
See you in the
morning, Scootaloo.
Come on, Scootaloo!
Do it for Ponyville.
Just gotta try 20
times as hard.
(grunt)
Thirty - times - as hard.
Oof!
Just a little harder...
(thud)
(grunt)
(sigh)
I can't fly.
I just...
can't!
(train bell ringing)
Crystal Empire!
All aboard!
Scootaloo?
Where IS she?
She better get here soon. This
here train is about to leave!
Here I am.
We were scared you were going
to miss the train.
I - I'm not going.
WHAT?
I'm the weak link.
If I go and fall, flop,
or do anything but fly,
I'm gonna blow it
for you two.
I can't believe you're
quitting on us!
But you're better
off without me!
But that's not
true, Scootaloo!
Ya know what, Sweetie
Belle? Forget it!
If she's gonna quit, we don't'
want her and we don't need her!
FINE!
Fine.
Conductor: All aboard!
(train chugging)
(train whistle)
How's my favorite
routine going today?
Oh, I just can't keep it in.
I want you to win so bad!
♪ "BumBUM, bumBUM". ♪
Then Scootaloo does
that KAPOW!
through the hoop!
Well, there ain't gonna be
a Scootaloo. She's staying home.
She's WHAT?
She got it in her head that the
only way to represent Ponyville
was by flying in our routine.
When she couldn't do it,
she told us she was quitting.
And then you tried to stop
her from doing that, right?
Well, actually we
kinda told her...
that we didn't
want a quitter.
Hang on! Are you NUTS?
You're a team and a team
never leaves a friend behind.
(screech)
Come on!
Sorry you
can't make it!
We'll take a picture for
you from the winners' circle.
(giggling)
I do not like them one bit.
Put on some speed, girls!
Rainbow Dash: Throwing
away your scooter?
Rainbow Dash?
Yup. But not just me.
I don't want to see them.
And what are they
doing here, anyway?
They're supposed to
be on the train.
We're not going.
Not without
YOU, Scootaloo.
What's gotten into
you, Scootaloo?
I didn't want to ruin
their chance to win
just because I couldn't fly.
And who said you had to?
But flying's what Pegasus
ponies are supposed to do!
YOU flew when you carried
the flag in the Games.
But that was me!
You're you!
And it just doesn't
matter if you can fly or not!
Your routine was amazing
'cause it represented
exactly what makes
Ponyville special.
You do still know
what that is, right?
Friendship.
Three kinds of ponies
living together as friends,
just like us!
Earth Ponies...
Unicorns...
And Pegasi.
But Rainbow Dash...
What if...what if my
wings never grow?
What if I never fly?
Listen, Scootaloo:
maybe you'll fly someday...
or maybe you won't.
You're all kinds of
awesome anyway.
Who's the toughest
little pony in town?
♪ Got the moves got the mojo
No harder working pony around. ♪
♪ We are a trio, work as a team,
We'll be the first ponies out ♪
♪ on the flag waving scene. ♪
So let's get to the
Crystal Empire.
And let's do the
routine as it was.
And let's WIN THIS THING!
♪ We've got hearts
as strong as horses. ♪
♪ And we're playing to win
As we gallop to glory! ♪
♪ We can conquer any challenge
we're in ♪
♪ We've got hearts! ♪
♪ Hearts strong as horses. ♪
♪♪
(whistling and cheering)
PONYVILLE FOREVER!
YAY!
(whistling and cheering)
Ms. Harshwhinny: In the
Equestria Games,
the Ponyville Flag will
be carried by...
"Cutie Mark Crusaders"!
WHOO-HOO!
♪♪
Ahem!
Look, what you three did was...
acceptable.
Ms. Harshwhinny: Acceptable?
Acceptable?
Why it was totally,
stupendously the single most
amazing thing
I've ever seen!
(giddy laughter)
Contain your
excitement, Ms. Harshwhinny.
Remember, professionalism.
Yes Yes, well, I...
(laughter)
You know what this means, right?
What?
We are totally gonna get
Cutie Marks in Flag Carrying.
Yeah!
(laughter)
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪