♪♪
Sweetie Belle:
I have to leave
for dress rehearsal
soon, Rarity.
Is it finished yet?
Ah, not quite.
I still feel it needs a
certain je ne sais quoi .
Perhaps it needs...
appliques.
Appliques?
Or...
sequins.
Sequins!
(crash)
Sweetie Belle.
I adore having you
help me, truly I do.
But...
Guess I got a
little carried away.
It's just that I know how
important it is for you
to finish this wardrobe in
time for Sapphire Shores
and her backup dancers.
This is without a doubt my
most prestigious order ever.
After all, Sapphire Shores
is THE Pony of Pop
and her Equestria-wide tour
launches in Canterlot next week,
which means she must have these
outfits by day after tomorrow
at the latest.
But is there time?
Barely. But I work
well under pressure.
Mmm. As long as I stay
calm I'll be fine.
Oh! Good!
Then maybe you could check the
stitching and finish the buttons
on the dresses I made for me,
Applebloom and Scootaloo?
I really want them
to look perfect
and I think I need
your expertise.
My, you've been so much help to
me, how could I possibly say no?
When do you need them?
Tomorrow night.
For the opening
night of our show.
(clunk)
But Sweetie Belle darling,
I'm behind as it is.
I understand.
I suppose if I got a few
more ponies to help me,
then maybe.
Oh! Thank you, thank
you, thank you, thank you!
You're the best sister ever!
The dresses are
right over there.
♪ (horror sting) ♪
(whimper)
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Cheerilee: My goodness
girls, it's time.
And the audience is
almost fully seated.
Costumes!
I can't believe Rarity
still isn't here
with the costumes.
She's been very
busy lately.
But how can she
still not be here?
She's known about
this for weeks.
Uh, she has known about
this for weeks, right?
I kept meaning to ask
her; I really did.
But I worked so
hard on this play.
I wrote it especially
for the three of us.
I directed it!
I'm in it!
I made the costumes!
It's just that this is
really my time to shine
doing something
completely myself
and I really wanted
to keep it that way.
But we wanted everything
to be perfect.
All our friends came
out to see it tonight.
Places!
♪ (tense) ♪
Ah! I'm here. I'm here!
You made it!
I beg your pardon for
cutting it so close,
but I made some improvements
to your original design
and I had a terrible time
with these froofy sleeves.
It is for the first play
you ever wrote, after all.
So I made quite certain
it came out just so.
Places? Hello?
♪ (orchestral) ♪
(approving murmurs
from the audience)
(applause)
(light clicks on)
(murmurs)
Forsooth and anon.
I cometh forthwith
and post haste
with glad tidings, m'ladies.
(wild ovation and cheers)
Wow! A standing ovation!
I still have goosebumps.
This must be like a dream
come true for you,
huh, Sweetie Belle?
Ooh, can you imagine
if this show
is how you got
your cutie mark?
Which do you think
you'd get it for:
writing, directing or acting?
(calming breath)
Let's not get carried away.
We've got a whole lobby
full of friends waiting
to shower us with
adoration and praise.
Try to be gracious.
Modest.
Classy.
(chatter)
Here we are! The
stars of the show!
You may tell us how
much you loved it now.
Line forms here.
Wow, you guys.
I think your sisters
would have loved it.
Would have?
They're sorry but they
had to go help Rarity
get Sapphire Shores'
wardrobe ready
to take to Canterlot
in the morning.
Even Rainbow Dash?
Yeah, Rarity fell
way behind.
(disappointed moans)
Aw, cheer up. The
show was great.
I'll get you some punch.
At least everypony else who
was able to stay loved it.
(enthusiastic agreement)
What did you all like best?
The writing, the
directing or the acting?
Oh my, I loved
the dresses!
I liked some of
those lines you said.
Oh really? Which ones?
I don't really remember,
but you were wearing
a pink taffeta dress
with lots of chiffon
when you said them.
Hoo-whee, that
outfit was a dazzler.
I liked that one almost as much
as the one with the lacy trim
and all the embroidered
cuffs. (giggle)
That was a nice one, too.
Grrrr.
Isn't there anypony here
who remembers anything
about the play
besides the dresses?
(hushed conversation)
(scream)
♪♪
All of this is
one headpiece?
Indeed.
This marvelous extravagance
is the creme de la creme
of the entire wardrobe.
But, alas, without this key
hidden stitch, it's just a...
I'm trying to think of a
classy way to say "big bummer".
Phew! Now perhaps we can all at
last take a moment to relax.
(door slams)
Whatever's the
matter, Sweetie Belle?
Didn't the play
go all right?
Not even close.
Oh dear!
Was something amiss with
the dresses I made you?
No. They were perfect!
And that was the whole problem!
Huh?
Oh, um. I think maybe I'll go
take that moment to relax now.
Sure do feel like relaxing.
Right behind ya.
How could you?
"Ooh, what amazing
dresses."
"Oh, how I loved the dresses."
"Ooh, dresses dresses
dresses dresses."
Oh, so they
did like them.
(chuckle)
You had me worried,
you silly filly.
There. I knew it.
You did this on purpose.
Stealing the spotlight
like you always do.
It's my fifth birthday
party all over again.
The what now?
Don't act like you
don't remember.
Or are you trying
to prove
you're a better
actress than me, too?
Sweetie Belle, if I did
anything to upset you then...
Admit you made those
dresses too good on purpose.
I thought they were
supposed to be good.
Yes. Good. Not
jaw-dropping amazing!
I only tried to do what
I thought you wanted.
HA!
(door slam)
Grr. I don't believe it.
After everything I put
up with all week long.
(imitates Rarity)
"Sweetie Belle, get me
some red ribbon."
"No that's not red,
that's cherry."
that's cinnamon."
(muffled)
For Pete's sake, it's all red!
I should probably
go talk to her, hmm?
At least Sapphire Shores
won't be all like,
"Ooh, who fetched you
that red ribbon?
Because I don't care about
anything else you made;
all I care about is that
AMAZING RED RIBBON."
Perhaps waiting would be best.
(growl)
(angry grunts)
Now I can't even sleep.
Happy now, big sis?
(running water and gulping)
I wish there was a way I could
take back all the work I did.
(soft snoring)
Even better.
(nasty chuckle)
(buzzing crowd)
(camera shutters clicking)
Now what?
(cheering)
And the winner of Best
Writer-Director-Actor
in an Awesome Play
Put On by a Pony
and Her Awesome Best
Friends goes to...
Sweetie Belle!
(excited crowd chatter)
(thunderclap)
(screams)
Don't go!
(evil laughter)
Stop!
Why do you have to
ruin everything?
(zap)
(explosion)
ENOUGH!
Princess Luna!
It's really you!
Or am I dreaming?
What do you think?
Let me see.
You just rescued me from a
maniacal laughing Rarity Cloud.
Yeah, probably dreaming.
I understand what you're
going through, Sweetie Belle.
I too have a sister who often
shines more brightly than me.
And with this I have struggled.
Wait! Come back! Luna?
Can you hear me?
Thank you for what you did.
Help! Luna! Luna!
(thud)
(happy chatter)
I remember this.
This is my fifth
birthday party.
I decided to make
a grand entrance.
I made myself all beautiful,
just like my big sister.
Finally I was perfect, and
then went to the stairs
to enter like the
belle of the ball.
When I finally came
out of my room,
I found the party
going on without me.
(cheers and laughing)
And I kept posing at
the top of the stairs,
waiting to be noticed,
but all I heard was...
These party favors
are the coolest.
(blast)
Awesome.
Where'd you get these?
Made them myself.
And of course you'll
all want cake, won't you?
(clamoring)
You're the greatest, Rarity.
Who needs a birthday girl
when you've got the birthday
girl's amazing big sister?
(snuffling and sobs)
That's when I learned
never try to shine
with my big sister around.
But perhaps you didn't
have the whole story.
I thought you said
you understood.
Luna?
(whoosh)
Where's Sweetie Belle?
I'm sure she'll be
along at any moment.
(yawn)
I'm tired of waiting.
I say we get out of here before
we all keel over from boredom!
Who's with me?
Poor Sweetie Belle!
Nopony's gonna come to another
one of her parties
after this fiasco.
Don't go. You'll miss out on
the... party favors.
I was going to save them
till the end but...
These party favors
are the coolest!
(blast)
Awesome! Where'd you get these?
I made them myself.
And of course, you'll all
want cake, won't you?
(cheers)
Who needs a birthday girl
when you've got the birthday
girl's amazing big sister!
(sobbing)
Oh no, no, no!
All of these things were
Sweetie Belle's idea.
I just assisted
with the execution.
I guess Rarity wasn't trying
to steal the spotlight.
She was trying to save my party.
(whoosh)
Luna?
♪♪
Luna!
(splash)
(dolphins squeaking)
♪♪
Should I hem the cloaks
now or wait until I'm there?
I could hem them now but
I might have to redo them.
When was this?
But if I wait until I'm
in Canterlot to hem them,
Sapphire Shores might not get
the best first impression.
Wait. This must've happened
earlier tonight.
Sapphire Shores is
such a big star
and such a stickler
for details.
What if everything's
not perfect enough?
Funny, I thought I was
the only one who got worried
about stuff like that.
Buck up, Rarity;
stop this foolishness.
You've done your best and
left nothing to chance.
All that's needed now
is a good night's rest.
(click)
(sigh)
I hope everything goes all
right for her tomorrow.
Hmm. How curious you
should say that.
(metal door opens)
Go. Go see what
the future holds
if you fail to rein in your
worst instincts as I once did.
(whoosh)
And here it is.
The creme de la creme .
Nooo!
The piece de resistance .
Don't!
(gasp)
Ooooh!
(shocked gasps)
The headdress!
Looks like I made
a mistake here.
But this is impossible.
I checked and
rechecked everything.
This couldn't have happened.
You sure about that, honey?
Please. You must believe me.
Listen to my sister!
(mocking chatter)
(bawling)
(scream)
I don't want to see any more.
Always check and recheck.
Who all wants to
hear a funny story
about my ex-costume
designer?
(laughter)
Check, recheck and
recheck and recheck!
Make it stop!
Princess Luna,
can you hear me?
Make me a dress, Rarity?
Please?
Go away. You know I
don't do that anymore.
(slam)
♪ (intense) ♪
Wake me up,
Princess Luna!
Wake me up! Wake me up!
(gasp)
(panting)
Rarity?
(gasp)
Oh no.
The boxes. Gone.
I'm too late.
She left for Canterlot!
(train track rattling)
The key is for you two to
distract Rarity long enough
for me to put the stitch back
in without her noticing.
If we're not too late already.
Oh my gosh!
I can't believe we're going
to see Sapphire Shores.
I'm such a huge fan.
I know all her songs.
"Get Your Pony On".
Ooh, that's one of
my favorites.
This isn't a trip to
see Sapphire Shores.
It's a trip to save my sister
from a horrible future.
"Serves Her Right".
(gasp)
How can you say that?
Rarity doesn't
deserve that at all.
No. "Serves Her Right"
is another one of
Sapphire Shores' songs.
You seriously didn't know that?
Don't you listen to her music?
I prefer showtunes.
(sigh of distaste)
♪ (dance beat) ♪
Five, six
seven eight, ba-bam!
♪ (music ends) ♪
Oh! Bravo!
Fabulous! Magnifique !
One more time.
From the top.
Let's not embarrass me
in front of my favorite
designer this time.
And a one-two-three-four!
♪♪
But you have to let us in.
I'm Sapphire Shores'
designer's sister.
You have to believe us.
Kid, the only thing I have to
do is make sure Sapphire Shores
doesn't get interrupted
all day by fans like you.
But I'm not a fan!
I am.
Me too.
Not helping.
♪ (music ends) ♪
(panting)
Now that's how I like it.
You rocked it, girls.
Get some water
and be back in ten.
Rarity, come on up here and
show me what you brought me.
Sapphire wants to see
it and to love it.
Almost.
(crash)
We've got to get in there. Now!
Sapphire: OK, then.
Liking what I see so far.
So is this the whole shebang?
Actually, I saved
the best for last.
♪ (scary) ♪
♪♪
(screams)
And here it is.
(crash)
You've gotta see this
with the cinnamon ribbon.
You'll love it.
Sweetie Belle!
You know her?
Uh, heh heh.
(ahem)
Just a moment.
(door opens and closes)
♪ (intense) ♪
♪♪
(slam)
♪ (dreamy) ♪
Oh good! This is
just a dream.
Actually, no. This
is very much real.
(sigh) Oh Luna, I wish none
of this ever happened.
What am I going to do?
Let's begin with this.
And I think I know how
you can even improve it.
(door opens)
I'd like to know what in the
wide wide realm of Equestria
this stunt of yours is all
about, and I want to know now.
Do you have any idea how
important this job is to me?
Actually, I do.
I was upset at you for stealing
the spotlight from me
at the play,
so I pulled out the center
stitch to the headpiece,
so it would fall apart.
What?
But then I realized I didn't
want your future to be ruined
forever and ever so I
came back to change it
before it was too late.
So here it is; it's all fixed.
Please forgive me.
Wait! What is this?
Trust me; Sapphire Shores
is going to love it.
Rarity, this isn't
going to work out.
You don't get to my
level of success
without learning
to read the signs,
and this situation has bad
luck written all over it.
I promise you'll
absolutely adore the headdress
as soon as you see it.
♪♪
My, it is attractive, but..
Look at the stitching.
Real close.
Well, I'll be.
It's a dolphin.
That's my lucky animal!
They swim with me in my dreams.
Wherever did you come up
with the idea for a dolphin?
Oh, it just came to me...
in a dream.
I'm sorry I got jealous
about those dresses;
I know now that you were
only trying to help.
Oh Sweetie, I
forgive you.
But I never did get
to see your play.
Any chance I could catch
an encore performance?
I don't think the play
was all that good.
To be honest? The costumes
were the best part.
Awwww.
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪