♪♪
What's wrong, Twilight?
It doesn't seem that my
new role as a Princess
equates to all that much.
I am Tirek! And I will take what
should've been mine long ago!
With each passing moment, he
grows stronger still.
And I know just the princess
who can stop him.
I'm afraid I must call in
another to stop Tirek.
Oh ho! You're talking
about me I presume.
Haven't you girls just
learned so much!
And there's something
interesting about the sections
that Discord bookmarked.
Each of you received
something from the pony
whose life you helped change.
There's still one key
missing: my element.
Join me, Discord and
reclaim your greatness.
Luna: Discord has betrayed
the ponies of Equestria
and joined forces with Tirek.
There is no doubt that Tirek
is after Alicorn magic.
We must rid ourselves
of our magic
before Tirek has the chance
to steal it from us.
(gasp)
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Luna: Tirek is set on
possessing Alicorn magic.
When he comes for us, we cannot
have what he is looking for.
I'm more than willing to do
my part and give up my magic.
Luna: You misunderstand.
Our magic cannot just
disappear into thin air.
Somepony must keep it safe.
That somepony is
you, Twilight.
Why me?
We do not believe
that Tirek is aware
that a fourth Alicorn Princess
exists in Equestria.
If we transfer our
magic to you,
Tirek will not know
where it has gone.
Do you understand what
we're asking of you?
Yes. It's just I'm only now
learning how to control
my own Alicorn magic. To
take on even more...
Twilight, you represent
the Element of Magic.
If there is anypony who
can do this, it's you.
Taking on this task will be one
of the most difficult things
I will ever do.
But with the help
of my friends...
I'm sorry, Princess Twilight,
but you must keep your
new abilities a secret.
I fear that your friends being
aware of your new power
could put them at great risk.
Do you still think you can
take on this responsibility?
This is the role I am meant to
play as a Princess of Equestria.
I will not
fail to do my duty!
Then we must begin at once.
♪♪
(zap)
That can't be right.
What can't be right?
Nothing. Carry on.
It is done.
(crickets)
(snoring)
You weren't gone very long.
Does that mean
everything's OK?
Yup. Everything's fine.
(zap)
Heh heh!
In that case, I'm
going back to bed.
Sun's not up, then
neither am I.
That's strange; the sun
should be up by now.
The sun should be up by now!
You can do this.
(buzzing)
Shining Armor. Why, whatever
are you doing here?
Back off, traitor.
Tirek: The only one Discord
betrayed was himself.
Abandoning his true nature
to make "friends"
with weak-minded equines
who offer him nothing.
How could you do this?
Why don't you go and
have a little fun?
I won't stand in
your way.
(laugh)
(heavy footsteps)
(smash)
What have you done?
WHERE IS YOUR MAGIC?
(explosion)
I have to gain better control.
I sure can't practice here.
Twilight? Where are we going?
Oh, uh, hi, Spike.
Gotta go...somewhere else.
(whoosh)
Whoa!
Twilight?
(scream)
(crash)
Oh my goodness. Are
you all right?
Jumpin' june bugs,
Twilight.
When did you learn
to fly that fast?
I must've caught a particularly
strong breeze...
(pop pop)
or something.
Must've been "or something"
because there wasn't
any breeze up there.
I don't know what happened.
But I don't really have time
to figure it out right now.
(zap)
Another visit to the Castle of
the Two Sisters, I presume?
We'd be more than
happy to accompany you.
Not today.
(zap)
Tirek may still be a threat.
I need you all to stay here
and encourage everypony
to remain inside.
Getting rid of your magic so
that I cannot take it from you?
That was your plan?
How does it feel?
Knowing that soon
every Pegasus, Unicorn,
and Earth Pony will
bow to my will
and that there is nothing
you can do to stop it.
You will not prevail, Tirek.
Give my regards to Cerberus.
Discord: You meant,
our will, didn't you?
Of course.
Here. I want you to
have something.
This was given to me by
someone very close to me.
I give it to you as a sign
of my gratitude and loyalty.
Oh my! I do love
a good accessory.
I suppose that's
Rarity's influence.
(chuckle)
Amusing. But we have no
time for such things.
With the Princesses out of
the way we can now--
Is this meant to be humorous?
Oh no!
I haven't touched that one yet.
There is a fourth?
And you did not
tell me this?
I just needed some assurance
that you truly considered
this a team effort.
And now I have it.
Then where can we find
this fourth princess?
Where is her castle?
Castle? Oh. No.
Princess Twilight lives
above a library in Ponyville.
Castle. Ha ha!
Not for much longer.
♪♪
Apple Jack: All right, y'all,
I think we've warned
everypony to stay inside.
I'm sure Discord
will catch Tirek
and this will all be over soon.
I'll bet he takes
his sweet time.
Discord: Or perhaps these
things just take time.
You're back!
Did you bring the
cucumber sandwiches?
I did!
I imagine they'll be your last
decent meal for quite some time.
(clang)
(angry shouts)
Ta-da!
You've gathered up all of them?
And her little dragon, too.
(chomp)
Why are you doing this?
I thought we were friends.
Oh, we were.
But Tirek offered me so much
more than just tea parties.
Surely you saw this coming.
I didn't. I really didn't.
(crash)
You really think she'd
do anything for them?
If Twilight has magic to
give, it will be yours.
Soon there won't be a Pegasus,
Earth Pony, or Unicorn
who will be able to
stand up against us.
Us? Who said
anything about us?
You did.
You've helped me grow strong.
You've provided the means
by which I can obtain
Princess Twilight's magic.
And now you are no
longer of any use to me.
But you said this was a sign
of your gratitude and loyalty.
A gift from someone
close to you.
My brother who betrayed me.
It is as worthless as he is.
Surely you saw this coming.
I didn't. I truly didn't.
I can do this.
See? Ha! Perfectly
controlled teleportation!
(groan)
Tirek: PRINCESS TWILIGHT!
(gasp) Tirek!
YOU HAVE SOMETHING
THAT BELONGS TO ME!
(explosion)
(whoosh)
(thud)
You're going to
give me what I want.
(explosion)
No!
(gasp)
(crackling fire)
(whoosh)
(explosion)
Now I understand what your
fellow princesses have done.
(boom)
(scream)
(growl)
(crash)
(boom)
(growl)
(explosion)
(roar)
(huge explosion)
It appears we are
at an impasse.
How about a trade,
Princess Twilight?
Their release for all the
Alicorn magic in Equestria.
(gasp)
(shouts of protest)
What's it going to
be, Princess?
♪♪
Rainbow Dash: Don't
do it, Twilight!
We aren't worth it.
Discord: Oh, but you
are, Fluttershy.
You're the pony who taught
me that Friendship is Magic.
I had magic and friendship,
and now I don't have either.
Enough! I want an answer.
And I want it now!
♪♪
I will give you my magic,
in exchange for my friends.
(all gasp)
As you wish.
All of my friends.
After the way he
has betrayed you,
you still call him a "friend"?
Release him!
If that's what you want.
Thank you, Twilight.
I'm sorry.
I know.
Your turn.
(cries of pain)
(shouts)
Twilight, what
were you thinking?
Tirek tricked me into believing
that he could offer me something
more valuable than friendship.
But there is nothing worth
more. I see that now.
He lied when he said that
this medallion was given
as a sign of gratitude
and loyalty.
But when I say that it is a
sign of our true friendship,
I am telling the truth.
Do you think that might
be the last one we need?
We have to get to the chest.
(whoosh)
♪♪
(heavy footstep)
Together!
I think we have to
do this together.
(amazed gasps)
♪♪
(snarl)
How is this possible?
You have no magic!
You're wrong, Tirek!
I may have given you
my Alicorn magic,
but I carry within me the
most powerful magic of all!
(shouts of pain)
♪♪
(rumbling)
Sweet Celestia! Are you all
seeing what I'm seeing?
Twilight: But whose is it?
I believe it is yours,
Princess Twilight.
You've been wondering what you
are meant to do as a Princess.
Do you know now?
As Princess, I believe I
have the power to spread
the Magic of Friendship
across Equestria.
That is the role I am meant
to have in our world.
The role I choose to have.
But I didn't defeat
Tirek on my own.
It took all of us
to unlock the chest.
Then it is unlikely
you are meant
to take on this
task alone.
All: Oooh! Wow!
You are now Twilight Sparkle,
the Princess of Friendship.
But what is the Princess of
Friendship without her friends?
Wait a minute.
Where's my throne?
I don't think you're
quite there yet.
Yes, well, I suppose not.
♪ upbeat ♪
♪ Each one of us has
something special ♪
♪ That makes us different
That makes us rare ♪
♪ We have a light that
shines within us ♪
♪ That we were always
meant to share ♪
♪ And when we come together ♪
♪ Combine the light
that shines within ♪
♪ There is nothing we can't do ♪
♪ There is no battle
we can't win ♪
♪ When we come together ♪
♪ There'll be a star
to guide the way ♪
♪ It's inside us every day ♪
♪ See it now! See it now! ♪
♪ Let the rainbow remind you ♪
♪ That together we
will always shine ♪
♪ Let the rainbow remind you ♪
♪ That forever this
will be our time ♪
♪♪
♪ Let the rainbow remind you ♪
♪ That together we
will always shine ♪
♪♪