♪♪
ROYAL GUARD: It's Princess
Luna and Princess Celestia.
They're missing!
PRINCESS TWIGLIGHT: The Everfree
Forest is ... invading.
I think I'm starting to
get a pretty good idea
of who we're up against.
I'm reformed; don't
you remember?
Why don't you ask
your zebra friend?
You can turn the potion
from purple to white.
You may see why the sky is day
and night.
Princess Luna!
There can only be one
princess in Equestria!
And that princess will be me!
(evil laugh)
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
(evil laughter)
(zap)
(crash)
(clattering rocks)
♪♪
(zap)
(crash)
Luna! Think of how long you
were banished to the moon.
You'll give us no choice but
to send you back there
if you don't stop.
Luna, I will not fight you.
You must lower the moon.
It is your duty.
"Luna", I am Nightmare Moon!
I have but one royal duty
now: to destroy you!
(zap)
(crash)
♪♪
And where do you
think you're going?
♪♪
(zap)
(crashing)
♪♪
(scream)
Celestia!
(laughing)
No.
Why would Luna do this?
Why now?
(sobbing)
You're all right.
You're all right!
Princess Celestia?
Oh, dear, sister.
I am sorry, but you have given
me no choice but to use these.
(grinding)
Are those...the
Elements of Harmony?
But that's how
they looked in...
the past.
This is the night
you banished her.
(whoosh)
♪♪
(high-pitched hum)
(explosion)
♪♪
(high-pitched hum)
Noooooo!
(whoosh)
♪ (peaceful) ♪
Why are you all looking
at me like that?
It's just you were
mumblin' to yourself.
Oh, and don't forget the
uncontrollable sobbing.
We were really
worried about you.
DISCORD: I, for one,
found it delightful.
Sort of a one-pony theater
piece, if you will.
You should really consider
taking it on the road.
(babyish crying)
Did you find out whose
rump we need to kick?
And where we can find 'em?
I saw something from
a long time ago.
But it didn't explain
what's happening now.
Perhaps farther back still
are the answers you seek.
Another sip of the potion
will give you a peek.
Are you sure about this?
(gulping)
(poof)
Oh, I do hope she breaks
into a song this time.
(zap)
♪ (eerie) ♪
Ho ho! Ho ho ! This
is so much fun!
How about a game of
pin-the-tail-on-the-pony?
(gasp)
Play time is over
for you, Discord.
Oh, I doubt that.
(munching)
Hungry?
Suit yourselves.
(munching)
Oooh. What have
you got there?
The Elements of Harmony.
With them we shall defeat you.
This must be when they turn
Discord into stone.
(mocking laughter)
You should see
yourselves right now.
The expressions on your face.
So intense. So sure
of yourselves.
Ah ha ha!
(zap)
Hilarious!
(guffaws)
(high-pitched buzz)
(gasp)
♪ (peaceful) ♪
The Tree of Harmony.
The Tree of Harmony?
♪♪
My Cutie Mark.
(zap)
Are you sure?
We have managed to
discover the only means
by which we can
defeat Discord
and free the citizens
of Equestria.
Even without these elements,
the Tree of Harmony will
possess a powerful magic.
(clanging metal)
♪♪
As long as that
magic remains,
it will continue to control and
contain all that grows here.
♪♪
(zap)
So, what did
you find out?
I still don't know what's
happened to Princess Luna
and Princess Celestia,
but I think I know why
the Everfree Forest
is acting this way.
Something's happened
to the Tree of Harmony.
The Tree of what now?
It's where Princess Celestia
and Princess Luna
found the Elements.
I think it's in danger.
Well, all right then,
let's go save a...
tree.
Uh, where is it exactly?
I think it's in there.
♪ (eerie) ♪
Hoo hoo!
I'm going to need
more popcorn.
Seems like only yesterday we
were heading into these woods
to find the Elements
of Harmony.
Seems like only yesterday
I was foolish enough
to think I should go
after them on my own.
I don't know what we're
going to face in there.
But whatever it is, I know
we need to face it together.
(agreement)
♪♪
We can use those to cross.
(squeals)
(scream)
(thud)
Rarity: A Cragidile!
Run for your lives!
(skid)
♪♪
(roar)
(grunts)
♪♪
Twilight: That was close.
A little too close
if you ask me.
You sure you're
all right?
I'm fine.
I just can't seem to get
these new wings to do
what I want them to do
when I want them to do it.
Aw, you'll figure
it out eventually.
"Eventually" isn't soon enough.
You have been havin' an awful
lot of trouble with those things
and well, who knows what
else is gonna come after us.
You know, maybe it wouldn't
be such a bad idea
for Twilight to go
back to Ponyville
and let us look for the Tree
of Harmony without her.
What? Why?
For starters, you just about
got eaten by a Cragidile.
We all did.
He wasn't after
just me.
Sure. But... well, the rest of
us aren't princesses.
What's that got
to do with anything?
Princess Celestia and
Princess Luna are gone.
If something happened to you,
I just don't think Equestria can
risk losin' another Princess.
Applejack does
make a valid point.
Even if we manage to
save the Tree of Harmony,
it won't necessarily
mean Princess Celestia
and Princess Luna
will return.
Equestria will need somepony
to lead in their absence.
But the Tree of Harmony.
I'm the only one who has seen it
and knows what it looks like.
Huge tree. Cutie
Marks on the trunk.
Probably being attacked by
something hideously awful.
Yeah. I'm pretty sure we'll
know it when we see it.
All of you feel this way?
Feel like I shouldn't be here?
It is probably
for the best.
♪ (cheerful humming) ♪
Help! Help!
Discord!
(poof)
(thud)
You're welcome!
Ha.
No luck finding your tree?
We ran into some trouble and my
friends decided it would be best
if I returned to Ponyville
while they continue the search.
Equestria will need me if
Princess Celestia
and Princess Luna
don't return.
I'm just surprised that
you agreed to their plan.
I never thought you'd
be the kind of pony
who would think she was
better than everypony else.
I don't think I'm
better than anypony.
Oh! Well, how silly of me to
assume you would think that.
All you did was choose to keep
your precious Princess-self
out of harm's way while your
friends thrust themselves
right into it.
I'm sure you'll all be
the best of pals again
when they return from
their terrifying,
yet deeply bonding
experience
that they're having
without you.
(snicker)
I never should have
agreed to come back here.
Come on, Twilight,
Discord may be reformed
but he's not that reformed.
He's just trying to
get under your skin.
Well, it's working!
♪♪
(poof)
Anypony else starting to
think this is a lost cause?
We're almost at Celestia
and Luna's old castle.
Maybe whatever
Twilight saw
when she took that crazy
potion wasn't real.
Maybe there is no
Tree of Harmony. Maybe--
Maybe it's
right down there.
It can't be.
♪♪
How are we supposed
to get to it?
(squeals and grunts)
(crash)
Take the stairs, silly!
Are we there yet?
I don't know where
we are. We're lost.
I never should've
left my friends.
We can't just give up.
Maybe if I get up there,
I'll be able to spot 'em.
Well, what do you know?
Twilight!
(coughing)
(gasp)
♪ (eerie) ♪
Fluttershy: I think it's dying!
So let's save it already.
(grunts)
(snap)
Oof!
Nice try.
(battle cry)
(whack)
Whoa!
Oof!
Valiant effort on
both your parts,
but the tree
remains in jeopardy.
And I suppose you've
got a better idea.
That's what I thought.
I know who would
know what to do.
But we sent her home.
♪♪
It was your idea, Applejack!
We all agreed it was the
best thing, Rainbow Dash!
We were tryin'
to protect her.
(grunts)
Twilight!
Trouble!
Help!
(zap)
(snap)
(thud)
(spit)
Listen here, you
rabid rhododendrons.
You mess with one of us.
You mess with all of us.
(party noisemaker)
(hiss)
Up here!
(whoosh)
Yoo-hoo! Come
and get me.
Don't forget about me!
♪ Ta-da! ♪
(screech)
(pop)
I sure am glad you
came lookin' for us.
Not as glad as I am
that you found me.
The truth of it is, Twilight,
we're simply lost without you.
Yeah. Equestria may
need its Princess...
But we need our friend.
♪♪
♪ (eerie) ♪
(gasp)
(squeal)
(zap)
(rustling)
CELESTIA WITH ECHO: Even
without these Elements,
the Tree of Harmony will
possess a powerful magic.
As long as that magic remains,
it will continue to control
and contain all that grows here.
I know how we can save the Tree.
We have to give it the
Elements of Harmony.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
How are we supposed
to protect Equestria?
How are we meant
to rein Discord in
if we can't use the Elements
to turn him back to stone?
Twilight, the
Elements of Harmony...
They're what keep us
connected no matter what.
You're right about
one thing, Applejack.
The Elements of Harmony
did bring us together.
But it isn't the Elements
that will keep us connected.
It's our friendship.
And it's more important and
more powerful than any magic.
My new role in Equestria
may mean I have to take
on new responsibilities.
And our friendships
may be tested.
But it will never,
ever be broken.
There's no time to lose.
Everypony ready?
All: Ready!
♪ (chimes) ♪
♪♪
(whoosh)
(horrified gasps)
(grunt)
♪♪
♪ (heavenly music) ♪
(zaps and rushing)
(thud)
Oh, poo!
(zap)
♪♪
We know how difficult it
must have been for you
to give up the Elements.
It took great courage
to relinquish them.
(rising energy sounds)
(zaps)
(whoosh)
♪♪
What's inside it?
How am I supposed to open it?
Celesia: Six locks.
Six keys.
I do not know
where they are.
But I do know that
it is a mystery
you will not be
solving alone.
Bravo, ladies! Bravo!
How ever did you save
the day this time?
Blast a beastie with your
magic necklaces, I presume?
(poof)
Where are those little
trinkets of yours?
You know, the ones you
use to send me back
to my extremely
uncomfortable stone prison.
(sigh)
Gone.
Gone? Ha ha.
Gone?
But our friendship remains.
And if you want to
remain friends,
you'll stop thinking whatever
it is you're thinking
and help us clean up.
Fine.
But I don't do windows.
One thing I don't get.
Why'd all this happen now?
Discord: I have no idea.
Those seeds I planted
should've sprouted up ages ago.
What did you say?
Oh. Why should I
try to explain it,
when you can see
for yourself?
(gulping)
(zap)
Play time is over
for you, Discord.
Oh, I doubt that.
Hungry?
Well, obviously things didn't go
according to my original plan.
My plunderseeds should
have stolen the magic
from the Tree of Harmony
and captured Princess
Celestia and Princes Luna
thousands of moons ago.
Alas, it seems the Tree
had enough magic
to keep the seeds from
growing up big and strong.
Until now, that is.
You realize this is information
we could have used hours ago?
And rob you of a valuable
lesson about being Princess?
What kind of friend
do you think I am?
(snap)
♪ (fanfare) ♪
♪♪
Citizens of Equestria, it is
no longer with a heavy heart,
but with great joy, that
I raise the summer sun.
For this celebration
now represents,
not the defeat of
Nightmare Moon,
but the return of my
sister, Princess Luna.
(cheers)
♪♪
(whoosh)
(gasps of amazement)
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪