♪♪
(splashing)
Apple Bloom: Just one
more time. Please!
All right, but this
is the last one.
Whoo hoo!
Wheeeee!
(splash)
(shouts and choking)
Oh dear me!
Sure wish you'd come
swimmin' with us, Granny.
Sorry, dear, but I just
can't bring myself anywhere
near that there
swimmin' hole.
How come?
Well, I wasn't
always this way.
(film clicking)
♪ (old time piano) ♪
Time was, I was an
aqua-pony all star.
In fact, I was the only
Apple to ever come close
to breaking the Equestria
high diving record.
♪♪
Falling six stories into
a deep-dish pie pan
takes a toll on
the hindquarters.
Oh, I was so sore,
it took years
before I could even
look at the water again.
Just the idea of swimming
makes my whole body ache.
Besides, these old legs can't
even paddle fast enough
to stay afloat.
(losing balance shouts)
Boy, I sure would hate
to be afraid of swimming.
Do you think I'll ever
be scared of the water?
♪ (Jaws theme) ♪
Aaah!
Nope.
(laughter)
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
♪ (banjo) ♪
Apple Bloom: Wow, Granny.
I can't believe you
were a high diver.
The best one in Ponyville.
Do you think I could
be a high diver?
Nope.
Absolutely not!
But...
Now you hold your horse
feathers, little seed.
I never said being a high
diver was a smart decision.
It's incredibly dangerous.
I know, but--
But nothin'!
It is the riskiest, scariest,
darned fool thing I ever did do.
That's not to say I don't wish
I was still young and spry
and confident, but
let's leave the flying
through the air to the pegasi.
Wow, when you put it that
way, it doesn't sound so fun.
(crowd chattering)
♪ (carnival music) ♪
Wow. I wonder where
everypony's heading.
♪♪
Now, where in Ponyville do
you two think you're going?
Oh, quit being such a worry
worm and follow your ears.
Come on, Applejack.
Aren't you curious?
♪♪
♪ (louder) ♪
♪ (music ends) ♪
(excited chatter)
Shhh!
(lights click on)
(squeaking)
(poof poof)
Thank you one and all for your
attendance and we guarantee that
your time here will
not be spent in vain.
In fact, we think it will prove
to be the most valuable time
you've ever spent.
The Flim Flam Brothers!
Yep.
This should be
interesting.
Welcome one and all to the
demonstration of a lifetime.
A demonstration
of a better life.
of a better time.
And if we haven't captured
your interest just yet,
by the time we finish an
unfortunate phenomenon
practically guarantees
that we will.
A phenomenon?
What's that?
It's a circumstance
perceptible by the senses,
but in this case it's
the simple fact that...
♪ There's ailments
all around us, ♪
♪ in everything we
touch and see. ♪
♪ The sickness that
lies waiting there, ♪
♪ in every breath you breathe. ♪
♪ Disease will up and grab you
as it crawls from land and sea ♪
♪ It's amazing how infected
that the natural world ♪
♪ and all its things can be. ♪
Now I understand that some of
you don't think you're sick
but twisted hooves
and aching joints
don't heal all that quick.
Consider just how dangerous
this world is, you might-
♪ Slip and fall, break or sprain
something here tonight ♪
♪ But luckily for you we've
got the thing you need. ♪
♪ And it's easier when
all you need's the cure ♪
♪ The Flim Flam Miracle
Curative Tonic ♪
♪ Is just what the
doctor ordered, I'm sure. ♪
Now I know our claims
seem fantastical...
impractical,
improbable,
impossible...
And magical!
So we welcome every
suffering pony
to make their way
up to the stage.
Now don't crowd.
And we'll prove our
tonic's effectiveness
before your very eyes!
You there! Come
up here, good sir.
I'll wager you're tired of
those crutches, my friend.
Try taking a sip of this!
(astonished gasps)
♪ That's why you're so lucky! ♪
♪ We've got the thing for you ♪
♪ Just come on up, we've
always got some more! ♪
♪ of the Flim Flam Miracle
Curative Tonic ♪
♪ I won't need these crutches
to dance out the door! ♪
Now, how do you like that?
I don't.
There's something funny
about this whole thing.
♪ Now some of you may suffer
from feelings of despair ♪
♪ You're old, you're tired,
your legs won't work ♪
♪ There's greying in your hair ♪
♪ Just listen; I'll tell you
that you don't need to fear ♪
♪ Your ears will work,
your muscles tone ♪
♪ Your eyes will see so clear! ♪
♪ Luckily for us you've
got the thing we need! ♪
♪ The answer to our
problems in a jar ♪
♪ The Flim Flam Miracle
Curative Tonic ♪
♪ It's the greatest ever
miracle by far! ♪
♪ Tonic! Tonic! Tonic! ♪
It cures the Reins, the
spurs and clydesdale fur blight
Hooferia and horsyntary,
cured in just a night!
You've got swollen
hooves and hindquarters
or terrible bridle bit cleft.
Saunter sits and gallop plop,
or give your tail some heft.
Mane loss, Hay Fever,
or terrible tonsillitis.
You heard it here folks, this
is the only place in all of
Equestria you'll find it.
♪ It can make you short or
tall or even grow old. ♪
♪ But who'd want that?
When with one drink, ♪
♪ you can be young again... ♪
SOLD!
Congratulations, Granny Smith.
You've just made the
purchase of a lifetime!
Are you as
worried as I am?
Yep.
(splash)
Ah! I just can't
believe all the things
that Flim Flam tonic can do.
When somepony says something's
too good to be true,
it usually is.
You mean Granny
wasted her money?
Well, I don't know about that,
but I don't think there's a
tonic in Equestria that can
make an old pony young again.
Granny: Howdeee!
♪ (old time piano) ♪
Granny?
Hang on now! We'll get you!
(splash)
♪ (old time piano) ♪
(crash)
Granny, I thought you were too
afraid of the water to swim!
And what about your hip?
Well, I reckon it might have
been a problem before I had
myself a dose of that
there Flim Flam Tonic.
I'm not so sure that tonic
really does anything.
Doesn't do anything?
What do you call this?
(slurp)
(giggling)
I'm glad you're
feeling good,
but how do you know
it's from the tonic?
Well, I looked out at
the water this morning
and I felt the same terrifying
aches and pains I always do,
but one sip of that magic
elixir and it all went away.
Why, I might even get a
head start on my chores.
What do you say, Big Macadoo?
Up for a little
afternoon apple bucking?
Uh, nope.
Aw, quit yer belly aching!
Gee, it looks like that
tonic works after all.
I wonder what's in it.
I think maybe it's
time we found out.
So, you're just gonna walk
up and ask them how it works?
I guess, though if
it's a genuine cure,
I don't suppose they'll be too
keen on sharing the recipe.
(crowd noises)
♪ ...to walk out the door! ♪
Wait a second!
That's that same
pony from before!
Hey!
♪♪
Now hold it right there, Mr...
Sh-sh-Shill.
Silver Shill.
W-w-what do you two want?
Our Granny took some tonic and
we want to know how it works.
Granny couldn't swim
before and now she can.
Just like you couldn't
walk and now you can.
But what are you
doing back here?
I mean, if the tonic
cured you and all?
(gulp)
Because he's part of the act.
It's time for you
to tell the truth.
You never needed
crutches at all, did you?
I... uh.
(whistle)
Hey!
Huh?
Well, if it isn't our
most favorite Apple!
What brings you back
to our humble abode?
You two charlatans sold my
Granny a bottle of tonic
and now she's off acting
like a filly again.
What's so bad about that?
If she keeps gallivanting
around like a yearling,
she's apt to drop from
exhaustion or worse.
What's more, I know for a
fact that your friend here
is dressing up as a
different pony every night
so he can pretend to be cured.
Well, that's quite
an accusation.
But let's say
that it's true.
Hypothetically.
Theoretically.
As I understand, your Granny
was a famous aqua-pony...
The star of the show,
once upon a time...
But hasn't set so much as
a hoof in the water since.
Until today.
That's right.
Well, then even if our tonic
were nothing more than a mixture
of apple juice
and beet leaves...
Hypothetically.
Theoretically.
The fact is that
Granny is happier now
than before she tried it.
I guess.
So, the question is...
Do you really want
to be the pony
who takes all that
happiness away?
I...
There you are!
I've been looking
all over.
Did you find out
what's in the tonic?
Honestly, Apple Bloom,
as long as it works,
I don't suppose
it really matters.
Well, if it doesn't
matter to you,
then it doesn't matter
to me either, sis.
That's the spirit!
Come back anytime!
Hey Granny, think you can
buck me over the water?
I don't see why not.
Come on, Big Mac,
toss her this way.
Granny, wait!
Whoo hoo hoo!
(laughing)
What were you saying, dear?
Granny, don't you think you
should take it kinda easy?
I've been taking it
easy for too long
and now, thanks to that Flim
Flam tonic, I don't have to.
Granny, do you think I could
be an aqua-pony like you?
Of course you can, sapling.
There's nothing to
it but to do it.
Well, the Ponyville
swim meet is coming up.
We could enter together.
A legendary water
pony like you?
We'd be a cinch to win.
Hmmm. I don't know.
Being back in the
water is one thing,
but a competition is a
pony of a different color.
Oh. OK.
I don't know, Granny.
A swim meet sounds pretty safe.
And after all, if that tonic
lets you swim in a river
and a swimming hole, a pool
should be no problem at all.
Well, I'll be a tart
turnover, you are right!
All we need now is
more tonic!
Welcome friends
and step right up!
The next show starts
in five minutes.
But why not buy your tonic
now and avoid the rush?
Right this way,
good sir.
Granny: We'll take
the whole case!
(clunk)
Are you saying this
stuff actually works?
It seems to work for Granny.
You heard it here first, folks.
Flim Flam Miracle Curative
Tonic is Granny Smith tested
and Applejack approved!
If Applejack says it works,
that's good enough for me!
(cheers and clamouring)
(nervous sigh)
♪♪
(splash)
Hoo ha hee hee! Ha hoo ha!
Just remember you two,
the most important thing
is to be safe and have
fun. Right?
Fiddlesticks!
With the routine we've
been working on,
I'll be a plum pudding if
we don't win this thing.
Uh...
Good luck, then.
Luck?
(scoff)
Who needs luck?
We've got tonic on our side.
Flim Flam's Magical
Curative Tonic!
Get your Applejack
approved tonic!
Granny Smith drinks
it, why shouldn't you?
(cheers)
(sigh) Right.
Granny: Now if you'll excuse us,
we've got some swimming to do.
♪ (classical) ♪
♪♪
(cheers)
Well, I'll be.
That was some of the most
amazing aqua-batics
I've ever seen.
How in Equestria did you do it?
Hard work? Lots of practice?
Yeah, but mostly it's the tonic.
That's Flim Flam's Miracle
Curative Tonic, to be precise.
Buy it now, while
supplies last.
(clicking cameras)
(clamouring)
What are you
doing here?
Things are going so well, Flim
and Flam gave me a promotion.
Just made my first
bit as a salespony.
No more costumes
for this pony.
This is more of
a uniform.
If you say so.
I used to wonder if I was
doing the right thing,
pretending to be cured,
basically lying to
folks about this tonic,
but thanks to you, I realized
that sometimes honesty
isn't the best policy.
Thanks to...
me?
With Film Flam's
Magical Curative Tonic,
my Granny can do anything!
Just ask Applejack.
(clicking cameras)
No! This has gotta stop!
If ponies keep believing that
tonic can do things it can't,
who knows what will happen?
Maybe something
like that?
(gasp)
Granny!
What in blazes does
she think she's doing?
Granny's going to break the
Equestria high diving record.
Land sakes!
(panting)
(spring board)
(gasp)
Now, what in tarnation
did you do that for?
That was the most
fool-pony thing
I've ever seen anypony
do in all my life.
You can't do a dive like that!
Aw, quit your fussin'.
I had enough tonic to do
a dive ten times as high.
Twenty times by
my count.
Thirty with a
favorable breeze.
♪ (celestial) ♪
I hate to disappoint
everypony,
but there's no way Granny
could have made that dive
because this
tonic is a fake.
(group gasp)
But you gave it your
stamp of approval!
Are you saying you lied?
I am.
(gasp)
I didn't mean to.
But everypony seemed
so much happier,
I couldn't bring
myself to tell you
when I found out the
tonic wasn't real.
I know it was wrong.
I just hope, with time, I can
win back everypony's trust.
But if the tonic is a fake then
how come Granny can swim again
and what about all that
aqua-batic stuff we just did?
I reckon sometimes you can
forget what you're capable of
and it just takes a little
extra confidence to remember
that it was inside
of you all along.
But telling ponies your tonic
can do things it can't
is just wrong!
But you just said it
boosts confidence!
And that's not all it
does, folks--
Yes it is!
In fact, it's not
a tonic at all.
I know because I
helped make it.
Watching Applejack save Granny
and then admit to lying,
well, that made me realize
I was making ponies believe
in a thing that
just wasn't so.
Believing in something can
help you do amazing things,
but if that belief
is based on a lie,
eventually it's going to
lead to real trouble.
Thank you, Applejack.
I got this through
dishonest means.
That was a mistake I
won't be making again.
I'd like you to have it.
As a reminder of how you helped
me finally see the truth.
I don't know.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll track down the pony I
sold that worthless tonic to
and give them another bit
to replace this one.
Honest.
I'm sorry, Granny.
I hope this doesn't mean
you'll stop swimming.
Why in tarnation
would I do that?
I just can't believe
those two salesponies
had me believing
I could near fly.
Hey, where'd they go?
Being honest sure gets hard
when it seems like the truth
might hurt somepony
you care about.
But I think believing a lie
can end up hurting even more.
Maybe someponies don't
care about that...
But I sure ain't one of them.
Now, you take it
easy, there, Granny.
Oh, I plan to.
Whee!
(splash)
(giggling)
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪