♪♪
(muffled conversation)
♪ (mounting tension) ♪
♪♪
(muffled conversation continues)
Whatever they decide, Apple
Bloom, we'll be here for you.
Totally.
Even though it could
change everything for you!
Forever! And ever!
(rattling)
(creak)
♪ (military snare drum) ♪
So.
We here have decided...
That you're old enough
to stay home alone
and take care of the chores
yourself for the afternoon.
(happy gasp)
I accept your decision.
♪ (snare drum) ♪
(happy shouts)
I'm staying home alone!
Whoo hoo!
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
♪ (banjo) ♪
Staying home alone.
By myself! On my own!
(crash)
(falling whistle)
I can't believe I'm
really doing it!
Now, hey there, filly.
I know you're excited.
But bein' the only pony here to
take care of the day's chores
is a big responsibility.
I know it!
And it means everything
to me that ya'll think
I'm grown up enough
to handle it.
I won't let you down!
Well, if'n I'm gonna make
my train, I best to be off.
When Great-Aunt Pine Apple
says a pony's gots to arrive
by a certain time, you
better be there!
You be sure and take
care now, Apple Bloom.
Y'all take care as well.
I don't know which of your
delivery routes is tougher.
You're each headed to a
mighty hard-to-reach town.
Yup.
We know, Granny.
That's the only reason I
agreed to let Apple Bloom
stay behind alone.
It is?
Oh, I didn't mean it
like that, Sugar Cube.
It's just, I take my job as
your big sister real serious.
Which is why I spent
all night making this.
What is it?
Just a little list
of helpful reminders.
"There's some soup for
you in the fridge."
"Be sure not to heat
it up too much."
"If its hot, blow on
it to cool it off."
"And take little sips;"
"if you gulp, you
could get hiccups."
You don't have to
worry about me.
I can take of myself
and the chores.
I'm ready for this!
(sigh) I guess you are.
I'm just not so sure I am.
But you trust me and believe I'm
grown up enough to handle this,
right?
(sigh) Right.
OK, then.
Good luck, little sis.
(thud)
(fast) OK great! see
you soon. Bye!
♪♪
All at once: Goodbye! So
long!See ya! Bye now!
♪♪
♪ (rising violins) ♪
Woo-hoo!
I'm alone!
At home!
I'm home alone!
This is going to be so AWESOME!
♪♪
(chattering)
(thud)
Heh heh.
Sorry, Big Mac.
I was just frettin' a
bit about Apple Bloom.
You think she's gonna
be OK on her own?
Yup.
I just keep on thinking
of things I forgot
to put on her list.
Like, I didn't write down that
if she wants to get a spoon
out of the drawer, she needs
to open the drawer first.
I know I'm probably
just being silly.
Yup.
But I know I'd feel a heap
better if I could just
check on Apple Bloom
one last time.
You go on ahead and
make your delivery.
I'm just gonna take quick
peek and then I'll make mine.
Apple Bloom: OK, number 172.
"Make sure to pump the bellows
to keep the stove warm."
(whoosh whoosh whoosh)
Check!
"Make sure the Hats and Bows
closet is fully stocked."
Check!
That's everything
on Applejack's list.
And now that my chores are done,
since there's no one else here,
I get to make all the decisions!
If I want to listen
to music, I can!
If I want to read a book, I can!
If I wanna just stand here in
the kitchen talking to myself,
I can!
Gah!
Apple Bloom!
Whoa!
(crash)
(clatter)
(sigh) Applejack?
I came back to check on you.
And I am so glad I did!
I never thought about how
dangerous things are
around here.
Thanks. But I'm
really gonna be OK.
You are now.
Because I'm here,
and I'm staying!
No way am I leaving
my little baby sister
home alone all by herself!
I'm not a baby!
I can take care of myself.
And what about those pies
you're supposed to deliver?
Pies? Ha. Family's way
more important than pies.
But I'm fine.
And actually, this was
kind of your fault.
I know.
I should never have
left you alone.
But I don't need you
looking after me.
I'm perfectly capable
of staying home alone.
Really!
Just look!
"There's some soup for you
in the fridgerator."
What was that?
Watch me.
(clatter)
(splat)
Whoa!
Oh, no!
This is worse than I thought!
Well, don't worry Apple Bloom.
I'm here now and I'm not leaving
you home alone ever again.
I'm sticking right
by your side, always!
♪♪
♪ (banjo) ♪
Apple Bloom?
Apple Bloom!
Applejack's just
over reactin' a bit.
I'm sure she'll snap out of it.
Whoa!
You need something?
I'm right here!
I know you mean well, but I
don't need you watching over me.
I can take care
of things myself.
(laugh)
Look!
♪♪
Huh?
Hey! Who put pillows
on this rake?
(chuckle) Oh, I don't know.
Maybe someone who really
loves her little sister
and doesn't want her
to get an owie?
(growl)
Hey, Applejack, watch me buck
these apples on my own
without anything bad
happening to me.
(grunt)
(rustling)
Huh?
(growl)
Agh! For the love of...!
You've gone and
baby-proofed everything!
(chuckle) Yup!
Your big sister
let you down once.
But I promise it won't
ever happen again!
But really, I'm fine.
I can take care of myself.
I don't need you
watching over me.
Aw, that's sweet.
I appreciate you trying
to make me feel better.
But don't worry; I'll
ALWAYS be here for you!
Always!
(growl turning to a scream)
(sigh)
And that's the reason I asked
y'all to come over quick.
Applejack: Hey, Apple Bloom,
you need anything?
A snack? A hoof massage?
Maybe a snack while
havin' a hoof massage?
Why that sounds delightful!
No thank you!
OK, well, you can count
on me being closeby
if'n you need anything.
(slam)
Whew!
You see what I mean?
If this keeps up, I'm never
going to be able to do anything
without Applejack
hoverin' over me!
Mm hm.
So what can we do?
Hmmm... Uh...
Hang on a sec!
I got it!
What?
The pies!
I'll sneak out
and deliver them!
Granny said they were going
to some incredibly
hard-to-reach town.
If I can do it alone,
that'll show Applejack
I don't need somepony
watchin' over me!
Just one problem: your
sister's gonna come back
and check on you any minute!
Which means you
need an escape plan!
Oooh! And I got
an idea for one.
(snoring)
See? It'll look just like
you're sleeping in bed.
Sweetie and I can take turns.
That way, when one of us gets
tired, the other can take over.
Brilliant, huh?
You know what?
It is!
I got a feelin' this
just might work!
♪ We're gonna make my
sister see ♪
♪ I don't need her
watchin' over me! ♪
Stop!
(hoof sounds)
No time for a song!
Applejack's coming!
If you're going to go, we've
got to get you out of here now!
Cutie Mark Crusaders!
Let's do it!
Whoa!
(thud)
(clattering wheels)
Everything all right
in there, Sugar Cube?
Quick! Get in while I hide!
Sweetie, No!
You gotta sleep
like Apple Bloom!
How does she sleep?
Like she does
everything. With sass!
Huh.
I guess you must've
been so tuckered out
you sent your friends
home and went to bed.
Then again, you are
a delicate flower.
Sleep tight, Apple Bloom.
I'll check on you
again in a bit.
(door closes)
(relieved sighs)
Just checking in on you again.
(door closes)
Need anything now?
How about now?
Need another blanket?
Did I hear a cough?
Want a glass of water?
(clock ticking)
(snoring)
(door opens)
(Applejack yawns)
Just checkin' in on you again.
(sigh) Look at you, dozin'
so peaceful-like.
Here I am, checkin' up on ya
every five seconds.
And you're totally fine.
Maybe you don't need me
frettin' over you all the time.
(excited gasp)
Wow! Apple Bloom will be
so glad to hear that!
Huh?
Scootaloo?
Uh, no.
Sweetie Belle?
But where's Apple Bloom?
She's not here!
She could be anywhere!
She could be lost, cold,
hungry, itchy, stuffed up,
needin' to go to the bathroom!
Don't worry. We know
exactly where she is.
Yeah. She's making
your pie delivery.
What? No!
Didn't she hear how difficult
and dangerous it was?
(horrified gasp)
I may never see my
little sister again!
OK, Rarity's on her way here
to look after you two.
Now tell me, did Apple Bloom at
least bring flame-proof boots?
A lion tamer's chair?
A snake-charming flute?
A hunk of ricotta?
(gasp)
OK.
Maybe there's still time to
catch her before she gets there.
When did she leave?
It must have been hours ago.
Oh no!
♪ (eerie) ♪
♪♪
I can't see a darn
thing in this swamp.
Ah!
(whoosh)
Well, now at least I can see.
(low growl)
(whoosh)
I'd stay where you are.
This is the only safe
spot around here.
It don't look
so safe to me.
Oh, we just mean
from the flames.
Yeah, not from us.
What was that?
Can you guys sssspeak up?
I was about to tell our guest
how we haven't eaten in days.
My sisters and I can never
agree on what to eat!
(hiss)
Except pie.
Well, unfortunately, I got to
get these pies to a town
on the other side of
the swamp. So uh...
Oh, you don't have
to worry about that.
Yeah, you don't have to
worry about anything anymore.
Because we're gonna
have our apple pie
with a sssside
of filly filet!
You don't say.
(nervous laugh)
(growling/bleating/hissing)
Now sisters, on three.
One.
Two!
(hiss)
Three!
(clattering hooves)
(skid)
No!
Where do you think you're going?
(threatening growls)
(whoosh)
(hiss)
(frightened shout)
(panicked whimpers)
Oomph!
(panting)
(grunts)
(whoosh)
♪♪
(growl/bleat/hiss)
Where are the pies?
They're not back here.
This is your fault!
You think you've always
got to be in charge.
You're lucky, you know.
You've got no idea what it's
like to have a sister
constantly looking
over your shoulder.
Uh, actually...
Let's try listening
to me for a change.
And I say: if
there are no pies,
let's settle for
the filly filet.
(hiss)
Any last words?
I really wish my
sister were here!
(hiss)
Hang on, Apple Bloom!
I'm a'comin'!
Together: Get her!
Hey, I thought I
was in charge now!
♪♪
(growl)
(hiss)
(thud)
(growl)
(roar)
(gasping)
(crunch)
Howdy!
(snap)
(smash)
(struggling grunts)
(snarl)
Mmmm. Ricotta!
(groans)
Let's go!
(whoosh)
Are you OK?
Thanks to you.
I told ya ya need your big
sister looking after you!
I'm just glad this
wasn't a whole lot worse.
I mean, sure, we lost the
cart and all the pies,
but at least you're--
The cart! And all the pies!
You actually got them all
the up way here, in the dark,
through the Flame Geyser
Swamp, past that monster?
By yourself?
Well... yeah.
Wow. That's mighty
impressive.
Anypony who can do
that on her own, well,
she don't need somepony
like me babying her.
♪ (Zydeco accordion) ♪
(splash)
Mmmmm!
Andouille!
(Cajun accent)
Dis pie's even tastier den ma
mama's swamp-water casserole!
(cheers)
Aw, now, Mama,
don't be like dat!
(excited chatter)
Just remember, you fellas
wouldn't be enjoyin' these pies
if it weren't for my sister.
And MY sister!
But this don't change the fact
that trying to make this
delivery on your own
was a plumb crazy
thing to do.
I know.
I bet Granny Smith grounds you
for a month for sneakin' out!
And if Big Mac, Granny Smith
and I ever have to be away
for the day again...
I would totally trust
you to stay home
and take care of
things on your own.
I guess I did get a little
carried away watchin' over ya,
and if ya hadn't snuck
out like you did,
maybe I wouldn't have
figured that out.
Yes! Now that is the kind
of looking out for me
I can definitely appreciate!
So we're good?
Little sister,
we're always good.
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪