♪♪
Whatcha doin'?
Aaah!
Aaah, yourself.
But that doesn't answer
my question, silly.
Just some genealogical
research.
Ohhhh.
(crash)
(whisper)I don't
know what that is.
Genealogy is the study
of family history.
You know. Where
ponies comes from,
and who they're
related to.
Ooooh. Fascinating.
Maybe you should pick
one from the...top.
Uh-huh.
Interesting.
I see.
That makes sense.
Not much of a surprise there.
WHAT?
THIS IS THE MOST
AMAZING THING EVER!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
HOW AMAZING THIS IS?
Genealogy is better
than cotton candy
on top of a fountain
of chocolate!
(crash)
You'll never believe who
it says I'm related to!
(knock on door)
Hey, cousin!
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Applejack: This is
just so excitin'!
I can't hardly
believe it!
I know! Isn't
it the best?
I have another
sister!
Well, you actually have
a fourth cousin
twice removed by a
fifth cousin,
but that's like,
exactly like a sister.
I try to tone it down a little
bit around non family members,
because I don't want to
make them jealous, but...
THIS IS THE
BEST FAMILY EVER!
(boing)
It really is.
You are going to
LOVE being an Apple.
I mean, you've got
the playful one...
(boing)
(crash)
The strong one...
EYUP!
(splat)
And of course,
there's Granny Smith
who knows everything
about everything.
A Ponyville snail can
hibernate for up to 48 moons.
Who knew?
And then there's me.
(inhale and sigh)
You smell that sweet
apple air, Pinkie Pie?
(sniff)
That was rhetorical.
Of course, you smell it.
You're an Apple now.
And Applejack is the
one responsible for it!
Aw, Apple Bloom
that is sweet but--
It's true!
I mean she keeps us all
organized and on schedule
and does her own part
on top if it all!
Mm hm!
I was already super
happy as a Pie.
And now I get to be a part
of this amazing family too?
It's even more amazing
now that you're in it!
♪ We're family!
We're family! ♪
♪ You and me are family! ♪
BEST FAMILY TWIRL EVER!
(crash)
I just can't believe we
never heard anything
about this before.
Hmmm.
What's wrong, sis?
I'm not seein' where exactly
it says we're family.
It's riiiiiiiiiiiight....
...here!
It is?
Uh-huh.
Applesauce of the Apple family
lineage is a fourth cousin
twice removed of the Pie family.
I see the part about our Great,
Great Auntie Applesauce
and fourth cousin
twice removed part,
but that last bit's
awful smudged.
Are you sure it says "Pie"?
I guess it is a
little smudged.
But I see most of it there,
and when I read it, I knew
in my heart it was true.
Well, ain't that just
the sweetest thing.
It is, it is.
I'd just hate for us
to get all excited
before we found
out for sure.
So how are we supposed
to find out for sure?
Cousin Goldie Delicious!
Her cabin's practically an
Apple family history museum.
If anypony has the records
to back up Pinkie's theory,
it's her!
I suppose we could always...
I mean Goldie Delicious doesn't
live all that far away...
And we haven't been on one as
a family in a real long time...
Are y'all thinkin'
what I'm thinkin'?
FAMILY ROAD TRIP!
Has anypony seen my
travelin' bonnet?
Isn't that it on your head?
No.
It looks an
awful lot like--
Well, it's ain't.
And that's final.
Hey everypony?
Since Pinkie Pie is back home
gettin' her stuff for the trip,
can y'all gather round?
I just wanted to say
something real quick.
I've had somethin' in my teeth
this whole time, haven't I?
Gadsnickety, what a way to
welcome a family member!
Uh, no, Granny, your
teeth are fine.
I just wanted to be sure that
we're all on the same page
about showin' Pinkie Pie how
awesome a family we really are.
We want her to get to know the
family she's been born into!
But like, the best
version of it, you know?
Oh! Don't you worry, honey!
We're a great family and
she can't help but see it.
I bet my future cutie mark's
gonna be a picture of me
being the best
behaved pony ever.
(crash)
That's how good
I'm gonna be!
Big Mac?
Eyup!
Pinkie: Are you all
ready to go?
Because I'm ready
to go go go!
Uh, Big Mac, are you sure we
really need all that stuff?
Eyup.
Are you sure you're
strong enough
to really pull
all that stuff?
Eyup!
Are you sure the wagon's
strong enough to hold it all?
Eyup.
Then let's get this
show on the road!
(squeaking and clanging)
Come on Apples, y'all
know this one, yeeeeehaw!
Eyup!
We travel the road
of generations, ♪
♪ Joined by a common bond ♪
♪ We sing our song cross
the pony nation ♪
♪ From Equestria and beyond ♪
♪ We're Apples forever
Apples together ♪
♪ We're family but
so much more ♪
♪ No matter what comes
we will face the weather ♪
♪ We're Apples to the core! ♪
♪ Eyup! ♪
♪ There's no place
that I'd rather be ♪
♪ than travelling
with my family ♪
♪ Friends all around
come to join and see ♪
♪ As we sing out
across the land ♪
♪ We're Apples forever
Apples together ♪
♪ We're family but
so much more ♪
♪ No matter what comes
we will face the weather ♪
♪ We're Apples to the core! ♪
♪ We're peas in a pod
We're thick as thieves ♪
♪ Any cliche you
can throw at me! ♪
♪ We're here for each other
through thick and thin ♪
♪ You're always welcome
with your Apple kin! ♪
♪ Wheee! ♪
♪ You're more fun
than the color pink ♪
♪ Or balloons flying over
your favorite drink ♪
♪ The love I feel here
is swim not sink ♪
♪ As we party
across this land ♪
♪ We're Apples forever
Apples together ♪
♪ We're family but
so much more ♪
♪ No matter what comes
we will face the weather ♪
♪ We're Apples to the core! ♪
(song ends)
(crash)
Big Mac!
I thought you said--
(stops herself)
I thought, I mean, not
that I'm blaming you,
because we don't blame
in this family,
but I thought you
said all this stuff
wasn't gonna be too heavy.
How are we supposed to get
to Goldie Delicious now?
I don't know, but I don't see
how we can go back now either.
We're closer to cousin
Goldie's than we are to home.
I have the best...
idea...
ever!
FAMILY RIVER TRIP!
Ha. Just one problem.
We haven't got a raft.
About the only thing
that didn't get packed.
Well, back in the old days
we used to use the sap
from a sugar pine tree
to glue things together.
That is, uh, fascinatin'.
Don't know that it's helpful,
but it is fascinatin'.
Not helpful, my patooty!
We're gonna build
ourselves a raft
outta these here jalopy parts
and keep it held together
with sugar pine sap.
Hm. Worth a shot.
Whoo hoo!
(crash)
Could be worse. I guess.
Now remember, this time we're
only packin' the necessities.
Wait a second!
(poof)
This one is for
the scrapbook.
Applejack: Pinkie Pie, when did
you have time to make this?
Applejack, when you're
family, you make the time.
Woo-hoo!
We did it!
Say "Soaked!"
(whoosh)
So what you're saying is, if
I have the courage to jump,
the parachute will open.
Eyup!
Whoa! That is deep.
Eyup.
Uh-oh.
All right, y'all.
Please tell me that the
map didn't get wet.
'Cause it looks like I'm
gonna need it right about now.
Found it!
♪ Who's got the map?
I got the map. ♪
♪ M to the A to the,
that's right, P. ♪
♪ Ain't no other pony
find a map like me. ♪
I'm Apple-- Uh-oh.
(gasp)
Oh!
(splash)
(snap)
(embarrassed laugh)
All you had to do
was bring it to me.
No singin', no
dancin', no games.
Just walk it over.
Eyup.
Say, "Best siblings ever!"
That's another keeper!
Granny: It's OK, y'all!
I traveled down this
river as a filly
and I know it like
the back of my hoof!
Are you sure you
know which way to go?
Does a june bug like
to hide in a tree?
I don't know.
Well, I do know.
And I also know we
wanna head Southeast.
Now step aside, young 'un.
Um, Granny?
Uh huh?
Are we supposed to
go through a cave?
Don't worry, child.
The scariest cave in Equestria
was down that other way.
The scariest cave
in Equestria?
Oh, it's a fright
all right.
Filled with creatures that'll
eat ya soon as look at ya.
Oooh! Sounds scary.
Tell us more.
Granny: Ponies go in.
But they never come out.
And you're sure
it's not that cave?
The one we're
headin' straight for?
Now Applejack, I
taught you better
than to question
your elder ponies.
You sure did.
All righty, then.
Now everypony just sit on back
and leave the steerin'
to your old Granny Smith.
♪ (scary music) ♪
Granny: See now. Told
you this was--
(screams)
(camera shutter)
Pinkie: Got it!
(frightened shouts)
Pinkie: Best scary
unidentifiable creature ever.
(ferocious roars)
Pinkie: Say "Terrified!"
(screams)
♪ (cheerful humming) ♪
Guess that was the scariest
cave in Equestria.
Of course, I meant to
take us through it.
Unexpected adventure
is good for the soul!
Best Granny
wisdom ever!
Uh-huh.
Why don't you just scooch
on over there, Granny?
Think I'll take it
from here on out.
Is that how I taught you
to treat your elder ponies?
Oooh. Oooh. Is it?
You taught me to
trust my common sense.
And my common sense says
we should get to Goldie
Delicious' cabin in one piece!
And that is exactly
what  I'm gonna do!
That is mighty
generous of you,
but I think you've done
enough for one day.
And how exactly are you
gonna know which way to go?
Hmmmmm?
It would be easier if the
map hadn't gone overboard.
Hey! There wouldn't have
been an overboard
if Big Mac hadn't
overpacked the jalopy.
Eyup. Hey!
Exactly.
So I think we can all agree
that from here on out,
I should be in
charge of everything.
(angry shouting)
(splash)
(quacking)
(squawk)
Heh heh.
I just want to say that I think
you are all super-duper
and I can't wait to make
the page in my scrapbook
about the amazing
waterfall we went down.
♪♪
(quacking)
(panicked shouts)
(screams)
Pinkie: Wheeeee!
(camera shutter clicks)
(screams)
Told ya that sugar pine sap
would hold this thing together.
(snap)
(splash)
(groans)
We're here! We're here!
We made it to
Goldie Delicious'!
You guys! There's a note!
(giggling)
Uh, Pinkie Pie?
Maybe you could read
that one out loud?
Oh right, sorry! I
haven't even read it yet,
I was just looking at
how pretty the paper is.
OK! It says that she ran
off to run some errands
but will be home soon.
Ah! That's perfect!
Why is that perfect?
Because it will
give me enough time
to get more
scrapbook paper!
See ya!
Worst family road
trip. Ever.
Eyup.
I can't believe she
witnessed our family
falling apart like this.
I can't believe I was
arguing with you so much
that I tore the
wheel right off the raft.
It's like I wasn't
myself at all.
Aw, that wasn't
your fault.
My stubborn streak got a
holda me somethin' fierce.
I shoulda let you take the
wheel long before that.
It was my fault the
map got all wet.
I was the pony..
Now now, Big Mac, you
gotta know we forgive you
for packin' the jalopy so
much that it collapsed.
You was just eager to please
Pinkie Pie like the rest of us.
Everypony, I think we have
to let Pinkie Pie know
that even if she does
discover that she's an Apple,
she does not have to feel
obliged to consider herself one.
Sure as apple sauce.
Pinkie: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
You guys are the
best family ever!
How can you say that?
We started out as one big
unit and now look at us.
Yeah! NOW look at you!
You're all here still
in one big unit,
loving each other and owning
up to what went wrong!
You never gave up, even
when things got tough!
She does make a
pretty good point.
You aren't just family,
you're best friends!
And I want to be an
Apple more than ever!
And we want you
to be one too!
Yippee! Hee hee hee!
Goldie: Now that's how
you run an errand.
HELLLLLO!
Hello, yourself.
You must be Goldie Delicious;
so nice to meet you!
And who exactly are you?
We're Apples!
Well, we think
we're all Apples.
But we need your help findin'
out if Pinkie Pie here
is our fourth cousin
twice removed.
Why didn't you say so?
If anypony can help solve this
genealogy mystery, it's me.
(grunts)
(creaking door)
I am sorry about this.
I wasn't exactly
expectin' company.
Let me try to
squeeze in here.
Get some oil ... the
hinges, heh heh heh.
All right then!
Just have to move a few things
out of the way of the door.
Ooh! Ah! Get off of
that, Mr. Puppy.
(yowling cat)
Come on, sweetheart.
Come on in!
Sorry about the mess.
(meowing)
Whoa!
Careful now.
Those belonged to your Great,
Great, Great, Uncle Apple Tart.
Whose was this?
That was my lunch.
A couple weeks ago.
And this here is the complete
record of our family tree.
It's not here, or here or here,
it certainly isn't here, is it.
Oh, here it is!
Oh dear.
"Oh dear"? What is it?
Am I not an
Apple after all?
That's just it.
I don't know!
The page is all smudged!
I sure am sorry, but I don't
think I can help you after all.
Don't be sorry.
It's OK.
I'm just a little disappointed
that I'll never know for sure
if I'm a part of this family.
Well, I know for sure!
What do you mean?
You can't know.
I can know for sure
that it doesn't matter
what the book says
or doesn't say.
After all you've
been through with us,
and all you've put up with,
it's obvious you're
an Apple to the core!
Darn tootin'!
Yes-siree!
Eyup!
Say "Best family hug ever!"
Best family hug ever!
(shutter click)
♪♪
Thanks again for
the wagon, Goldie!
See you soon!
Y'all sure you don't want
to take any of these
Apple family heirlooms
home with ya?
(clatter)
(meow)
Nope.
♪♪
♪ We're Apples forever
Apples together ♪
♪ We're family but
so much more. ♪
♪ No matter what comes
We will face the weather. ♪
♪ We're Apples to the core! ♪
Twilight agreed this was
definitely an experience
worth puttin' in the journal.
Think I'll write about
how bein' a good family
isn't about bein' perfect
as much as it is about
bein' able to get through
the rough patches together.
About bein' able to forgive
each other for mistakes.
Don't forget to mention how
really good friends
can also feel like
your family.
Eyup.
You know what?
Maybe I should write it.
I'm good at makin'
things sound excitin'.
I have a history of
excellent story telling.
I should probably
do it-- Hey!
Where in the haystack do
you think you're going
with that there pen?
(shouting)
Look at me; I'm part of the
Apply family too. I'm arguing!
Argue-argue-argue!
Bicker, bicker!
(arguing continues)
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪