♪♪
Spike: There you are, Rarity.
That's the last of your bags.
Actually Spike, I've got one
last pile of bags over there.
Won't you be a dear?
Sure. I'll be a dear.
(grunt)
An entire week in the
fabulous city of Manehattan,
plus all of my very best
friends there with me!
Of course, we'd
all come along
to support you during
Fashion Week, Rarity.
Not that you'll
need it.
We're sure
you'll win.
Ooh, I can't begin to
tell you how excited I am
that you'll all
be there with me.
However, perhaps
I can show you...
What's that?
Oh, oh, oh, I know!
A paper fan!
No.
It's a magic trick!
You know, where I pick a card
and remember what it is
and then put it back in the deck
so you can't look at it and--
These are tickets to the
hottest musical on Bridleway.
You couldn't mean
Hinny Of The Hills,
because that show's been
sold out for months...
or could you?
I could. I do.
Oh Rarity, you didn't
have to do that.
But since you did...
(cheers)
This trip is fun already!
I love jumping up and down!
Wheee!
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Aaaaahhh! ♪
♪ (upbeat) ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun. ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ My Little Ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
(train chugging)
Rarity: Come along, ponies.
I found us a place to stay only
a block from the train station,
in the very heart of
this glorious metropolis!
♪♪
Applejack: Hey, look!
There's the theater where
Hinny Of the Hills is playing!
All: Cool!
Twilight: Wow, Rarity.
How'd you manage to get us
seats for tomorrow night?
I gave some designs to
the costume designer,
so he pulled a few strings.
Cool!
Rarity: That is makes Manehattan
so splendid and amazing.
You do something
nice for somepony,
and you never know when they'll
do something nice for you.
Applejack: So then you can
do something nice for us.
Like get us in to see
Hinny Of The Hills.
Which is only the best
musical in all of Equestria!
It must be good if Rainbow
Dash is impressed.
Normally, she doesn't
even like musicals.
I know.
Ponies just bursting into
song in random places
at the drop of a hat.
Who does that?
♪ Oh Manehattan,
what you do to me. ♪
♪ Such a huge
bustling community. ♪
♪ And there's always opportunity
to do the friendly thing. ♪
♪♪
♪ If some are grouchy,
pay no mind. ♪
♪ Surprise instead with
something kind. ♪
♪ Lo-and-behold you
may just find ♪
♪ a smile is what
you'll bring. ♪
Welcome to the Mane Fair Hotel.
Please allow me to take those
bags to your room for you.
Only if you'll accept
this gratuity first.
Oh ho ho! I'll
get your change.
Do keep it all.
I insist.
♪ Generosity! I'm here to
show all that I can give ♪
♪ Generosity! I'm here
to set the bar ♪
♪ just sit back and
watch how I live ♪
After you.
Why, thank you.
Please take mine.
Wow. OK!
♪ Some may say, Rarity, ♪
♪ Don't be so
big-hearted and bold. ♪
♪ Treating strangers
like they're friends ♪
♪ This town's too
big and cold. ♪
♪ But this is how I play my
cards; I'm not about to fold. ♪
♪ Where I see a frown,
I go to town. ♪
♪ Call me the smile patrol. ♪
♪♪
♪ Oh Manehattan,
what you do to us. ♪
♪ What if you find a
Gloomy Gus? ♪
♪ It's no intimidating thing. ♪
♪ Just be kind
without a fuss. ♪
♪ Generosity! I'm here to
show all that I can do ♪
♪ Generosity! you are the key ♪
♪ Manehattan I'm
here just for you. ♪
♪ Just for you. ♪
(song ends)
To think my dresses
could soon be displayed
on the most glamorous
shopping thoroughfare
of the most glamorous
city in Equestria.
Oh! It would be my
dream come true.
Is there anything left to
do we can help you with?
Hm. Nothing I can think of.
The dresses are all
completely finished,
all made from a
fabulous new fabric
I've been developing
for months.
Stretchy but not clingy,
shimmery but not showy.
Sounds amazing.
There's nothing left for me to
do but check in at the runway
with my dresses by
two this afternoon.
That's funny, because
that clock over there
makes it seem like that's
only ten minutes from now.
(thunderclap)
(rainfall)
Oh, my ribbons and threads!
And the runway ballroom is
all the way across town.
If I don't get there,
I'm disqualified! Taxi!
Oh no! We've got to help
her find a cab now!
I'm on it.
Hey buddy, is this cab taken?
The line ends
back there, buddy!
Huh? What?
Does everypony in
this town want a cab?
I'm afraid getting a
taxi at this time
could prove almost
impossible.
Please, won't you let
her have this taxi?
She has somewhere very
important to be right away.
Not likely!
She can get in line
like the rest of us!
(angry shouts)
Oh, it's no use.
The cab drivers just
drive right past
to get to the next
pony in line.
New wheel works
like a charm.
So now which of you nice
folks are hoppin' in?
Fashion Runway Plaza
in seven minutes.
Can you make it?
Hang on!
Ta ta!
Phew! That was close.
(agreement)
Anypony else got a
sneaking suspicion
we're forgetting something?
The dresses!!
♪♪
Good afternoon. I'm
here for Fashion Week.
Everypony's gathered in front of
the runway and about to start.
So you'll just have to bring
your dresses along with you
and store them
backstage later.
My dresses? How could I
possibly forget them?
Ah! Ah! Ah!
I'm doomed!
Got 'em right
here, ma'am.
Your friends told me you
need these in a hurry
so I offered to race
them over myself.
"Anything for that
nice mare" I told 'em.
You're a life saver!
Whew! I made it!
And with seconds to spare.
Hello, everypony!
Pleased to meet you all.
Rarity, I presume?
You must be Prim Hemline,
the host of this grand event.
How do you--
Miss Rarity, how is it
that all your competitors
are here half an hour early,
and yet you arrive
seconds before we begin?
Oh, um, heh heh.
Just lucky I guess.
Once we're done here, you're
to finish setting up backstage,
so you'll be ready for your
run-through appointment.
You'll show your
designs last.
We keep to a precise schedule
so let's try to be more than
a few seconds early, hmm?
Tomorrow is the contest
to see which one of you
gets to stay to meet top
designers all across the city.
The rest of you
must go home early.
So sad.
Dismissed.
I'm so glad you
made it, Rarity.
Me too, but everything just
seems to keep working out.
Don't you remember me?
Suri Polomare, from the
Ponyville Knitter's League?
Oh! Yes of course, of course!
I thought you looked familiar
but I couldn't place it.
You haven't been
back in years.
Because I moved here to make it
in the big city. (laugh) OK?
Oh! Good for you, Suri!
It's so good to see you.
And now here we are...
Competing. (laugh) OK.
Yes, yes.
Well, good luck.
Oh, I don't need luck.
Would you like a hoof
with your things?
Why thank you so much.
My, your collection is gorgeous!
Oh now, I'm sure your
collection is equally lovely
if not more so.
It's all right, but
nothing like this!
Take my culottes, for example.
They are simply crying out
for just the right accent
but I haven't the
slightest notion where--
(gasp)
Actually, just a touch of this
fabric could be perfect with it.
Hey, would you mind terribly
if I took a swatch?
Oh, not at all.
Here, I have loads extra.
You're sure?
Positive.
Well, it's been wonderful
getting caught up
and I don't wish to be rude,
but I need to finish
my preparations
and I am a bit late
as it... is?
Hello, I'm here
half an hour early
for my run-through appointment,
just the way Prim likes.
Get in line over there.
Oh my, that fabric's gorgeous.
Did you make that yourself?
Why yes, it's...
stretchy but not clingy.
Suri: Shimmery but not showy.
And the entire line is in
this same adorable pattern
that works on everything from
skirts to tops to shoes.
(chuckle)
Bravo! I've never seen
anything like it.
You stole my fabric!
(laugh) I didn't
steal it, OK?
You gave it to me, remember?
I gave you the
fabric for accents,
not for your whole line!
And how could you possibly
make all those outfits
out of it so fast?
Fast! Ha!
Coco Pommel here took
practically forever.
Nearly got me
completely disqualified.
Well, I wanted to
make sure you'd win,
so I took the
extra time to--
Quiet!
I pay an assistant to sew and
get coffee, not talk. OK?
(sob) How could this happen?
Aw sweetie, don't
blame yourself.
It takes some small town
fillies a while to learn
it's everypony for herself
in the big city. OK?
(sobbing)
I hope you realize how fortunate
you are to have me as a mentor.
Now get me some coffee!
Twilight: Oh my gosh,
what a great afternoon!
That was almost
too much fun.
Better pace yourself, 'cause the
rest of the day is jam packed.
First, there's the
salon appointment
to get our manes done.
Then our fancy dinner
at the Far Field Tavern.
And after that?
All: Hinny Of The Hills!
(crash)
(giggling)
Is everything OK?
You got the dresses the
bellhop brought you
and everything, right?
(bawling)
But he said he brought them.
And then Suri stole them!
I let one of the
other contestants
use some of my one-of-a-kind
fabric
and then she turned it into a
wardrobe just like mine,
only now it looks like I'm
the one copying her!
My generosity has
ruined me, I tell you!
Ruined!
(bawling)
Now Rarity, whatever went wrong,
we're all here to help
you get through it.
No matter what it takes.
(shouts of agreement)
Come on, Rarity, buck up.
All we need is some fabric and
you'll be back in business.
♪♪
(gasp)
This new line is going
to be marvelous!
Perhaps even better
than the last.
It's daring! It's bold!
Perhaps I still have
a chance after all!
(happy sigh)
(humming machines)
♪♪
Twilight, sew these
pieces together
according to that
pattern there.
You said if we skipped
dinner at the Far Field Tavern,
you'd order a meal for us to
eat while we keep working.
Don't fret. It will
be here in an hour.
That's not going to
be a problem, is it?
Well...
we're supposed to be watching
Hinny Of The Hills by then.
Oh. I see.
I go out of my way to get
you tickets for a show,
and this is how you repay me?
By abandoning me
in my hour of need?
Fine! Go and see Hinny
Of The Hills tonight.
Then tomorrow morning when you
come to see my fashion show
without any fashion to show, you
can have more entertainment.
"Why look, there's our friend
Rarity going down in flames."
"Isn't friendship magic?"
Rarity, calm down.
What's gotten into you?
What's gotten
into YOU?
Go ahead, see
your little show.
Congratu-pony-lations,
fillies!
Sounds like you've all
figured out already
it's every pony for
herself in this town!
(door slams)
(machines start back up)
♪♪
There, that's the last of them.
Finally.
You're welcome.
Let's have another round of
applause for Suri Polomare's
amazing collection.
(cheers)
That fabric! So original!
(sigh)
Well, look who's here.
Going to show off your
copycat collection?
(little laugh)
And now, Rarity from Ponyville
with her brand new line...
and I mean brand
new: Hotel Chic.
♪ (techno) ♪
(excited buzz)
♪♪
They're liking it.
I think I may have
just won this thing.
Oh, I can't wait to
celebrate with...
my friends.
They didn't come.
What have I done?
(shutters clicking)
(cheers)
Rarity, they all adore you!
Aren't you going to tell them
about your fabulous pieces?
♪♪
I have to go.
Come back at once!
This is unheard of!
How do you do, ma'am?
Contest going well?
No time to talk.
I have to find my friends.
Oh. They're
gone already.
I saw them headed
out this morning.
Oh no!
Back to Ponyville, I imagine.
Oh! They worked so
hard on my behalf
and I repaid them
with unkindness.
What have I done?
Oh. Here you are.
But Miss, I
didn't do anything!
(thunder and rain)
♪♪
♪ Oh Manehattan,
what have I done? ♪
♪ The thought of
Fashion Week was fun ♪
♪ But I went way too far. ♪
♪ My friends gave to me
in ways so kind ♪
♪ And I gave them nothing
but a hard time ♪
♪ And now alone I stand
And now alone I stand. ♪
(song ends)
(desk bell rings)
I need a moment
with Prim Hemline.
I have to rush
back to Ponyville
but I just wanted to
thank her first for--
Uh oh oh. You best steer
clear of Prim for a while.
She's pretty furious.
Isn't that right?
Um...yes.
There you all are!
I can't believe it! I
thought you went back home.
We missed the show
because we overslept.
Suri told us you lost;
we're really sorry.
I lost?
You know what? I
don't even care.
I'm just happy you're all still
here after how I treated you.
Taking advantage of your
friendship the way I did.
How could you
ever see past it?
Yeah, you were
pretty rotten.
Wow, Applejack.
I know your thing is
honesty, but come on!
Last night we may not have
seen you at your best,
but we know you.
And we would never let
one thing like that
change how we
feel about you.
Oh! Thank you.
You really are the most
wonderful friends
a pony could have.
You know, I already arranged
to make it up to you
this afternoon.
Hope you're all available
for an exclusive performance
of Hinny Of The Hills.
(cheers)
And that is how it's done.
Pretty clever how I convinced
her to stay away from Prim,
wasn't it?
Wouldn't have wanted her to find
out the truth, now would we?
♪ And I'm a dancing pony! ♪
(cheers)
Wow, that was even
better than I imagined!
I LOVED IT!
Uh, I mean, it was all right.
(giggle)
How did you ever get them to
agree to do an extra performance
just for us?
Remember my costume designer
friend who got me the tickets?
Well, I offered to make all
the costumes for his next show.
Here in Manehattan?
Well, um... yes.
It will keep me away from
Ponyville for a while...
(sigh)
But I so wanted
you to see this show!
And working for this designer
is such a great opportunity.
We know.
We're happy for you, Rarity.
We're just sad for us.
Mind if I join you?
Sure. Come on down.
This is the First Place
Trophy for Fashion Week.
With my name on it.
But I thought I lost!
You didn't. You won.
Suri was hoping that if you
didn't claim your prize,
the judges would
consider it a forfeit
and first place
would go to her.
So she lied to make you and
your friends go away, and...
well, I lied, too.
I've worked for
Suri for so long,
I started to believe
that it really is
every pony for
herself in this town.
Until I saw how generous
you were with your friends.
And how generous
they were with you.
It made me start believing
there was something
better for me out there.
So I, I quit.
I brought you something
to say thank you.
I suppose you'll need a job now
that you're no longer with Suri.
How would you like to
work for my friend
making all the costumes
for his next show?
Manehattan was simply grand.
It was in this magnificent
metropolis that I learned
that while there are ponies
who will take advantage
of your generosity,
you should never, ever
let that cause you
to abandon your
generous spirit.
Nothing feels worse
than taking advantage
of the giving nature
of your friends.
♪♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪