( Apple Bloom groaning )
Oh, what to wear?
What to wear?
Scoot your boot, Apple Bloom.
It's not like it's
the Harvest Day Parade.
We're just going
to the train station.
Oh, too casual.
Too summery.
Your cousin isn't gonna care
what you're wearing.
Just pick something.
This is my first time
meeting her.
And she's from Manehattan.
I want to make
a good impression.
You know what would make
a good impression?
What?
Being on time to pick her up!
Ah...
( Apple Bloom groans )
You got nothing to worry about,
sugar cube.
Y'all are gonna
get along great.
You already have
something in common.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
Neither of you have
your Cutie Mark.
What?! How could you forget to
tell me something like that?
Well, I--
Oh, this changes everything.
Meet you at
the train station.
I gotta tell Sweetie Belle
and Scootaloo.
You know your cousin
is supposed to sleep in here!
♪ My Little Pony
My Little Pony ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ You have my little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
( ponies giggling )
You really think
she'll want to join?
She doesn't have
her Cutie Mark.
Of course she'll want to join
the Cutie Mark Crusaders.
I'm just so excited
I could burst.
( train whistles )
Is that the train
from Manehattan?
Yep.
That's her! Oh, wait,
no, no, that's not her.
Oh, wait. No, that's her.
Um, no. Wait.
That's not her either.
Apple Bloom, you've never
met Babs Seed, remember?
Oh, heh-heh, yeah.
Ah, that's her.
Babs! Babs!
It's me, your cousin,
Apple Bloom.
And this is Sweetie Belle.
And this is Scootaloo.
And we are so, so,
so glad you're here.
Thanks, I'm happy to--
This is going to be
the best week of your life.
Sure hope it's gonna be--
Seriously, we are
gonna have a blast.
( chuckles )
SWEETIE BELLE:
The Summer Harvest Parade
is going on while you're here.
We get to ride in a float.
Really? I've never been
on a float before.
And we've got a really big
surprise for you.
Yeah. Uh, a surprise?
APPLE BLOOM:
I give you...
...the Cutie Mark Crusaders
Clubhouse.
BABS:
The Cutie Mark Crusaders?
A club devoted to helping ponies
get their Cutie Marks.
We're its founding members.
Technically,
we're its only members.
But we're always
looking to expand
and you seem like
the perfect candidate.
I do?
Well, yeah.
Since you don't have
a Cutie Mark and all.
Oh. Yeah. That.
Allow me to show you just
some of the highlights
of our clubhouse, should
you choose to join us.
This is where
we do our roll call.
Huh.
APPLE BLOOM:
This is where
we eat our lunch.
Sometimes we stand here
and think up great ideas.
Yeah. Uh...
Uh, could you excuse us
for a moment?
Sure.
Thought she'd be
more impressed.
She's from Manehattan.
If we want to impress her
we need to really wow her.
ALL:
Hmm...
Ah! The float.
She can ride with us on our
Summer Harvest Parade float.
That's perfect.
This really is a good spot
for thinking up great ideas.
ALL:
Mm-hm.
APPLE BLOOM:
Here it is.
The official Cutie Mark
Crusaders float
for the Summer
Harvest Parade.
As a member of
the Cutie Mark Crusaders
you'd be able to ride
on it with us.
It'd be totally fun.
Uh...
More like funny...
BOTH:
Looking! Ha-ha-ha!
What is that thing?
A giant orange?
( both laugh )
It's a pumpkin.
More like a lame-kin.
( laughs )
Who's the new blank flank?
She's my cousin, Babs.
She's from Manehattan.
Manehattan, huh?
Well, I guess you have
that going for you.
Suppose you're gonna join
their little club?
What's it called?
The Cutie Mark Crusaders.
( tense theme playing )
( puffs air )
More like
the Cutie Mark Crybabies.
( chuckles )
Hey!
Ooh. Big city attitude.
I like it.
Mm-hm.
Oh, yeah? Well, there's more
where that came from.
Check this out. Unh!
Oh, no, she didn't.
( all laughing )
( creaking )
( dramatic theme playing )
Looks like somepony's pumpkin
just got squashed.
( both laugh )
When I tell Applejack--
You gonna tell
Applejack what?
Well, you know, uh...
What are you, a snitch?
Come on, Babs.
You should hang with us.
You know, the cool ponies.
Not these babies.
What just happened?
I think Babs just
went to the dark side.
We have to tell Applejack.
No. We're not snitches.
Yeah.
And we're not babies.
Then why do I
feel like crying?
I still can't believe
she ruined our pumpkin float.
I'm related to such
a big stinking bully.
What are we going to do?
We're gonna build a new float,
that's what.
Why bother?
She'll probably just
ruin that one too.
( groans )
We could always
tell Applejack.
What are you, a snitch?
BOTH:
No!
We're not gonna be
a bunch of tattletales.
Besides, she's only here
a couple of weeks.
We'll just avoid her like
the plague until she goes home.
Avoid her. Yeah.
How hard can that be?
ALL:
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ First we thought that Babs
Was so really, really sweet ♪
♪ A new friend to have ♪
♪ And it seemed like
Such a treat ♪
♪ But then we found the truth ♪
♪ She's just a bully
From the east ♪
♪ She went from Babs, yeah
To a bully and a beast ♪
♪ Everywhere we turn
She's just a step ahead ♪
♪ Babs Seed, Babs Seed
What we gonna do? ♪
♪ Got a bully on our tail ♪
♪ Gotta hide
We gotta bail ♪
♪ Babs Seed, Babs Seed
If she's after you ♪
♪ Gotta run
We gotta flee ♪
♪ Gotta hurry
Don't you see ♪
♪ Babs Seed, Babs Seed
She's just a bad, bad seed ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Hiding from a bully
We know it isn't right ♪
♪ But the Cutie Mark Crusaders ♪
♪ We aren't lookin'
For a fight ♪
♪ Oh, she'll go home soon ♪
♪ And then we'll have
Some peace again ♪
♪ But for now we're stayin'
Out of her way till then ♪
♪ Everywhere we turn
She's just a step ahead ♪
♪ Babs Seed, Babs Seed
What we gonna do? ♪
♪ Gotta a bully on our tail
Gotta hide, we gotta bail ♪
♪ Babs Seed, Babs Seed
If she's after you ♪
♪ You gotta run
We gotta flee ♪
♪ Gotta hurry
Don't you see ♪
♪ Why so mean? ♪
♪ Why so crude? ♪
♪ Why so angry? ♪
♪ Why so rude? ♪
♪ Can't you be nice? ♪
♪ Can't we be friends? ♪
♪ Isn't it sad
Is this how it all ends? ♪
♪ Babs Seed, Babs Seed ♪
♪ She's just a bad, bad ♪
♪ She's just a bad, bad seed ♪
Babs may have
run us out of town,
but at least we still
have the club--
( dramatic theme playing )
Hey! What are you doing
at my clubhouse?
Your clubhouse?
This is our clubhouse!
Well, it was yours.
And now it's mine.
And mine.
That's not fair, Babs.
We never did anything to you.
And let's keep it that way.
Now scram, crybabies.
ALL ( chanting ):
Bump, bump
Sugarlump, rump!
( all laugh )
( sniffling )
( shrieking )
That Babs has really
gone too far this time.
Kicked out of
our own clubhouse.
And my own bed.
Seriously?
Super seriously.
We need to talk
to Applejack.
( ominous theme playing )
BOTH:
No!
Rarity?
BOTH: No!
Twilight?
No, no, no.
We need to fight back.
Yeah, fight back!
How are we gonna do that?
By making her the guest of honor
at the Summer Harvest Parade.
Yeah! Wait. What?
( chuckles )
When you look up "embarrassed"
in the dictionary,
her face will be there.
( Babs snoring )
SWEETIE BELLE:
Moo!
( chuckles )
( suspenseful theme playing )
APPLE BLOOM:
Are those from
the Carousel Boutique?
Yep.
Excellent.
Ooh!
Luster dust from
Sugercube Corner.
They use it for
decorating cakes.
That must be what Rarity uses
on her emergency edible boots.
SCOOTALOO:
The gears and bands for
the moving mechanism,
my tools and stuff.
Did you bring the thing?
From the place?
SWEETIE BELLE:
What's that?
Granny Smith's
kitchen timer.
What's that for?
You'll see. Heh-heh.
Come on, y'all.
Let's get to it.
We only got a few hours
before morning
and this thing
has to look so good,
Babs won't be able to resist
wanting to ride in it.
( dramatic military theme
playing )
( yawns )
Is this it?
I think we're a go.
Good, because we better
get out of here
before Babs finds us.
ALL:
Cutie Mark Crusaders, ho!
( upbeat theme playing )
Hot carrot crepes!
Get 'em here.
Get 'em hot!
( puffs air )
BABS:
Whoa!
Isn't it smashing?
No, I didn't mean smash.
I mean, isn't it a hit?
No, no hit! No hitting.
I mean---
Well, don't even think
about riding it, Babs.
( grunts )
( suspenseful theme playing )
You had your chance.
( ominous theme playing )
See you later,
Cutie Mark Crybabies.
The timer set?
Teach her to fool
with the Cutie Mark Crusaders.
Y'all are lettin' Babs ride
in your golden apple float?
Yeah.
We thought she deserved to be
the center of attention.
( all chuckle )
Well, that's just
super sweet of y'all.
Makin' Babs feel so special.
After all the heartache she's
been having in Manehattan.
Heartache?
Well, I didn't say nothing
because I didn't want her
to feel singled out,
but there's been some bullies
back in Manehattan
just been teasin' her to pieces
for her blank flank.
T-T-Teased?
B-Bullies?
Yup.
She came out to the farm
to get away from all her
problems back home.
I'm so proud of y'all.
You done a good deed.
So that's why she jumped in
when Diamond Tiara
and Silver Spoon
started giving us
a hard time.
She didn't want to be
bullied like at home
so she decided to
be a bully instead.
SWEETIE BELLE:
And now we've turned
into bullies too.
( suspenseful theme playing )
ALL:
What'll we do?
( crowd cheering )
Nice float, Babs.
Snagged it from those
whiny-baby blank flanks.
Too cool for mule, Babs.
( brays )
We gotta stop that float.
( suspenseful theme playing )
Applejack. Quick, you have--
( band playing loudly )
Huh?
Quick, you have to help us!
What?
We booby-trapped it!
Babs. Bully. Payback.
No time to explain.
We've just got to get
Babs out of that float.
( suspenseful theme playing )
PONY: Oof, my popcorn!
APPLE BLOOM: Sorry! Excuse me!
Excuse me. Ow! Whoops.
( grunts )
( dramatic theme playing )
Pinkie Pie, let us in.
( laughs )
Funny joke.
No, really.
Let us in!
Oh!
Here.
( dramatic theme playing )
( crowd yelling )
Babs, you gotta
get out of that float!
You're not getting your
float back, crybabies.
But it's booby trap--
Veggie salad!
ALL: Huh?
( crash )
Veggie salad.
Seriously?
PINKIE PIE:
Hey, don't leave me!
Ha-ha! "Leave" me!
Ha-ha-ha!
( suspenseful theme playing )
( alarm ringing )
What the--?
APPLE BLOOM:
Babs!
( tires screeching )
( dramatic theme playing )
( grunts )
Oh, sweet apple sauce!
( all groaning )
Maybe we'll get
our cutie marks
in "Stupidest Ideas
of All Time."
( shutter clicking )
Are y'all okay?
APPLE BLOOM:
Yeah, we're fine.
No sweat.
After I'd been so mean to you,
you saved me.
Uh, about that...
BABS:
I don't get it.
I saw it all happen.
You pushed me out
just when the float
was about to head
into the lake.
Except we were the reason
it was headed into the lake.
We booby-trapped the float.
You see, Babs,
we were trying
to get you back
for being a big bully.
But then Applejack told us
about how you were being
bullied back in Manehattan.
And we figured out
you were just doing it
to avoid getting
picked on in Ponyville.
But by then, we were
the ones being bullies.
And...
Oh, why does life
have to be so ironic?
Guess what we're
trying to say is...
ALL:
We're sorry.
( puffs air )
I'm sorry too.
Ah. You know, this all
could've been avoided
if y'all just came to me
in the very beginning.
That's what I
kept on saying.
So can we start over?
Definitely.
Yeah.
( upbeat theme playing )
( pounding solemn beat )
( playing upbeat rhythm )
SWEETIE BELLE:
"We, the Cutie Mark Crusaders,
"elect Babs Seed to join us
"as a sister, friend,
confidante,
"ally, bosom buddy,
gal pal,
compadre, chum of chums--"
( clears throat )
Well, you wrote this.
Oh, uh, yeah.
"Homegirl, amiga..."
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh, yes, here.
"And fellow
Cutie Mark Crusader!
"You are solemnly sworn in
here this day
"in witness
of your fellow sisters,
"friends, confidantes,
bosom buddies, compadres--"
Congratulations.
Gotta remember
to revise that.
( all laugh )
( upbeat theme playing )
( puffs air )
So you promise
you're going to start
our Manehattan branch of the
Cutie Mark Crusaders, right?
Yeah. And I promise
to keep talking
to my big sis about
the teasing back home.
Good, and if you have
any problems,
we've got your back too,
you hear?
DIAMOND TIARA:
So you're leaving, huh?
Great. Now we're stuck here
with these lame blank flanks.
Hey! That's not
how you talk to my friends.
F-Friends??
Yeah, you got a problem
with that?
Well, what if I do?
What are you gonna
do about it?
( tense theme playing )
Tell your mothers about
your bad attitudes.
I'm sure gonna miss
that bad seed.
Bad seed?
I thought y'all
were friends now?
No, see, first
we called her "Bad Seed,"
as in actually
a "bad seed."
But now she's "bad"
as in "good." Get it?
Uh... No.
( all laugh )
( train whistles )
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪