( suspenseful theme playing )
May I help you,
traveler?
Hmm.
Something drew you
to my shop.
Something powerful.
SHOPKEEPER:
Ah! You have a keen eye.
The Alicorn Amulet is one of
the most mysterious and powerful
of all the known
magical charms.
Uh, I'm afraid this
is far too dangerous--
Would you like that
gift wrapped?
♪ My Little Pony
My Little Pony ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ You have my little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
( mellow theme playing )
Don't be scared,
little friends,
Twilight is wonderful
with magic.
Anything happens to them,
Twilight, so help me...
Aw, don't worry,
Fluttershy,
Twilight's magic
has gotten a lot better
since she accidentally
crushed me and Applejack
with a giant snowball.
Of course she's good with magic,
Twilight's great with magic.
I guess I just don't want
my little friends to be scared.
Oh, oh,
look how scared they are!
( animals chittering )
I promise, Fluttershy,
nothing bad will happen to them.
I know!
( magical theme playing )
Stop! Stop!
They can't take it!
( animals whooping )
Twilight,
that looks amazing!
Whew!
That's all for now,
little ones.
Maybe we can practice again
later,
if Fluttershy says
it's all right.
( animals whooping )
Your magic
has really improved
since we came to Ponyville,
Twilight.
Princess Celestia
is gonna love it!
Thanks, Spike.
I have to be at my best
when she arrives with the
delegates from Saddle Arabia.
I can't believe she's trusting
me with the entertainment.
( crashes )
Twilight,
come quick!
It's an emergency!
( suspenseful theme playing )
Oh, you beast!
This shade of brown
should only be used for accents!
Come on, Applejack,
we've got to get her in
a nice, soothing pink! Stat!
What's going on here?
GIRL'S VOICE:
Well, well, well,
if it isn't...
Twilight Sparkle.
( gasps )
Trixie!
What's she doing here?
You call that
"great and powerful"?
( yelling )
Ooh! She's
Rainbow Wobble now!
Yeah,
ha, ha!
( yelling continues )
Good spell,
oh great and powerful Trixie!
You two, quiet!
Hey! Uh, what happened?
Get off of me!
SNAILS: Hey! Come on! Let go!
SNIPS: No, this way!
Stop picking on my friends,
Trixie!
You and I have
some unfinished business.
My magic's gotten better
since I was here last.
And I'm going
to prove it.
Me and you,
a magic duel.
Winner stays,
loser leaves Ponyville forever.
Forget it! I'd never
make a deal like that!
Hm. Your choice.
( yelling )
Trixie!
Put him down!
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Because you humiliated me!
After you showed me up
with that Ursa Minor,
I became a laughingstock.
Everywhere I went, I was
laughed at and ostracized.
I even had to take a job
on a rock farm
just to earn a living!
A rock farm!
PINKIE PIE:
Hey!
You're lucky a rock farm
would take the likes of you.
Now I want revenge.
And I'll just keep
casting spells till you agree.
Well?
What do you say?
( Rainbow Dash yells,
Pinkie Pie cries )
All right, Trixie.
Let's duel.
Excellent!
( sighs )
( grunts )
If I lose, I won't set hoof
in Ponyville again.
But if you lose,
you're the one banished
from this one-horse town.
( all gasp )
( dramatic theme playing )
Draw!
( all gasp )
( gasping )
( grunts )
( sighs, then gasps )
( sighs )
( all laughing )
Snips! Snails! Step forward!
Wh-wh-what is it, oh great
and p-p-powerful Trixie?
( wailing )
(knees knocking )
An age spell?
But...how can you
do an age spell?
That's only for
the highest level unicorns.
Well, Twilight? Give up?
( sighs )
( grunts )
Come on,
Twilight, you can do it!
( horn hums )
( humming stops )
( wailing )
Trixie is
the highest level unicorn!
( laughs maniacally )
And now it's time for you
to leave Ponyville...
forever!
That's enough,
Trixie!
You've proved
your point!
But you can't possibly expect
Twilight to leave Ponyville!
You fools!
She's already gone!
( yells )
( magical theme playing )
It's okay, guys.
I'll figure something out.
Just take care of
each other,
and keep an
eye on Trixie.
There's something strange
about her.
Twilight?
( dramatic theme playing )
( grunting )
Aargh!
It's impossible!
How could Trixie know
such advanced magic?
Without Spike,
I can't get a message to
the Princess in Saddle Arabia,
so who else do I know
who understands strange
and powerful magic?
( exotic theme playing )
Your tale of woe
Upsets me so
No wonder you're dour
It's an abuse of power
I don't know what to do,
Zecora.
I feel like
I've abandoned my friends,
but I can't take her on
horn to horn.
If you train with me
So good you'll be
I'll show you the way
To make sure she won't stay
You'll train me
in magic?
But she was doing age spells,
weather spells, you name it!
When it comes to magic
It would be tragic
If somepony licked me
Especially Trixie
You really
think I can beat her?
Mm hmm.
Okay. When do we start?
TRIXIE:
You two, hurry up
with my throne!
And you,
how long do I have to wait
for my applesauce facial?
Forget it, Trixie!
I ain't doin' nothing 'til
you let Twilight come home!
( gasps )
( laughing )
Okay! I'll do it!
Make it stop! Whoo!
I thought I told you to dance!
( groans )
Trixie's cruel magic
is ruining Ponyville-- Ow!
( whimpering )
Ooh! Somepony has to help us.
( exotic theme playing )
Aah! No noise, no sound,
No din, no fuss
Must interfere with
Your focus
Unlearn what
You have learned
Only then can victory
Be earned
( grunts )
TRIXIE'S VOICE:
Trixie is the highest level
unicorn! Ha-ha-ha!
Aah!
There is much,
Much that I can teach
But the answer you need
may still be out of reach
I'm sorry, Zecora.
I'm trying my best, but I can't
stop thinking about Trixie.
There was something different
about her.
It's like she's gone from
high-and-mighty
to mean-and-nasty.
Your thinking needs a readjust
Total concentration is a must
( dramatic theme playing )
( scoffs )
This doesn't seem to be
getting us anywhere.
( muffled whimpering )
I hear ya, Pinkie.
I can't find anything
that describes the kind
of magic Trixie's doin'.
Ah, there must be something.
Twilight has
every magic book there is.
Um, I think I may have found
something--
Yes, it's time for us
to consider our futures
in this new
Trixie-led Ponyville.
This sounds an awful lot
like Trixie's magic--
She wants me to grow
apples with no peels!
Now how the hay
am I supposed to do that?
Um, there's a picture here
of that necklace Trixie wears--
( muffled shouting )
It's called
the Alicorn Amulet
and whoever wears it
is blessed with untold--
Hey, everypony, look.
This book has a picture
of Trixie's necklace.
It's called
the Alicorn Amulet
and whoever wears it
is blessed with untold powers.
If you read a little further,
you'll see--
Even though it provides
great power,
it also corrupts the user.
Yes, but, um, you can't--
You can't just take
the Alicorn Amulet off her neck.
It has a magical lock.
Trixie's the only pony
who can take it off.
Maybe we--
We need to get this information
to Twilight.
She'll know what to do.
But how--
If any of us try to leave,
Trixie's magical force field
will tell her.
Maybe we should--
I've got it.
Trying to sneak past
the force field
will be impossible
without help.
But I know who's got the goods
to get into those woods.
It must be--
Fluttershy!
What?!
What do you say,
Fluttershy?
Can you handle the mission?
No! I'll crack under
the pressure.
I'll snap like a twig.
Perfect.
Fluttershy will sneak out of
Ponyville and find Twilight.
But I-- I--
( ominous theme playing )
Ah. Okay.
All right!
Let's do it!
I know just the design for
a dangerous mission outfit.
( Snips & Snails grunting )
( grunting )
Pull, you fools.
Somepony set off
the magic force field
and Trixie intends
to punish them.
But wouldn't it be faster
if we had some wheels?
The great and powerful Trixie
doesn't trust wheels.
Now pull faster.
I'm telling you, Snips,
she's getting weirder
and weirder.
( grunting )
Stop!
You there.
What are you doing?
( chittering )
Why is she so mean to us?
Yeah, I miss the days
when she was just a fraud.
( chittering )
Oh, dear.
Rarity's dangerous mission
outfit is ruined.
Guess we better go back.
( animals chittering
and chirping )
Oh. Okay, okay,
you're right.
I need to be brave
and find Twilight.
( birds chirping )
Oh. You found her?
She's in the Ever-Free Forest?
Oh, but this is me
being brave.
I want to be brave at home.
Locked in my closet.
With my teddy bear.
I can't believe I didn't
recognize the Alicorn Amulet.
The more she uses it,
the more it will corrupt her.
But how am I supposed
to beat that amulet?
My magic's not good enough.
Twilight Sparkle,
much work have you done.
You learned all of my lessons,
all but one.
If Trixie's tricks
have you in a fix,
you must nix your magic
and use the six.
Nix your magic,
use the six...
use the six.
Use the six.
That's it!
Zecora, you're a genius.
Now, we'll need to get you back
inside Ponyville, Fluttershy.
( mellow theme playing )
This better not
be another false alarm,
or the great and powerful
Trixie will--
You!
What's the matter,
Twilight Sparkle?
Not enjoying your exile?
I know about
the Alicorn Amulet.
I know you cheated.
Cheated? Moi?
Yeah, and I thought
you might want to see
what a real magical amulet
looks like.
Zecora gave it to me.
It's from beyond
the Ever-Free Forest
and it's way more powerful
than your measly
little Alicorn Amulet.
Ha! Nothing's more powerful
than the Alicorn Amulet.
And nopony's more powerful than
the great and powerful Trixie.
TWILIGHT:
Care to put your amulet
where your mouth is?
How about another duel?
Why should I?
I already beat you.
That's up to you,
but I guess you'll never see
the totally awesome magic
from beyond
the Ever-Free Forest.
Come on, Zecora.
Wait.
Okay, okay, you're on.
A second duel.
( thunder rumbling )
( ominous theme playing )
Let's start with a simple
age spell, shall we?
Let's.
Snips. Snails.
( both crying )
An oldie but a goodie.
Now let's see what
your little charm can do.
No problem.
Um, Applejack? Rarity?
Could you help me, please?
Huh?
( suspenseful theme playing )
Ho-hum.
So you can do an age spell,
big deal.
( majestic theme playing )
That's--
That's impossible!
That's nothing.
Yow!
How did you--?
Duplication spell.
Ever seen one pony play
ten instruments?
( playing upbeat polka music )
This-- This can't be!
Ooh, one more.
I can turn a mare
into a stallion.
( in deep voice ):
Eyup.
Well, Trixie,
looks like my amulet
is more powerful than yours.
Hey! Give it back!
( cackles )
With this amulet,
I shall now rule
all of Equestria.
( Trixie cackles )
Witness, my subjects.
Gaze upon an ever greater
and powerfuller Trixie!
( cackling )
Hey!
I don't need that
old Alicorn Amulet.
I have this.
Ha-ha! Stop it.
That tickles.
Tickles?
That was supposed
to make you writhe in agony.
This amulet is defective.
Give mine back.
Sorry. This is going
back into hiding
where it belongs.
By the way, Trixie,
the amulet around your neck?
It's one of
Zecora's doorstops.
But how did you
do those spells?
Nopony can do those spells.
You're right.
Not even me.
Zecora taught me so much about
magic while I was in exile.
She even taught me
when to not use it.
My magic alone
wasn't powerful enough
to take on the Alicorn Amulet
head to head,
so I needed to use
a different kind of magic.
The magic of friendship.
I also knew
that the only pony
who could get the amulet
off your neck was you.
But what about the pony
with the ten instruments?
That's not magic,
that was just Pinkie Pie.
( playing upbeat polka music )
( all cheering )
( birds chirping )
( upbeat theme playing )
CROWD:
Ooh!
( all gasp )
Trixie?
It's the least I could do.
I treated you and
your friends so horribly
when I was wearing
that Alicorn Amulet.
I just couldn't control myself.
You can forgive me, can't you?
Hmm...
Sure.
Oh, good.
Don't you think the great
and apologetic Trixie
is the most magnificent
humble pony you've ever seen?
( mellow theme playing )
( muffled shouting )
( gasps )
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪