( mellow theme playing )
( upbeat rock theme playing )
( inaudible dialogue )
( all shouting
and gasping )
Whoo-hoo!
Nice moves, kid.
Nice moves?
Rainbow Dash thinks
I've got...
Ah! Nice moves!
( moos )
♪ My Little Pony
My Little Pony ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ You have my little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
Then, all of a sudden,
I'm airborne.
And then Rainbow Dash
looks over and is like,
"Nice moves, kid."
Wow!
She really said that?
I mean, it's like
she practically told me
she wanted to take me
under her wing,
teach me everything she knows,
and become, like, my big sister.
I don't know
about all that.
It was a really
nice compliment and all but--
I know, I know.
But all that stuff
I said could happen, right?
Sure.
Absolutely.
I just need to find a way
to spend some time with her.
You know, so she can see
more of my awesomeness.
Well, Applejack and I are
supposed to be camping
up at Winsome Falls
this weekend.
Maybe I could get my big sis
to invite Rainbow Dash,
and then
you could come too.
Really?!
Sure.
I wanna go.
Well, duh.
Of course you can go.
And I'll get Rarity
to come too.
Rarity loves camping!
I despise camping!
All of that--
Ugh! --nature.
Applejack's going
with her little sister.
But, you know,
if you don't want
to spend time with me...
Oh, all right.
Oh! Of course I will need
to find an outfit
more appropriate
for roughing it. Ooh.
See? Told you
she'd want to go.
You pack the bug spray?
Yep.
You got the canteens?
Looks like
we're all set then.
Hey!
Gee, Rarity,
did you remember to pack?
Oh, well, see who gets
the last laugh
when you're absolutely desperate
to curl your lashes
and realize you didn't bring
your eyelash curler.
Well, looks like
we're all set now.
But what
about Rainbow Dash?
Isn't Rainbow Dash coming?
Course she is,
sugarcube.
She's gonna meet us
up at our first campsite.
Oh.
All right, y'all,
let's move 'em out.
( majestic theme playing )
Oh, are we there yet?
The last thousand times you
asked that, the answer was no.
This time,
it's actually yes.
There's Rainbow Dash
up there right now.
( upbeat rock theme playing )
Wow!
All right, Scootaloo,
just play it cool.
Hey, Rain--
( clears throat )
Hey, Rainbow Dash,
what's up?
What took
you guys so long?
Well, some of us
didn't pack as light
as the others,
so we were slowed down a bit.
( upbeat theme playing )
Looks like you'll be sharing
a tent with me, huh?
If that's okay
with you.
Sure, long as
you don't snore.
You don't snore,
do you?
Nope, no way,
not me.
Never snored a day
or night in my life.
Then you and I are gonna
get along just fine.
You have to got
to be kidding me.
Sweetie Belle,
do be a dear and see
if you can find some fresh
flowers for my bedside vase.
Hey, Scootaloo,
do be a sweetheart
and see if you can
gather some firewood.
( both laugh )
Seriously though,
can you get us some wood
for the fire?
Of course.
Okay, everybody
get comfortable.
Because I'm about
to tell you
the best story
you ever heard.
Is it about the time
when Rarity had wings,
and then they got ruined,
and then you saved her
from plummeting
to her doom?
Okay, maybe it's the second-best
story you ever heard,
but probably
still the scariest.
You like
scary stories, right?
( gasps )
Mm-hm.
It all happened
on a night
just like this one,
in a forest
just like this...
And then
the Olden Pony asked,
"Who's got
my rusty horseshoe?"
Not me.
You do!
BOTH: Aah!
( laughs )
( coughs then
clears throat )
Something
in my throat.
I wasn't scared at all.
Ha-ha. Good story!
Knew you
wouldn't be scared.
Way you jumped
that cart the other day.
You're like me,
fearless.
Yeah, fearless.
( owl hooting )
Don't worry,
Rarity is here
to keep you safe
and sound. Ooh.
( yawns )
Think it's about time
for me to hit the straw.
( teeth chattering )
Don't you worry,
little sis,
there's no Olden Pony
in our tent.
Heh-heh, that sure
was funny, wasn't it,
how they were all afraid
of the Olden Pony?
But not me. Heh.
That's because
you're tough,
just like when
I was your age.
( screams )
I'm hitting the sack.
Come in whenever
you feel like it.
( branch cracks )
( wind howling )
It's nothing,
just my imagination.
( trees creaking )
And that isn't the thundering
stomp of the Olden Pony.
( animal howling )
( snoring )
( distant voices chattering )
Uh, is anyone
out there?
( hoof beats approaching )
( pony muttering in distance )
( suspenseful theme playing )
( pony muttering )
( panting )
Who's got
my rusty horseshoe?
( sighs )
Who's got
my rusty horseshoe?
( screams )
( panting )
( ominous theme playing )
SCOOTALOO:
Rainbow Da--
You do!
( screams )
( snoring )
( humming )
( suspenseful theme playing )
( Scootaloo humming )
( yawns )
( humming )
What's that noise?
Is there a bug in here?
I don't know about you,
but I slept like a filly.
Best night ever.
Glad you're rested up,
because we've got
a long trek ahead.
Totally gonna be worth it
when we get to Winsome Falls.
Yeah, totally.
( Rarity groans )
Am I sweating?
Oh, I think
I'm sweating!
Oh, uh, but it's
absolutely worth it
to get to spend time
with my little sister.
It's just that
this cart feels like
it's getting heavier
all the time!
APPLEJACK:
I don't care if that cart's
as heavy as a pack of mules.
If we don't
get a move on,
it'll be dark before
we get to the campsite.
Ah, dark?
I'll just ride ahead
to make sure the path is clear.
Now, we don't want to be
out here after dark, right?
Doesn't matter to me.
Well, you know,
it's for
the scaredy ponies.
( yawns )
( gasps )
Don't fall asleep now.
We've got to get
to that campsite before dark.
( snoring )
( growls )
RARITY:
...and that's why it's
always important to bring
your own trough
on any public outing.
( gasps )
Um, don't come this way!
Take the path,
it's, um,
way better than going
through the bushes.
( screams )
You're more nervous than a worm
in an apple on cider-makin' day.
What gives, Scootaloo?
Uh, nothing.
I just thought
I heard something.
( hooting )
Aah!
You sure you're okay?
Because you seem
a little jumpy.
Just getting
my exercise.
You know how important
it is to stretch out
those hind quarters
every so often. Ha.
( croaks )
Uh, do y-you need
a little help?
That's so sweet.
Thank you.
Um, what are
friends for?
( grunting )
No need for tents
tonight, y'all.
We'll just take shelter
in that cave.
All right,
a deep dark cave.
Ha, perfect for the story
I've got for tonight.
All we need is a campfire
and we're good to go.
( gulps )
Of course.
( animal howling )
SCOOTALOO:
I'll be right back with lots
of firewood from the deep,
dark,
not-scary-at-all forest.
Thanks.
( ominous theme playing )
( panting )
( sighs )
Okay, I can do this.
At the count of three,
I will get those branches.
One, two, three!
( sighs )
Here, branches,
branches, branches.
APPLEJACK:
Ooh-whee! It's colder than
a timberwolf's toenail.
Brr!
Where's that Scootaloo?
( screaming )
Here you go!
That's it?
It's all I could find,
because, you know,
there aren't
that many trees around here.
It's all we need.
Why don't you sit
with Rainbow Dash
for a while?
Now, where was I?
Oh, yeah,
the scary part.
( cackles )
Hey, I have an idea.
How about
I tell tonight's story?
All right,
just make sure
it's a horrible one.
SCOOTALOO:
There once was
a really, really nice pony
who lived in
a bright and sunny land,
where there were
rainbows every day
and lots and lots
of happy friends, and--
No offense, but it's not
a real campfire story
unless
somepony's shaking.
I've been told
that these very woods
are haunted...
...by the Headless Horse!
It gallops only at night.
If it doesn't have a head,
then how in tarnation
does this pony
know where it's goin'?
It's headless,
not brainless.
Looking for
little lost ponies...
So where's its brain?
Ugh.
Fear was dripping
from the air...
...and they were never
heard from ever again!
Ah! Never?
Never.
( fire cracks )
( both scream )
( both chuckle )
( teeth chattering )
Don't worry,
you'll be safe
with me tonight.
It's not time
for bed yet, is it?
Afraid so, Scootaloo.
Uh, but
we haven't even sung
any campfire songs yet.
You don't have
to ask me twice!
♪ 99 buckets of oats
On the wall ♪
♪ 99 buckets of oats ♪
♪ Take one down,
Pass it around... ♪
♪ You got 81 buckets
Of oats on the wall... ♪
♪ 41 buckets of oats ♪
♪ Take one down
Pass it around ♪
♪ You got 40 buckets
Of oats on the wall... ♪
♪ One bucket of oats ♪
♪ Take one down
Pass it around ♪
♪ You got zero buckets
Of oats on the wall! ♪
( snoring )
( all yawn )
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, y'all.
Sleep tight.
How about
just one more song?
Anyone?
How about
a dance contest?
I know you love
to cut a rug,
so how about we mess up
a cave floor?
I have a brilliant idea!
Hide and seek,
who's with me?
( yawns )
Maybe tomorrow.
Aww.
Seems like you
don't really want
to go
to sleep tonight.
Is there
some reason why?
( scoffs )
Of course not.
I just love camping and hanging
out with Rainbow Dash so much
that I don't want to waste
a single minute with sleep.
( yawns then chuckles )
Silly sleep.
That's cool
and all, Scoot,
but this pony needs
her shut-eye,
and she needs it now!
Uh, this is so unfair.
( sighs then yawns )
I'm falling aslee...
( snoring )
( hoof beats approaching )
( suspenseful theme playing )
If the Headless Horse
catches me,
I'm never gonna
be heard from again,
and I want
to be heard from!
Whoa! Whoa!
( whimpering )
( ominous theme playing )
SCOOTALOO:
It's all over!
( whimpering )
( dramatic theme playing )
LUNA:
A warm welcome to you,
Scootaloo.
SCOOTALOO:
Princess Luna.
I thought you were
the Headless Horse.
You were mistaken,
but I hope not disappointed.
You are so, so much better
than the Headless Horse.
But what are
you doing here?
Shouldn't you be
in Canterlot?
I am the princess
of the night,
thus it is my duty
to come into your dreams.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, this is
just a dream?
But it feels so real.
I assure you
that you are asleep.
But when you wake,
the thing that frightens
you most will still exist.
Uh, the Headless Horse?
Mm, is the Headless Horse
really what frightens
you the most?
Mm-mm.
I'm afraid Rainbow Dash
will find out
I'm not as tough
as she thinks I am.
Everypony has fears,
Scootaloo.
Everypony must face them
in their own way.
But they must be faced,
or the nightmares
will continue.
( groaning )
Face your fears!
Princess Luna?
Ah, it was just a dream.
( gasps )
But the Headless Horse isn't!
Rainbow Dash said
it lives here,
in these very woods!
( horse whinnying in distance )
It's the wicked whinny
of the Headless Horse!
( whinnies )
( Scootaloo panting )
So it's a horse
without a head,
which means
it doesn't have a mouth,
and if it doesn't
have a mouth,
then it's not
a horse-eat-pony kind of horse.
But still,
it's a horse
without a head!
( screaming )
Hello?
Is anyone out there?
Anyone except
the Headless Horse?
( cracking )
Help!
( dramatic theme playing )
( screaming )
I got you!
Rainbow Dash, is that you?
Thank you! Thank you!
What were you doing out here
in the middle of the night?
It is time for you
to face your real fears,
Scootaloo.
( sighs )
I'm so, so sorry,
Rainbow Dash.
I just wanted you
to hang out with me
and see how cool I was so
you'd take me under your wing,
teach me everything you know,
and become, like,
my big sister.
But then you started telling
those spooky stories,
and I got scared.
I thought I heard
the Headless Horse
so I ran out here
by myself and--
Well, I guess
you know the rest.
( sniffling )
Hey, I'm gonna
tell you something,
but if you ever tell anypony
else, I'm gonna deny it.
First time I heard
those stories,
I was scared too.
You were?
Sure.
I mean, I got over it,
because I realized pretty quick
that if there was such
a thing as a Headless Horse,
I could
totally take it on.
So you're looking
for somepony to take you
under their wing, huh?
Mm-hm.
Yeah, I might be up
for something like that.
Really?
As long as
you don't go falling
into any more rivers
in the middle of the night.
Hm, it's a deal.
( upbeat theme playing )
I call sister teams!
Last pair to make it
to the falls is a moldy carrot!
Ugh, if you insist.
( chuckles )
It is so on!
They think they can beat
the two of us?
( majestic theme playing )
( suspenseful theme playing )
( grumbling )
Who's got
my rusty horseshoe?
RAINBOW DASH:
Here it is, for pony's sake!
Now take it
and stop all your moaning!
Thank you,
and have a nice day.
( Luna laughs )
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪