( tender theme playing )
( squeaking )
Ooh, I wish the mail pony
would just come already.
I can't wait another minute
to find out
if Rainbow Dash
got in or not.
Pinkie Pie, you're more nervous
than Rainbow Dash. I'm
not nervous at all.
When I get
into the Wonderbolt Academy--
"If" you get in?
Don't jinx it.
I'm telling you,
it's in the bag.
Don't jinx it.
She is the best flyer
in Ponyville.
In Ponyville?
( upbeat theme playing )
I'm probably the best flyer
in all of Equestria.
I wouldn't be surprised
if they just went ahead
and made me a Wonderbolt
on the first day.
Got a letter here
for Rainbow Dash.
( wistful theme playing )
I didn't get in.
( gasps )
Gotcha.
( laughs )
You guys are so gullible.
Like I wasn't gonna get in.
I'm just so happy for you.
Uh, thanks.
( straining )
Pinkie Pie,
I kind of need to get going.
Okay. I'm done.
Sooner I get there,
sooner I get to show them
my stuff.
See you guys in a week.
Good luck.
Won't need it.
Don't forget to write.
( voice echoing )
( rumbling )
Do you think she heard me?
♪ My Little Pony
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it all
Complete ♪
♪ You have
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
( upbeat theme playing )
Oh, yeah.
This is gonna be sweet.
SPITFIRE:
Well, lookie what we got here.
( ominous theme playing )
Bet you all think
you're Wonderbolt material,
don't you?
ALL:
Yes, ma'am!
Think you've got what it takes
to be an elite flyer?
ALL: Yes, ma'am!
Well, then,
let me be the first
to tell you
you don't!
If you had what it took
to be an elite flyer,
you'd already be
a Wonderbolt.
Still think
you're something special?
No, ma'am.
( whimpers )
You think you're hot stuff?
( whimpering )
You look like
you're the worst flyer
in the whole academy.
You'll probably quit
after the first day.
No, ma'am.
I'd never quit, ma'am.
Ha.
What about you?
Bet you couldn't fly
past the first flagpole
without getting winded.
Try me, ma'am.
What's that?
Let me show you
what I've got, ma'am.
Oh, you want a chance
to prove yourself, huh?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, then,
now's your chance.
Give me 500 laps.
All of you!
( all groan )
Now!
( blows whistle )
( upbeat theme playing )
( all coughing )
Lap 499.
One more lap to go.
You're on.
Five hundred.
( screeching )
Not bad...
for a couple of newbies.
Name's Lightning Dust.
Rainbow Dash.
Wanna grab some grub
in the mess hall?
Definitely.
( tender theme playing )
Pinkie Pie, Rainbow Dash hasn't
even been gone 24 hours yet.
Give her a chance
to settle in first.
Why don't we just go see
what Twilight's up to?
I hear Princess Celestia's
got her working
on some new spells.
New spells, huh?
Okay.
Wait. If I'm not here
when Rainbow Dash's letter
arrives,
I won't be able to read it
right away.
If I don't read it right away,
I can't write back right away.
And if I don't, she might think
I didn't get her letter.
Then she might worry
it got lost.
And if she's worrying,
she'll be distracted.
If she's distracted, she
won't do well at the academy,
then she'll get kicked out.
If she gets kicked out, they'll
never let her be a Wonderbolt.
If she doesn't get
to be a Wonderbolt,
all her dreams
will be crushed!
And it will be
all my fault.
So in other words,
you're sticking by the mailbox.
Yup.
Suit yourself.
SPITFIRE:
The Wonderbolts are the fastest,
best precision flyers
in the world.
But spinouts
can still happen.
And when they do,
a Wonderbolt must be able
to recover quickly.
This is the Dizzitron.
It's gonna to make you very,
I repeat, very dizzy.
Your task
is to try to recover
and fly straight again,
as soon as possible.
Once you have recovered you must
come in for a smooth landing.
Now who's first?
You.
You're up.
Me?
( gulps )
Now!
Ready?
Yes, ma'am.
Go!
( Dizzitron whirring )
Release.
( groaning )
( sighs )
Ah, 15 seconds. Decent.
But I wouldn't go writing home
about it. Who's next?
All right, Rainbow Dash,
let's see what you got.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, go.
( Dizzitron whirring )
Release.
Six seconds.
That's an academy record.
You make it look so easy.
I make everything look easy.
SPITFIRE:
Okay, Lightning Dust,
you're up.
Ma'am, can you put
the Dizzitron at maximum speed?
I wanna push my limits.
You sure about that?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay. You asked for it.
( Dizzitron whirring )
Release.
Six-point-five seconds.
Not bad.
Oh, yeah.
Ha.
SPITFIRE:
Next!
( screeching )
No pony even came close
to six seconds.
They should make us
Wonderbolts right now.
Yeah, they should.
( chuckles )
Listen up.
You'll be working in pairs.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll post the teams,
including who will be
lead pony
and who will be wingpony.
Good luck.
Like we're gonna need it.
Yeah.
( upbeat theme playing )
So which one of you lucky gals
gets to be my wingpony?
What?
Uh, you might wanna check
the wall.
A wingpony?
They made us a team.
Isn't that awesome?
( ominous theme playing )
( upbeat theme playing )
Permission to enter, ma'am.
What is it, Rainbow Dash?
I had the best time
on the Dizzitron,
only six seconds.
And?
And you made me a wingpony.
Because I believe you
and Lightning Dust
will be an unstoppable team.
Do you not think
you'll be an unstoppable team?
Yes, ma'am.
I mean, no, ma'am.
I mean, we'll be
an unstoppable team, ma'am.
Then what's the problem?
I think I should be lead pony,
ma'am.
And I think Lightning Dust
likes to push herself
a little harder than you do.
That's why I made her
lead pony.
Got it?
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
( military theme playing )
Today you will all
be participating
in a flag hunt.
We'll divide you
into two teams:
Red and Blue.
Whoever finds the most flags
of the opposing team's color
wins.
( all cheering )
Oh, this is gonna be
so much fun.
If you think
this is gonna be fun,
you are sadly mistaken.
This is for training purposes,
this is not recess.
Lead ponies and wingponies
must fly together.
If any pair splits apart,
they will be
immediately disqualified.
Do you understand?
ALL:
Yes, ma'am.
Then let's go.
( blows whistles )
( suspenseful theme playing )
Ready to rock and roll?
Ready.
You spotted any flags yet?
Not yet.
Oh, there's one.
Good eyes.
RAINBOW DASH:
We should slow down.
It doesn't look like both of us
can make it at this speed.
Ha.
Ow.
Lightning Dust and Rainbow Dash
have found the first flag.
Come on,
let's find some more.
Uh, sure,
just give me a second.
Oh, you're fine.
Yeah, totally.
( groans )
( snoring )
( gasps )
( melancholy theme playing )
She's still at it.
I just wish
we could help her.
Help me? The only thing
that could possibly help me
right now
is a letter from Rainbow Dash.
It's been three days already.
By now, she probably doesn't
even know our names anymore.
She probably can't remember
our faces.
"Pinkie Pie?
I never heard of a Pinkie Pie.
Who is Pinkie Pie?"
Well, if you're so worried,
then why don't you
send her a letter first?
Of course.
That's a great idea.
( all sigh )
Wait.
I got an even better idea.
How about we send Rainbow Dash
a care package?
You know, before she forgets
all about us.
Although, come on,
let's face it,
it's probably too late
for that.
But, uh, maybe it'll jog
her memory somehow.
Pinkie Pie, I'm sure Rainbow
Dash still remembers our faces
and who we are.
But I think sending her
a care package is a great idea.
A care package it is.
We'll send it
through the mail.
Wait! Ah!
That won't work at all.
Why not?
Because what if the package
gets lost in the mail?
What if somepony else
gets the package by accident
and then she remembers us
instead of Rainbow Dash
and then she becomes
our new friend.
And then the real Rainbow Dash
won't ever know
that she used to have friends
and she forgot them.
Is anypony else
following this?
ALL: Uh-uh.
I've got it!
We'll deliver the care package
to Rainbow Dash in person.
I wouldn't mind
a little trip.
I'll go.
Count me in.
Me too.
Me five.
But don't be upset if she
doesn't recognize you at first.
It may take a while for her
to get her memory back.
( suspenseful theme playing )
( trumpet blowing )
SPITFIRE:
Today we'll be doing our famous
air obstacle course.
The object of this exercise
is to work
on your precision flying
under extreme circumstances.
And don't worry
about winning.
It's not a race.
Now, everypony
get on your marks.
( blows whistle )
( wind gusting )
Ugh!
Can't they go any faster?
It's no good.
I can't get around them.
It doesn't matter.
We can still fly
completely in sync
and blow Spitfire's mind
with our moves.
I guess.
( wind whistling )
What are they,
a couple of snails?
It's just a little weather.
( thunder rumbling )
Now's our chance
to pass these slowpokes.
( ponies grunting )
( upbeat theme playing )
Not bad.
And in record time too.
Definitely made
the right decision
making you two a team.
The others seem to have had
a little trouble
with the precision part
of the exercise.
I better go help
sort them out.
Why don't you two
go hit the mess hall early?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, ma'am.
Um, Lightening Dust?
Next time, maybe we don't cut
the other teams off like that.
Hey, you snooze, you lose.
Besides, Wonderbolts
are supposed to be able
to recover from a spinout.
You saw them
on the Dizzitron.
They could use the practice.
I mean, it's not our fault
we're so much better
than those other guys.
Not everypony is destined
to become a Wonderbolt.
Only the best of the best,
right?
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Of course I'm right.
Now let's go fuel up.
Kicking all that tail's
made me hungry.
( slow theme playing )
( blows whistle )
( dramatic theme playing )
( air whooshing )
Yeah!
( upbeat theme playing )
I have an idea
about how we can literally
blow away our competition.
But we're already way ahead.
Are you in or not?
SPITFIRE:
Lightning Dust likes
to push herself
a little harder than you do.
That's why I made her
lead pony.
I'm in.
Then follow my lead.
I can't control it.
( suspenseful theme playing )
It's a twister.
( ominous theme playing )
Hold on!
( all screaming )
No.
( screaming )
( gasping and sighing )
Are you guys okay?
ALL:
Uh-huh.
Pinkie Pie.
You remember me.
Well, yeah,
of course I remember you.
But what are you all
doing here?
We wanted to bring you
a care package.
Didn't realize
you'd be in the middle
of some crazy tornado drill.
That was awesome.
Awesome? My friends could've
been smashed to pieces.
Yeah.
But they weren't, right?
Can't say the same
for the clouds.
We totally wiped them out
with that tornado.
The other cadets will have
to be up there for days
to bust as many as we did.
A hoof bump? Seriously?
You made me clip my wing.
You sent half of our class
into serious tailspins
on the obstacle course.
You unleashed a tornado
that nearly demolished
my friends.
Yeah. And?
And I get that you wanna
be the best. So do I.
But you're going about it
in the wrong way.
The Wonderbolts don't seem
to think so.
After all,
Spitfire did make me the leader
and you the wingpony.
( sighs )
You're right, she did.
This better be important.
You're supposed to be
up there
busting clouds
with your partner.
We're done with that,
ma'am.
Already?
That's an academy record.
Explain your methods.
That's why I'm here,
ma'am.
Lightning Dust decided
to use a tornado.
A bit excessive
for cloudbusting.
But judging from your time,
it was obviously
an effective tactic.
Yeah,
well, that effective tactic
nearly took out my friends.
No disrespect, ma'am,
but there's a big difference
between pushing yourself
as hard as you can
and just being reckless.
And if being reckless
is what gets rewarded
around here,
if that's what it means
to be a Wonderbolt,
then I don't want any part
of it.
What are you saying, newbie?
I quit.
APPLEJACK:
You did what?
But being a Wonderbolt
was your dream.
Not anymore.
I'm sorry, Rainbow Dash.
I know how much
this meant to you.
Rainbow Dash.
How dare you
storm out of my office
without giving me
a chance to respond.
The Wonderbolts are looking
for the best fliers
in Equestria.
But you were right,
being the best
should never come at the expense
of our fellow ponies.
It's not just
about pushing ourselves,
it's about pushing ourselves
in the right direction.
You've shown
that you're capable
of doing just that.
You're no wingpony,
Rainbow Dash.
You're a leader.
Oh, my, gosh. Oh, my, gosh.
Now get up there
and give me 20.
Yes, ma'am.
( majestic theme playing )
Wait. You didn't even get
to open your care package!
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪