( "Morning in Ponyville"
playing)
♪ Morning in Ponyville
Shimmers ♪
Shines ♪
♪ And I know
For absolute certain ♪
♪ That everything
Is certainly fine ♪
♪ There's the mayor en route
To her office ♪
♪ There's the sofa clerk
Selling some quills ♪
Morning, kid.
♪ My Ponyville
Is so gentle and still ♪
♪ Can things ever go wrong?
I don't think that they will ♪
♪ Morning in Ponyville
Shimmers ♪
Shines ♪
♪ And I know
For absolute certain ♪
♪ That everything
Is certainly-- ♪
Rainbow Dash.
That's not funny!
RARITY:
Terribly sorry, darling,
I'm afraid I'm not good
with the thundery ones.
( Twilight gasps )
Something tells me
everything is not going
to be fine.
♪ My little pony
My little pony ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ You have my little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
( suspenseful theme playing )
What are you doing? What
happened to your Cutie Mark?
Whatever do you mean,
Twilight?
I'm simply doing
what I've done
since the day
it first appeared.
Does my sky look fabulous
or what?
( all speaking indistinctly )
Too last season?
Where is Rainbow Dash?
Why isn't she handling this?
( yawns )
I still don't know
what you had to wake me up for.
I love sleeping in the rain.
TWILIGHT:
It's not about the weather,
Spike.
Rarity had Rainbow Dash's
Cutie Mark
and said this was
Rainbow Dash's cottage.
Something strange
is going on.
Hey, guys.
Rainbow Dash.
Why is Rarity doing your job?
( thudding )
And what in Equestria
is going on in here?
( animals squealing
and growling )
( "What My Cutie Mark
is Telling Me" playing )
♪ These animals don't listen
No not one little bit ♪
♪ They run around
Out of control ♪
♪ And throw
Their hissy fits ♪
♪ It's up to me to stop them
'Cause plainly you can see ♪
♪ It's got to be
My destiny ♪
♪ And it's what my Cutie Mark
Is telling me ♪
♪ I try to keep them laughing
Put a smile upon their face ♪
♪ But no matter
What I try ♪
♪ It seems a bit
Of a disgrace ♪
♪ I have to entertain them
It's there for all to see ♪
♪ It's got to be
My destiny ♪
♪ And it's what my Cutie Mark
Is telling me ♪
♪ I don't much care much
For pickin' fruit ♪
♪ And plowin' fields
Ain't such a hoot ♪
♪ No matter what I try ♪
♪ I cannot fix
This busted water chute ♪
♪ I've got so many chores
To do ♪
♪ It's no fun being me ♪
♪ But it has to be
My destiny ♪
♪ 'Cause that's what
My Cutie Mark is telling me ♪
♪ Lookie here at what I made
I think that it's a dress ♪
♪ I know
It doesn't look like much ♪
♪ I'm under some distress ♪
♪ Could y'all give me
A hand here ♪
♪ And help me fix
This mess? ♪
♪ My destiny
Is not pretty ♪
♪ But it's what
My Cutie Mark is telling me ♪
♪ I'm in love
With weather patterns ♪
♪ But the others
Have concerns ♪
♪ For I just gave them
Frostbite ♪
♪ Over top
Of their sunburns ♪
♪ I have to keep on trying
For everyone can see ♪
♪ It's got to be ♪
♪ My destiny ♪
♪ And it's what
My Cutie Mark ♪
♪ It's what
ALL:
♪ Yes
It's what my Cutie Mark ♪
♪ Is telling me ♪
This is bad.
This is very, very bad.
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
Last night
when you were taking
one of your seven-hour
bubble baths,
I got a special delivery
from the princess.
"Dear Twilight Sparkle.
"The spell contained
on the last page of this book
is Star Swirl the Bearded's
secret unfinished masterpiece."
( gasps )
Ooh!
"He was never able
to get it right
"and thus abandoned it.
"I believe
you are the only pony
"who can understand
and rewrite it.
Princess Celestia."
"From one to another
Another to one
A mark of one's destiny
Singled out alone fulfilled"
That doesn't make any sense,
it doesn't even rhyme.
TWILIGHT ( narrating ):
I cast the spell so I could
find out what it was.
but nothing
seemed to happen.
But now I know
something did happen.
The spell has changed
the Elements of Harmony.
That must be
why their Cutie Marks
are all wrong.
So just cast a counterspell
to switch them back.
There is no counterspell.
Why don't you just use
that memory spell you used
to fix everypony
when Discord was here?
It's not their memories,
Spike.
It's their true selves
that have been altered.
Zecora's cure
for the Cutie Pox?
That won't work either.
Well,
maybe it won't be so bad.
Maybe our friends will grow
to like their new lives.
No, Spike.
They're not who they
are meant to be anymore.
Their destinies
are now changed,
and it's all my fault.
( "I've Got to Find A Way"
playing )
♪ I have to find a way ♪
♪ To make this all okay ♪
♪ I can't believe
This small mistake ♪
♪ Could have caused
So much heartache ♪
♪ Oh, why? ♪
♪ Losing promise ♪
♪ I don't know what to do ♪
♪ Seeking answers ♪
♪ I fear I won't get through
To you ♪
♪ Oh, why? ♪
Oh, Spike.
What have I done?
( melancholic theme playing )
Aw, come on, Twilight.
You'll figure out a way
to fix this.
These are your friends.
You're right, Spike.
And they mean more to me
than anything.
My friends.
( upbeat theme playing )
Twilight? Are you all right?
I've got it.
I know what to do.
You do?
I may not be able to remind them
of who they are,
but I can show them
what they mean to each other.
They'll find the part
of themselves that's been lost
so they can help the friend
they care about so much.
Come on, Spike.
TWILIGHT:
Fluttershy, wait.
Oh, hey, Twilight.
Where are you going?
I'm moving back
to Cloudsdale.
I don't know what's wrong,
but I can't seem
to make any pony laugh.
( squishing )
Before you go,
I was wondering
if you might be willing
to help Rainbow Dash.
She's really struggling
with her animals.
But I don't really know
anything about animals.
But you do know something
about Rainbow Dash.
I know
that she's a true friend.
And I'll do anything
I can to help her.
RAINBOW DASH:
Help!
Rainbow Dash!
RAINBOW DASH:
I'm in here! Help!
I'm trapped!
Hurry, Twilight.
Can't you do some sort of spell
to get her out?
No.
Fluttershy, you're the only one
who can help.
Rainbow Dash needs you.
Um, hello?
Little woodland creatures?
( growling and squealing )
I know
that you're all very upset
and feel like giving
Rainbow Dash a hard time,
but we'd all
really appreciate it
if you'd calm down
and maybe rest for a bit?
Oh, uh, look.
Here's some nice juicy leaves
for you to munch on,
and some crunchy,
munchy acorns too.
Wouldn't you like
to take a break
and have a little snack?
( squeaks )
FLUTTERSHY:
Aw, look at that,
I guess you were all
just cranky
because you were hungry.
Oh, you are very welcome,
little friends.
Mm.
Goodness. It's like
I can understand them.
I feel strange,
like this is
what I'm meant to do.
Like this is who I am!
My destiny.
FLUTTERSHY:
What happened?
Fluttershy, look!
Your Cutie Mark.
It worked. It worked!
Oh, I'm so happy
you're back to normal.
Now we need your help.
TWILIGHT:
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ A friend will be there
To help them see ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ To see the light ♪
♪ That shines
From a true, true friend ♪
Um, hello?
Friend trapped inside,
remember?
♪ Rarity needs your help ♪
♪ She's trying hard
Doing what she can ♪
♪ Would you try?
Just give it a chance ♪
♪ You might find ♪
♪ That you'll start
To understand ♪
ALL:
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ A friend will be there
To help you see ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ To see the light ♪
♪ That shines
From a true, true friend ♪
Uh, what just happened?
There's no time to explain,
but we need your help.
Applejack's trying
to make dresses.
Say no more.
♪ Applejack needs
Your help ♪
♪ She's trying hard
Doing what she can ♪
♪ Would you try ?
Just give it a chance ♪
♪ You might find ♪
♪ That you'll start
To understand ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ A friend will be there
To help them see ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ To see the light that shines
From a true, true friend ♪
Aah! Oh, my.
What a terrible dream I had.
Or maybe
I'm still having it.
Rarity, Pinkie Pie is about
to lose the apple farm.
We need Applejack's help.
Lose the apple farm?
Well, we can't let that happen,
now can we?
♪ Pinkie Pie
Is in trouble ♪
♪ We need to get there
By her side ♪
♪ We can try to do
What we can now ♪
♪ Or together
We can be her guide ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ A friend will be there
To help them see ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ To see the light that shines
From a true, true friend ♪
Yeehaw!
Now that's more like it!
What's next?
The townspeople are furious.
We need
the old Pinkie Pie back.
I'm on it,
I know just the thing.
♪ The townspeople need you
They've been sad for a while ♪
♪ They march around
Face a-frown ♪
♪ And never seem to smile ♪
♪ And if you feel like helpin'
We'd appreciate a lot ♪
♪ If you'd get up there
And spread some cheer ♪
♪ From here to Canterlot ♪
Come on, ponies!
I wanna see you smile!
ALL:
Pinkie!
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ A friend will be there
To help them see ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ To see the light
To see the light ♪
♪ That shines
That shines ♪
♪ From a true
True friend ♪
TWILIGHT:
A mark of one's destiny
singled out alone fulfilled.
( gasps )
Wait a second, that's it.
I understand now.
I know how to fix the spell.
From all of us together
Together we're friends
With the marks
Of our destinies made one
There is magic without end
( all gasp )
( all gasping )
( wind swooshing )
( all speaking indistinctly )
Ah, what happened?
Where on earth did she go?
Oh, no!
( suspenseful theme playing )
( mysterious theme playing )
Hello?
Where am I?
What is this place?
Congratulations, Twilight.
I knew you could do it.
Princess, I don't understand.
What did I do?
You did something today
that's never been done before.
Something even a great unicorn
like Star Swirl the Bearded,
was not able to do.
Because he did not understand
friendship like you do.
The lessons you've learned here
in Ponyville
have taught you well.
You have proven
that you're ready, Twilight.
Ready? Ready for what?
( "Celestia's Ballad"
playing )
♪ You've come
Such a long, long way ♪
♪ And I've watched you
From that very first day ♪
♪ To see
How you might grow ♪
What you might do ♪
♪ To see
What you've been through ♪
♪ And all the ways
You've made me proud of you ♪
♪ It's time now
For a new change to come ♪
♪ You've grown up
And your new life has begun ♪
♪ To go where you will go ♪
♪ To see
What you will see ♪
♪ To find
What you will be ♪
♪ For it's time for you ♪
♪ To fulfill your destiny ♪
Twilight? Is that you?
( upbeat theme playing )
( all gasp )
( Applejack gasps )
I've never seen anything
like it.
Ha, Twilight's got wings!
Awesome!
A new flying buddy.
Ha, ha.
Why, you've become
an alicorn.
I didn't even know
that was possible.
PINKIE PIE:
Alicorn Party!
( Pinkie Pie blowing horn )
( crowd cheering )
Wow! You look
just like a princess.
That's because
she is a princess.
ALL:
Huh?
Hold on a second!
( spits )
A...
A princess?
Since you've come
to Ponyville,
you've displayed the charity,
compassion, devotion,
integrity, optimism,
and, of course, the leadership
of a true princess.
But does this mean I won't be
your student anymore?
Not in the same way
as before.
I'll still be here
to help and guide you,
but we're all
your students now too.
You are an inspiration
to us all, Twilight.
( upbeat theme playing )
But what do I do now?
Is there a book about being
a princess I should read?
(chuckles)
There will be time
for all of that later.
We are gathered here today
in celebration
of a momentous occasion.
My most faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle,
has done many
extraordinary things
since she's lived
in Ponyville.
She even helped reunite me
with my sister, Princess Luna.
But today, Twilight Sparkle
did something extraordinary.
She created new magic,
proving without a doubt
that she is ready
to be crowned
Equestria's newest princess.
Fillies and gentlecolts,
may I present
for the very first time,
Princess Twilight Sparkle.
♪ The Princess Twilight
Cometh ♪
♪ Behold, behold ♪
♪ The princess here
Before us ♪
♪ Behold ♪
♪ Behold, behold ♪
♪ Behold, behold
Behold, behold ♪
♪ The Princess Twilight
Cometh ♪
♪ Behold, behold
Behold, behold ♪
♪ The Princess is ♪
♪ The Princess is here ♪
( crowd cheering )
Say something, princess.
Oh, um...
Ahem. A little while ago,
my teacher and mentor,
Princess Celestia,
sent me to live
in Ponyville.
She sent me
to study friendship,
which is something
I didn't really care
much about.
But now, on a day like today,
I can honestly say
I wouldn't be standing here
if it weren't
for the friendships
I've made with all of you.
Each one of you taught me
something about friendship,
and for that
I will always be grateful.
Today, I consider myself
the luckiest pony in Equestria.
Thank you, friends.
Thank you, everypony.
( crowd cheering )
Twilight,
I'm so proud of you.
Are you crying?
Of course not.
It's liquid pride,
a totally different thing.
( both laughs )
Way to go, princess.
Best coronation day ever!
We love you, Twilight.
I love you too, girls.
( "Life in Equestria"
playing )
( crowd cheering )
♪ Life in Equestria
Shimmers ♪
Shines ♪
♪ And I know
For absolute certain ♪
ALL:
♪ That everything ♪
♪ Yes, everything ♪
♪ Is certainly fine ♪
♪ It's fine ♪
TWILIGHT:
Yes!
Everything is gonna be
just fine.
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ A friend will be there
To help them see ♪
♪ A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need ♪
♪ To see the light ♪
♪ That shines ♪
♪ From a true
True friend ♪