Ah, found them.
( sneezes )
Gesund-hoof.
Why, thank you,
Applejack.
I still can't believe
it's been almost 100 moons
since our last
family reunion.
Oh, I remember it
like it was yesterday.
Well, you have been
talking about it
pretty much every day
since then.
Apple Bloom, how are them
RSVPs coming along?
Who's showing their muzzle
at the reunion?
Everypony.
Everypony?
Feathers on a goat.
Are you sure?
Well, I got RSVPs from
Apples from Yonderhill,
Hollow Shades,
Galloping Gorge,
Foal Mountains,
Apples from Fillydelphia,
Tall Tale Town,
and all the Apples
from Apple-Loosa.
Huh?
Oh, and how could
I forget?
Mane-hattan.
Babs is coming.
I get to see
my favorite cousin.
I think we're gonna need
a bigger cider trough.
♪ My little pony
My little pony ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ To have
My little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
Whoo-whee, looks like
the family's grown tenfold
since the last reunion.
I'm gonna be busier than
a worm in a rotten tomato
trying to get
everything ready.
I could
always help out.
Me too.
Yup.
Oh, I sure would
appreciate that.
Granny's a little rustier
in the giddyap
since the last time
the Apples all got together.
You may be a tad old, Granny,
but you're as feisty
and full of spark as ever.
Who you calling old?
I-- I just meant, why don't you
let me take over
putting the reunion together
this time around?
Then all you'll need to worry
about is enjoying yourself.
Hmm. All right,
young 'un.
You got yourself a deal.
You are in charge.
I won't
let you down, Granny.
You just tell me what
the reunion needs,
and I'll take care
of the rest.
I'll do better than tell you
what the reunion will need.
I'll show you.
We've been hosting these things
at Sweet Apple Acres
every 100 moons
since we first planted roots
here in Ponyville.
Hey, who's that?
That'd be your great great
Auntie Applesauce
when she was just
about your age.
Now she used to go by
another name,
but everypony
started calling her Applesauce
after half her teeth fell out
when she was making apple jam.
Yeah. Never did find
them teeth in all those jars.
Hey, that's you, Granny.
GRANNY:
Sure is.
Apple family's been working
on that same old quilt
since our first reunion.
I can do it.
Oh, fingle-fangle.
Well, nopony told me
you actually had to knot
the end of the thread.
Okay, so I'll need to get
new quilting materials.
Fabric, needles, thread.
You've really been
working on the same quilt
since the first reunion?
Surely have.
I don't think we're ever gonna
finish that doggone thing.
Hey, what's going on
here?
GRANNY:
Well, you know us Apples
enjoy a good fritter.
Ooh! Hot, hot, hot.
Hey, where'd all them
apple fritters go?
And, who are you,
little one?
I'm Applejack.
More apple fritter?
GRANNY:
That's how we figured out
your sister had the appetite
of a full-grown stallion.
Better get twice as much
honey and flour, then,
50 more buckets of apples,
more oil, wood for the fire.
Now, stick an apple in my mouth
and roast my rump.
This one sure
brings back memories.
You know how Babs
is your favorite cousin?
Well, Apple Rose is mine.
The two of us
entered the seven-legged race
every reunion.
We're gonna win this one,
cousin.
You bet your hot diggity
derriere we are.
Come on, cousin,
speed it on up.
( upbeat theme playing )
Whoa!
Never won a single one
of them races.
Races. We'll need
cloth ties, a finish line.
Not much to a seven-legged
race, hmm.
And of course we can't forget
to take the big family photo.
We always snapped a photo
in front of the barn
at the end of every reunion.
It lets us see how
our family's grown.
Photo in front
of the barn, got it.
You sure have
some great memories
of these reunions,
don't you?
Indeedy, and I'm looking
forward to making more
at this one.
Oh, I'm sure everypony is,
and I do mean everypony.
We got the whole family
together this time around.
Who knows if they'll all be
able to make the next one?
That's true.
Busy as everypony's lives
are getting these days,
chances are pretty slim we'll
be this lucky next time around.
Don't worry, Granny,
I'm gonna make sure this
is the most memorable reunion
we've ever had.
I better get started.
I've got some planning to do.
Oh, hootenanny, would you look
what your second cousin
is wearing on her head.
Apple Bloom, what are you
doing up?
I was gonna ask you
the same thing.
I can't sleep.
My gears are turning in my head
about this reunion.
Yeah, I can't wait
to see my cousin Babs.
We're gonna do
so many fun things together.
Fun? That's just
the beginning of it.
Granny Smith handed me
the reins of this reunion,
and I'm gonna make
the most of it.
Apple Bloom, I've got so many
things planned,
you won't even have
a minute's rest.
( snoring )
Trust me, little sis.
This reunion
I'm putting together
is gonna be
worth the wait.
( snoring )
( crowing )
Whoo!
Rise and shine.
We don't have
much time.
( burps )
Don't forget the glitter.
( coughs )
( upbeat theme playing )
Think that'll do it.
And just in time too.
They're here.
( all cheering )
Apple Rose.
Oh.
Ooh, this is more exciting
than when it rained frogs.
Howdy, y'all.
And welcome
to the Apple Family Reunion.
( all cheering )
My name's Applejack, and I just
wanted to let y'all know
that I got a real big day
planned for you.
We're gonna start off
with an obstacle course
for the young 'uns
and some fritter making
and quilting
for the not-so-young 'uns.
And there's lots more to come
after that.
Hope y'all enjoy it.
Where is she?
Babs.
Coz.
I know it's hasn't
been that long
since we've seen
each other but--
It felt like forever.
I can't wait to tell
you about my new school.
I can't wait
to hear all about it.
Jeepers, where do I start?
Okay, so first day--
Babs. So glad
you could come.
What am I, gonna miss out
on spending time
with my favorite cousin?
Forget about it.
Why don't you two head over
to the obstacle course?
We kind of want to catch up
a little bit first.
Don't you worry.
There'll be plenty of time
for family bonding
while you're racing against
your other cousins.
All righty, ponies,
ready to have some fun?
Wow, is that
the finish line?
It's, like, a mile away
or something.
Actually, that's
just the marker
where you go on to
the next leg of the race.
There's more?
Much more. Trust me.
I have put together something
you are never gonna forget.
After the seven-legged race,
you're gonna want to hurry up
and head over here where you'll
be bobbing for apples.
Then you'll run around
these trees 50 times
until you're real
good and dizzy.
Then you'll jump
these big wooden hurdles,
and then there's the final leg
where you'll balance plates
on your head while saying,
"pappy pony picked a pluck
of pickly pluffnuggets"
over and over and over again.
The last pony standing wins.
Seriously?
Seriously. Come on, y'all, let's
start making some memories.
On your mark,
get set, go.
Whoo-whee.
Looking good, everypony.
Better go check
on the quilt.
How long you had those new
chompers, Auntie Applesauce?
A lady never reveals
the age of her teeth.
Ugh.
Don't you roll your eyes at me,
Miss Apple Rose.
I imagine you two think
I have forgotten
what you did to my
parasol six reunions ago.
We were just using it to help
break open that piñata.
Applejack,
delightful to see you.
Are you gonna join us
in some quilting?
Sorry, Auntie Applesauce,
I am busy,
busy, busy.
Y'all should
get started though.
We couldn't find
our rocking chairs.
I got rid of them
to make room for these.
This is the year
y'all are finally
gonna finish that quilt.
Finish it?
Won't that be exciting?
What's that?
I said,
won't that be...
exciting?
I suppose,
although I have been told
that too much excitement
can wreak havoc on this
youthful complexion of mine.
Oh.
( laughs )
That's the spirit.
What did she say?
Huh?
Good gracious.
Golden Delicious--
I think he's racing
with his cousins.
How is Scootaloo
and Sweetie Belle?
Great. Oh.
You all right?
So dizzy.
Oh.
You've got eight now,
don't you?
Oh sure do.
Tell you what.
My Apple Tart may just be
a baby, but he is a hoot.
Having fun?
Sure are.
Better pick up the pace
on these fritters though, huh?
Roll, fold, crimp,
slide to the left.
Now you try.
That's it. Gotta keep this
assembly line moving, gals.
We want every Apple here
to get the chance
to taste the best
darn fritters in Equestria.
BOTH:
Pappy pony picked
a pluck of pickly pluffnuggets.
Any other blank flanks
at your new school?
Yeah, two.
Do they want to be Crusaders?
Totally.
Great. Pappy pony picked a pluck
of pickly pluffnuggets.
Pappy pony picked a pluck
I can't feel my tongue.
Me, neither.
All right, Apples, break.
( sighs )
Finally.
Ooh, can't forget to capture
all these memories
for Granny's album.
Nothing
all that memorable there.
Or there.
Come on, Applejack, think.
You gotta kick
this thing up a notch.
Hmm.
I get that my big sis
wants this
to be, like,
a super awesome reunion,
but that was ridiculous.
I thought we'd never get
a minute to just hang out.
APPLEJACK:
And your minute's up.
Your fellow Apples are waiting
for you to join them.
Applejack, I haven't had
any time with Babs.
We were so busy with
that obstacle course
we didn't
even get to talk.
There'll be plenty of time
to bond with Babs
when we do the hayride.
Hayride?
All right, everypony,
step right up, take a seat,
and leave the driving
to these stallions.
Now, I know y'all
have been working real hard
making some
awesome memories,
and in all of our past reunions,
we always had
a nice and relaxing hayride
around the farm.
Which is why I decided
to change things up a bit
and try something
just a wee bit more exciting.
So let's get this show
on the road.
Giddyap.
( whinnying )
( upbeat country theme playing )
ALL:
Whoa!
I just had those
professionally polished.
Where in the world
does that girl have us headed?
The west orchard?
Yep.
What? I was joking.
Why, we haven't
tended those fields
since all the trees went
and got filled up with--
(Bats chirping)
ALL:
Oh.
Wowsa. I've ever seen
real fruit bats before.
Uh-oh.
( screaming )
( all gasping )
Everypony, don't move.
Ruined.
Everything is ruined.
Oh, Granny,
I'm so, so sorry.
Oh, it's all right,
child.
But it's not all right.
Just look at this.
The barn, and all my plans
for the perfect family reunion
are completely destroyed.
Maybe that's
good thing.
How can that possibly be
a good thing?
GRANNY:
Applejack, you've had us
so caught up
in all the doing, we haven't had
a second to enjoy the company
of the folks
we've been doing it with.
Really?
( all murmuring agreement )
Oh, Granny Smith,
here, you let me be in charge
of creating great memories,
and the only thing anypony's
gonna remember
about this reunion
is that it was the worst one
we ever had.
Hey, now, everypony's
still here, ain't they?
Still plenty of time
to make good memories.
You just gotta give everypony
a chance to actually make them.
The family photo.
Guess we can't take it
in front of the barn this year.
Unless...
Everypony,
I have one more activity.
Applejack.
Trust me, Granny Smith,
this'll be one we'll remember
for all the right reasons.
Whoo-hoo.
♪ Raise this barn
Raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Together
We can raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Up, up, up
Go the beams ♪
♪ Hammer those joints
Work in teams ♪
♪ Turn 'em round quick
By the right elbow ♪
♪ Grab a new partner
Here we go ♪
Come on, Apple family.
Let's get to it. Whoo-hoo.
♪ Raise this barn
Raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Together
We can raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Finish the frame
Recycling wood ♪
♪ Working hard
You're doing good ♪
♪ Turn 'em round quick
By the right elbow ♪
♪ Grab a new partner
Here we go ♪
ALL:
Yeah!
Whoo-whee.
♪ Raise this barn
Raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Together
We can raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Slats of wood
Come off the ground ♪
♪ Hold 'em up
And nail 'em down ♪
♪ Turn 'em round quick
By the left elbow ♪
♪ Grab a new partner
Here we go ♪
Come on, Apples.
Get her done.
♪ Look at us
We're family ♪
♪ Working together thankfully ♪
♪ We Apples
We are proud to say ♪
BOTH:
♪ Stick together the pony way ♪
APPLEJACK:
♪ Bow to your partner
Circle right ♪
♪ Get down
If you're scared of heights ♪
♪ Forward, back
And twirl around ♪
♪ The barn's gonna be
The best in town ♪
ALL:
Yeah!
Yee-haw. Attagirl.
All right,
let's get to it.
♪ Raise this barn
Raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Together
We can raise this barn ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Take your brushes
Young and old ♪
♪ Together paint it
Bright and bold ♪
♪ Turn 'em round quick
By the left elbow ♪
♪ Grab a new partner
Here we go ♪
ALL:
♪ We raised this barn
We raised this barn ♪
♪ Yes, we did ♪
♪ Together we sure
Raised this barn, yes we did ♪
♪ Being together
Counts the most ♪
♪ We all came here
From coast to coast ♪
♪ All we need
To strive to be ♪
♪ Is part of the Apple family ♪
Yeah!
( tender theme playing )
Oh!
( both laugh )
I can't wait
for the next reunion.
Me neither.
I mean, obviously we have
to get together before then.
( laughs ):
Obviously.
Well, you did it,
Applejack.
You put on a reunion that
everypony will remember.
Just had a couple minor hiccups
along the way.
Yeah, just a couple.
Oh, that's a good one.
( both laugh )
APPLEJACK:
"Dear Princess Celestia,
"today I learned a great lesson
about family,
"which if you think about it,
"is really the first group
of friends you ever make.
"Turns out that when you are
with folks you care about,
"you don't have to do much
to make that time memorable.
"Even the simplest
of activities
"can take on
a whole lot of meaning,
"and you'll find that you
remember the who
"long after
you've forgotten the what.
Your humble subject,
Applejack."
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪