( mellow theme playing )
( door opens )
News from
Northern Equestria,
uh, Your Highness.
Yes?
I am simply to tell you
that it has returned.
( gasps )
Find Princess Cadence
and Shining Armor.
Yes, Your Highness.
My dearest Twilight,
you must come
to Canterlot at once.
♪ My little pony
My little pony ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic
Makes it all complete ♪
♪ You have my ♪
♪ My little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
Where are all my quills?
( pants )
No. No. No. No.
No. Ugh!
I need the Magical Compendium,
Volumes 1 through 36.
Where is it?
( dramatic theme playing )
Flash cards.
I should make some flash cards.
Spike, I'm gonna need you
to quiz me
on everything, everything
I've ever learned.
Ever.
That isn't gonna be
enough cards.
Twilight, calm down.
It's just a test.
Just a test?
Princess Celestia wants
to give me some kind of exam,
and you're trying
to tell me to calm down
because it's just a test?
Uh, yes?
I'd say she's handling things
pretty well...considering.
( Twilight Sparkle screaming )
Are you sure you don't
want me to go as well?
Yes. Princess Cadence
and Shining Armor
are already there.
The others
will be joining them soon.
The empire's magic
is powerful.
It cannot fall again,
my sister.
She will succeed at her task,
and when she does,
we'll know that she is
that much closer to being ready.
( clears throat )
Trust me, little sister.
You wanted to see me?
To give me a test?
I brought my own quills
and plenty of paper
to show my work.
Sorry. Sorry.
This is a different kind
of test.
The Crystal Empire
has returned.
The Crystal Empire?
I'm sorry.
I-- I thought I'd studied.
Ooh, I don't think there's
anything in any of my books--
There wouldn't be.
Few remember
it ever existed at all.
Even my knowledge
of the empire is limited.
But what I do know is that
it contains a powerful magic.
One thousand years ago,
King Sombra, a unicorn
whose heart was black as night,
took over the Crystal Empire.
He was ultimately overthrown,
turned to shadow,
and banished to the ice
of the arctic north.
But not before he was able
to put a curse upon the empire,
a curse that caused it
to vanish into thin air.
If the empire is filled
with hope and love,
those things are reflected
across all of Equestria.
If hatred and fear take hold...
( ominous theme playing )
Which is why I need your help
finding a way to protect it.
You want me to help protect
an entire empire?
It is, as I said,
a different kind of test
but one I'm certain
you will pass.
How do I begin?
By joining Princess Cadence
and Shining Armor
in the Crystal Empire.
My brother is there?
He is.
And your Ponyville friends
will join you there as well.
I have every confidence
you will succeed.
And when you do,
I'll know you are ready
to move on to the next level
of your studies.
But what if I fail?
You won't.
But what if--?
But, Twilight,
in the end,
it must be you and you alone
who ultimately assists
Princess Cadence
and Shining Armor
in doing what needs to be done
to protect the empire.
Do you understand?
Mm-hmm.
Then go.
There is no time to lose.
Ah, Twilight!
That was fast.
Let me guess.
You got a perfect score.
A-minus?
B-plus?
Ah, Twilight, did you...
fail?
♪ I was prepared
To do my best ♪
♪ Thought I could handle
Any test ♪
♪ For I can do so many tricks ♪
♪ But I wasn't prepared
For this ♪
♪ Levitation
Would have been a breeze ♪
♪ Facts and figures
I recite with ease ♪
The square root of 546
is 23.36664289109.
She is correct.
♪ I could ace a quiz
On friendship's bliss ♪
♪ But I wasn't prepared
For this ♪
♪ Will I fail or will I pass? ♪
♪ I can't be sure ♪
♪ She can't be sure ♪
♪ My mind is sharp ♪
♪ My skills intact ♪
♪ My heart is pure ♪
♪ Her heart is pure ♪
♪ Oh, I've taken my share
Of licks ♪
♪ I've made it
Through the thin and thick ♪
♪ But, no, I wasn't ♪
♪ Oh, no, she wasn't ♪
♪ Oh, no, I wasn't ♪
♪ No, I wasn't ♪
♪ Prepared for this ♪
Uh, prepared
for what, exactly?
Twilight.
Did you pass?
Are we gonna celebrate
your awesomeness
with Princess Celestia?
TWILIGHT:
Not quite.
We're going
to the Crystal Empire.
Huh?
Crystal what?
( train whistle blows )
Ha, and you all made fun of me
for packing so many scarves.
Ugh! I didn't say a word.
Ah!
Hey. Come here.
SHINING ARMOR:
Twilight!
Shining Armor?
Twily, you made it!
We'd better get moving.
There are things out here
we really don't want
to run into after dark.
What kind of things?
Let's just say the empire
isn't the only thing
that's returned.
Something keeps trying
to get in.
We think it's the unicorn king
who originally cursed the place.
But Princess Celestia
said I was being sent here
to find a way
to protect the empire.
If King Sombra can't get in,
then it must already
be protected.
( creature howling distantly )
Ah! That-- That's one
of the things, isn't it?
We have to get
to the Crystal Empire now!
( snarling )
Go! Go!
SHINING ARMOR:
Almost there.
( sighs )
Everypony okay?
( ponies pant )
Oh, no.
Shining Armor, your horn.
Sparklerific!
RARITY:
It's gorgeous.
Absolutely gorgeous.
( stammers )
There are no words!
Focus, Rarity.
We're here to help Twilight,
not admire the scenery.
RAINBOW DASH:
Eh, I don't see
what the big deal is.
Just looks like another
old castle to me.
( scoffs and spits )
Another old--
Have you lost your mind?
Look at the magni--
( laughs )
Very funny.
Cadence!
Oh.
BOTH:
Sunshine, sunshine.
Ladybug's awake.
Clap your hooves
and do a little shake.
( both laugh )
One of these days
we need to get together
when the fate of Equestria
isn't hanging in the balance.
Are you okay?
Cadence has been able to use her
magic to spread love and light.
That seems to be
what is protecting it.
But she hasn't slept.
Barely eats.
I want to help her,
but my protection spell
has been countered
by King Sombra.
It's all right, Shining Armor.
I'm fine.
She's not fine. She can't
go on like this forever.
And if her magic were
to fade...
Well, you saw what's out there
waiting for that to happen.
That's why we're here.
APPLEJACK:
Why we're all here.
ALL:
Mm-hmm.
With Cadence putting
all her strength
into keeping her spell going
and me trying to keep an eye
on signs of trouble
in the Arctic,
we haven't been able
to gather much information
from the Crystal Ponies.
Crystal Ponies?
( laughs )
There are Crystal Ponies?
Um, ahem,
please continue.
But we have to believe
one of them knows
how we can protect the empire
without having
to use Cadence's magic.
A research paper.
Huh?
That must be part
of my test.
To gather information
from the Crystal Ponies
and deliver it to you.
This is gonna be great.
I love research papers.
Yeah. Who doesn't?
Oh, oh, oh,
let me guess.
Is it Spike? No, no, no.
Fluttershy? Rarity?
Don't worry, big brother.
I am really good
at this sort of thing.
Are you sure?
Absolutely sure?
I'm sorry.
I wish I could help you.
But I can't seem
to remember anything
before King Sombra came
to power.
And I don't want
to remember anything
about the time he ruled
over us.
( shuddering )
King Sombra's spell
must be why
their coats aren't...
crystally.
Have we really been gone
a thousand years?
Yes.
It feels like it was
just yesterday.
If you think of anything,
even the smallest thing...
Of course.
Well, that was
a total bust.
Maybe the others
are having better luck.
A way to protect the empire.
You know anything
about it or what?
I wish I could help you.
Really.
Come on.
You gotta know something.
But I don't have
any information.
Oh, um, excuse me.
Oh, hello.
Um, I was just wondering...
Oh, oh, that's okay.
Um, you all look really busy.
( laughs nervously )
Time to gather some intel.
It just feels like something
is missing.
I know.
It looks the same,
but it doesn't feel the same.
Because it isn't.
A spy!
( screams )
A spy?
How did they know?
Ah, must have noticed
my night-vision goggles.
Ooh, night visiony.
( hums )
And when you flip your mane,
it simply must create
a rainbow of color.
Wouldn't I look
just magnificent?
So sparkly.
( giggles )
I got nothing so far.
Oh, me neither.
My cover has been blown.
I repeat, my cover
has been blown.
Okay.
Sorry, Twilight.
These Crystal Ponies seem
to have some kind
of collective amnesia
or something.
Only thing I was able
to get out of them
was something
about a library.
( gasps )
A library?
Well, why didn't you say so?
Uh, thought I just did.
I just--
I don't even know what to--
There are no words.
( clears throat )
May I help you?
Yes. We're looking
for a book.
We have plenty of those.
You do. You really do.
We're looking
for a history book,
something that might tell us
how the empire
might have protected itself
from danger back in the day.
Yes, of course.
History. History.
Ah, yes.
Which is where, exactly?
I...I can't seem
to remember.
I'm not sure
I actually work here.
Ugh!
We'll just take a look around.
I'm sure we can find it
on our own.
Let me know
if you find anything.
I like her.
Uh, anyone else starting
to think this is a lost cause?
No. No. No. No.
No.
Yes!
History
of the Crystal Empire.
I just hope
it has the answers we need.
A Crystal Faire.
According to this book, it was
established by their first queen
and became
their most important tradition.
The faire was held
every year to...
"Renew the spirit of love
and unity in the empire
so they could protect it
from harm."
My friends and I
can put it together.
Everything we need to know is
in the book.
That sounds
pretty promising.
We'll get started
right away.
Come on, Spike, we've got
a Crystal Faire to put together.
( groans )
♪ Princess Cadence
Needs our help ♪
♪ Her magic
Will not last forever ♪
♪ I think we can do it
But we need to work together ♪
♪ We have to get this right ♪
♪ Yes, we have
To make them see ♪
♪ We can save the Crystal Ponies
With their history ♪
♪ It says that they
Liked jousting ♪
♪ They flew a flag
Of many hues ♪
♪ Made sweets
Of Crystal Berries ♪
♪ They had a petting zoo
With tiny ewes ♪
♪ Oh, we have to get
This right ♪
♪ Yes, we have
To make them see ♪
♪ We can save the Crystal Ponies
With their history ♪
♪ There was
A Crystal Flugelhorn ♪
♪ That everypony
Liked to play ♪
♪ And a Crystal Kingdom anthem ♪
♪ Can you learn it in a day? ♪
♪ Oh, we have to get
This right ♪
♪ Yes, we have to
Make them see ♪
♪ We can save
The Crystal Ponies ♪
♪ With their history ♪
It looks amazing.
I don't know how I could have
done this without you.
One last check to make sure
everything is in place
and then the festivities
can begin.
What's this thing for?
The last page of the book
mentioned a crystal heart
as the faire's centerpiece,
so I used my magic to cut one
out of a crystal block.
Nice work, Twi.
Think we're ready to get
this faire up and running.
( inhaling deeply )
( playing off-key notes )
Hear ye, hear--
Flugelhorn!
( laughs nervously )
My bad.
( clears throat )
Hear ye, hear ye!
Princess Cadence
and Prince Shining Armor
do cordially invite you
to attend the Crystal Faire.
( Crystal Ponies murmuring )
Come on in, y'all.
Got food and drinks
thataway.
Games and crafts
are thataway.
Crystal Heart's in the back
near the princess.
Did she say,
"crystal heart"?
( murmuring )
We totally nailed it, right?
Must be feeling a lot of love
and unity about now.
Gonna have some grub, huh?
What are you thinking?
Crystal Empire Berry Pie?
Maybe some
Crystal Corn on the Cob?
What is with these ponies?
Seeing all of this,
I feel like I'm starting
to remember,
remember things
from before the king.
Me too.
( gasps )
BOTH:
The Crystal Heart!
Do you think
they really have it?
Of course we have it.
Can't have a Crystal Faire
without the Crystal Heart,
right?
Of course you can't.
The whole purpose
of the Crystal Faire is
to lift the spirits
of the Crystal Ponies
so the light within them
can power the Crystal Heart
so that the empire
can be protected.
I do work at the library.
What's that
about powering the heart?
I just can't believe
you found it.
King Sombra said
he'd hidden it away
where we would never
see it again.
I only hope it will still be as
powerful after all these years.
Mmm, funnel cake.
( squeaks )
Why did you--?
I think we may have
a problem.
I didn't know
it was an actual relic.
The book didn't
mention anything
about the Crystal Ponies
powering the heart.
There was a page missing.
How did I not notice?
It's all right,
Twilight.
Twily.
( creature howling distantly )
( ominous theme playing )
( wind howling )
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪