SPIKE:
Six, seven, eight, nine,
10, 11, 12.
Hm,
that's not that many.
Are you kidding?
How are you supposed
to read 12 books in one weekend?
Princess Celestia obviously
thinks I can
or she would never have assigned
them to me.
I'm not planning
on letting her down.
Well, I hope you're not planning
on sleeping, then, either.
Actually, Spike, why don't you
take the day off?
Really?
Why not?
These books are gonna
keep me busy for a while.
Hm, I do have a long list
of things I've been dying to do.
"Touch nose with tongue."
Done.
"Play bongos on my belly."
"Smell my dirty feet."
[SNIFFING]
Done!
Huh. That didn't take nearly
as long as I thought it would.
♪ My little pony
My little pony ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic
Makes it all complete ♪
♪ You have my ♪
♪ My little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
What to do?
( cat screeches )
A hot air balloon ride.
Oh, no. Wait.
Runaway balloon!
Sorry!
Whew.
That was a close one.
If I didn't know better,
I would swear that I was
in the middle of the dark
and scary Everfree forest.
( animal yelps )
What was that?
Come on, Spike.
Just because this forest is full
of wild, dangerous animals
doesn't mean
that you're gonna see one.
( sniffing )
( branch snaps )
Ah!
( growling )
( screams )
( timber wolves barking
and snarling )
Come and get me,
you big goons.
Run.
I'm running.
( Spike screaming )
Whew.
SPIKE: Wow, Applejack.
That was amazing.
You rocketed those boulders
at them like they were rockets.
Pow! Pow! Pow!
You saved my life.
Aw, don't mention it,
Spike.
Come on, we should be heading
on back now.
Man, am I lucky you were
out here.
Uh, why were you
out here?
Saw the balloon floating
by with no pony in it
and I came out here
to investigate.
Guess you did too, huh?
Uh, yeah.
I was investigating
the runaway hot air balloon too.
So now that that mystery's
been solved,
let's get out here, huh?
Thanks for walking me home,
Spike.
That was mighty kind
of you,
but now I have some chores
that need tending to,
so see you later.
What chores?
I'll do them.
That's sweet,
but you don't have--
It's the least I can do.
You saved my life.
I need to repay
the favor.
Shoot, Spike, that's what
friends do for each other.
You don't need
to repay the favor.
Yes, I do.
Sugar, it's okay.
It's not necessary.
Applejack,
you don't understand.
This is something
that I really need to do.
I hate to get in the way of you
doing something you need to.
Great.
What should I do?
Uh...Apple Bloom's over yonder,
giving little Piggington
a bath.
I was gonna lend her
a hoof,
but maybe you could lend her
one instead.
On the double.
Applejack said
I could help you.
Great.
I could use all
the help I can get.
Wait till Applejack sees
how you sparkle.
Ta-da.
Good job, you two.
Applejack,
is it okay if I get going?
I don't wanna be late
for my Crusaders meeting.
We're getting fitted
for water skis.
Ha. You definitely don't want
to be late for that.
Water-skiing Cutie Mark,
here I come.
Spike,
you can head on out too.
I reckon you have re-paid me
in full
so we are officially
even-Steven.
What? Oh, no.
We aren't even close
to being even-Steven.
Please, Applejack, you must
allow me to assist you further.
I don't know, Spike.
Just don't feel right
to have you doing things
for me.
Please.
Really, you don't--
Pretty please.
It's just not necessary--
Pretty, pretty,
pretty please.
Oh, all right.
You can help Granny Smith
and me bake some...
Pies. Pies.
I'm helping Applejack make
some pies.
Spike,
little feller,
could you get us
some more eggs?
SPIKE:
Coming right up.
( crash )
SPIKE:
Ah, oops.
Sorry, Applejack.
Let me get something
to clean that up.
Appreciate all your help today,
sugar cube,
but I can take it
from here.
Don't be ridiculous.
It is my honor
and my duty.
Today is just
the beginning.
What's that now?
You saved my life.
According to the
"Spike the Dragon Code,"
I owe you a life debt
and must serve you.
Now,
what about Twilight?
Doesn't she need your help
and such?
Huh. You're right.
I better break the news
to Twilight.
I just hope she doesn't take
it too hard.
Be right back.
Come on, Spike.
This is your personal moral,
ethical Dragon Code
we're talking about.
You have to do this.
It's not like you and Twilight
won't be friends anymore.
But it won't be the same.
But it has to be done.
Twilight, Applejack
just saved my life
from horrible,
dragon-eating timber wolves.
Mm-hm...
And, as you are aware,
I adhere to my Dragon Code
and this means
I must serve her
for the rest
of my natural-born days.
I'm sure you understand.
Mm-hm...
It's been an honor being
your faithful assistant.
Sounds good.
( sighs )
She said it was okay.
Really?
So with Twilight's blessing,
I am free to follow my code
and serve you until...
Well, until forever.
Listen, sugar cube, I completely
respect your Dragon Code,
truly I do,
but I just can't cotton
with you permanently serving me.
Please, Applejack.
My Dragon Code is a part
of me.
I have to be true to myself.
If you don't let me do this,
I won't be
a noble dragon anymore.
Oh. Well,
I can't have you feeling
like you're not a noble dragon,
now can I?
Great.
Then from here on in,
your wish is my command.
Oh. Um. Okay.
I would like you to...
Hm...
Oh...
Help me take some of the pie
you made to--
Rarity?
Uh...
Sure. Why not?
I helped bake it.
Ugh.
You even look good
when you're chewing.
Who looks good
when they're chewing?
Aren't you gonna have
some more?
I had a big lunch.
It's 10 in the morning.
Breakfast.
A big breakfast.
Oh. Okay.
Maybe you could take her plate
back to the kitchen
and wash it off?
As you wish.
What was
that all about?
Ah, I saved Spike
from some timber wolves
in the Everfree Forest
and now he thinks
he has to serve me forever.
Oh!
What I wouldn't give to have
some pony forever in my debt.
I'd get them
to organize my closets
and give me pedicures
and help me with my sewing--
Okay, I get it. Having somepony
to do things for you
would be
a dream come true.
But I don't feel right
having Spike thinking
he owes me something.
And you tasted
that pie.
Sometimes his help isn't
that helpful.
( crash )
Do you have
a broom I could borrow?
A.J., Rary.
What's happening?
Applejack saved Spike's life
and now he has
to serve her forever.
Sweet. What are you
having him do?
Wash your laundry?
Clean your room?
Help you
with your unfinished novel?
Mine's about this awesome
Pegasus
who's the best flyer ever
and becomes the captain
of the Wonderbolts.
How ever did you come
up with that ingeniously woven,
intricate plot line?
Just came to me.
Thing is I don't really want him
to serve me forever.
But I don't know how
to get him to stop.
That's easy.
Just make him help you with
something really, really hard.
I don't know.
I don't want him to get hurt.
Please.
He'll quit way before
there's even a chance
of getting hurt.
( crash )
Leave this
to me.
So, Spike, Applejack was gonna
help me stack some hay
so I could practice smashing
through it,
but I'm feeling extra,
extra powerful today.
You are?
Yeah, I am.
So instead of hay,
I'm gonna
smash through rocks.
Rocks?
Yeah, a tower of rocks.
And you're gonna build it.
I am?
Yeah.
I mean, unless you don't want
to help Applejack.
I do.
It is Spike's Dragon Code.
Then get to it.
Trust me.
This is going to work like
a charm.
( panting )
Huh. I was sure he'd give up
after, like, three rocks.
Oh, goodness.
If it'd been me,
I'd have just pretended I didn't
have anything for him to do.
Why didn't I think
of that?
SPIKE:
Is this is high enough?
APPLEJACK:
That's plenty high.
Come on down, Spike.
Bad news: He actually ended up
building the whole rock tower.
Good news:
I've got a rock tower
to knock down.
( Spike laughing and cheering )
You can do it.
( Spike laughing )
All right! Yeah!
( loud crash )
That was awesome.
Wanna do it again,
Rainbow Dash?
Applejack can re-build it
for you.
And when I say "Applejack,"
I of course mean me.
Sure. Why not?
No.
I mean, I don't
think Rainbow Dash
needs any more
of your help.
My help--
She doesn't need it.
Right,
Rainbow Dash?
Yeah.
I guess I'm good.
For now.
And so am I.
I just can't think of one more
thing I need help with.
So you don't have
to do anything else.
What do you mean you can't think
of anything else
I can help with?
Exactly that.
There's nothing else.
I don't want you
to do anything.
If I don't help you,
how will I know
I'm a noble dragon?
Well, uh--
Maybe there's things you need
help with
that you don't even realize
that you need help with.
If she needed help
I think she'd realize it.
Maybe not.
Maybe Applejack needs help
realizing
what she needs help with.
Like,
maybe your back itches.
That does feel good.
( laughing ):
See?
Or you might need help
remembering your favorite song.
♪ The dragon is
The finest creature ever ♪
♪ There's more to him
Than just guarding treasure ♪
I don't think that's her
favorite--
Or you might need help
breathing.
Breathing?
I certainly do not--
See? There are plenty of things
I can help you with.
And you don't even have
to trouble yourself
with thinking of them.
No. I'll think of them.
Let me think of them.
As you wish.
Twilight? Twilight,
are you there?
Twilight.
Ah!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
( sighs ):
No, it's okay.
I need to take
a break anyway.
What's going on?
I know Spike told you
that he was gonna follow
his Dragon Code
and serve me forever for saving
him from the timber wolves
and that you were okay
with it, but--
Wait. What?
He said he told you
all about it.
I'm guessing maybe you were
a little distracted
when he told you.
Maybe a little.
Should've realized you wouldn't
have let him go so easily.
Well, now that you know what's
going on,
maybe you could talk some sense
into him.
Oh, Applejack,
I wish I could,
but this is the Dragon Code
we're talking about.
Surely you know how important
the Dragon Code is to a dragon?
I sure am starting to.
There's only one other way Spike
is gonna fulfill
the debt he feels he owes you.
Seventy,
71, 72, 73, 74, 75...
All right, you all,
here's the deal,
Spike needs to save my life.
And you want us to shoot you
out of a cannon
toward a hornet's nest
and give Spike a butterfly net
so he can catch you mere seconds
before you hit the nest
and are stung
by a angry hornets.
I'll wear this moustache.
No. I am gonna be attacked
by a timber wolf.
( both gasp )
Can I still wear
the moustache?
APPLEJACK:
When I give the signal,
Pinky Pie and Rarity
will come running
out of the woods
being pursued
by the timber wolf.
I'll start to run too,
but then pretend to get
my hoof stuck.
I'll ask Spike
to help me dislodge it.
And he will
and I'll be able to get away
from the terrifying timber wolf.
Having saved me
from certain doom,
Spike will then consider
us even.
Everybody get it?
Uh-huh.
I'll do my best.
Just one question.
Yes.
No.
Suit yourself.
( clears throat )
We're all ready
to play our parts,
but are you sure you're ready
to play yours, Applejack?
What do you mean?
Show us your best
damsel-in-distress move.
Uh...oh,
well, uh...
How's this?
Whoo!
Absolutely horrendous.
Okay, this needs
some serious work.
Now, first you must
lift your foreleg
up to your forehead
like so.
SPIKE:
Applejack.
No time.
Here he comes.
Uh, over here, Spike.
You said you had something else
you needed me to do?
Oh. Yes, I...
I was just hoping
you could maybe, uh,
sweep up all those leaves
for a compost pile.
But, of course.
Oh, by the way,
there are exactly
24,567,837
blades of grass
at Sweet Apple Acres.
I can't believe you counted
every single one of them.
SPIKE:
You asked me to.
And as a noble dragon
and follower
of my Dragon Code, I--
( Rainbow Dash roaring )
That was very
convincing.
RARITY:
Timber wolf!
( sobbing ):
We are doomed!
( screaming )
See? Like that.
( hooves beating )
( laughing )
( roaring )
APPLEJACK:
Oh, no.
I seem to have got
my hoof caught
in between two rocks.
I cannot run away.
I am a damsel
in distress.
Help me, Spike.
Wait a minute.
No, no.
Don't wait a minute.
Save me from the terrifying
timber wolf.
Well, he would be terrifying
if he
wasn't...a fake.
You got the clomping
of his claws.
The roar was spot on.
And the detail on his face
is pretty good.
But you forgot
one thing.
His breath.
You can smell a real
Timber wolf's breath
from a mile--
( both sniffing )
( laughing )
Too late.
I'm already on--
( Twilight Sparkle screams )
RAINBOW DASH:
Timber wolf!
( snarls )
( all roaring )
SPIKE:
Timber wolf!
( screams )
( crashing )
Ow.
Uh-oh.
Applejack, come on.
( straining )
I can't.
I'm really stuck.
No more messing around.
Let's go.
( Applejack straining )
( growling )
Come on.
( roaring )
Forget it, Spike.
You gotta
get out of here.
Would you just forget
your Dragon Code already and go.
( timber wolf roars )
No.
I have to save you.
( hacking )
Let's get out of here.
( grunting )
( coughing )
What happened to you
guys back there?
Thought you were
right behind us.
My hoof was stuck
and that timber wolf
was coming right at me.
Wait, you were
actually stuck?
Uh-huh.
But Spike picked up a pebble
and rocketed that thing right
at the huge timber wolf's mouth
and saved my life.
Ah, it was nothing.
It was something
all right.
Of course I wouldn't
have needed help
if I hadn't been trying
to stage a fake
Timber wolf attack
in the first place.
Yeah.
What was that all about?
( sighs )
I know this code thing's
important to you,
but if something like this
comes up in the future,
think maybe we can
go back to my code,
say that's what
friends do,
and leave
it at that?
I promise I won't think
of you as any less noble.
Sounds good to me.
But maybe let's just try
to avoid situations
where one of us actually needs
the other one
to save their life.
You got yourself a deal.
Thanks, Spike.
Happy to help.
Don't know what I'd do
without you.
No, really. I'm really, really,
really happy to help you.
( laughs )
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
Aww.
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪