&gt;&gt; TRY AGAIN, TWI.
YOU CAN DO IT.
&gt;&gt; PHEW!
THIS SPELL'S A TOUGHIE.
BUT I FEEL LUCKY THIS TIME.
ONE, TWO...
&gt;&gt; HI!
[ TINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
PINKIE, WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
&gt;&gt; 'CAUSE HUGS ARE FUNERIFFIC!
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU THROW ONE
AROUND A FRIEND.
WHATCHA DOIN'?
&gt;&gt; TRYING TO TURN THAT APPLE
INTO AN ORANGE.
&gt;&gt; BUT YOU KIND OF THREW HER AIM
OFF.
&gt;&gt; WHEE!
WHAT A CUTE ORANGE BIRDIE!
DO ME NEXT, TWILIGHT!
DO ME! DO ME!
[ BOING! ]
OOH!
RARITY, WANT TO SEE TWILIGHT
TURN ME INTO AN ORANGE?
IT'S GONNA BE FUNNA-FUN-FUN!
&gt;&gt; AS FUN AS CREATING AN
HAUTE-COUTURE ENSEMBLE THAT I
JUST FINISHED MAKING?
DELIGHTFUL, NO?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
THIS IS TERRIBLE!
&gt;&gt; I ADMIT IT'S PERHAPS NOT MY
FINEST WORK, BUT I --
&gt;&gt; YOU HAD TOTAL, AWESOME,
AMAZING FUN, AND I MISSED OUT ON
IT?!
[ WHIMPERS ]
WAIT.
WHAT IF THERE'S MORE AWESOME,
AMAZING FUN WITH FRIENDS
HAPPENING SOMEWHERE IN PONYVILLE
RIGHT NOW THAT I'M MISSING OUT
ON, TOO?!
[ WHOOSH! ]
&gt;&gt; WE WEREN'T GONNA TURN HER
INTO AN ORANGE.
I SWEAR!
[ WHIP CRACKING ]
&gt;&gt; HEY, RAINBOW DASH.
WHATCHA DOIN'?
&gt;&gt; THIS PUNK CLOUD GOT SO HEAVY,
IT'S MAKING FOG.
FIGURE I'LL THIN THIS BAD BOY
OUT SO IT FLOATS BACK UP.
&gt;&gt; OOH! FUN!
[ TWIRL! ]
GOTTA GO!
&gt;&gt; UH, THANKS, PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; HEY, APPLEJACK.
THAT LOOKS LIKE FUN.
CAN I JOIN YOU?
WHEE!
NEXT TIME, I'LL PULL YOU.
[ ZOOM! ]
&gt;&gt; [ SLURPING ]
&gt;&gt; FLUTTERSHY!
[ Panting ] THERE...
YOU...
ARE.
DOING...
ANYTHING...
FUN?
&gt;&gt; NOT ESPECIALLY.
&gt;&gt; OH, GOOD.
FUN IS HARD!
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
&gt;&gt; FEELING BETTER, PINKIE?
&gt;&gt; ABSO-TUTELY-LUTELY!
THANKS FOR LETTING ME REST IN
YOUR BUTTERFLY GROVE WHILE I GET
MY PINKIE STRENGTH BACK.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S JUST THE THING!
I'VE GOT SO MANY WONDERFUL
FRIENDS HAVING FUN IN EVERY LAST
CORNER OF PONYVILLE, I CAN'T
FIGURE OUT HOW TO KEEP UP WITH
IT ALL.
IT'S DRIVING ME EVEN MORE
COCO-LOCO THAN USUAL!
&gt;&gt; I CAN PROMISE TO NOT DO
ANYTHING FUN AT ALL IF THAT
WOULD HELP.
&gt;&gt; YOU ARE SUCH A GOOD FRIEND.
&gt;&gt; THERE YOU ARE, PINKIE.
BEEN LOOKING EVERYWHERE FOR YOU,
GIRL.
&gt;&gt; HEY, PINKIE.
GOT SOMETHING FUN PLANNED THIS
AFTERNOON, THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO KNOW ABOUT.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
WELL, I'LL BE AN APPLE CRISP.
I'M HERE FOR THE SAME REASON.
&gt;&gt; THIS IS PERFECT!
EVERYONE WILL NOW BRING THEIR
FUN TO ME.
OH! THIS WILL SOLVE EVERYTHING!
WHY DIDN'T I THINK OF THAT?
&gt;&gt; ACTUALLY, WHAT I MEANT IS
AFTER I'M DONE WHIPPING UP
TODAY'S WEATHER, I'LL BE
CHILLING BY THE LAKE, CATCHING
SOME RAYS.
WANT TO HANG?
&gt;&gt; I AM SO THERE.
WHEE!
&gt;&gt; AND MY FAMILY'S HAVING A BARN
RAISING THIS AFTERNOON AT
SWEET APPLE ACRES.
&gt;&gt; AND I'M ALSO SO THERE!
WHEE! WHEE!
&gt;&gt; BUT THAT'S WHEN I'LL BE AT
THE SWIMMING HOLE.
OH, WELL. DOESN'T MATTER.
WHICHEVER ONE YOU CHOOSE IS OKAY
WITH ME.
&gt;&gt; ME TOO.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
CHOOSE?
&gt;&gt; ONE...
TWO...
[ TINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; [ CROAKS ]
[ BOING! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
&gt;&gt; PINKIE!
WHAT IN THE WIDE-WIDE WORLD OF
EQUESTRIA ARE YOU DOING NOW?
&gt;&gt; TIMING MYSELF GALLOPING BACK
AND FORTH BETWEEN THE SWIMMING
HOLE AND SWEET APPLE ACRES.
I'M TRYING TO CUT DOWN MY TIME
SO RAINBOW DASH DIVES OFF THE
SWING, I CAN GET TO SWEET APPLE
ACRES TO HELP WITH THE BARN
RAISING, AND THEN BE BACK IN
TIME TO SEE RAINBOW DASH HIT THE
WATER AFTER DOING A DOUBLE FLIP.
IF I CAN CUT MY TIME BY ONLY
20 MINUTES, I'M GOOD.
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
OH, PINKIE.
I'M AFRAID NO MATTER HOW HARD
YOU TRY, THE ONLY WAY TO PULL
SOMETHING LIKE THAT OFF IS IF
THERE'S MORE OF YOU TO GO
AROUND.
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
[ ALARM RINGS ]
&gt;&gt; THAT'S IT, TWILIGHT!
THE LEGEND OF THE MIRROR POOL!
&gt;&gt; LEGEND OF THE WHO-WHAT NOW?
PINKIE!
I'M FAMILIAR WITH LOADS OF
LEGENDS, AND I NEVER HEARD OF --
&gt;&gt; DOES THIS MEAN PRACTICE IS
OVER?
&gt;&gt; OF COURSE NOT.
BACK TO WORK.
&gt;&gt; SEEMS LIKE HARDLY ANYPONY'S
BEEN HERE IN AGES.
I HOPE I'M REMEMBERING THE
RHYMES RIGHT FROM MY
NANA PINKIE'S STORY.
WHERE THE BRAMBLES ARE THICKEST,
THERE YOU WILL FIND A POND
BEYOND THE MOST TWISTED OF
[echoes] VINES.
WHO'S THERE?!
I HEARD A VOICE!
OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
IT WAS ME.
OUCH! OH!
STOP SCRATCHING AT ME, BRAMBLES!
WHOA!
[ PING! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ Echoing ] THE MIRROR POOL!
OH, AND THERE'S THAT VOICE
AGAIN.
AH, PINKIE, YOU HAVE GOT TO STOP
TALKING TO YOURSELF.
STARTING NOW.
AND INTO HER OWN REFLECTION SHE
STARED, YEARNING FOR ONE WHOSE
REFLECTION SHE SHARED AND
SOLEMNLY SWEARED NOT TO BE
SCARED, AT THE PROSPECT DOUBLY
THERE.
&gt;&gt; WHEE!
&gt;&gt; WOW. THE LEGEND IS TRUE.
IT REALLY WORKED!
OKAY, WAIT, I PROMISED NOT TO
TALK TO MYSELF ANYMORE.
I SHOULD SAY SOMETHING TO HER.
OR WOULD THAT STILL BE TALKING
TO MYSELF?
EXCUSE ME...ME, CAN I HAVE A
WORD WITH YOU?
UH, I MEAN, ME?
LISTEN, I CAN SEE YOU'RE HAVING
LOTS OF FUN, BUT --
&gt;&gt; FUN! DID SOMEBODY SAY FUN?!
WHERE?!
&gt;&gt; I DID OVER HERE.
&gt;&gt; I THOUGHT SOMEONE SAID
SOMETHING ABOUT FUN!
WHERE IS IT?!
OVER HERE? OVER HERE?
I DON'T SEE IT.
WHERE IS IT? WHERE IS IT?
&gt;&gt; OH, CALM YOURSELF.
THERE'S LOADS OF FUN TO BE HAD
IN PONYVILLE WITH MY GIRLS.
TROT ON OVER BACK TO PONYVILLE
WITH ME, AND I'LL TELL YOU ALL
ABOUT IT.
AND THEN THERE'S RARITY.
SHE'S THE ONE WITH ALL THE FANCY
CLOTHES AND RIBBONS AND STUFF.
I'M THINKING SHE CAN MAKE US ALL
MATCHING T-SHIRTS THAT SAY
"TEAM PINKIE" AND --
&gt;&gt; IS THIS PONYVILLE?
WHERE'S THE FUN?
&gt;&gt; UH, WELL, LET'S SEE.
APPLEJACK'S HAVING A BARN
RAISING AT --
[ ZOOM! ]
IT'S THATAWAY!
[ ZIP! ]
WAIT! COME BACK!
DON'T FORGET TO MEET ME BACK
HERE TO TELL ME EVERYTHING ABOUT
EVERYTHING, LIKE I WAS THERE
MYSELF.
BECAUSE I'M YOU AND -- AND
YOU'RE ME AND -- OH, MY GOSH!
THIS IS THE GREATEST PLAN EVER!
[ SQUEAKS ]
NOW, OFF TO DOUBLE MY FUN!
[ ZOOM! ]
&gt;&gt; [ YAWNS ]
&gt;&gt; LET'S ROCK THIS POOL, PONIES!
[ POP! ]
WHEE!
COMING IN, DASHY?
THE WATER'S GREAT.
IT'S TOTALLY WET AND EVERYTHING.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW.
CLOUD BUSTING WAS TOUGHER WORK
THAN USUAL TODAY.
I'M KIND OF EXHAUSTED.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S FINE. YOU RELAX.
AT LEAST WE'LL STILL BE
TOGETHER.
&gt;&gt; GLAD YOU MADE IT, PINKIE.
I THOUGHT YOU MAYBE WENT TO
APPLEJACK'S INSTEAD.
&gt;&gt; I DID.
&gt;&gt; OH. THE BARN UP YET?
&gt;&gt; I HAVE NO IDEA.
&gt;&gt; BUT I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU
WERE JUST AT APPLEJACK'S.
&gt;&gt; ACTUALLY, I'M PROBABLY STILL
ON MY WAY THERE NOW!
WHEE!
&gt;&gt; OH, PINKIE PIE.
I'M SO GLAD YOU WANDERED BY.
I KNOW I PROMISED NOT TO HAVE
ANY FUN TODAY, BUT, OH, I
COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
ALL OF MY CRITTER FRIENDS WANTED
A PICNIC, AND I COULDN'T
DISAPPOINT THEM.
COME JOIN US.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF HAY JUICE AND
MARMALADE TO GO AROUND.
DON'T WE, CRITTERS?
[ CRITTERS CHATTERING ]
[ MOUSE SQUEAKS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHOMP ]
WAIT!
BUT THAT SOUNDS SUPERFUN!
OH, BUT APPLEJOHN SOUNDS
SUPERFUN, TOO!
AND -- AND I CAN'T DO ONE
WITHOUT MISSING OUT ON THE
OTHER!
&gt;&gt; WHO'S APPLEJOHN?
&gt;&gt; TWO FUN THINGS AT ONCE!
BUT WHICH -- WHICH -- OH, CAN'T
DECIDE!
[ PANTING ]
TROUBLE BREATHING.
[ GASPING ]
WALLS CLOSING IN!
&gt;&gt; WALLS?
BUT WE'RE OUTSIDE.
&gt;&gt; AAH!
[ ZOOM! ]
&gt;&gt; GOODNESS.
WAS IT SOMETHING I SAID?
[ BEAR GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; YES!
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; SO, YOU SEE, THAT'S HOW I'M
ABLE TO HAVE FUN IN TWO PLACES
AT ONCE.
&gt;&gt; DUPLICATES OF YOU, HUH?
[ SCOFFS ]
YEAH, SURE, PINKIE.
[ Yawning ] I WAS JUST GEARING
UP TO CATCH SOME Z's.
SO, UH...
&gt;&gt; GOTCHA!
I'LL HAVE THE REST OF MY FUN
REALLY QUIETLY.
Whee!
&gt;&gt; HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
&gt;&gt; JUST TRYING TO SHOW A LITTLE
CONSIDERATION FOR MY SLEEPY
FRIEND.
[ WHIP! ]
[ WHIFFLE! ]
OOH! OOH! GOTTA RUN!
LOOKS LIKE I'M TRYING TO GET MY
ATTENTION.
EXCUSE ME.
&gt;&gt; AND ME.
[ RATTLE! ]
&gt;&gt; OOH! OOH!
TELL ME ALL ABOUT IT!
DID THEY PULL THE WALLS OF THE
BARN UP SLOW OR FAST?
&gt;&gt; I --
&gt;&gt; MAYBE SLOW TO MEDIUM-FAST?
SOMEWHERE IN THAT RANGE?
&gt;&gt; I --
&gt;&gt; OOH! DID YOU GET ICE CREAM?!
WHAT KINDS DID THEY HAVE?!
BANANA BRICKLE?
&gt;&gt; I DIDN'T MAKE IT!
I WAS ON MY WAY THERE, AND THEN
FLUTTERSHUTTER --
&gt;&gt; FLUTTERSHY.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, HER.
SHE OFFERED SOMETHING ELSE FUN
FOR ME TO DO -- A PICNIC, WITH
CUTE LITTLE ANIMALS.
&gt;&gt; AW.
HOW COULD YOU SAY NO TO THAT?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING!
THEN I WOULD HAVE MISSED THE
SUPERFUN THING WITH APPLESAUCE!
&gt;&gt; APPLEJACK.
&gt;&gt; [ Crying ] SO I DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING FUN AT ALL!
&gt;&gt; OH, MY POOR, POOR ME.
THERE, THERE.
TELL ME WHAT.
WE JUST NEED A COUPLE MORE
PINKIE PIES.
EASY-PEASY.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
&gt;&gt; COME ON!
WOULD I LIE TO ME?
&gt;&gt; Both: AND SOLEMNLY SWEAR NOT
TO BE SCARED AT THE PROSPECT OF
BEING DOUBLY THERE.
&gt;&gt; LOOK! A DOUBLE ME!
&gt;&gt; I THINK YOU MEAN A
DOUBLE-DOUBLE ME.
PLUS ANOTHER DOUBLE-DOUBLE ME,
WHICH MAKES TWO
DOUBLE-DOUBLE ME's, OR A
DOUBLE-DOUBLE-DOUBLE ME, IF YOU
WILL.
&gt;&gt; WHEE!
&gt;&gt; DID SOMEBODY SAY FUN? WHERE?!
FUN, FUN, FUN, FUN, FUN!
&gt;&gt; FUN, YOU GUYS!
FUN!
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; NOW APPLEJACK, RAINBOW DASH,
AND FLUTTERSHY ARE COVERED, PLUS
ONE EXTRA PINKIE PIE IN CASE WE
GET AN EXTRA INVITE FROM SOMEONE
ELSE.
PERFECT!
OKAY, LET'S GO!
&gt;&gt; All: AND SOLEMNLY SWEAR NOT
TO BE SCARED AT THE PROSPECT OF
BEING DOUBLY THERE.
&gt;&gt; OKAY. GOOD ENOUGH.
PINKIE PIES, MOVE IT OUT!
&gt;&gt; All: ...NOT TO BE SCARED AT
THE PROSPECT OF BEING DOUBLY
THERE.
&gt;&gt; WHAT IN THE NAME OF PINK?!
KNOCK IT OFF!
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; TO PONYVILLE, EVERYONE!
FOLLOW ME!
[ SIGHS ]
YES, IT'S FUN THERE.
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; [ WHISTLES ]
OKAY, BETWEEN THE BUNCH OF US,
WE SHOULD HAVE EVERY NOOK AND
CRANNY OF FUN IN PONYVILLE
COVERED AT ALL TIMES, AN
UNPRECEDENTED AND MASSIVE
UNDERTAKING!
BUT FIRST, A POP QUIZ ON THE
NAMES I TAUGHT YOU.
&gt;&gt; All: APPLEJACK!
FLUTTERSHY!
PINKIE PIE!
&gt;&gt; EXCELLENT!
OKAY, LET'S GET ON WITH THIS,
FOLKS.
FAN OUT ON THREE.
ONE --
[ ZOOM! ]
EH. GOOD ENOUGH.
♪ LA LA-LA LA-LA LA-LA ♪
♪ LA LA-LA ♪
WHEE!
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; AH-CHOO!
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE --
WOW!
PINKIE PIE WASN'T KIDDING ABOUT
THE DUPLICATES.
EXCEPT NOW THERE'S
TRIPLICATES...
AND QUADRUPLICATES.
&gt;&gt; DASH IS GONNA LOVE THIS.
OH, IF I PUSH HER AROUND ON THIS
FLOATY THING, IT'LL BE FUN AND
RELAXING.
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; UH-OH.
&gt;&gt; NO MORE PINKIES!
I CAN'T TAKE IT!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; GOSH. UH...
I WONDER WHAT FUN THEY'RE HAVING
RAISING THE BARN AT APPLEJACK'S
RIGHT NOW.
MAYBE I BETTER GO CHECK.
[ ZOOM! ]
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; OH!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; OH, PHEW!
LOOKS LIKE I HAVEN'T MISSED A
THING.
&gt;&gt; I WANT TO KNOW RIGHT NOW
WHERE ALL YOU PINKIES CAME FROM
SO I CAN FIND OUT WHO'S
RESPONSIBLE FOR Y'ALL RUINING
OUR BARN RAISING!
[ CRASH! ]
&gt;&gt; UH, YOU LOOK PRETTY BUSY
RIGHT NOW, SO...
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY] MAYBE WE
SHOULD TALK A LITTLE LATER.
[ ZOOM! ]
&gt;&gt; FUN!
&gt;&gt; FUN! FUN!
&gt;&gt; Y'ALL COME BACK HERE AND
CLEAN UP AFTER YOURSELVES THIS
INSTANT!
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; OH, NO.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
WHAT HAVE I DONE?!
MY POOR FRIENDS!
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
&gt;&gt; OKAY, EVERYPONY.
PLEASE, CALM DOWN.
&gt;&gt; CALM DOWN?!
I JUST HAD A PINKIE HURRICANE
RAGING THROUGH MY SHOP!
&gt;&gt; AND THEY TRASHED OUR CRITTER
PICNIC.
[ PONIES SHOUTING ANGRILY ]
&gt;&gt; PLEASE, EVERYPONY.
HANG ON WHILE I TRY TO FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT.
COME ON, SPIKE.
I'VE GOT TO TRY TO REMEMBER THE
NAME OF THAT LEGEND SHE
MENTIONED.
[ CRANKING ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ THUD ]
&gt;&gt; AHA! HERE IT IS!
THE LEGEND OF THE MIRROR POND.
IT DESCRIBES A SPELL I CAN USE
TO SEND THEM BACK WHERE THEY
CAME FROM.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S PERFECT. LET'S GO.
&gt;&gt; BUT THERE'S A CATCH.
IF I CAN'T FIGURE OUT WHICH
ONE'S THE REAL PINKIE, I MIGHT
SEND HER BACK BY MISTAKE.
&gt;&gt; WELL, WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT WHO THE REAL ONE IS,
THEN.
SHOULDN'T BE TOO HARD.
&gt;&gt; DOES ANYPONY HERE KNOW HOW WE
CAN TELL THE REAL PINKIE PIE
FROM ALL THE REST OF THEM?
&gt;&gt; UH...
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW.
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT!
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU!
I NEED YOUR HELP!
&gt;&gt; EXCUSE ME, WHOEVER YOU ARE,
BUT I'M NOT TALKING TO ANY OF
YOU PINKIES UNLESS YOU'RE THE
REAL PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; OOH!
BUT -- BUT I AM THE REAL PINKIE!
&gt;&gt; NO, YOU'RE NOT!
I'M THE REAL PINKIE!
&gt;&gt; I'M THE REAL PINKIE!
&gt;&gt; NO, I'M THE REAL PINKIE!
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; HOW IN TARNATION ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO TELL WHICH IS THE
REAL PINKIE?
&gt;&gt; I HAVE NO IDEA.
&gt;&gt; ME EITHER.
OH, WE'VE ALL GOT THE SAME
ADORABLE TAILS.
WE'VE ALL GOT THE SAME ADORABLE
MANES.
HOOVES!
WHICH ONE OF US IS THE REAL
PINKIE?!
OH! I HAVEN'T THE SLIGHTEST
CLUE!
AND IF I CAN'T TELL US APART,
WHO CAN?!
[ CRYING ]
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; OH, THIS IS HOPELESS.
&gt;&gt; MAYBE THAT ONE'S THE REAL
PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE, THE REAL PINKIE PIE
NEVER SAT THAT LONG IN ONE PLACE
HER WHOLE LIFE.
&gt;&gt; I'M GONNA GO ASK.
&gt;&gt; OF COURSE SHE'S GONNA SAY
SHE'S THE REAL PINKIE.
THEY ALL DO.
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
&gt;&gt; SO, LET ME GUESS.
YOU'RE THE REAL PINKIE PIE.
&gt;&gt; HECK IF I KNOW.
COULD BE ANY ONE OF US, IF YOU
ASK ME.
AND IF I SAID I WAS THE REAL
PINKIE, YOU WOULDN'T EVEN
BELIEVE ME ANYWAY.
SO JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
I'VE GOT SOME IMPORTANT POKING
THE GROUND WITH MY HOOF TO DO.
&gt;&gt; OH, SPIKE, HOW ARE WE GONNA
DO THIS?
I CAN'T RISK SENDING THE REAL
PINKIE BACK INTO THE POND.
&gt;&gt; I MISS THE REAL PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
I BET SHE MISSES YOU, TOO.
BET SHE'D DO JUST ABOUT ANYTHING
TO GET TO BE WITH HER FRIENDS
AGAIN.
[ BLINK! ]
HEY.
HEY!
WHAT IF YOU GAVE THEM A TEST?!
PICK SOMETHING REALLY HARD FOR A
PINKIE TO DO, SOMETHING NOT FUN
AT ALL.
ANY PINKIE THAT CAN'T DO IT GOES
BACK INTO THE POND.
BUT WHOEVER WANTS TO STAY THE
MOST -- THAT MUST BE THE REAL
PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW, THAT'S NOT A BAD
IDEA.
&gt;&gt; THIS IS GREAT!
IF I PASS, I GET TO BE WITH MY
FRIENDS AGAIN!
[ GASPS ]
BUT WHAT IF I DON'T PASS?
OH, WHAT IF I'M NOT THE REAL
PINKIE PIE?
OH!
STUPID MAGIC-MIRROR WATER!
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
AND MINE.
&gt;&gt; HEY, TWILIGHT.
[ ZIP! ]
&gt;&gt; I'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER
FOR YOU PONIES.
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING HERE?
&gt;&gt; FLUTTERSHY SPOKE WITH THE
WOODLAND CRITTERS, AND THEY'VE
AGREED TO TAKE US INTO THEIR
HOME TILL THE PINKIE STORM DIES
DOWN.
&gt;&gt; YOU GUYS, WE'RE GONNA FIX
THIS, AND I KNOW EXACTLY HOW.
&gt;&gt; ARE WE GONNA LOSE OUR REAL
PINKIE PIE?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T THINK SO.
NOW COME ALONG.
I'VE ALREADY GOT APPLEJACK AND
HER FAMILY ROUNDING UP ALL THE
PINKIES.
[ PINKIE PIES SHOUTING "FUN!" ]
&gt;&gt; YAH, YOU PINKIES!
YAH!
&gt;&gt; OOH!
THEY WANT TO PLAY CHASE!
THIS IS FUN, TOO!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; OH, GIVE IT A REST.
&gt;&gt; WELCOME, PINKIES. WELCOME.
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT AND MAKE
YOURSELVES COMFORTABLE.
OKAY.
I SUPPOSED YOU CAN'T BE
COMFORTABLE STAYING IN ONE
PLACE, BUT HAVE A SEAT ANYWAY.
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; SIT DOWN!
[ SHOUTING STOPS ]
BETTER.
NOW, I SUPPOSE YOU'RE ALL
WONDERING WHY I'VE GATHERED YOU
ALL HERE TODAY.
&gt;&gt; FOR FUN?
&gt;&gt; NO.
JUST THE OPPOSITE, ACTUALLY.
&gt;&gt; WAIT UP!
I GOT ONE MORE!
FOUND THIS ONE POKING AT THE
GROUND WITH HER HOOF, DRAWING
FROWNY FACES.
&gt;&gt; HAVE HER COME SIT WITH THE
OTHERS.
[ THUD ]
PINKIES, YOU'VE BEEN BROUGHT
HERE TO TAKE A TEST.
[ PINKIE PIES GROAN ]
&gt;&gt; DON'T WORRY.
IT'S A SIMPLE TEST.
ABOUT AS SIMPLE AS THEY COME.
AND WHOEVER PASSES GETS TO STAY.
&gt;&gt; OH! OH!
&gt;&gt; HEH.
&gt;&gt; CURTAIN, PLEASE.
&gt;&gt; THE TEST...
WE'LL BE WATCHING PAINT DRY.
[ PINKIE PIES GASP ]
ON YOUR MARK. GET SET.
GO!
[ SLOOP! ]
&gt;&gt; OH! THIS IS SO EXCITING!
OKAY.
MAYBE NOT THAT EXCITING.
[ BIRD CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; OH, HEY! LOOK AT THE BIRDIE!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
[ ZAP! ]
[ BLINK! ]
&gt;&gt; WATCH ME BOUNCE TO TOUCH THE
CEILING!
[ ZAP! ]
[ FROG CROAKS ]
&gt;&gt; IS THAT -- IS THAT A FROG
CROSSED WITH AN ORANGE?
&gt;&gt; COOL!
&gt;&gt; WHERE?!
[ ZAP! ]
&gt;&gt; LOOK WHAT I CAN DO WITH MY
HOOVES.
[ POP! POP! POP! ]
[ POP! ]
[ ZAP! ]
&gt;&gt; BETCHA CAN'T MAKE A FACE
CRAZIER THAN...
THIS!
[ ZAP! ]
[ ZAP! ZAP! ]
&gt;&gt; UGH!
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE!
SOMEPONY'S MAKING BALLOON
ANIMALS!
&gt;&gt; WHAT?! WHERE?!
[ ZAP! ]
&gt;&gt; PINKIE, YOU CAN LOOK AWAY
NOW.
&gt;&gt; I PASSED?
&gt;&gt; YOU PASSED.
YOU'RE THE ONLY PINKIE WHO KEPT
STARING AT THE WALL.
&gt;&gt; I HAD TO. I JUST HAD TO.
I COULDN'T LEAVE MY FRIENDS.
I JUST COULDN'T.
BUT I GUESS SOMETIMES I WILL
HAVE TO CHOOSE BETWEEN THEM.
&gt;&gt; I KNEW YOU'D BE UP TO THE
CHALLENGE.
&gt;&gt; I'M ME!
I'M ME!
OR AM I?
YEAH. I'M PRETTY SURE I AM.
[ TING! ]
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE FUN, BUT IT'S
EVEN GREATER TO HAVE GREAT
FRIENDS.
AND HAVING LOTS OF FRIENDS MEANS
THAT YOU SOMETIMES HAVE TO MAKE
CHOICES AS TO WHOM YOU SPEND
YOUR TIME WITH.
BUT THAT'S OKAY.
BECAUSE GOOD FRIENDS WILL ALWAYS
GIVE YOU LOTS OF OPPORTUNITIES
TO HAVE FUN.
SO EVEN IF YOU'RE MISSING OUT,
IT'S NEVER FOR LONG.
RESPECTFULLY YOURS, PINKIE PIE."
[ WHOOSH ]
&gt;&gt; HI, PINKIE PIE.
WE WERE THINKING WE SHOULD GO
OUT AND CELEBRATE.
&gt;&gt; YOU UP FOR SOME WHEELBARROW
RACES?
&gt;&gt; OR I COULD TAKE EVERYPONY ON
A CLOUD RIDE.
&gt;&gt; I COULD THROW A PARTY WITH
PUNCH AND ZESTY CUCUMBER
SANDWICHES!
OOH!
&gt;&gt; YOU WANT TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
I FEEL LIKE DOING RIGHT NOW?
[ SIGHS ]
[ SNORING ]
&gt;&gt; THAT LOOKS LIKE FUN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪