( peaceful music playing )
I love it when Princess Celestia
comes to Ponyville!
I got my hooves shined just like
Rarity for the occasion.
You like?
I certainly do.
I'm surprised
she's not here yet.
I wonder what's
taking so long.
And where are Applejack
and Fluttershy?
RARITY:
Fluttershy's detained
helping Applejack
with a mishap at
Sweet Apple Acres.
They'll be along.
I still don't get why the
Princess would be so late.
She's bringing
an important visitor.
That could be part
of it.
A visitor who's
important and slow.
Maybe it's somepony so terribly
important she still had many
more terribly important things
to do before she got here.
( gasps )
Maybe the visitor has a deer
antler, a goat leg, a bat wing
and a snake tail.
Yeah, right.
That's Discord.
Why in the wide wide
world of Equestria would
Princess Celestia bring along
someone like that?
M-maybe you should
ask her.
( scary music playing )
( gulp )
♪ My little pony,
My little pony ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
Friendship could be ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ You have my little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
( peaceful music playing )
With all due respect,
Princess Celestia,
( shouting ):
how could you bring
Discord here?
( clears throat )
( meekly ):
Your majesty.
I'm fully aware that the
last time Discord was here,
he created serious havoc.
If by "serious havoc" you
mean turning Ponyville
into the chaos capital
of the world.
And tricking us all into being
the opposite of our true selves.
And making yummy delicious
chocolate milk rain all over
the place without a single
dollop of whipped cream to go
with it anywhere in sight.
Not a single dollop!
Yes, I understand, but I have
use for Discord's magic
if it can be reformed to serve
good instead of evil.
This is why I've
brought Discord here.
Because I believe that
you are the ponies
who can help him do just that.
This will never work!
This is a disaster!
How will we ever control him?
We're doomed!
Need I remind you that you are
the ponies who turned him back
into stone like this
in the first place?
I suppose we can just use the
Elements of Harmony
against him again
if he gets out of hand.
We probably need
a volunteer to run away
from here right away
to get them.
I'll do it!
No need, Spike.
I have them right here.
And I've cast
a spell so Discord can't
take them and hide them again.
Now where
is Fluttershy?
I believe she may know best how
to begin reforming Discord.
Fluttershy?
Really?
( chittering )
What's he goin'
on about now?
Good news.
Mr. Beaverton Beaverteeth has
agreed to take his dam apart
and move it.
Well, it's
about time.
APPLEJACK:
My apple trees are
so waterlogged
I can practically
hear 'em gargle.
( indignant beaver sounds )
But he says first you'll
have to apologize
for calling him
"a nuisance."
Apologize? He's lucky I didn't
call him a varmint!
( outraged beaver sounds )
( gasps )
Mr. Beaverton Beaverteeth!
Such language!
Fine. Fine.
I apologize.
( growling )
( wood crashing )
Whew!
Thanks, Fluttershy.
Don't know what I woulda
done without ya.
Glad I could help.
Hey, slackers!
Double-time it on over
back to Ponyville, would ya?
We're all waiting on you.
( harp music plays )
PRINCESS CELESTIA:
I realize that this is a tall
order, but I wouldn't ask
if I weren't confident you could
get him to use magic obediently
of his own
free will.
And you really think
I'll know best how to do that?
I do.
Now I must return to Canterlot
for Equestria's Royal Summit.
You may release Discord
when ready.
Okay, ponies. Guess it's time
to get started.
Let's just hope this
releasing spell works.
Or let's not.
TWILIGHT:
We'd best keep our elements
on at all times
till further notice.
PONIES:
Check!
( elements powering up )
( dramatic music playing )
( stone cracking )
( roaring )
( yawns )
Oof!
Well, it's about time somepony
got me out of that prison block.
What a relief!
( gasp )
What do you think
you're doing?
Oof!
Why, stretching of course!
When you're a creature of chaos,
stone bodysuits aren't your
typical go-to fashion choice.
( snaps )
( roaring )
( gasp )
Make that bunny
cute again. Now!
Oh, bah!
He's adorable
the way he is.
( roars )
You know what else is adorable?
You ponies truly believe
you can reform me.
And that you're putting your
faith in this one here
to make it happen.
Makes me wanna just pinch
your little horsie cheeks.
How'd you know
about that?
Being turned to stone
doesn't keep me
from hearing every word
Celestia says.
Although I'll admit it made
rolling my eyes a challenge.
Well, unless you want us to
turn you back to stone,
you'll zap those animals back to
the way they were, pronto.
Oh, you wouldn't dare
turn me back to stone
and risk disappointing
your precious Princess.
Try us, Dip-cord!
You think you can treat poor
defenseless animals like that
and get away with it?
You go, Fluttershy!
You best watch your step,
buster, or I'll give you
the stare!
( mocking fear ):
The stare? Oh no,
please not that.
Anything but your
disapproving eyeballs!
( Discord laughing )
Oh no! No, no, stop!
No, no!
I can't!
Stop, I can't take
it anymore!
I'll do whatever
you say because...
( laughing ):
You're hilarious!
If it turns out we need to use
our elements against you,
I'm sure we can convince
Princess Celestia
it was for
a good reason.
Hm.
I suppose
that's correct.
( roaring )
( nasty snarling )
Oopsie.
Well, it looks like I know where
I'll be crashing while I'm being
"reformed."
With you, Fluttershy!
( laughs )
Oh dear.
( peaceful music playing )
He may be horrible,
but that doesn't mean we have
to act the same way.
We should at least try
to be hospitable.
You don't mind giving up your
favorite spot on the couch,
do you, Angel Bunny?
( angry bunny noises )
FLUTTERSHY:
Oh! I'm sorry
about Angel.
Are you all right?
Oh, yes. Thank you, Fluttershy,
for your concern.
If only your pony friends
could be as considerate.
Don't listen
to him, Fluttershy!
He's just trying to drive
a wedge between us
like he
always does.
Now why in the world
would I ever try
to do a thing like that?
So we can't unite
and use
the Elements of Harmony
against you, that's why.
I never thought of that.
RAINBOW DASH:
You big liar!
DISCORD:
Now look who's a liar.
Anyone can plainly see
I'm not big at all.
Oops.
There. All better.
I can't watch.
We'll be outside.
You sure you're okay
with this?
I know it's not going
to be easy,
But Princess Celestia is
counting on me.
And I think I actually
know what to do.
You do?
I think the key is
to befriend him.
Being kind to him and letting
him be my houseguest
is probably the
best way to do that.
And you really think
that will work?
I think it's
worth a try.
Okay. But if you
need us,
all you need to do
is whisper "help"
and we'll be back here
with our Elements.
So watch that goat-legged
step of yours, pal.
Wha-- What?
Look at me, I'm practically
reformed already.
She's really all right
with him staying there?
That's what she said.
Personally, I think we should
come up with a back-up plan
in case this whole befriending
business doesn't work out.
Rainbow Dash is right.
This is Discord we're
talking about, girls.
It wouldn't be a bad idea
to have another trick
up our sleeves.
And I think I know
just the trick.
Discord?
Oh, there you are.
Listen, Discord, I just want
to make sure you know
that if there's anything
I can do to--
Uh, um--
Are you eating paper?
Am I?
Huh. How odd of me.
Well, um, I'm just heading out,
so you just make yourself
at home while I'm gone.
DISCORD:
Bye-bye! Have a nice time!
Everything is fine here.
Bye-bye!
DISCORD:
You like carrots, Angel?
I'm playing your owner
for a fool. Ha, ha.
How do you like them carrots?
( screams )
That's weird. The spell I had
in mind isn't in here.
Spike, where are the other books
I asked you to pull?
Right here, Twilight.
I really want to have a
reforming spell
up and running pronto.
But what if he makes
the Elements of Harmony
disappear like he did
last time?
Princess Celestia cast a spell
protecting them, remember?
Uh-oh.
What's wrong?
Princess Celestia didn't cast a
spell protecting our books!
Everywhere I thought I'd find
the reforming spell--
( gasps )
Are you sure this isn't
overdoing it?
You said to make myself at home
while you were gone,
but I wouldn't want
to overstep my bounds.
I did say that.
So, if this makes you more
comfortable, by all means,
please feel free.
Oh, well, it does.
Very much so.
You're so very kind,
my dear Fluttershy.
I always knew you were the
understanding one.
Not like those
nasty friends of yours.
My friends aren't nasty.
Well, of course
you'd say that.
It just goes to show how
understanding you truly are.
You know, I think Princess
Celestia is right when she
singled you out as the
one who could reform me.
You're off to such
a good start,
I'm seriously considering
actually being reformed.
TWILIGHT:
Fluttershy!
Fluttershy, can you hear me?
Goodness! I hear Twilight!
TWILIGHT:
Fluttershy, what's going on?
Are you okay?
We're fine.
Everything's going great.
Isn't it, Angel?
We've come to get you
away from Discord.
He's just terrible and,
from the looks of it,
completely out of control.
Oh but you're wrong.
We're making great progress.
TWILIGHT & SPIKE:
Seriously?
I'm earning his trust
by giving him a little space
to be himself.
Hate to break it to you, but he
used that "space to be himself"
to tear out all the reforming
spells from the library.
That does explain
the paper eating.
He ate them?
( groans )
But we aren't going
to need a spell.
He's already really
considering being reformed.
He said so.
And you believed him?
If I'm going to be his friend,
I have to start by giving him
the benefit of the doubt.
Tell you what,
bring all the ponies over for
a dinner party this evening,
and I'll bet his manners will
have really improved by then.
I'll even get him to put
the cottage back
on the ground first.
( sighs )
All right. Dinner it is.
Ugh.
I can't believe
we're having a dinner party
with Discord.
This evening is sure
to be a disaster.
Glad I didn't bother wearing
my fanciest outfit.
Fluttershy thinks this is
the way to reform Discord
and asked us to give it
a chance.
Oh, our pony guests.
We're so delighted that
you've come.
Please do come in.
FLUTTERSHY:
See what a beautiful job
he did helping?
Discord set the
entire table himself.
I'm so proud.
May I take your--
Ahem, hats, ladies?
Hang on to your
Elements, girls.
It's gonna be
a bumpy night.
FLUTTERSHY:
As you all know, Princess
Celestia hoped we'd help Discord
use his magic
for good instead of evil.
FLUTTERSHY:
Pinkie Pie, care
for some gravy?
You bet!
Allow me.
( panting, whimpers )
Ooh, what a cute
little gravy boat you are!
Yes you are,
yes you are!
That's one creepy little
gravy boat if you ask me.
Oh come on now, Dashie, you're
not even giving this a chance.
( panting )
Hey, that's hot!
Oops! Well,
I'm so sorry.
He did that
on purpose!
Oh, well I don't
know about that.
Mistakes happen.
Ooh, look, everypony.
Dancing candles!
I'm not falling
for that!
Discord's just trying to
distract us from--
Hey! Knock it off!
I suppose that's
another "mistake?"
No, I think you just
made them mad.
There's something
fishy going on.
Discord?
Well, it's hardly my fault if
the soup tureen finds the term
"something fishy"
to be offensive.
Not the dress,
not the dress!
That tureen's only doin' what
you're makin' it do!
Now let's not jump
to any conclusions.
Fluttershy, can't you
see what he's doing?
He's playing innocent with you
so you'll never agree
to use the Elements
of Harmony against him.
Oh, well that's
a bit harsh, isn't it?
You see what I'm saying,
right, Fluttershy?
Fluttershy?
You know what I see?
I see that Discord's far
from perfect,
but I also see none
of you giving him a chance.
PONIES:
Come on!
RAINBOW DASH:
What's gotten into you?
Why do you keep cutting him
so much slack?
Because that's
what friends do.
( softly ):
We're friends?
Why, of course.
I can't remember my house
ever being this lively
before you came along.
Oh...
Well, I've never really had
a friend before.
Well, now you do.
Now is not a good time, Angel.
We're having a dinner party.
APPLEJACK:
Hold up. I think he's tryin'
to tell us somethin'.
ALL:
Apple! Applejack!
( groans )
Oh, oh, oh!
Sweet Apple Acres?
Flooding at
Sweet Apple Acres!
And we all know who's
behind that, now don't we.
Who, me?
RAINBOW DASH:
Oh, give it a rest.
What do you think of your
friend now, Fluttershy?
( suspensful music playing )
APPLEJACK:
I've never seen
the floodin' this bad!
They've built dams around here
before, but never like this.
What's goin' on?
( angry chatter )
( gasp )
Such language!
Oh, it's no use! They won't
listen to a word I say.
You see Discord's
behind all this, right?
Well, of course I do.
Do you all think I'm
a silly, gullible fool?
PONIES:
Oh, no, well, not exactly.
I've just been trying to gain
his friendship any way I can
so he'd come to trust
and listen to me.
DISCORD:
Hey there, Fluttershy!
You want a turn?
The water's great!
Time to see if it worked.
Fluttershy, oh,
there you are.
A sight
for sore eyes.
As you can see, there's
a big mess down here
at Sweet Apple Acres
Oh yes, awful business
that, mm-hm.
It is awful.
This is Applejack's home
and it's being destroyed
by innocent creatures who would
never be acting this way
if it weren't for your
reckless behavior.
You need to fix this.
Well, yes. Very well,
I will fix it.
I only ask one thing
in return.
Yes?
I ask that you never use your
Element of Harmony against me.
As a sign of our friendship.
I will never use my Element
of Harmony against you.
Excellent!
DISCORD:
There, much better!
I do prefer ice skating
to water skiing, don't you?
La da da dee dee ta!
Discord!
That's not fixing it!
Why I ought to--
Where are you going?
What's wrong, pal?
Don't call me
your pal!
Pshaw!
Come skating with me, and
we'll let bygones be bygones!
Here you go,
Fluttershy. Game on!
He fixes this, or he goes
back to being stone.
TWILIGHT:
Princess Celestia
will understand.
I made a promise not to use my
Element against him,
and I'm going to keep it.
( groans )
Ha, ha!
You see? She wants to have fun
with me because we're friends.
She can't use the elements
against me
because we're friends!
I'm free forever,
ha, ha, ha!
( growling )
Not! Your! Friend!
Who cares? I can do whatever
I want, whenever I want.
I'm Discord,
the Master of Chaos!
You think you can boss
Discord around?
You think I'm just going
to turn all this back
because you say so?
Because if I don't, I'll lose
the one friend I ever had?
( sighs )
DISCORD:
Oh...
Well played, Fluttershy.
Well played.
( triumphant music playing )
PONIES:
Woo-hoo!
All right, Fluttershy!
I liked it better
my way,
but I guess when
you're friends,
you can't always have things
exactly your way
all the time, eh?.
( peaceful music playing )
Yes, Princess.
I'm ready to use my magic
for good instead
of evil.
( muttering ):
Most of the time.
PRINCESS CELESTIA:
Congratulations
on your success, ponies.
I definitely sense
a big change in Discord.
I'll leave the Elements
of Harmony with you, Twilight.
Just in case.
You were right when you said
Fluttershy would be
the one to find a way
to reform Discord.
By treating Discord as a friend,
she got him to realize
that friendship was actually
important to him.
And something that, once he had,
he didn't want to lose.
Go on, say it.
Oh, all right.
( rushing ):
Friendship is magic.
See? He can be a real sweetheart
once you get to know him.
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Friends... ♪