TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
You wanted to see me?
To give me a test?
CELESTIA:
The Crystal Empire has returned.
You want me to help protect
an entire empire?
It must be you
and you alone.
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
But what if I fail?
Let's just say the empire.
It isn't the only thing
that's returned.
Go! Go!
Sparkle-rific!
Well, with Cadence,
putting all our strength
into keeping the spell going,
and me trying to keep an eye on
signs of trouble in the Arctic,
we haven't been able
to gather much information
from the Crystal Ponies.
There are Crystal Ponies?
I wish I could help you.
But I can't seem
to remember anything
before King Sombra
came to power.
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
History of the Crystal Empire.
The last page of the book
mentioned the Crystal Heart
as the faire centerpiece.
So I used my magic to cut
one out of the crystal block.
The whole purpose
of the Crystal Faire
is to lift the spirits
of the Crystal Ponies
so the lights within them
can power the Crystal Heart,
so that the empire
can be protected.
I think we may have a problem.
I didn't know
it was an actual relic.
It's all right, Twilight.
( creature howling distantly )
Twily.
♪ My little pony
My little pony ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends ♪
( ominous theme playing )
( croaks )
The empire is under attack.
( roars )
I have to find
the Crystal Heart.
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
No. You stay here with Cadence.
She needs you,
Shining Armor.
I'll retrieve the heart.
Let's do this!
I've been trying to figure out
how I'm meant
to pass
Celestia's test.
Retrieving the Crystal Heart
must be it.
But there is something
else you can do.
Name it.
You and the rest of our friends
have to keep
the faire going.
What? With that thing
moving into the empire?
The whole purpose
of the Crystal Faire
is to lift the spirits
of the Crystal Ponies
so they can activate
the Crystal Heart.
Yeah? And?
If the Crystal Ponies
find out that King Sombra
is trying to take over
the empire again,
their spirits are going to be
anything but lifted.
It won't matter if I find
the Crystal Heart.
They won't be able
to make it work.
You have to keep them
happy here at the faire.
Keep the faire going
and the Crystal Ponies'
spirits high.
Done and done.
SHINING ARMOR:
Twily...
Be careful.
I will.
( croaking )
( calliope music playing )
Okay, here's...
( whispering inaudibly )
Huh?
I just found out
they're offering face-painting
for the little ones.
Ha-ha.
( whispers )
Uh-huh, we can do that.
Twilight's doing what?
He really loves
getting his face painted.
Ha-ha.
Who wants a flugelhorn?
I want a flugelhorn.
Who else wants
a flugelhorn?
I want a flugelhorn!
SPIKE:
Twilight! Wait!
I'm coming with you.
You can't.
I have to retrieve
the Crystal Heart by myself.
I know.
I promise I won't lift
a claw to help you.
Not a claw, Spike.
SPIKE:
Where are we going exactly?
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
I think I might know where
King Sombra hid
the Crystal Heart.
SPIKE:
The castle?
The king would have been
counting on the fact
that no pony would dare
come looking for it here.
They'd have been too afraid
to even try.
SPIKE:
I hope you're right.
You and me both.
What're you looking at?
That's what I thought.
Uh, Rainbow Dash?
We're supposed to be acting
like nothing's wrong.
Exactly.
APPLEJACK:
What I mean is...
Maybe you should let me keep
the Crystal Ponies
away from the fake heart
while you show off
your jousting skills.
Seeing my awesomeness
does have a way
of putting ponies
into a pretty good mood.
( sheep bleating )
Come on, Knight Fluttershy.
Huh?
It's showtime.
How y'all feeling?
Having a good time?
The best I've had
in over a thousand years.
Well, that's good.
Got to renew that spirit
of love and unity
if you're gonna power up
that Crystal Heart, right?
I sure would like
to see it before the ceremony.
It's been such a long time.
Oh, I hear you.
But, uh, whew.
Getting a little toasty
out here.
Bet you'd like to cool off with
a little Crystal Empire nectar.
Uh, you tried
the Crystal Empire fritters yet?
Made from a traditional
Crystal Empire recipe.
You're gonna love them.
Uh, I hear there's
a jousting match about to start.
You don't wanna miss that.
Come on, Twilight.
These Crystal Ponies are more
curious than a cat.
( panting )
( sighs )
It's got to be here
somewhere.
It's just got to be.
Not a claw, Spike.
Uh...
(laughs nervously)
Celestia's orders.
CELESTIA:
If the Empire is filled
with hope and love,
those things are reflected
across all of Equestria.
If hatred and fear
take hold--
Of course!
( grunts )
What? Did you find it?
No.
Because this isn't
King Sombra's castle.
SPIKE:
Well, isn't this where he lived
when he was in power?
It is. But it didn't
look like this.
( grunts )
SPIKE:
Whoa.
When did you learn to do that?
That was a little trick
Celestia taught me.
( gulps )
( whimpers )
You stay here.
If you insist.
Can you see
what's down there yet?
Not yet.
I can't even tell
how far down this goes.
( crystal clinks )
Spike?
SPIKE: Yeah?
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
Can you see outside?
( thunder crashing )
( growling )
Yes.
Crystals.
It's not good.
Cadence's magic must be fading
faster than before.
( suspenseful theme playing )
( grunts )
( grunting )
SPIKE:
Twilight? Are you okay?
Yes.
What in the...?
Stop...
moving!
Spike,
I think it's here.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I opened the door and--
And now you must go.
Go where?
It doesn't matter to me.
You failed the test,
Twilight.
I don't understand.
The test?
Not only will you
not move on
to the next level
of your studies,
you won't continue
your studies at all.
I...
You didn't say anything
about no longer
being your student
if I failed.
Didn't I?
But what do I do now?
( evil laugh )
( whimpers )
SPIKE:
Twilight? Twilight!
Twilight!
I know you told me
to stay up there
but you were here
for such a long time.
And I got worried
so I came down here,
you were just staring
at that wall.
I was calling but I couldn't
get your attention and...
What were you looking at?
I mean,
it's just a wall.
Ponyville?
How did I get...?
No! I don't want to go.
Please, Twilight,
don't make me.
( door slams )
King Sombra's dark magic.
A doorway that leads
to your worst fear.
We were home.
You told me
you didn't need me anymore.
You were sending me away.
A fear that will never
come to pass.
I'm never going
to send you away.
And I'm not going
to fail my test.
SPIKE:
What's in there?
( sighs )
Stairs.
Lots and lots of stairs.
Maybe you should
come with me this time.
( uplifting theme playing )
( thunder rumbling )
( King Sombra laughing )
( crowd cheering )
( whimpering )
( thunder rumbling )
( trumpet blows )
Ah!
( screams )
( all cheering )
CRYSTAL PONY:
Bravo, Knight Rainbow Dash!
( whimpers )
Isn't there somepony else
who could take over
the jousting demonstration
with you?
The fate
of an entire empire
rests on us showing
these ponies a good time.
But, you know, if that
isn't important to you...
( sobs )
Okay. Okay. I'll take it
easy on you next time.
But not too easy.
I've got a reputation
to maintain.
( panting heavily )
What if this is just more
of his magic?
He makes a door that leads
to your worst nightmare,
why not a staircase
that goes on forever?
Hold on to me.
Uh...
Whoa.
Whoa! Yah!
( ponies whimpering )
RARITY:
Excuse me. Pardon me.
I am running out
of weaving materials
for the traditional
crafts booth.
I just made a hat
out of three pieces of hay
and a drinking straw.
I made it work, but still.
We gotta do everything we can
to keep this thing going.
The princess isn't looking
so good.
I can't imagine her magic
is gonna last much longer.
It's gonna be fine.
These ponies are gonna power up
that Crystal Heart
when the time comes,
and we won't be needing
her magic anyway.
PINKIE PIE:
I sure hope that time
comes soon.
Even I can't keep this party
going forever.
Whoa!
This isn't
the Crystal Heart.
Oh, of course it isn't.
The real one is--
On its way.
I was going to say
"being polished"
to buy us some more time.
Oops.
( King Sombra cackling )
It's him.
KING SOMBRA:
Crystal heart...
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
Whoa!
( laughing )
I actually studied
gravity spells
thinking it might be
on my test.
Turns out,
I was prepared for this!
Wooo-hoo!
( laughs )
( alarm sounds )
( growls )
( evil laugh )
( thunder crashing )
( wind howling )
The heart?
Where is the crystal?
Here. It rolled over to me
when you dropped it.
Don't move!
You can move.
Just not toward me.
How could I have been
so foolish?
I was just so eager
to get it.
Then when I saw
what was going on outside, I...
SPIKE:
You have to get out of there.
You have to brings the Crystal
Heart to Princess Cadence.
If you don't,
you fail Celestia's test.
King Sombra is already
attacking the empire.
He could reach
the Crystal Ponies
at any moment.
Reach Princess Cadence,
my brother, my friends.
There may not be enough time
for me to find a way to escape.
You have to be the one
to bring the Crystal Heart
to the faire.
Me? But, Twilight--
Go.
But--
Go!
( ponies whimpering
and screaming )
APPLEJACK:
Now don't y'all worry
your pretty,
little Crystal heads.
The real Crystal Heart
will be here any second.
I don't know
if they believe you.
if I believe me.
( gasps )
He's back!
I can't take it!
Ah!
( growls )
Ah! King Sombra.
My crystal slaves.
( whimpering )
( grunts )
Hey! Up here!
Spike?
I got the Crystal Heart!
That is mine!
( ominous theme playing )
Spikey-wikey!
Huh?
CRYSTAL PONY:
Who is that?
Behold!
The Crystal Princess!
The Crystal Heart
has returned.
Use the light
and love within you
to insure that King Sombra
does not.
What?
No! No!
Stop!
( majestic theme playing )
Oh!
( screams )
( uplifting theme playing )
( all cheering )
( sighs )
Good job, Spike.
RARITY:
I do so wish it was permanent.
Did you see how my mane
just absolutely sparkled?
But good things are better
when they're a rarity.
Oh!
SHINING ARMOR:
Everything's going to be okay.
You've got to stop
saving my rump like this.
It's starting
to get embarrassing.
Wasn't me who saved you
in the end, it was Spike.
It's just a test.
Maybe she'll let you retake it.
I don't think she's going
to give me a new test.
Keep it together, buddy.
Gotta stay strong...for Twilight
It's beautiful.
I wish it had been me
who ultimately made it so.
But it wasn't.
Twilight, as I understand it,
Spike brought Princess Cadence
the Crystal Heart
because you weren't sure
how quickly
you could find a way
to escape the tower.
You weren't willing to risk
the future of the citizens
of the Crystal Empire
in an effort
to guarantee your own.
Far better that I have
a student who understands
the meaning
of self-sacrifice,
than one who only looks out
for her own best interests.
Does this mean...?
She's totally
going to lose it.
Keep it together, buddy.
I gotta stay strong
for Twilight.
I passed!
( all cheer )
♪ You were prepared
To do your best ♪
♪ Had what it takes
To pass the test ♪
♪ All those doubts
You can dismiss ♪
♪ Turns out you were... ♪
ALL:
♪ Prepared for this ♪
♪ You clearly have just
What it takes ♪
♪ To pass a test
With such high stakes ♪
♪ We knew for sure
You would prevail ♪
♪ Since when does
Twilight Sparkle ever fail? ♪
♪ All those doubts
That you can dismiss ♪
♪ Trust yourself
And you cannot miss ♪
♪ Turns out you were... ♪
♪ Turns out I was... ♪
Turns out you were...
♪ Prepared for this ♪
( laughs )
Yeah. I knew everything
was going to be fine.
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Friends ♪