( upbeat theme playing )
( train engine chugging )
You absolutely sure
you can do this?
Of course. Wouldn't have agreed
to it if I couldn't.
Piece of cake.
Speaking of cake,
I've got a little something
I need to attend to.
Yeah, like keeping an eye
on a house full of critters.
Uh, yeah, that was totally
what I was talking about.
Relax.
Go do your welcoming thing
in the Crystal Empire.
Spike's got it all
under control.
( Opal screeching
and Winona barking )
Hurry up, Twilight,
we can't miss our train!
Tickets.
APPLEJACK:
Oh, this is gonna be
a real treat.
Princess Cadance said
she's never seen
the Crystal Ponies
so excited.
RAINBOW DASH:
Duh.
Of course they're excited.
They're up
for the Equestria Games.
It's only the biggest
sporting event
in all of Equestria.
Didn't Cloudsdale host
the Equestria Games one year?
No. Cloudsdale should've hosted
the games one year.
I'll never forget
when we got the bad news.
GAMES ANNOUNCER PONY:
The Equestria Games go to
the city of Phillydelphia.
No!
These Crystal Ponies
lost a thousand years
to an evil king's curse.
They've had enough bad news.
No way we're letting them
experience the pain
of losing out on these games.
Exactly. Princess Cadance
is counting on us
to do our part to convince
the Games Inspector
to choose
the Crystal Empire.
And we are not
gonna let her down, are we?
No!
What? I was just answering
Twilight's question.
♪ My little pony
My little pony ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder
What friendship could be ♪
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
Its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ It's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
All complete ♪
♪ You have my little ponies ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
My very best friends? ♪
PONIES:
Four, three, two, one.
The Crystal Empire,
that's the one!
Okay, everypony. Great job.
Sounds like we're ready.
( all speaking
indistinctly )
One more time. From the top.
Oh.
Oh, please.
I think that was perfect.
Agh. But we've run this
like 12 times already.
I think we've got it.
Cadance said
the Games Inspector
really puts folks through
the ringer on her visits.
There's no margin for error
here.
And this time, we need
to practice the steps.
On a train car?
You heard the pony.
On your hooves.
ALL:
Two, four, six, eight.
( rumbling
and all screaming )
Crystal Empire, ladies.
Watch your step
leaving the train.
( sighs )
Probably should've watched
our step
while we were still
on it too.
( engine chugging )
Wow!
The Crystal Empire looks
crystalier than ever!
APPLEJACK:
They must have everypony
in the Empire
out sprucing it up.
TWILIGHT:
This must be why
were asked us to handle
the welcome committee
routine.
And it's probably also because
we'll be awesome at it.
Princess Cadance was right.
These ponies do look
pretty darn excited.
Yup.
I remember that feeling.
But not as much
as I remember
the crushing wave
of disappointment that came
when things didn't work out.
RAINBOW DASH:
That right there.
That is the face
I do not want to see.
APPLEJACK:
Uh, mm-hm.
We're here.
Ha, ha,
there are my girls.
CADANCE & TWILIGHT:
Sunshine, sunshine
Ladybugs awake
Clap your hooves
And do a little shake
( Twilight and Cadance
giggling )
Oh, my, this is spectacular.
Please, everypony, stand back.
I need air.
Go ahead
and try whatever you like.
It's all complimentary
for the welcome committee.
( giggles )
That over there
is a crystal mud bath,
which relaxes your body
and rejuvenates your coat.
Now, I realize it can be kind
of strange to climb into mud,
but if you'll just give it
a chance, I'm sure--
PINKIE PIE:
Whoo-hoo!
Pinkie! No!
( Pinkie Pie laughing )
( sighs )
So relaxing.
Pinkie Pie! Honestly.
BOTH:
Hmph.
( both sigh )
Go ahead.
Have a good time
while I get my ceremonial
headdress done.
Ceremonial headdress?
When meeting
with important guests,
it was tradition for rulers
of the Crystal Empire
to weave crystals
into their manes
in a very specific way.
The Games Inspector is known
for doing her homework.
She'll certainly be expecting
my look
to reflect the importance
of her visit.
( door opens )
Princess.
If I may have a word.
I have two pieces of news
for you.
First, your mane-stylist
has the flu
and won't be able
to make it
for fear
of you catching it too.
Oh, well...
I hope she's better soon.
Do any of the other
stylists here know
how to do the traditional
royal ceremonial headdress?
( all indistinctly
chattering )
Oh.
( sighs)
Just a small detail.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're trying to land
the Equestria Games here.
There's no such thing
as a small detail.
Rainbow Dash.
I suppose
I could give it a shot.
Oh, Rarity,
you would do that for me?
Way to step up, Rare.
Fortunately,
I have all the precise
instructions right here.
RARITY:
Oh, my.
You sure
you're up to this?
Working on the hair of royalty
on such an auspicious occasion
is the opportunity
of a lifetime.
I will give it everything
I've got.
See? No worries.
Besides, the Games Inspector
isn't expected
for several hours.
I'll have plenty of time
to figure out exactly
how to do this.
Oh, Rarity,
that's wonderful.
You said you had a second
bit of news?
Yes, quite.
The Games Inspector,
Ms. Harshwhinny,
will be arriving
on the next train.
ALL:
What?
What? You couldn't have
told her that news first?
That's 15 minutes
from now!
FLUTTERSHY:
Oh, my goodness.
( Rainbow Dash gasping )
( gasps then sighs )
How long before Cadance
is ready?
Hmm...
I'm sure to find
some shortcuts.
Can you have her back
at the castle when we're done?
Done.
Okay, we'll be fine.
TWILIGHT:
Everypony,
just be on the lookout
for the pony
with the flower print luggage.
PINKIE PIE
Easy peasy,
pudding in the freezy.
We bring the Games Inspector
back to the castle,
put on our big welcome committee
how-do-you-do, and then--
Put the pudding out to thaw
before you eat it
or you'll crack a tooth?
I'll just ignore that.
We need to remember
that the Games Inspector
arriving early
is probably part of a plan
to psych us out.
What do you mean?
You said it yourself.
She's got a rep for trying
to catch hosts off guard.
Just to see if we can handle
the kind of massive pressure
that comes with hosting
the Equestria Games.
Oh, no,
we're gonna blow it.
Not if we always stay
one step ahead
and don't fall
for any of her mind games.
Anything she throws at us,
we just need to remember
she's testing us,
and roll with it.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Yes? What is it?
Oh, no.
Be cool.
Well, I know
you're not expecting us
but we're here
to personally welcome you
to the Crystal Empire.
The whole lot of you
came to do that?
Uh, well, um, yes.
Well, darn tootin'!
Ain't that the cat's meow.
Y'all didn't need
to do that.
Why, I hardly expected
anything like this.
( sighs )
The princess wouldn't
have had it any other way.
The Princess?
Princess Cadance?
None other.
Well, tie me up
and throw me down.
This just keeps getting
better and better.
Can we help you
with your bags?
Don't mind if you do.
Ooh! I love flower print.
( squishing )
Sorry.
PINKIE PIE:
Our first stop is the castle
where we've got a big
razzamatazzy welcome
planned for you.
The castle?
Are you kidding?
Hot diggity dog!
See that?
Just gotta roll with it
until the Princess gets there
and we'll be just fine.
( engine chugging )
( slow theme playing )
( hair dryer whirring )
CADANCE:
So how's it going so far?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's just all so complicated.
( chuckles )
I can fix it.
CADANCE: Fix what?
Well,
I was looking for shortcuts
and I thought
step 12 was optional.
But it's not.
GAMES INSPECTOR:
My golly,
the Crystal Castle!
Why, I've seen pictures,
but I never expected to see it
with my very own eyes!
( gulps )
From the inside.
Oh, my gosh, she's so nice.
You're letting her
lull you
into a false sense
of confidence.
Watch that.
It's all part of the game.
Oh, my, I'm so excited.
TWILIGHT:
Please have a seat,
won't you?
Mind if I take a quick run
outside first.
It was an awfully long
train ride
and my legs could use
a stretch.
Oh, well,
we were just about to start.
Oh, never you mind.
You go on ahead.
I'm listening.
She was probably testing us
to see
if we could remain in control
of a complex situation.
Looks like we passed.
Bump.
Yeah.
We'd like to thank you
for this opportunity
to introduce you
to this wonderful kingdom.
Oh, well,
the pleasure is all mine.
And since we're not even
from here ourselves,
who better than us
to let you know
just how welcoming
this place can be?
ALL ( chanting ):
Two, four, six, eight
Name a place
That's really great
One, two, three, four
And keeps you coming back
For more
Two, seven, nine, three
The place that we'd all
Wanna be
Four, three, two, one
The Crystal Empire
That's the one
( fireworks expoding )
( cheering and whistling )
( all panting )
GAMES INSPECTOR:
Oh!
I tell you,
I have traveled far and wide,
but I have never,
ever been welcomed anyplace
in the fashion that you all
have done here today.
That's fantastic.
Princess Cadance would be
so glad to hear that.
Honestly, I'm surprised
she knows anything
about me at all.
Of course she does.
She's been looking forward
to your visit for weeks.
Oh, goodie. Is she here?
Uh...
Where the heck is she
anyway?
Wasn't she supposed
to be here by now?
Oh, that's all right.
( suspenseful theme
playing )
( gulps )
Maybe-- I'll just take
my little run outside now.
( panting )
Or, if you like,
we could give you a tour
of the castle.
RAINBOW DASH:
That way,
you could be learning
and stretching
all at the same time.
Oh, a tour
of the Crystal Castle.
I'd love that a whole heap.
Dash, we've hardly ever
even been here before.
It's just another test.
We gotta roll with it,
remember?
Ooh, let me give the tour.
PINKIE PIE:
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Let me, let me, let me.
( sighs )
Fine. You will start
giving her the tour
and I'll go see
what's keeping Cadance.
( upbeat theme playing )
( groans then grunts )
Hello there.
Hello yourself.
First hello of the day.
Oh. Ugh.
( grunting )
( Twilight humming )
Aah!
What are you doing here?
We finished
the welcome committee song
and we just wanted to introduce
Ms. Harshwinny to--
No, no. Princess Cadance
isn't ready.
Something's gone
terribly wrong.
TWILIGHT:
I need to speak
to the princess.
RARITY:
You can't, mustn't.
She's in a delicate
conditioning rinse
that must go perfectly
if there's to be any hope
for her hair.
TWILIGHT:
Come on. How bad could it be?
Imagine her mane
turned into a porcupine.
Oh.
Please, I'll bring her back
from the brink of tragedy,
but you have got to buy me
some time.
There's no other way.
So you see, this here,
this, um--
This is, um...
A big round room.
It's known
for its roundness and bigness.
And did I mention
that it's round?
I think they call it
a rotunda,
a small, confining rotunda.
Pfft. Whatever.
Round is round, am I right?
Easy, Pinkie.
Let's play this safe.
We got her in a good mood,
so let's not do anything
to ruin that.
You know, I love
this sort of architecture.
I detect a neo-gothic
inspiration in the design, yes?
Hey, look at me.
( babbles )
( sighs )
And not a moment too soon.
Where's Cadance?
Tell me she's right behind you.
There's a bit of a problem
with her headdress.
How's it going here?
Boingie boingie boingie.
I, uh, hate
to be a bother,
but the legs
are cramping up on me
with all
this standing around.
Huh?
She's getting bored,
and we have to buy Rarity
some more time.
( sighs )
I'll see if Shining Armor
can come help.
Can't one of you other ponies
take over in the meantime?
I got this.
Wanna stretch your legs,
huh?
Well, whatever you need,
I'm sure we can provide.
Let's just make our way
to the castle's gymnasium.
Our tour
will now be headed--
This way.
And we're walking,
and we're walking.
( Twilight humming )
( all speaking
indistinctly )
Twiley.
Hello there.
Shining Armor,
you've gotta help me.
Everything okay?
I left the other ponies behind
giving the Games Inspector
the worst castle tour ever.
SHINING ARMOR:
Come on, gang!
Are we gonna gallop
or are we gonna trot?
A castle tour, huh?
I'm pretty sure I can give you
a hoof with that.
Let's move, move, move!
Everything's gonna be
okay.
I know. I'm not worried.
I'm not worried, it worked.
( sighs then screams )
I'm outside.
( laughing )
Feels so good
to stretch the old legs.
What the-- ?
Turns out the Crystal Castle
doesn't have a gymnasium.
Watch it!
( Games Inspector screams )
Make her stop.
Wait.
That's the Games Inspector.
Let her do her thing.
Good, oh, these hooves,
I'm outside.
Why would she do that?
I have no idea.
But that's why
she's in charge
of choosing who gets the games
and we're not. Heh.
( crashing )
Aah! Oh.
Get me outside
for a run.
Look out!
Yeah. Okay.
We need to stop her.
( Games Inspector
screaming )
Where is she going
in such a hurry?
GAMES INSPECTOR:
Ah. Oh, yeah!
Closer, closer,
I think we got her.
GAMES INSPECTOR:
Oh!
( Rainbow Dash screams )
( scratching on glass )
Whoo-wee!
That felt good.
Nothing like a great run
to shake the cobwebs
off these old bones.
( Rainbow Dash panting )
Hey there, Speedy.
Oh! These wide open spaces
you all got here
remind me of home.
This is great.
Oh, so you're enjoying
your visit.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Oh, good golly, yes.
I just love to travel
and see new places.
Such a beautiful spot
you got here too.
Why, thank you so much.
I'm Shining Armor.
Oh. The prince.
What's going on?
From the looks of it,
just locking up the games
for the Crystal Empire,
is all.
Ain't no thing.
My, oh, my.
I never met a prince before.
Ha-ha-ha. I'm surprised.
I'd think
in your line of work
you'd meet princes
all the time.
Hardly, just an ordinary
Wild Mustang from Mustangia
here to enjoy
a little vacay.
Never thought I'd also
be meeting royalty to boot.
( giggles )
You are Ms. Harshwhinny,
the Equestria Games Inspector,
aren't you?
Inspector of what now?
( suspenseful theme
playing )
We got the wrong pony?
No!
I mean, yes!
( panting )
( ominous theme playing )
APPLEJACK:
Oh, please, still be here.
Oh, please, oh, please,
oh, please.
There's got to be
another pony
with flower print luggage
around here somewhere.
Except that there isn't.
We've gotta find her
before Cadance finds out
what a mess
we've made of things.
Okay, here's what we do:
We split the empire up
into five sectors.
Each of us search a sector.
Well, except for the spa.
What's the point
of checking there?
That's where Cadance is.
If Ms. Harshwhinny is there,
well, then game over. Right?
( all gasp )
HARSHWHINNY:
Every city in the empire
wants to host
the Equestria Games.
So I have to go through
all the big phoney baloney
song and dance,
though of course I'm never
getting the real inside scoop.
TOURIST:
Oh, golly.
I've been having a swell time
since I got here.
I'm actually thinking
of extending my stay.
And what exactly has made
your visit so "special"?
Oh, gosh, where to start?
Oh, there she is.
We're in luck, I don't think
either of them knows yet
that the other one's here.
Wonderful news.
Look, Princess Cadance,
better than new.
Princess Cadance?
So this is where you've been.
I will have you know
this is by far
the worst welcome I've had
in all my years.
I can't believe it.
What was wrong
with your welcome?
There wasn't one.
What is going on?
Princess, we gave our welcome
to the wrong pony,
left the right one
waiting at the station,
and completely
ruined everything.
Cinnamon bun?
When I was a little filly,
I wanted so badly
for Cloudsdale to win
the Equestria Games.
But it didn't happen.
So I thought I could make up
for that disappointment
by helping the Crystal Empire
win the chance
to host the games.
But it looks like I ruined
your chances instead.
Not so fast, Speedy.
I just finished hearing
about how this pony
was just treated
to the warmest,
funnest,
most fabulous reception
she ever had.
Darn tootin'.
Courtesy of these fine ponies
right here.
Which, in my expert opinion,
amounts to the first ever
unvarnished, unrehearsed,
and unbiased appraisal
of a potential host
of the Equestria Games.
Which can only mean
one thing.
The next host
of the Equestria Games
is The Crystal Empire!
( crowd cheers )
RAINBOW DASH:
We did it.
CADANCE:
Congratulations,
Crystal Ponies.
You know it feels good
to help others get something
you always wanted
but never had.
Almost as good
as getting it yourself.
Almost.
We'll still be able
to come back here
and watch the games
when they're played.
You're right. That'll rock.
Oh, my goodness.
CONDUCTOR:
All aboard.
Ha! Huh, Bummer,
Spike had to miss out
on all this.
He would've had fun here.
I'm sure he's having
a great time
watching all the critters
back at home.
Think he's still
got a handle on things?
( sighs )
If he's staying calm
and collected,
I bet he's doing
a terrific job as a leader.
( growling )
You all hear that?
( suspenseful theme plays )
♪ My little pony ♪
♪ Friends... ♪