♪♪
[snap]
Oh!
[gurgling]
[whoosh]
Ah. Thank goodness.
I thought I had too
many deep fried gems.
It's from my parents!
Spike!
They won a zeppelin cruise and
get to take the whole family!
Aww... I wish I had
time to go with them,
but there's just too
many Princess duties
I have to take care of.
Come on, Twilight.
Even Princess Celestia
takes a break sometimes
and she raises the sun!
Ugh. You need a vacation.
I can keep track of
the Friendship log,
boost community morale and
answer fan mail for a few days.
But Spike, you're as much a
part of my family as anypony.
I can't just leave you
here to do all that work.
What?
I can't hear you.
You're on vacation.
I guess I could use a little
time off from being a Princess.
You're the best, Spike.
I know.
I'm going to go pack everything
neatly into one suitcase!
Wait for it.
Cruises have activities, right?
I should probably
make a schedule!
There it is.
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[chatter]
Oh, gee, I am really looking
forward to a relaxing vacation.
Watch out.
She won't admit it, but
when your mother says
"relaxing vacation"
she means "doing
something crazy."
Last time she ended up bungee
jumping over Luna Bay.
What was that, hon?
Oh, I was uh just
telling Twilight
about my new uh, bingo
strategy book.
It's a real page-turner!
Oh, I can't wait to get on this
zeppelin and fly like a pegasus!
Really? I remember
you getting air-sick
on Admiral Fairweather's Wild
Ride at Pony Island.
Ah please, I grew out of
air-sickness a long time ago.
[microphone feedback]
[drill sargeant voice]
I hope you ponies feel welcomed
aboard BECAUSE YOU ARE!
Well, that was an
assertive welcome.
♪♪
Wow!
Looking good!
Ohhh!
This is cool!
Guess this is what it's like
to be big-time prize winners.
Ha ha ha.
I just wish I could remember
what contest we won.
Wait. You don't know where
this prize came from?
When somepony offers
you a free vacation,
you just sign the paperwork
and don't ask questions.
Especially when it means we
all get to fly off together.
What should we do first?
Well, I did categorize
the ship's activities
and make a schedule organized
by each of our interests!
Dad, you're easy.
Bingo competition right here.
Oh, I just love how the numbers
and letters are organized
in their little boxes.
It's so satisfying!
Shining Armor, they've
got a tiny boat race
in a tiny pool, here.
Aw, sis, only you would
remember I love tiny things.
And Cadance?
There's a Pee-wee
Princess Playtime here
that Flurry's gonna love.
[giggles]
Wonderful!
Hmmm.
This barrel jumping at Neighagra
Falls sounds interesting.
Eh.
I just want to see
you all have a good time.
And this works out perfectly,
because we have room for
the one thing I want to do!
Our ship passes the
Frozen North at sunset,
which is the only time you can
see the astrological phenomenon
known as the "Northern Stars."
It's like the stars are shooting
out of the setting sun!
Aw!
That sounds amazing!
Wow!
Well, we definitely
don't want to miss that!
Then it's settled!
Hm, but we don't have
anything to do right now.
Any suggestions?
[feedback]
ATTENTION CRUISE PONIES: DON'T
LET THIS ZEPPELIN BE A BORE;
LEAVE YOUR ROOM
AND SEE THE TOUR!
A tour could be fun.
Hmm yea!
OK, Sure.
♪♪
I'm flying! I'm--
[gag]
I'm afraid
Flurry may be air-sick.
Since I know that isn't
a problem for you,
would you mind
taking her below?
FAR TO OUR RIGHT, YOU
CAN JUST MAKE OUT
THE WHITE TUFTS OF CLOUDSDALE
WHERE PRINCESS TWILIGHT SPARKLE
ONCE TOURED THE WEATHER FACTORY.
[excited chattering]
How'd he know that?
And why announce it on a cruise?
[chatter]
Why don't we move to the
other side of the deck?
WE ARE NOW HIGH ENOUGH
TO SEE ALL OF CANTERLOT,
EVEN THE ROYAL TREE WHERE
PRINCESS TWILIGHT
AND HER BROTHER SHINING
ARMOR WERE BORN!
What? That's not right.
[excited chatter]
Let's get down for that!
Um, you guys know that's
not where we were born.
What are you so excited about?
Well, it is a really
nice tree, sweetheart.
We just wanted to say how
excited we are to be here!
Um, yeah, us too.
ON OUR ROUTE NORTH, WE WILL PASS
THE SPIRES OF THE CRYSTAL EMPIRE
WHERE PRINCESS CADANCE RESCUED
HER ALICORN BABY, SPIKE,
FROM A MONSTER MADE OF FIRE!
Well, that doesn't
even make sense!
[Night Light] "Well,
Royal Grandparents"
sounds a bit fancy,
but of course you
can take our picture.
[shutters clicking]
What?
[murmurs]
OH!
OK, that's it!
Does anypony know where
the cruise announcer is?
Excuse me, sir.
YOU CAN CALL IRON
WILL, IRON WILL.
What are you doing here?
And why do you keep
announcing random things
about me and my family?
THE ASSERTIVENESS
SEMINAR MARKET DRIED UP,
SO IRON WILL STARTED
A NEW CAREER...
ORGANIZING THEMED
VACATION PACKAGES.
And the theme of this
vacation is...
Everypony! Stomp your hooves if
you are here for the premier
'Cruise of the
Princesses' experience!
[excited clamoring]
[excited chatter]
Iron Will, I'm not sure it was
entirely honest of you to offer
this cruise to my family
without telling us
that ponies bought tickets
just to see Cadance and me!
Iron Will outlined all the
details of the cruise in the
prize acceptance and consent
form that you signed.
Well, when somepony offers
you a free vacation,
who reads the fine print?
Iron Will prides
himself on providing
a quality vacation experience,
but if Twilight Sparkle and
her family don't want it,
Iron Will can cancel the cruise
and break the hearts of every
Princess-adoring pony on board.
Ugh...
I love you Princess
Twililight!
As much as I want
a family vacation,
I don't think I could entertain
all these cruise ponies.
My hooves are pretty full
taking care of Flurry Heart.
I guess we were just so excited
by the idea of a family cruise.
[sigh] All right, I guess we
better turn this ship around.
Wait! Iron Will, what if
I offered you a deal?
If I agree to do whatever
princess activities you want,
will you promise
that my family
gets to do the
activities they want?
Sis, you don't
have to do that.
We want you to
enjoy yourself too.
[baby coos]
I don't want the vacation to end
now or let down all of these
ponies who were looking
forward to seeing us.
So what do you say, Iron
Will? Do we have a deal?
PRINCESS TWILIGHT
HAS A DEAL!
Great!
So it looks like we have some
time before Dad plays Bingo.
ACTUALLY, WE HAVE JUST
ENOUGH TO PICK THE WINNER
OF OUR GRAND PRIZE RAFFLE.
Oh. Well, [chuckle] who
doesn't like prizes?
ALL RIGHT CRUISE PONIES:
WHEN THE ZEPPELIN FLIES
IT'S TIME FOR A PRIZE!
[squeals of excitement]
Thank you all for being so
gracious and respectful
to me and my family.
And now, without further
ado, the winner is...
Star Tracker!
[hooves knocking on deck]
Congratulations, Star Tracker!
Enjoy your prize.
OK Dad, bingo time!
Uh... Oh!
I'm sorry, I don't
have the prize.
CONGRATULATIONS TO STAR TRACKER
WHO WINS THE GRAND PRIZE:
SPENDING THE DAY WITH TWILIGHT
AS AN HONORARY MEMBER
OF HER FAMILY!
[cheers]
That's the prize?
Uh huh... heh heh.
OK! Well, I guess you
should come with us,
honorary family member!
Sure! Hah. There's always
room at the bingo table.
Ahem.
Is everypony ready?
Sure are, sweetie.
Give that cage a whirl!
Dad?
What did you say?
Uh... he... He said to
uh... give it a... a whirl.
Oh! Um, thanks.
I-19!
Hey! Now we're talking!
This Princess Bingo is great!
Did you get that one, Dad?
Can anypony tell me
how my dad is doing?
He uh... he said the Princess
Bingo is uh great hah.
Princess Bingo!
Twilight is my
favorite time of day.
Ha ha. And it's
also your name.
Ha ha. I just thought
that was cool.
[nervous titter]
Whew!
Just made it!
And I'm ready to give you the
tiny boat race of your life!
Are you sure you're not
air-sick, Big Brother?
No way.
How can I be air sick?
I'm in the water, so
it totally cancels out.
I don't think that's how it
works, but I'm ready if you are!
TECHNICALLY, PRINCESS TWILIGHT
SPARKLE SHOULD OFFICIATE
THE PRINCESS PADDLE BOAT RACE.
Well, I suppose I could
race your brother.
Oh.
Well, as long as Shining Armor
gets to race, I'm happy.
[poof poof]
[shutters clicking]
Ha ha.
Sorry.
I'm going to write about this
race tonight in my journal.
Ha ha. Uhhh! It's
just so exciting!
On your mark...
Get set...
GO! Ha ha!
Woooooooo!
Ha ha! My word,
that was exciting!
Wasn't it, son?
Ha ha ha!
Just so everypony knows, I'm
getting out of this boat
because of how not sick I feel.
[splash]
Awww, that's all right dear,
we'll take you back to the room.
THAT WAS JUST THE
FIRST HEAT OF TEN.
[popping]
NOW WHO'S READY TO
SEE A PRINCESS FACE
WHEN THEY WIN
THEIR RACE?
Yeah!
Whoo hoo!
[babies cooing and giggling]
Cadance.
I'm so glad you got in the
Pee-wee Princess Playtime.
Flurry is having
a wonderful time.
That's great; I'm just
on my way to take some
Old-Time Appleoosan Photos.
Themed photo shoots
are the best. Ha ha.
And then do a quick question and
answer session on becoming an
Alicorn before Mom's barrel
ride at Neighagra Falls.
I really hope I don't miss that!
Twilight, are you sure
you don't mind doing
all of these Princess
activities?
Mind? What? Absolutely not!
I mean, you guys are
having fun, right?
Ughh... besides, I have to make
sure these cruise ponies
are happy if I want to
be a good Princess.
You're already a good
Princess, Twilight.
Honestly, as long as I get to
see the Northern Stars tonight
with everypony, I'll be happy.
But right now I gotta
go take some pictures.
See ya later!
Why don't you play and
make a Princess friend!
[babies giggling]
I am so sorry, everypony, but it
looks like Flurry needs her nap.
♪♪
Oh! Why did that last question
have to be a two-parter?
I just hope I have time for
one barrel ride with Mom.
Ohh!
Neighagra Falls was amazing!
The endless open air!
The water in my mane!
Oh! The small confines
of the barrel!
Ha ha! Another "relaxing
vacation" in the books, hon.
[kiss]
♪♪
[splash]
Oh, honey, I know
you're disappointed,
but we waited as
long as we could.
Maybe you should take a break
from these Princess things?
Disappointed? No!
I've just been answering
some detailed questions
about Alicorns.
You know how much
I love details!
I just don't want you to
forget it's your vacation, too.
How can I when it's a
totally successful vacation?
All right.
Well, we can't wait to
see those Northern Stars!
IRON WILL LIVED UP TO
HIS SIDE OF THE BARGAIN
AND PRINCESS TWILIGHT
ONLY HAS ONE MORE THING
TO DO FOR THE DAY.
IT'S YOUR LAST CHANCE.
COME GET IN LINE IF YOU
WANT THE PRINCESS TO SIGN!
[happy clamoring]
[excited squeal]
[moan]
How long have
you been waiting?
[murmur]
Oh, no.
What time is it?
[panting]
[gasp]
[excited murmurs]
[sob]
I missed them? I missed
the Northern Stars?
[sobbing]
You were right, Twilight.
They were breathtaking.
[baby giggles]
We wish you'd been here
to see it, sweet pea,
but we're sure you're making
a whole bunch of
cruise ponies happy.
I'm so happy I could cry.
Oh, yeah.
The cruise ponies are happy.
My family is happy.
Even Iron Will is happy.
You know who isn't happy?
ME!
[crunch]
Ow! My hoof!
I'm sorry, but maybe that
wouldn't have happened
if you weren't practically
standing on my tail!
Not even my real
family stands so close!
[whimper]
Ugh!
Twilight?
I only made that deal with
Iron Will so my family
and the cruise ponies could have
the vacation they wanted.
What about what you wanted?
I just want everypony
to be happy.
Well, sometimes ponies
want more from a Princess
than you can give
and it can be hard to know
where to draw the line.
You seem to know
pretty well.
Once I had Flurry Heart, the
line was easier for me to see.
You will always have
obligations as a princess,
but you also have an
obligation to yourself.
[sigh]
You're right.
I think I need to set some
boundaries, but first,
I owe somepony an apology.
Aww... how's that, dearie?
Better, thanks.
[door opens]
♪♪
Agh! But I think I should go!
No, Star Tracker,
you should stay.
I have something to
tell you... all of you.
I'm glad you all got to
do the things you wanted,
but I should have
stood up for myself
so that I could do
what I wanted too.
It wasn't fair of me
to lash out at you.
If I felt like you were
standing too close,
I should have said something.
I'm sorry.
What do you say we do
something off the schedule?
[gasps]
Who are you?
Yep! We're gonna do something
I want us to do as a family.
Honorary members too.
♪♪
[giggles]
[laughter]
You and your family have been
really kind to include me,
but you deserve your
own vacation together.
Ha ha. And I'm really
glad we met too. Ha ha.
Oh!
Attention, cruise ponies!
If it's your dream, come
to the deck for ice cream!
Oh no!
Leave the Princess alone!
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO IRON WILL?
It's OK, everypony.
Ahem.
First, I want to thank
all of you for coming.
It means a lot that you'd
spend your hard earned bits
just to be with us,
but I honestly came
on this cruise
to take some time off
from being a Princess.
I'm just a pony too, after all.
And even though I want
everypony here to be happy,
I'd really like to spend
the rest of the cruise
relaxing with my family.
Of course, Princess Twilight!
But why was this trip advertised
as a Cruise of the Princesses
if you just wanted to get away?
[casual whistling]
Iron Will's Cruise of the
Princesses makes no guarantees
as to the participation
of actual princesses.
What?
[angry
shouts]
BUT, IRON WILL LEARNED
HIS LESSON BEFORE.
SATISFACTION NOT GUARANTEED.
NO REFUNDS!
Wow. He may be pushy
and manipulative,
but nopony can say that
Minotaur isn't prepared.
There's still plenty
of activities.
We pass Filly Delphia
on the way back;
I could give Flurry Heart
a quick history tour!
That's very thoughtful,
but right now,
the family and I have
something scheduled for you .
Behold the Northern Stars!
♪♪
You did all this for me?
This is amazing! Thank you!
And Shining Armor, I can't
believe you're up there
even though you're air-sick.
I am not-air-- OK, maybe
I'm not feeling great.
[laughter]
Whatever you say!
Now this is the only
activity I need.
♪♪