♪♪
Hey, Apple Bloom!
Rarity's re-organizing her
shop and look what she found!
Old costumes from
the talent show!
We thought they'd come in handy
in case we ever help
a pony put on a play
or need to make a quick
escape disguised as clowns!
Here you go, Big Mac.
Whoa! That sure is
a lot of apples!
Are you making another delivery
to Starlight's old village?
Yeeeup.
That's an awful long way
for a pony to go, isn't it?
Yeeeup.
You've been going
there a lot lately.
What is this? Your
fifth trip this week?
[giggle]
Yeeeup.
OK, well, have fun!
So what other costumes did
you bring, Sweetie Belle?
Are you crazy?
We can't talk about costumes
at a time like this!
Time like what?
Your brother is
hiding something.
Did you see the
way he was acting?
Yeah, he totally blushed
when you brought up
how often he's been going
to Starlight's old village.
Something is
definitely going on.
There can only be one reason
a pony would travel
so far, so often.
He's taking private
skiing lessons!
He's training for a marathon!
I've been cooking
a lot of broccoli
and he wants to get
away from the smell!
[laughter]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
Maybe he's a spy on a mission
to thwart an evil villain
with his secret weapon:
an apple cannon!
No, that's crazy. I think
it's my broccoli thing.
Why don't we just
ask him?
You saw how shifty he
was acting earlier.
There's no way he'll
tell us what he's doing.
Plus, I really want
to go undercover.
We already
have costumes.
Call me: Agent Rainbowhead.
I'll be Shimmering Spectacles:
a librarian with
a mysterious past.
And I'll be a pirate
spy. Argh. A spyrate!
Avast! Our ship be leaving port!
Huh?
Big Mac's leaving.
If we're gonna be
spies, we gotta go NOW!
[whistling]
Big Mac's comin'!
Quick, act like apples!
What? How?
♪♪
[no audio]
Who's that pony?
Let me see!
I don't know. Shouldn't
have taken the binoculars.
I don't know
anypony here.
That must be
Sugar Belle.
Applejack told me
about her bakery.
Obviously, she's just been
ordering a lot of apples.
So nothing fishy's
going on.
No way! We came
here to be spies!
And no spy I know has ever
solved a case that quick.
How many spies
do you know?
That's not important.
What's important is
that we do more recon!
Follow my lead.
♪♪
Whoa, she sure likes her apples!
What is she doing? Making the
biggest apple pie in Equestria?
Thanks for coming all
this way, Big Mac.
It sure is nice seeing
you again so soon.
♪♪
Yeeeup.
All I used to bake were
boring old muffins.
But thanks to your
apple deliveries,
I get to bake all kinds
of delicious treats!
Apple pies, apple
fritters, apple turnovers,
caramel apples,
caramel apple cakes...
[sigh]
I just wish I had more
room to display it all.
My shelves only hold so much.
I'm telling you, this pony
really likes her apples!
[gasp] Or Big Mac!
Huh?
Just look!
Ooh! Uh!
[giggle]
Sweetie Belle, I
think you're right!
I think my brother has a crush!
Shhhh!
Psst! Big Mac!
Now remember, my
brother's super shy
so he's probably going to be
embarrassed about his crush.
Just try and make
him feel comfortable.
Hey, Big Mac! It's
me: Apple Bloom!
Yeeeup.
We're here, too!
Mm hm.
I'm going to ask you a
very personal question
and I want you to
answer honestly.
Do you... have a crush...
on... Sugar Belle?
Yeeeup.
Well, that was easy!
This is so exciting!
My big brother has
his very first crush!
First crush? What
about Cheerilee?
It doesn't really count
when you trick a pony
into drinking a love
potion, does it?
Nope.
My brother has a cra-ush!
Wait. Does Sugar Belle
even know you like her?
Nuh uh.
Then you gotta
tell her!
[gulp]
We're pretty sure
she likes you!
I mean, she keeps
ordering apples
just so she can
see you again!
Ya think so?
Totally. But you'll never
know if you don't try.
OK.
Go get 'er, Big Mac!
♪♪
[crash]
Hey girl. I was writing
poetry by the pond
when I saw these flowers.
I thought I'd show them
how pretty you are.
Oh. Thanks,
Feather Bangs!
Um, is it possible to
have two crushes at once?
Because it looks like Big
Mac may not be the only pony
Sugar Belle likes!
♪♪
Hey, Big Mac! Where you goin'?
Home.
You can't let that Feather
fella get in the way
of your one true love.
You've gotta take him down!
What can he do that you can't?
That!
Whoops! Ha ha. These
balls are like you.
I'll always catch
you if you fall.
[swooning]
Seriously? That line worked?
She'll never pick me.
Sure she will, cause
we're gonna help you!
No love potions!
[laughter]
Don't worry, Big Mac. We learned
our lesson the hard way.
Yeah, we're never
gonna do that again.
Besides, I know
exactly what to do!
When I was younger I
read all the fairy tales.
When you were
younger, huh?
Well, I was younger
on the way here.
It was a long ride!
Anyway, as long as we
do what the book says,
you're pretty much
guaranteed a happy ending!
How 'bout this one?!
Rescuing a damsel pony in
distress. That's perfect.
Of course, we'll have to
improvise without a dragon.
Too bad Spike isn't here. Not
that he's very threatening.
[giggles]
So what should we do?
Wait around for Sugar
Belle to get herself
into a scary situation?
OR we bring the danger to her!
[gulp]
All right, Scootaloo's
gonna pretend to take
Sugar Belle's things, then you
swoop in and stop her. Ready?
Nope.
C'mon, you're gonna be her hero!
In fairy tales, the
Knight in Shining Armor
always gets the girl.
Somepony help!
♪♪
Here's your sugar, Sugar. Though
it is not as sweet as you.
[swooning]
Thank you, Feather!
That smooth-talking
pony stole our rescue!
And it totally
would have worked!
Eeyup!
We're just gonna
have to keep trying!
Big Mac, are you ready
to take it up a notch?
Oh, Eeyup!
Oh, Nope.
Trust us. There's nothing
more romantic than waking
your special pony
from a sleeping spell
with a magical kiss!
See? They rode off
into the sunset.
[sighs]
Any sign of Feather Bangs?
Negative. Coast is clear!
It's now or never, Big Mac!
[gulp]
[smooch]
Ah!
Oh, girl, you've been
workin' hard all day.
Allow me to treat you
like the princess you are!
[sighs]
Hey! That's our metaphorical
sunset they're riding off into!
All right. This ends now!
Feather Bangs may
have good timing.
And a good mane. But let's
see him compete with a song!
Say what now?!
Of course! Why didn't
we think of it before?
Every great love story hinges
on the romantic musical number!
Big Mac, you've gotta write
a song for Sugar Belle!
Eyup!
♪♪
Come on, Big Mac!
Feather Bangs is
so romantic
When he speaks, I pretend
he's talking to me.
Come on! You can do better than
him! Just like we practiced.
[gulp]
♪ [country guitar] ♪
♪ We'll take a walk
down by the river. ♪
♪ Watch the sunset
from the field. ♪
♪ We'll plant the seeds
of love together. ♪
♪ And water them right
for a really good yield. ♪
♪ Sugar Belle sweet as pie.
You're the apple of my eye. ♪
♪ A cherry blossom
in a field of rye. ♪
♪ And when the heifer's
milked and fed ♪
♪ and the pigs are
in the sty, ♪
♪ won't you be there
by my side?♪
♪ Oh, oh. Oh, oh. ♪
♪ When you appeared before me
my heart stopped beating. ♪
♪ Stars crossed the sky to
come see what I was seeing. ♪
♪ You were the one that made
me believe I could fly. ♪
♪ Wo-ah wo-ah wo-ah. ♪
♪ Birds could not sing a
song that's as beautiful ♪
♪ I'd do anything
that's irrefutable ♪
♪ cause you are the sun
painting my heart in the sky. ♪
♪ Whoa-oh Sugar, Sugar Belle ♪
♪ wha oh when will you tell
me that you feel the same ♪
♪ like an angel on
a candy cane ♪
♪ or the sunlight shining
through a drain. ♪
♪ Sugar Belle, when I
look in your eyes, ♪
♪ I see the colour blue
♪ and it reminds me of
the sky above ♪
♪ which is also blue. ♪
♪ [dance beat] ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey
Be my sugar plum. ♪
♪ I will be your watermelon. ♪
♪ Every time you smile, I can
feel my heart a swellin'. ♪
♪ Blood is rushing from my
head to my hooves yeah. ♪
♪ I start movin when I'm
feeling that groove, yeah. ♪
♪ I've been writing
this song for you. ♪
♪ Searching for the
perfect rhyme. ♪
♪ For the words I
want to say... ♪
♪ something something
something be mine. ♪
♪ [dance beat] ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh oh.
Every day I see you ♪
♪ I know you could
be the one for me. ♪
♪ Feel my heart a-beating like
the rain upon a bumble bee ♪
♪ don't cha see that
I go ah oh. Ah oh. ♪
Whenever you are
near me I'm so ah oh. ♪
♪ Sugar Belle! Roses are
red and violets are blue. ♪
♪ Sugar, sugar my
love is burning hot ♪
♪ like a cheese fondue! ♪
♪ Sugar Belle! ♪
[crash]
What in Equestria has
gotten into you two?
If you think I'm
the kind of pony
that likes all
this nonsense,
then you clearly
don't know me at all!
I wish everypony would
just LEAVE ME ALONE!
♪ sad music ♪
♪♪
Big Mac!
Well, nopony's seen him.
I feel terrible. I've never seen
my brother so upset before.
BIG MAC! Big Mac!
Are you OK?
Nope.
Sorry it didn't work
out with Sugar Belle.
We don't get it.
Big, grand gestures always
work in the fairy tales!
But Sugar Belle's not
a fairy tale princess;
she's a real pony.
She's kind and she works hard
and she's sweeter than
everything in her bakery.
That's it! We should
have been thinking about
what would mean a
lot to Sugar Belle!
Hmmm.
[gasp]
I know just the thing! But
I'm gonna need your help.
Really? Even after
we messed it up?
Yeeup! C'mon!
♪♪
Hello! My name's
Shimmering Spectacles
and I'm a librarian
with a mysterious past.
Oh. OK. I'm-- wait a
minute. You look familiar.
I shouldn't. Um... I'm new in
town. Mind showing me around?
Uh, sure.
That's the whole town.
It's just the one street.
♪♪
[clatter]
Oh, no, clumsy me! Here,
let me help you clean it up.
I don't think Scootaloo can
hold her off much longer!
Uh... now hold on
a minute.
Are you sure I
can't buy you a new bag?
I'm good. It's no big deal.
But... uh...
OK, what's going on?
The cupcake has landed! Repeat!
The cupcake has landed!
Big Mac!
♪♪
You made me a new display case?
Yeeeup...
And you made it bigger!
You remembered!
Now I have twice as much
room for all my desserts.
[gasp] Which means...
I can make even more!
I've been dying to try baking
cream pies and whoopie pies
and icebox cakes and of
course, more apple treats.
Oh, Big Mac, thank
you so much.
This is the sweetest thing
anypony's ever done for me.
Ummm... yee-- nooope... uh...
I like you, too.
[sigh]
Awwwwwwww!
That was the most
romantic thing ever!
Wait a minute. I
recognize you fillies!
Have they been with
you this whole time?
I'm Big Mac's little sister.
And these are my friends.
We're sorry for everything
we put you through today,
Sugar Belle.
Big Mac never would have gone
through with all of those crazy
Over-the-top...
Downright ridiculous...
attempts to impress you if
we hadn't put him up to it.
But we learned our lesson!
Romance isn't about
impressing somepony;
it's about doing something
that means something special
to that pony you lo--
[ahem] like a lot.
Uh, Apple Bloom? I
think they get it.
[giggle]
♪ Sugar Belle!! Whoa!
Oh! Whoa, whoa! ♪
Sorry, Feather. You're
a little too late.
Yeah, Sugar Belle's already
picked her special somepony.
But don't worry.
You've got three not-so-secret
admirers right behind you!
[sigh]
What should I say to them?
Uh. You're asking us for advice?
Uh huh. Look, I can mane-flip,
write poetry and juggle,
but actually talking to a pony?
It scares me almost
as much as loneliness.
Will you help me? Please?
Gee, I don't know about this.
He just needs a little nudge in
the conversation department!
Besides, I don't think Big
Mac's ready to leave just yet.
Let's do it!
Feather Bangs, the Cutie Mark
Crusaders are at your service!
[laughter]
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ friends ♪