[male voice] The best elements
within us can spread light
and virtue and I know ponies
who represent them all:
strength, bravery, healing,
beauty, hope and sorcery.
Myself and these Pillars of
Equestria were gathered together
by another to maintain
and share the light
of these powerful ideals.
But we soon came to believe the
pony who brought us together,
only wanted that
power for himself.
Cast out and alone,
this power-mad pony
turned to darkness to
satisfy his thirst.
Transformed into
a Pony of Shadows,
he returned for revenge, to
extinguish the Pillars' light
and rob the world of hope.
To stop him, the Pillars and I
must make a grave sacrifice.
But we shall leave behind a
seed in hopes that one day
it will grow into a force to
stand against the darkness
for all time.
We must now face the fiend
with the only plan we have.
"I only hope it will be enough."
That's the last entry.
And maybe Starswirl's final
words before he vanished.
♪ My little pony
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
I've always wondered
what happened to Starswirl.
This is quite a
discovery, Sunburst.
So it's genuine?
You can verify that this
journal really belonged
to Starswirl the Bearded?
Indeed.
From the looks of it,
the last thing he wrote
before facing the
Pony of Shadows.
Uh, so, the Pony of
Shadows was really real?
It appears so.
We never met the other
Pillars and we were too young
to understand the
danger they faced.
[Applejack] Hold
on a second now!
All those legendary
ponies were real too?
And they went off with Starswirl
to face the Pony of Shadows
and then none of them were
ever heard from again?
Ah, yeah. Weren't
you listening?
But what happened
to them all?
They must have
defeated the villain,
since Equestria's still
full of light and hope.
But how? And where
did they go?
My Olde Ponish
is a bit rusty,
but I wonder if the answers
can be found somewhere
within the pages
of this book.
Well, I just happened to be
an expert in Olde Ponish.
I mean, I've practically
memorized every ancient text
about Starswirl there is.
Seriously. All
of them.
We have fond memories
of our old teacher.
If you could discover
what happened to him,
we would be most grateful.
Solving a thousands-year-old
mystery could take forever!
Think of the research, the
re-reading, the re-re-reading.
You might find
you need help.
Luckily, she's got a whole
bushel of helpers right here.
Totally!
Uh, how long will all this
research take, exactly?
Let's get this
back to my library.
I'm sure we'll figure out
what happened in no time.
[excited chatter]
♪♪
[yawn]
Figure it out yet, Twilight?
Wha-WHAT?
What did you figure out?
You figured something out?
[slurp]
What is it?
Nothing.
I mean, Starswirl was
a genius, obviously,
but forget Olde Ponish.
There's parts where
his hornwriting
is like another language!
Agh!
Twilight, we've been
studyin' and referencin'
and cross referencing for
three days straight now.
Ugh. I haven't spent
this much time reading
since the last Daring
Do book came out.
Perhaps it is time
to take a break.
This mystery is over a
thousand years old, after all.
Another day or two
won't make a difference!
Two days?
I don't want to
waste two seconds.
♪♪
I'm close to an answer.
I can feel it.
"Hearg sylfum se
Ponhenge," What's that?
The Temple of Ponhenge?
You can read that?
The hornwriting's
pretty sloppy,
but it's nowhere
near as bad as mine.
"Toward dol grimlic
of fola firgenbeorg?"
At the base of Foal Mountain...
"User endemest scield... "
Our last stand.
Well, that sure sounds
like a clue to me.
♪♪
This is it.
Ponhenge.
I can't believe it.
I've never seen magical
runes like these before.
Have you?
Uh uh.
I don't think anypony's seen
any of this for a long time.
[thud]
It'd take a whole team of ponies
to clear away all this brush.
Even then, I'm not
sure we'd find out
what happened here over
a thousand years ago.
You're right.
I suppose it was a long shot.
Cheer up, Twilight.
Finding a whole set of ancient
ruins is pretty impressive.
Maybe you could
write a paper on it!
I guess I hoped we'd get here
and the mystery would just
magically be explained.
Uh, Twilight?
[gasp]
♪♪
[whoosh]
Starswirl?
I-- I've wanted to
meet you my whole life.
I can't believe
you're here!
♪♪
I don't think
he is here.
I don't think any
of them are.
♪♪
[evil laughter]
You summon me at your
peril, Starswirl.
Once I defeat all of you, this
realm will embrace the darkness
as I did so long ago.
♪♪
[evil laugh]
Drawing me here will
only make me stronger.
You will never defeat me!
We did not come
here to defeat you.
♪♪
What are you doing?
We came to contain you.
Aaaaahhh!
Well, you did ask for
a magical explanation.
♪♪
Uh, what just happened?
It looked like
Starswirl cast a spell
that banished the
Pony of Shadows.
Of course! Powerful
magic like that
would leave an impression
on this place.
Bringing the book back here
let us see what happened.
Which was what?
Starswirl and the rest of the
Pillars sacrificed themselves
to save Equestria.
It's amazing to think one of the
greatest mysteries of Equestria
was solved with a musty old
book from an antique shop.
But I wouldn't say
the mystery's solved.
Starswirl's spell was one of the
most powerful feats of magic
in all of history.
It'll take years of study
before we fully understand it.
I think I understand
Starswirl's spell!
I know I've finished one of
Starswirl's spells before
but this one was on a
whole different level!
Was it an explosion
of magical feedback?
An evocation?
A kind of incantation?
It's Starswirl, so the
possibilities are endless!
And once Starlight set
me on the right track
with his crazy hornwriting--
I mean, he was a genius,
so I guess we can forgive
a little messiness--
I went through the journal
again and it's amazing!
Twilight, darling, we
understand you're excited,
but that's all we understand.
What exactly is so amazing?
Only how Starswirl
and the other Pillars
sent the Pony of
Shadows to limbo!
They did what now?
They used their magic to
open a portal between worlds,
to limbo and pulled the
Pony of Shadows inside.
[poof]
Darling, your diorama!
I made more.
Starswirl thought the only way
to trap the Pony of Shadows
in limbo was for the
Pillars to take him there.
So they got stuck too.
The Pony of Shadows must
have been really awful
for them to do that.
I suppose being trapped for all
time with a super-duper bad guy
in limbo might be OK if
you were doing the limbo,
but that's still pushing it.
The thing is, I think
I can get them out.
Twilight, are you serious?
You can save the most
legendary ponies of all time?
I don't know.
Opening portals between worlds
didn't work out well for me.
Are you sure it's safe?
First of all, you opened
portals through time.
And second of all,
Starswirl wrote the spell
you used to do it.
If he'd been here, he
could have stopped it.
Equestria would be
safer with him in it.
We have to save him.
But you'd be savin'
all the Pillars, right?
And they disappeared
ages ago.
That's the thing
about limbo.
It isn't one
place or another.
It's in between, so
time stands still.
If we can pull them out, it'll
be like they never left.
I actually built another
model to demonstrate--
Agh!
[bang]
What can we do to help?
If I'm right, we need to find
items that are connected
to the Pillars in some way.
You mean, like, stuff
that belonged to them?
How would we know
what to look for?
Or where?
Luckily, Starswirl
took a lot of notes.
My compatriots are as varied
as the realm itself
and hail from every
corner of our land,
bringing with them artifacts
and talismans of great power.
Um, Twilight, what
are you doing?
I'm not doing anything!
Rockhoof's shovel!
Flash Magnus' shield!
Mistmane's flower!
Meadowbrook's mask!
And the blindfold
Somnambula wore
when she faced
that nasty sphinx!
I guess we don't need to figure
out who should get what!
♪♪
Professor! It's a
Mighty Helm headpiece!
Maybe it belonged
to Rockhoof himself!
Legends don't wear helmets.
This belonged to a real pony.
[Applejack] Oh, I
can guarantee
Rockhoof was as real
as you and me.
[laughter]
And I suppose that ravine was
dug with his trusty shovel
to save the village from
an erupting volcano.
Probably.
I love old legends
as much as anypony,
but a pony strong enough to save
a village from rushing lava
with a shovel is preposterous!
[crack]
[rumble]
[shouts]
[grunt]
[crash]
I can't believe
you just did that.
You saved us!
I bet if you told
somepony else the story,
it might sound
preposterous.
♪♪
I suppose some
stories might be true.
And Rockhoof's appears
to be one of them.
[slap]
OW!
You keep those hooves
to yourself, dearie!
This place has been in my
family for generations
and I'm not about to
let some whippersnapper
take the last good
piece of it.
Time was, ponies came from far
and wide to see these gardens.
But that flower's the only
worthwhile thing left.
♪♪
Perhaps it just seemed like
your gardens were worthless,
but a little pruning
can work wonders.
Of course you will
have to look after
more than just
one flower now.
You've given me back
my family's legacy.
The flower you wanted seems
like a fair trade for that.
♪♪
I can't believe Flash
Magnus' shield
ended up in the Dragon Lands.
Good thing you brought the
Official Equestrian Friendship
Ambassador To The Dragons to
help you navigate our customs.
Like our favorite
sport: gorge surfing!
Whoo hoo! HA HA AH AH!
[cheering]
OK. That was
awesome!
Dragon Lord Ember commanded
us to make peace with ponies,
but it doesn't mean you
can surf in our spot.
[growl]
Whoa! Fellas.
As the Official Equestrian
Friendship Ambassador
To The Dragons, I have to say,
that's not very friendly.
Well, what do
you know?
The puny, pony dragon's
sticking up for his pony pal.
Hey! That's an ancient
pony artifact.
Hooves off my gorge board!
I found it in the desert
and finders keepers.
It isn't yours.
Huh. It sure looks like mine.
But, I might consider
racing you for it.
No problem.
Um, no.
I mean you.
Heh heh.
[jeering shouts]
[raspberry]
[gulp]
On your marks...
Get set...
Surf!
[panicked shouts]
I won? I won! WOOO-HOOO!
Give up the shield, Garble.
Lord Ember only commanded
us to be nice to ponies.
She never said anything
about pony-loving dragons.
Since Dragon Lord Ember
commanded you
to make peace with ponies,
you can't very well
attack one of their
friends, can you?
I guess we'll find out!
[grunt]
[shout]
Ugh. Why is he always
hiding behind ponies?
I wasn't hiding when I
beat you down the ridge.
You fell.
Wow, you must be slow, if
all Spike had to do to win
was fall down.
I'm faster than you.
Doubt it.
Fine.
I'll race you back to the top.
If you win, you can
have your pony junk.
But if I win, you'll leave
and I get to give it to him!
Fine. I'm pretty sure I
could beat you anyway,
but with that heavy hunk
of metal on your back,
it'll be a snap.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Thanks for the tip.
[clank]
See ya at the top, loser!
Hey! That's mine!
Finders keepers, remember?
See, because that's
what you said to them
when they first
showed up and--
♪♪
Just remember not to
turn away from them, Cattail.
Flash bees can get
pretty aggressive.
I guess that's why none of
the other bayou animals
can get to the water.
Wouldn't it make more sense
for you to wear the mask
that calms the bees?
It would... if I didn't have to
fly up here to move their hive.
There!
Now the other bayou creatures
can get to the water
without the bees
feeling threatened.
You know, you didn't
have to help with this.
I would've lent you
the mask anyway.
I know.
But I couldn't leave
without helping.
I don't think anypony can
find anything in there.
I wouldn't give
up hope just yet.
This old blindfold was
stuck in the drain.
Weren't you looking
for a blindfold?
Oh, yeah!
I can't believe I'm going to
meet Starswirl the Bearded,
you know, outside of my dreams.
I can't believe you're actually
going through with it.
What do you mean?
I'm all for pushing the
envelope, obviously,
but this is pretty out
there for you, Twilight.
What's "out there" about saving
the most legendary ponies
of all time from a
thousands year-old prison?
Well, nothing when
you say it like that.
Unless "the most legendary
ponies of all time"
knew what they were doing and
we shouldn't mess with it.
I'm sure Starswirl and the
Pillars did the best they could
back then, but magic
has come a long way,
mostly because of
the work they did.
That's true. And you
did get your wings
from finishing one of
Starswirl's spells.
Exactly.
But, then I messed with one and
nearly destroyed the universe,
so...
Starlight, Starswirl the
Bearded is the greatest wizard
who ever lived.
The chance to have him back in
Equestria is worth the risk.
[Spike] That's good news.
Otherwise, we'd have brought
this shield for nothing!
[Applejack] I hope you don't
think you're the only one
to find her artifact, because
this here shovel says otherwise.
Honestly, you two.
Not everything is a competition.
But Mistmane's
flower is by far
the most attractive
of the artifacts.
You're just saying that because
you didn't have to scuba dive
in a pit of green
slime to get yours.
Or move a Flash Bee hive.
Good work everyone.
Let's do this!
[zapping]
♪♪
[crashing]
What-- What has happened?
It worked! We brought you back.
To where?
You and the others have
been trapped in limbo
for over a thousand years,
but I figured out
how to get you ho--
What!?
No, no, no, no! You must
undo what you've done!
What? Why?
I mean, I don't
think I can.
You cannot
bring us back!
But I did.
I brought all the Pillars back.
You cannot bring only
the Pillars back.
[thunder]
[screams]
♪♪
[evil laugh]
Oh, no...