♪♪
Morning, Pinkie Pie.
Get your Ponyville
Chronicle right here!
Fan-tizzy-astic!
I just love to read about happy
happenings and it's always good
to be a pony in
the know, you know?
And there's so much to know!
Seems like a bunch of
boring hooey to me.
Does "NEW SHRUBBERY
IN CASTLE GARDEN"!
sound like boring
hooey to you?
Snooze.
What about...
"PARASPRITE INFESTATION IN
FILLYDELPHIA ERADICATED?"
That's great news!
Another day, another
parasprite hype story.
Noodles named official
food of Whinnyapolis!
Author A.K. Yearling
announces retirement!
Cloudsdale election
heating up for candidate
in favor of
cooling it down!
WHAT? Let me see that!
I never knew you were so
into politics, Rainbow.
No, this!
It CAN'T be true...
I'd have never have picked
noodles as the official food
of Whinnyapolis, either.
But here we are!
No, Pinkie!
I can't believe...
that the greatest author...
and secret pony
adventurer of all time...
A.K. Yearling... is retiring!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
A.K. Yearling just
retired, like, today.
Are you sure she wants visitors?
Pinkie, the A.K. Yearling
I know would never quit
and retire out of the blue!
Something could
be really wrong
and we need to make
sure she's OK.
OK!
Hey, you're not just trying
to make sure she writes
more Daring Do
books, are you?
Of course not!
But that wouldn't
hurt either.
Now, come on!
[fast knocking]
Uh, maybe she's not home.
Maybe she went to the
editor-in-chief of the
Ponyville Chronicle to
correct the misprint
they've made!
Nope. She's home.
How do you know?
Because she's right there...
looking all sad and alone.
I knew it.
Something is wrong!
A.K!
Now she's sighing with
the weight of the world.
Now she's hanging her
head in utter despair!
Now she's shaking her hoof
and cursing the heavens
like nothing could ever
possibly be the same again!
Why oh why did this
happen to her?
What?
Whoops.
Never mind, that time
she was just stretching.
A.K., it's us! Rainbow
Dash and Pinkie Pie!
Your friends!
♪♪
Oh, no. Did somepony ransack
your cottage again
and steal some ancient
mysterious relic
that's the key to saving
all of Equestria?
Oooh! Sparky!
[gasp]
[relieved sigh]
Nothing's been stolen.
Then is somepony blackmailing
you and forcing you to retire?
Cause if they are...
No. Nothing like that.
So you're just quitting
and moving away?
WHY. WOULD. YOU. DO. THAT?
I already explained everything
to the Ponyville Chronicle.
Oh, really?
"Author A.K. Yearling
announced yesterday
that the next adventure novel
in her popular series,
'Daring Do and the Curse
of the Pharaoh's Tomb'
will be her last.
Yearling looks forward
to her retirement."
That doesn't
explain anything!
[small groan]
It just says you're
giving up writing stories.
But most ponies don't know that
you actually are Daring Do
and that the
stories are real.
So what you're REALLY saying
is that you're giving up
being Daring Do, but
you're not saying why!
Of course, if you don't
feel like talking about it,
that's A-OK, A.K.!
As your friends, we
completely understand.
Right, Rainbow Dash?
Oh. Yeah. We just came to
make sure you're all right.
That's really why we wanted
to find out what's going on.
If you really
want to know...
My last quest took me to a
village in Southern Equestria
where I started seeing these.
"WAKE OF DESTRUCTION:
DARING DO RUINS ENTIRE
VILLAGE MARKETPLACE!"
"DARE OR SCARE?
LOCAL ROGUE 'DARING DO'
INVOLVED IN FRIGHTFUL FIASCO?"
"DARING DO LEADS BULL INTO CHINA
SHOP DURING HIGH SPEED CHASE--"
That's enough!
[sigh]
Everypony I tried to
help is mad at me.
That's not true!
They're not mad
at A.K. Yearling.
They're mad at
"Daring Do."
They don't sell my books
in Southern Equestria.
The ponies there don't
know who A.K. Yearling is.
They only know Daring Do
and apparently she does
more harm than good.
I guess it's a good thing
you look so different
as A.K. Yearling!
So all we have to
do is go down there
and explain to these ponies that
none of this stuff is true.
Easy-peazy-cheezy!
But that's just the thing...
it is true.
WHAT?
I guess I've always
been so focused
on saving priceless relics
and stopping the bad guys
that I never really thought
about the mess I leave behind.
Then you ARE in
a tricky pickle.
But why is all this
happening now?
I guess ponies are
finally fed up.
Either way, I'm done with
adventures: having or writing.
Come on!
For every one
pony who's upset,
there must be at least a hundred
that know you're a hero.
I don't think so, Dash.
Well, why don't we go visit
this village "Somnambula"
and see for ourselves?
Those articles seem to
make it pretty clear
how the villagers feel.
But if we go there, the ponies
can tell you in person
just how much they
appreciate you.
And what a heap of rotten apple
cores these articles are!
You really think so?
I know so!
Let's go!
[sigh]
♪♪
This is so cool!
It looks just like that
village in your last book
where Daring Do recovers
the Doomed Diadem
from The Wild Bunch Gang
who chase after her
through the desert!
It should.
I based that entire chapter
on my experiences here
in Somnambula.
What happens? No
wait, don't tell me.
I CHANGED MY MIND! TELL ME!
Daring Do thwarts Ahuizotl's
evil plot to separate
the Sister Crown Relics.
And if it wasn't for her, the
region would be cursed
with eternal night and the
entire town of Somnambula
would have sunk
into the ground!
Ah Pssht! There's no
chance that these ponies
don't think you're a hero.
Watch this.
Hiya there, Mister!
I was hoping you could tell me
about a pony named Daring Do.
I hear she's an awesome
adventure-pony hero.
Daring Do?
Oh, she's awesome, all right.
Awesome at destroying
ponies' apple carts
[crash]
and priceless,
sacred statues!
♪♪
Indeed. Daring
Do is a menace
who destroys everything
she touches!
[murmurs of agreement]
What? No!
Daring Do is the exact
opposite of a menace.
I tried to tell you!
Coming back here
was a mistake!
♪♪
Come on, A.K.! So we
picked a bad example.
That was just one angry pony!
Two angry ponies!
It doesn't matter.
I never should
have come with you!
You two should just go home.
Come on! We gotta
follow her!
I dunno...
it really seemed like
she doesn't want us
cramping her saddle.
But we have to convince her
that ponies do appreciate her!
As her friend, I have to
make sure she believes that.
Look, Pinkie! It's
the "Get On Inn."
Daring Do stays here all
the time in her adventures.
Which means there must be
ponies here who love Daring Do!
Maybe they can help us.
Mmmmm.
My nose is telling me to
help myself to muffins.
[ding]
Come on.
Ooo, she's fancy.
I got this!
A good evening
to you, Madame!
We are but weary travelers who
humbly wish to inquire
on the status of a
certain mare of intrigue
taking residence here.
What in Southern Equestria
are you on about?
Is it true that
Daring Do stays here?
Ha! Not anymore, she doesn't!
Why not?
The last time I rented
that rascal a room,
she was in a such a rush to
high-tail it outta here,
she didn't even pay her bill!
But--
After that, a band of
ruffians showed up
and destroyed half the
rooms looking for her.
Guess she made them even
more mad than she made me!
No, no, no. You've
got it all wrong.
How do ya figure?
Daring Do was trying to
save everypony from the
Curse of the Doomed
Diadem of Xilati!
And she was only in a rush
because she had to get the crown
back to the Tiara of Teotlale
before the curse took effect.
Chapter seventeen.
Sounds like a tall tale to me.
And a hard one to believe now
that I know Daring Do
is a scoundrel and a thief!
Every year, ponies come to
offer precious glowpaz
to the Sonmambula
statue in the village
in hopes for a good future.
Why that poor fella had
his glowpaz necklace
stolen by Daring Do
just yesterday!
Hmmmm.
[gasp]
THERE'S A.K.!
Daring Do RUINED our town and
stole our precious glowpaz!
We need to make sure that
if she turns up again,
there will be consequences!
Everypony who's with me,
meet at the statue tomorrow!
[crowd agrees]
Now I'm getting blamed for
things I didn't even do?
Why would I steal from them?
They are SUPER BAD!
But... we're still
staying the night, right?
Because I already ate all
the free mini muffins!
Listen, A.K., after a
good night's sleep,
we're going to fix
all of this.
I promise.
I shouldn't be
here, Rainbow Dash.
This is never
going to work.
Of course it will!
All I have to do is go up
there and explain to everypony
how wrong they all are.
Yeah! And then I'll be
like what she said!
Easy-peazy-cheezy.
Exactly!
Here it is! The
remains of your--
I mean our
Somnambula statue.
Now that Daring Do has
destroyed it, tell me...
where will we hang our glowpaz?
We don't even have any glowpaz
because they were stolen
by Daring Do!
[shouts of agreement]
Daring Do would
never steal anything!
And OK, she destroyed
your statue,
but it was because she was
trying to save you all
from Ahuizotl!
[curious chatter]
Ahuizotl?
He's about yea big?
Long neck?
Itty-bitty face?
Weird claw thingy on his tail?
Ooo! Ooo! I know him!
He's a baddie.
[concerned murmurs]
Trust me, if Ahuizotl had gotten
away with the Doomed Diadem,
your entire village would
have been swallowed up!
And that's a lot worse than
losing some CRUMMY old statue!
[gasp]
Ahem!
This was not some
crummy old statue.
It was the namesake
of our town.
If you want to understand us,
you must first understand her.
Who?
Somnambula...
Long ago this village fell
prey to an evil Sphinx
who demanded most
of their crops.
Like her fellow villagers,
Somnambula didn't have much,
but she used what she had to
keep others from giving up hope.
The son of the
Pharaoh, Prince Hisan,
was so moved by
her compassion,
that he decreed nopony
would go hungry again.
♪♪
But when Hisan stood
up to the Sphinx,
the beast captured him, telling
the Pharaoh the only way
to get Hisan back was to
solve her riddle.
Nopony would volunteer
to save the prince.
Nopony except Somnambula.
♪♪
The Sphinx gave her the riddle,
"I shine brightest in the dark.
I am there but cannot be seen.
To have me costs you nothing.
To be without me costs
you everything."
As Somnambula thought
of the hardship
she and her fellow
villagers had experienced,
she instantly
knew the answer.
"HOPE!"
She shouted.
The Sphinx was so enraged, it
seemed she might still refuse
to release the prince,
so Somnambula asked her
for one more challenge,
but if she
accomplished it,
the Sphinx would leave
from the kingdom forever.
The Sphinx quickly agreed,
asking only that Somnambula
walk to the prince...
across a deep
chasm, blindfolded!
Further, the Sphinx had
cast a powerful spell
that prevented
Somnambula from flying.
[evil laugh]
But Somnambula never lost HOPE!
She knew she'd need to
make a leap of faith
to save the prince.
Guided by the sound
of the prince's voice...
she easily made it across.
[roar]
♪♪
The Pharaoh asked how
Somnambula prevailed
and she explained that
she had always hoped
she could make things
better for her people
and that hope
had carried her through.
The Prince replaced the
pearls Somnambula gave up
with a string of Glowpaz.
And around her neck, they
glowed bright enough
to light the entire kingdom.
Forever after, Glowpaz
became our symbol of hope.
Wow. I had no idea how special
the statue was to you.
Somnambula sounds like
a pretty cool pony.
But I bet if she were here,
she'd tell you how cool
Daring Do is too
because they've both
fought to protect this town!
[chattering]
If Somnambula were here today,
she would condemn Daring Do
for destroying yo--
OUR symbol of hope!
[booing and shouts]
♪♪
Hey, buddy!
What did Daring Do ever do
to you to deserve all this?
Only... everything!
Dr. Caballeron?
Yes... Rainbow Dash.
[nasty laugh]
When I saw you,
her closest friend,
I knew that Daring Do
would not be far behind.
I really do owe you for
leading her right to me.
But I didn't mean--
Thank you for helping me
break Daring Do's spirit
by destroying
her reputation,
but I can't have you running
off and telling her my plan.
[whistle]
♪♪
HELP!
Caballeron?
No!
He's got Rainbow Dash!
Come on!
[panting]
I'm... coming...
Rainbow... Dash...
I knew you'd come!
You did?
I sure didn't.
What if I cause
more trouble?
You won't.
How do you know?
I just do!
You wouldn't let anything
happen to Rainbow Dash.
You care too much.
You're right.
Which way did they go?
To the pyramid!
[Dash] Somepony help!
Somepony! Anypony!
Pinkie Pie! Daring Do!
Is that you?
Don't worry, Rainbow!
We'll save you!
[rumbling]
[gurgling]
[evil laugh]
If my previous plan didn't cause
you to give up, Daring Do,
then the shame of losing your
dear friend Rainbow Dash
to the slime will!
Oh, and that ancient magic
from the legend is real.
There'll be no flying
in the pyramid!
Good luck, Daring Do!
[laughter]
[slam]
He's right! We'll never
get to her in time!
If this really is like
Somnambula's story,
then we just have to
have hope that we can!
I think we need more
than hope, Pinkie.
There was a bridge in the story
and there's no bridge here.
What are we going to do?
[moans]
I don't know, but Rainbow
Dash is our friend!
Just like Somnambula. We
need to make a leap of faith
and hope that we can save her!
PINKIE!
Wheeee!
Hee hee hee!
♪♪
I knew we'd do it!
Thanks for reminding me to
never give up hope, Pinkie.
And I'm kinda hoping you
ponies will untie me
before we all take a bath
in bubbling green slime!
We're on it!
♪♪
Not so fast, Caballeron!
YOU stole our glowpaz!
[angry shouts]
I should have known you were
just trying to sully my name
so that you'd be free to
steal whatever you wanted.
Of course that was
the plan, Daring Do!
At first I just
wanted the Glowpaz...
But then I saw an opportunity to
write you out of the story
FOR GOOD!
[gasps]
And with the destruction
you leave in your wake,
it didn't take too much
to convince ponies
you were a villain.
You're wrong, Caballeron.
And I won't let you
break my spirit again.
Because I'm never
going to give up hope
that I can protect ponies
and ancient treasures
from miscreants like you!
[agreeing shouts]
Remember! She
ruined your statue!
You're fools to
believe in her!
You'll pay for this, Daring Do!
[cheers]
OK, OK that's enough!
Thanks for helping
me come to my senses.
You two are true friends.
Are you kidding?
That.
Was.
Awesome!
We're just glad you're back
to your old self again!
[giggle] Me too!
But I'm glad I realized that
even if you're fighting
for something good, you're still
responsible for your actions.
And if something bad happens
that you didn't intend,
you shouldn't give up hope
or lose faith in yourself.
Yeah! All ya gotta do
is make it right.
Feel free to use that
in your next book!
You know, I think I will.
[squeals]
♪♪
[ding]
[cheers]