♪♪
That's the last entry...
Starswirl's final words
before he vanished!
[Applejack] All those legendary
ponies were real too?
And then NONE of them were
ever heard from again?
They used their magic to
open a portal to limbo
[screaming moan]
We need to find items
that are connected
to the pillars in some way.
We brought you back!
You cannot bring ONLY
the pillars back!
[evil laughter]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[evil laughter]
Your pitiful attempt
to imprison me
has FAILED, Starswirl!
[zap]
You must return us to limbo.
It's the only way to stop him.
I only figured out
how to bring you back.
Working on it.
No table of contents.
Allow me to assist.
[crashing]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
There!
Without the power of Ponehenge,
your banishing spell is useless.
You have studied my writings.
Surely you have some other plan.
No. I just wanted to save
you, I didn't think--
Don't fret.
When I extinguish the light and
hope of this miserable world,
you won't remember any of this.
No!
This one is almost as
strong as you, Starswirl.
But even in my weakened state,
she cannot stop the
might of shadows!
[shouts]
Lucky for her,
she's not alone.
ARRGGGHHH!
Know this, fiend.
We will not rest until we find
a way to return you to limbo.
[snarl]
Never!
Your days of glory are
through, Starswirl.
Now my dark power will reign
and you six will bow to me!
[whoosh]
Um, where'd he go?
That is a riddle
we must unravel.
And quickly.
How long have we been gone?
Over a thousand years.
Then my spell worked before
it was meddled with.
And the realm has been at
peace for a millennia!
Well, we did have to save
everypony from Nightmare Moon
and Discord and Chrysalis and
King Sombra and Lord Tirek and
there was that one time when
Starlight traveled through time
and almost destroyed
life as we know it!
But that's all in the past.
If you are truly
this accomplished,
we will stop the Pony of
Shadows twice as fast together.
We shall see.
It is an easy thing to say
you have saved the world.
It is quite another to do it.
Oh, we've saved
the world, beardo.
And we can do it again.
Be that as it may, the problem
of locating the Pony of Shadows
remains and this land is vast.
It sounds like you need a map.
Luckily, we have just the thing.
Something about this
magic seems familiar.
[whoosh]
[astonished cries]
Did you know he
could do that?
He's Starswirl!
He can do anything!
This map and, indeed, this very
castle are grown from the seed
we planted over a
thousand years ago.
Then it did work!
What worked?
Each of us infused a crystal
seed with our magic
in hopes that it would grow
into a force for good.
We wanted to leave something
to protect the realm
in our absence,
but we never dreamed our gift
would become so powerful.
Y'all mean the
elements came from you?
You know, the sparkly
crystal things that grow
from the Tree of Harmony
and represent each of us?
Laughter.
Honesty.
Generosity.
Loyalty.
Kindness.
And magic!
They are reflections of our own
elements of hope, strength,
beauty, bravery,
healing and sorcery.
We had no idea our
small seed would bloom
into the living
spirit of the land.
I am glad our mantles have
passed to such capable ponies.
[Starswirl] More importantly, we
no longer need Ponhenge
to send our foe
back to limbo.
We can use the stored magic in
this "Tree of Harmony."
But doesn't a banishing spell
take a lot of power?
We'd have to sacrifice
the elements for that.
Mm hm
They'd be gone.
Forever?
Starswirl, I don't think
the Tree can survive
without the elements.
If it dies, Equestria
will suffer.
If the Pony of Shadows has his
way, your land will not exist.
So unless you have
a better idea...
[whoosh]
♪♪
Our foe will seek dark places
from which to draw power.
I will prepare my spell,
so that we may strike as
soon as you find him.
What are we waiting for?
I like your spirit!
Uh huh! Oh yeah!
What about
this one?
Sea Pony etiquette isn't going
to help right now, Spike.
Uh, Twilight?
Are you OK?
I just unleashed ultimate
evil and doomed Equestria
because I was obsessed
with meeting my idol.
Why wouldn't I be OK?
[thud]
You didn't know that
was gonna happen.
But I should have listened to
you and left things alone.
Now the elements of harmony
will be lost to fix my mistake!
Maybe there's another way.
If there is, Twilight
will find it.
Portal gate... portal keys...
portal spells.
YES! If the Pillars can hold
open the gateway to limbo,
a powerful pony can do the
banishing spell herself!
Do you know what this means?
I can stop carrying books?
The Pillars don't have
to leave Equestria!
Even though we'll
lose the elements,
we'll have the ponies
that created them.
And the Pony of shadows
will be banished for good!
That's great.
But I was thinking
of another way
that maybe doesn't involve
"banishing" at all?
Starswirl knew what he was
doing when he cast that spell.
If I can make it
even better,
maybe he'll see that I take
magic as seriously as he does.
[traffic noises]
It seems the dark places
Starswirl indicated on
the map have changed.
I bet the Pony of Shadows
would've loved the
Ghastly Caverns
before 1000
years of erosion
turned it into the
Ghastly Gorge.
The "Appeloosian Wastes" sure
sounded dark and desolate.
Who knew they would become
such a popular square
dancing destination?
And I get how this
part of Equestria
used to be cast
in eternal night
where the Pony of Shadows could
draw power and wreak havoc
while ponies were powerless
to stop him, but,
it's kinda made a comeback.
Did I mention it's
really bright?
It seems there are fewer dark
corners in the realm these days.
Isn't that a good thing?
True. The Pony of Shadows
will have a hard time
regaining power.
When he rears his
head, we'll be ready!
Isn't there some way to banish
him without losing all of you?
I wish there were.
But to save our home, we
are willing to leave it.
[door opens]
I don't think you'll have to!
My spell isn't finished yet,
but I think we can send The
Pony of Shadows to limbo
without all of you
having to go as well!
While I appreciate your
enthusiasm, Twilight,
this is hardly the time to take
risks on half-baked spells.
[whimper]
Begging your pardon,
Mr. The Bearded.
But Twilight doesn't
do anything half-way.
Especially not magic!
Seriously! She got her wings by
finishing one of your spells.
I think you'll find her
work is worth reading
before you dismiss
it out of hoof!
Mm hm!
While it is an
unconventional approach,
I believe it could work.
Hm.
I suppose there
is a chance.
But we still have no idea
where to find the villain.
♪♪
Maybe we should try there?
The Hollow Shades.
I think a branch of the
Apple family lives there.
They'd have to be
pretty distant.
The Hollow Shades was
abandoned eons ago.
Hm, that's odd.
The only time the map's called
all of us to one place
was Starlight's village.
So it's like a
super-villain tracker!
No offence.
Do you think the map could
be trying to tell us
where the Pony of Shadows is?
Hmmm.
The Tree of Harmony acting to
protect the light of the realm.
Yes, a good thought, Twilight.
I will make my
notes on this spell.
Ready yourselves for battle.
Uh, I know I'm not as
experienced as all of you,
but is banishment
really the only option?
I mean, it's been a long time.
Maybe the Pony of
Shadows is ready to talk?
I doubt we can save our
homeland with a conversation.
But we could try.
Starlight, I'm sure Starswirl
and the others did try.
The Pony of Shadows was not
interested in reconciliation.
Once a villain,
always a villain.
Twilight? Sunburst?
Would you accompany me?
I wish to refine this
spell for our use.
Come! We must prepare
for the struggle ahead.
I know Starswirl
is a great wizard,
but this whole
plan seems wrong.
The map's only ever sent us
to solve friendship problems.
Maybe so, but the
Pony of Shadows
doesn't really seem like the
friendship type.
Honestly?
We don't know
anything about him.
Nopony does.
That's not entirely true.
You all knew the Pony of Shadows
before he became what he is now.
You must've been friends.
So what happened?
The tale of our
rift is a sad one.
♪♪
♪ [hypnotic singing] ♪
[shouts]
♪ [singing continues] ♪
[Rockhoof] Stygian was a pony
like the rest of us,
though more scholar than hero.
He recognized our
emerging world
would need champions
to defend it.
[whoosh]
[roar]
[zap]
[Flash Magnus] He may have
gathered us together,
but he, himself was just
an ordinary unicorn
who soon grew jealous
of our abilities.
[Mistmane] He stole objects
from each of us ...
artifacts to use in a spell.
[Meadowbrook] And we cast
him out for it.
[Somnambula] We always
thought he'd return
and seek forgiveness.
But when we saw him again, his
heart was bent on revenge.
He dashed even my
hope of saving him.
[zap]
But why did he steal
the artifacts from you?
No doubt it was an enchantment
to take our powers for himself.
Hm.
♪♪
That looks like a lot of work.
It is what must be done
and it would be best
if we were not disturbed.
I'm sorry, Starlight, but
we can't stop to talk.
The stakes are too
high and we have to...
banish Stygian to limbo.
I get it.
Uh, who? Stygian
was the name the
Pony of Shadows gave up
when he turned to darkness.
And I'm just trying
to figure out why.
Envy. He wanted more
power than he had
and that desire led
him down a path
from which there is no return.
I know from experience
that's not always true.
When the map called
you six to my village,
it was for a
friendship problem.
Are you sure this is different?
I...
Stygian wants to destroy all
that is good in this world.
There's no way to
befriend a pony like that.
[door closes]
I guess I'm lucky your
idol wasn't around
when you decided to
be my friend.
I might've been
banished to limbo too.
♪♪
[doors slam]
[Somnambula] I am glad we
have the chance to see
what has grown from our
efforts so long ago.
It seems a shame
to harm it.
A necessary sacrifice.
With the elements' power,
we will bind the Pony
of Shadows in limbo.
And thanks to Twilight,
we will remain to watch
over the realm ourselves.
[zap]
Um, how do we use them?
Well, you--Oh. I'm not sure.
They simply work for us.
The elements are
attuned to you.
We must use their
magic in pairs.
[Rainbow Dash] No problem!
We're used to banishing
evil before breakfast.
And it'll be an honor to
save Equestria with y'all.
I really hope Twilight
knows what she's doing.
♪ [ominous music] ♪
I don't remember reading
anything that said
the Hollow Shades
was like this.
[Mistmane] The Pony of Shadows
must have twisted it
to his purposes.
Prepare yourselves.
He is here.
Stygian! Show
yourself and face us!
[evil laughter]
[rumbling]
[crashing]
♪♪
I definitely would have
remembered reading about this.
[evil laughter]
Welcome to the Well of Shade!
When you turned your backs on
me, I discovered this place.
The darkness spoke to me of
a power beyond any
I could imagine and I listened.
The shadow and I became one.
Soon all of the realm
will be the same.
Then all ponies will
feel the despair I did
when you cast me out!
[Starswirl] We did
what we had to do.
You tried to steal our
powers for yourself.
No! It was you who were selfish!
And now you will pay!
[zap]
Are you still sure this
isn't a friendship problem?
Ready?
Open the portal...
[crash]
NOW!
♪♪
No! You will not
trap me again!
Twilight! Push him in!
Huh?
There's a pony in there.
Are you...
Stygian?
I was, once.
Until my friends betrayed me.
But Starswirl says
you betrayed them.
You wanted their magic.
No! I wanted
their respect.
I brought them
together.
I planned strategy and
I read all I could
about the beasts we faced.
But I didn't have
magic or strength.
So nopony every noticed me.
I went to Ponehenge to make my
own copies of the artifacts.
With them, I thought I
could be a Pillar too!
And stand by their
side in battle.
I never wanted to
steal their power.
But instead of sharing
and letting me help,
my friends threw me out.
So I became stronger
than any of them!
The darkness welcomed me
when no pony would.
I will do what I
must to protect it!
This is all a
misunderstanding!
If the Pillars
knew how you felt,
I'm sure they wouldn't have
turned their backs on you.
The shadow isn't
who you really are.
Let me help you
be Stygian again.
Even if my friends
did still care,
what makes you think you
have the power to help me?
Because it's
what she does.
I wasn't so different from you
and Twilight helped me change.
If there's one pony in Equestria
that can save a friendship,
it's her.
I--I want to believe you.
But the darkness
will not be stopped!
[shouts]
Fight the darkness, Stygian!
You don't need it anymore.
Revenge isn't what you
want, friendship is!
Twilight!
[grunt]
[roar]
The shadow won't let go of him.
He wants to stop, but
he can't do it alone.
Then we must help him.
♪♪
[bellowing cries]
[grunt]
[sigh]
♪♪
YEAH! It felt so good
to do that again!
Friendship power rush!
WOO!
The elements!
They didn't disappear.
Maybe because we used them
for healing magic
instead of banishing?
Look!
Long ago you needed
our help, Stygian,
but instead of listening,
we turned our backs on you.
Pride clouded my judgment.
I owe you an apology.
Thank you for helping us see the
errors of our ways, Twilight.
It seems I never accounted
for the magic of friendship.
Thank you, Swirlstar.
Starswirl!
♪♪
AHEM.
So apparently a conversation
can save Equestria?
[chuckle]
Something tells me I will be
making a lot of apologies today.
I simply cannot believe
how tall you've gotten!
Well, it has been
over a thousand years.
Will you stay here and
teach magic once again?
My sister and I have such fond
memories of your lessons.
As long as you don't ask for
those essays we owed you
before you disappeared.
[chuckle]
I am not certain Canterlot
is where I belong.
The realm has grown and I
believe I'll have a look around
before I settle
in any one place.
And I long to see what
has become of my home.
I believe we all do.
Then I hope you will return to
Canterlot on occasion
and share the wisdom of
your great experience
with the next
generation of ponies.
We would be honored, but
if it is wisdom you seek,
look no further
than your own pupil.
She showed me that the
power of friendship
is a magical force indeed.
And that in turning
away from others,
you hurt yourself as well.
It's funny. I thought
meeting my idol
would give me all the
answers I ever wanted.
But instead, I forgot
what I already knew.
Good thing I had a student
of my own to remind me.