♪♪
[excited chatter]
Hm.
♪♪
Ah, thank you!
You must be new.
I'm Apple Bloom.
I'm Grand Pear.
Welcome to Ponyville!
You mean, welcome
back to Ponyville!
Grand Pear was
originally from here
before he opened his famous
pear jam store in VanHoover!
Really? Why'd you move back?
I uh, well, I needed
a change of pace.
Ah.
[chomp]
This is delicious!
I can't believe I've
gone my whole life
without ever having this!
Glad you like it.
How much?
Nah.
Wow, thanks, Mr.
Grand Pear, sir!
It was real nice meetin' you!
[chatter]
Glad you're back, sugar cube!
Just in time for
breakfast-for-dinner!
I got the perfect topper for
flapjacks at the market today!
[gasp]
PEAR JAM?
What were you thinking?
[door closes]
[tense music]
Quick, hide it!
Huh?
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
What's the big deal?
It's just Pear Jam!
The big deal
is that there
is a long-
standing feud
between the Apples
and the Pears!
Yeeup!
Why?
Well, uh, actually
I'm not really sure.
You have any idea, Big Mac?
Uuuuh, nope.
Then I guess we
should ask Granny?
Ask me what?
Uh, what goes better with
apple fritter flapjacks,
caramel syrup or praline?
Praline!
Oh ho ho, that smells
great, Applejack!
I'm gonna wash
up for supper.
Be right back.
[door closes]
[sigh]
Listen, sugar cube.
Anytime Big Mac and I ever
asked Granny about the feud
or the Pears, she'd get so
upset she couldn't talk.
Best not bring it up.
OK. But that Grand Pear
was really nice to me,
even though I'm an Apple.
I wonder what happened.
Me too.
But if we can't ask Granny,
I don't know who--
We can ask Goldie Delicious!
If anypony knows about the
feud, it's the family historian!
I'm in! Whaddya
say, Big Mac?
Sibling trip first
thing tomorrow?
Yeeup!
[knock]
[yowling cats]
[crash]
Now that's how you
make an entrance.
Or is it an exit?
Well, anyway, it's so
wonderful to see you three!
To what do I owe
the pleasure?
Well, Goldie, we were hoping you
could tell us about the... uh...
feud with the Apples
and the Pears.
Oh... oh, dear!
Does Granny Smith
know you're here?
No, ma'am.
But I ran into Grand Pear
yesterday and he was real nice.
Maybe the feud was a
misunderstanding or something
and we can fix it?
Hmm. Well, I don't know
about that, little one.
But if it's the
story you're after,
I suppose you have
a right to know.
Let's see here, I got a stack
of books here someplace.
Oh! Apple family history
volume one-thirty-seven.
Here we are!
Feud with the Bears.
I mean Pears.
My eyes ain't what
they used to be.
A long time ago,
Sweet Apple Acres
wasn't the only
farm in Ponyville.
In fact, there was another
one just right next door,
Come and get your apples!
Nothing sweeter than
biting into a crisp apple
on a beautiful fall day.
Unless, of course, you could
bite into a juicy pear!
Please!
Pears are just what happens
when you ain't no good
at farming apples.
Pears are nature's candy!
Apples are sour,
like the expression on
your face right now!
[chuckle]
[Goldie] And so it went.
Granny and Grand Pear were
always at each other:
Who was the best farmer?
Who took better
care of their trees?
If Granny read to
her trees at night...
"...And then the little
tree reached its branches
up to the moon and the
moon said good night."
...why then Grand Pear had
special blankets made
for his trees so they
wouldn't get cold.
Good night, trees.
[kiss]
I've got you covered.
Mm hm.
[snarl]
[shouts]
In fact, all the Apples and the
Pears were rivals to the core.
The only Apple and Pear
who ever got along
were Bright Macintosh
and Pear Butter.
Psst.
I'm not supposed
to talk to you.
I'm not supposed to
talk to you either.
My mom says if you hold a
buttercup under your chin,
it'll make your
chin glow.
But it doesn't
work on me.
See?
Does it work on me?
[heartbeat]
It sure does, buttercup.
Buttercup. I
like that name.
[Applejack] Wait an
apple pickin' minute!
Bright Mac and Buttercup?
Those are our parents names!
Course, Buttercup was just
the nickname your father
gave your mother.
Pear Butter. Well, that
was her given name.
Are you saying our
mother was a Pear ?
[gasp]
So we are
half-Pear?
I can't
believe it!
How did we
not know?
Well, nopony called your
mother Pear Butter...
And her cutie mark was a
preserve jar but pear butter
don't look too much different
from apple butter...
so no clues there.
Is there anything else you
can tell us about them?
I know they loved
each other very much!
They had that
magical, star-kissed,
other side of a
rainbow kind of love.
You couldn't be
around 'em too long
and not feel a little bit
lighter than air yourself.
[giggle]
Anything else?
I'd need volume one hundred
and thirty-eight for that.
[snarl]
I'm sure I could wrangle it...
in a couple days.
That's all
right, Goldie.
It was nice
just to hear--
Ooh ooh! I just
remembered somethin'!
Your dad and his
buddy, Burnt Oak,
would get in all kinds of
trouble together as colts!
Burnt Oak?
The firewood salespony?
I haven't seen
him in ages.
He and your dad were thick
as thieves back in the day.
Y'all should talk to him.
[crash]
[growl]
Well, well, if it
isn't the Apples!
What can I do for you?
I know you're not
here for firewood.
You've got more trees
than anypony in Ponyville!
You're right.
We're not here for that.
Come to ask
about your dad?
Uh, eeeyup.
I wondered if you might.
I hoped you would.
It's nice to talk about him.
[laugh]
We had a lot of laughs.
In fact, this one time...
we were racing to see who
could till the fastest
and Bright Mac was
leavin' me in the dust!
He would've won too if he
wasn't so distracted.
Whoa!
[crash]
[splash]
Oh!
Pear Butter! What
did you do?
I... I'm not sure.
[Bright Mac] She
didn't do it, sir.
Excuse me?
The water silo.
It was my fault.
You owe me a
new silo, boy.
And you, come with me.
No daughter of mine is gonna
make goo goo eyes at an Apple.
♪♪
Grand Pear never
would have known
it was your
father's fault!
But there was no way
he'd let your mother
take the blame for
something he did.
So Dad was super honest!
Apple doesn't fall far from
the tree huh, Applejack?
Your dad worked the
apple farm all day
and then headed over to the
Pear's on his breaks
to fix the water silo.
I didn't see him for weeks!
Not that he minded.
Gave him a chance to
get to know your ma.
Did you know our mom, too?
Buttercup was a real
peach of a Pear
but if you want to
know more about her,
you should ask
Mrs. Cake.
Mrs. Cake?
She and your mom
were inseparable
when they were fillies!
Then let's go!
Thanks, Burnt Oak.
Would it be OK if we
stopped by again sometime?
To hear more stories?
I'd like that very much.
♪♪
Well, cinnamon sugar on toast,
all three Apple siblings!
Hi, Mrs. Cake. We heard you
and our ma used
to be real good friends
and we were hoping you could
tell us a bit about her.
Oh, I would love to.
I never knew the right
time to bring it up,
but I'm so glad you came.
For starters, did you all
know that it was your mom
who convinced me
to pursue baking?
But isn't your name Mrs. Cake?
Not always.
Back when I was Chiffon Swirl,
I had no idea what I
was supposed to do.
But one day, your mom brought me
some candied pears, eggs, flour,
sugar and vanilla and told
me to just be creative.
Next thing I knew,
I was whipping up
pear upside-down cake
and I got my cutie mark!
It was like she knew what
I was supposed to do
long before I did.
Just like you, sugarcube!
Or rather, you're
just like her!
That was the first
of many cakes for me
and Buttercup was with
me through it all.
She'd be my taste tester...
help with the
decorating...
and prep new ingredients.
Over the years, I
perfected my recipes.
Your mom did so much for me,
one day I wanted to
surprise her with a cake.
♪♪
[laughter]
[sneeze]
[giggle]
[crack]
[gasp]
Oh, it's just you!
Sorry.
I just brought you a little
something to say thank you...
but I see you're busy.
[giggle]
Promise you won't say anything.
What in tarnation are
you doin', Bright Mac?
We do not fraternize
with Pears!
Ptui!
♪♪
You and Bright Mac?
I wouldn't believe it if I
hadn't seen it with my own eyes.
Your families hate each other!
I can't help it, we
just sort of happened.
Then Pear Butter told me
the sweetest love story
I have ever heard.
Happy one-hundred-and-thirty-one
-thousand-four-hundred-
and-fifty-six-hour
anniversary, Darlin.
What? Ha ha.
That's way longer than
we've been together.
I know.
But it's the anniversary
of the first time
I called you Buttercup.
It's OK if you didn't
get me anything.
Actually, I did.
A guitar? For me?
But I don't know
how to play!
Quiet, you.
♪♪
♪ We're far apart in
every way, ♪
♪ but you're the best
part of my day... ♪
♪ And sure as I
breathe the air, ♪
♪ I know we are the
perfect pair. ♪
♪ On a prickly path that
goes on for miles, ♪
♪ but it's worth it just
to see you smile... ♪
♪ And I cannot
be pulled apart, ♪
♪ from the hold you
have on my heart. ♪
♪ And even if the world
tells us it's wrong, ♪
♪ you're in my head
like a catchy song. ♪
Wow. It's just
... wow.
Do you like it?
Be honest now.
It's the best gift you
could have given me!
♪ Seasons change and
leaves may fall ♪
♪ but I'll be with you
through them all ♪
♪ and rain or shine
you'll always be mine. ♪
♪ On a prickly path that
goes on for miles. ♪
♪ You're the only one who
makes it all worthwhile ♪
♪ and you should not
blame me too ♪
♪ if I can't help fallin'
in love with you. ♪
Hey! No fair!
I was gonna tell
you the same thing!
You're just mad
I beat you to it.
I'm telling ya.
I was gonna pull you
up, cover your eyes,
lead you over here...
and say "surprise"!
And then you'd say,
"Oh, Bright Mac. I love it"!
And then I'd say
"I love you."
Too bad it didn't
work out, though.
Yup. Too bad.
The Pears are moving!
[gasp]
I mean, I figured
the Pears moved
but I didn't know all that
stuff happened before
with Granny and Grand Pear.
It must have been really
hard on our parents.
Oh, it was...
We're moving?
To Van Hoover?
But that's so far!
It's what's best.
There's acres of
untouched land
and a warehouse to
make our jams!
We'll get to expand
our business
and get away from those
gosh darn Apples!
[Mrs. Cake] Pear Butter
was devastated.
But seeing no way out of it,
she did what she had to do.
So, that's it?
What do you want me
to do, Bright Mac?
We're moving.
I love you but I have
to stay with my family.
Then Bright Mac did the
most romantic thing
I've ever seen anypony do.
What? What? Tell us!
We're gonna need one more
pony to tell that story.
Mayor Mare, you
knew our parents?
Not as well
as Mrs. Cake,
but I did play a part
in their love story.
The night before the
Pear family moved,
Bright Mac asked
me to meet him
at the edge of Sweet
Apple Acres...
[gasp]
♪♪
I don't want to be
apart from you, ever.
I'm not sure what we'll
do but I'm sure of us.
So sure that I'd
marry you today.
I would too!
I think that's my cue.
I had the honor of officiating
your parents' secret wedding.
And it was perfect.
Bright Mac knew Buttercup
wouldn't want a big splash--
[Apple Bloom] Reminds me of
somepony else I know...
[Big Mac] Hee hee. Eeeyup.
[Mayor Mare] So they had a
special way to seal their vows.
I now pronounce you--
[Granny] What is goin' on?
What's with all
these here candles?
[Grand Pear] Pear
Butter, where are you?
You're supposed
to be packing!
What are you two doing?
Ma, Grand Pear...
Buttercup and I are in love.
What?
And we'll be married as
soon as Mayor Mare says...
Oh! I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
Doesn't that feel nice.
[kiss]
What are you talkin'
about? Married?
You two can't be married!
Finally something
we can agree on!
Pear Butter, enough
of this nonsense.
We're moving and you gotta
stick with your family.
But... the Apples are
my family now, too.
♪♪
You can't be serious.
Are you choosing
to be an Apple?
Over being a Pear?
Are you making
me choose?
Yes. I am.
Then yeah.
I guess I am.
Fine!
[sobbing]
I can't believe Grand Pear
just up and left Ma like that.
No wonder Granny never
told us about any of this.
These things are never easy.
And it's hard to know
when it is a good time.
It seems to me that
now's as good a time as any.
To talk to both
our grandparents.
♪♪
[Apple Bloom] 'Scuse me?
Grand Pear?
I'm Applejack and
this is Big MacIntosh
but you already know
who we are, don't you?
Sure do.
Did you really move to Ponyville
just for a change of pace?
No.
Then you came here
because you're sorry
and you want to get
to know us, too?
I'm so sorry.
I was just so angry,
but I never...
It's in the past, Grand Pear.
Ooh, can I call
you Grandpere Pear?
[chuckle] Sure can!
♪♪
Now where'd you all get to?
I ain't seen hide nor
hair of you's all day.
We've been all over.
Learning about our parents.
Ye have?
And our grandfather.
So you're back, hmmm?
Sure am.
Never should've left.
Finding you and learning all
about Mom and Dad...
I feel like I found
a piece of me
I didn't even
know was missing.
Hearing their story makes me
feel closer to them, somehow.
I'm sorry, I shoulda told
y'all about them sooner.
And I should
have been here.
I can't believe I let a silly
feud keep me from my family.
Nothin's keeping
you from us now.
Let's not miss
anything else.
Applejack's right.
Welcome back, prickly old pear.
Thanks, you old crab apple.
Now that we're
all together,
there's something we
want to show you.
Mom and Dad left us something
to remember them by.
Come on!
Whoa!
It's beautiful!
It's impossible.
♪♪
If anything's
gonna make it through,
it's Apples and Pears.
[chuckle]
♪♪