♪♪
[stressful whimper]
Oh, no I have to...
I can't believe the winter
to spring transition
is almost here.
La. La. La. laaaa. Oh, I
know. I love it so much,
I gave it its own
term: Springsition!
Ha ha ha ha !
Oooh. I like that.
I'm going to have to
re-label all my binders.
Right after we finish--
--Everything! We still
have so much to do!
Oh, my bustles and
bows! Rarity, did we--
Already hemmed, ruched
and cuffed, my dear.
[relieved sigh]
Oh!
Rarity, no reason to panic,
but um, we seem to be
temporarily low. And when
I say "temporarily low,"
I mean completely out of--
The baby blue sapphires?
They arrived this morning.
Oh! Wonderful!
[sigh of relief]
[panicking again] Oh! What
about the design for the--
And done.
Wow. You are good.
And you've really outdone
yourself this time!
The Morning Sunshine
Tulip frock is gorgeous.
Oh, thank you. Now, I know
you're worried about something
slipping between the cracks.
but with your managerial skills
and my fabulous designs
we have everything covered.
You're right, you're right.
There are no cracks.
Would you be a dear and fetch
me some vermillion satin
from the back?
And I'll start on the
Eternal Elegance Empire
silhouette evening gown.
My most certain pleasure.
♪♪
Oh! I love this picture!
When was the last time we had
that kind of fun together?
I... I can't remember.
Has it been that long?
I guess I've been so
busy running my shop.
Oh, no. Something, or
should I say somepony
is slipping between
the cracks!
[squeals of dismay]
I miss my Sweetie Belle!
[sobs]
Rarity, we're running
low on vermillion satin.
[blubbering]
I... I can order more!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[sobbing]
...and this is when we pretended
we were storybook princesses
[sniff sniff]
and here we pretended
we were on a dangerous-
yet-stylish safari...
[sobbing]
So many wonderful memories!
[blast]
[blubbering]
Not to put too fine a
point on it but ....
[loud bawling]
Sweetie Belle loves playing
dress up. I miss her so much!
Then why don't
you go visit her?
I wish I could, but between
running three stores
and the springsition,
I couldn't possibly!
But you've already
done almost all the work.
I can handle the rest.
But--
Rarity, go! I have
everything well in hoof.
[blubbering]
Point taken.
I am going to visit my sister!
Way to immediately
turn that around!
We can spend the
whole day together!
And we can do all of
her favorite things!
I'm sure she'd
love that!
Oh, Sassy, thank you!
Of course! Now
get out of here!
I'm going! I'm going!
Hang on, sis. I'm coming!
[giggling]
Excuse us!
Coming through!
Cutie Mark Crusaders
mid-mission, here!
[screams]
[crash]
♪♪
That was fun!
Let's do it again!
Scoot, we've got
a job to do.
Later?
All right, Chip Cutter.
We've done our part.
The rest is up to you.
You really think I have
it in me to be a sculptor?
Yup.
But... why?
Because you said you
weren't good at anything
except getting in trouble
for making sculptures
out of your lunch, right?
Yeah. I can't help it.
When I look at my sandwich,
it's like it's just asking
me to turn it into a dragon.
Well, what is this slab asking
you to turn it into?
Hmmmm. I see.
♪♪
[jackhammer sound]
[thunk]
[cracking]
♪♪
[Apple Bloom] Wow!
That's incredible!
It looks
just like us!
We knew you had
it in you, Chip.
This is way better than
sandwich sculpting!
Chip, we're proud of you.
I finally got my cutie mark!
Woo-hoo! All right!
Yes!
Way to go!
Not a bad way
to start a day.
at all.
Helping ponies is just about
my favorite thing to do.
Another satisfied client!
Mm hm!
So who's up next?
Pretty sure it's Zipporwhill.
She needs help reconnecting
with her cutie mark:
three puppy paw prints.
When is she swinging by?
Well, I think she should be
arriving right about now.
Wow, you are good!
Come on in, Zipporwhill.
OK, so what seems to
be the problem exactly?
It's my puppy, Ripley.
We used to be so close.
In fact, I got my cutie
mark the day I found him
and took him home.
But now, it's like he wants
nothing to do with me.
Don't you worry; you've
come to the right place.
The Cutie Mark Crusaders
are on the job.
Trust us, before
you know it,
you and your puppy will
be back to being besties!
You have the CMC guarantee!
No matter what it takes,
we promise you'll have
our full attention.
Guess who's here to
spend the whole day
with her little sister?
Rarity!
Whoa!
So sorry, dear! You're tiny.
I didn't even see you there!
Tend to get carried
away with my entrances!
♪ Ta da! ♪
Rarity, what are
you doing here?
I am here to spend
the day with you!
I'm so excited, I could
practically faint.
You don't happen to have a
fainting couch in here, do you?
NO!
Of course not!
It's a tree house.
That would be
très gauche.
Right, well, I sure am happy to
see you! And spending the day
with you does sound like
a lot of fun, but...
I'm kinda right in the middle
of something important.
I have responsibilities and--
Oh...
Go on, Sweetie Belle.
We've got this covered.
How often do you get to
spend time with your sister?
Yeah, go have fun.
You sure you two can
handle our client here?
"Client?" Oh, that
is so adorable!
Uh, thanks? I think?
Oooh! You have mints to
offer your 'clients'!
How 'professional'!
[munching]
Are you sure you
two got this?
We have it handled.
Oh, my! Look at this
wall of satisfied customers!
You girls really
have come a long way.
Well, all right then.
But let me know if you need
me or run into any trouble!
Come on, come on. You'll never
guess what I have planned!
[squeal] So fun!
What?
It's just I know how much
you love these puppet shows!
I did.
Oh, it's just like old times!
You, me, greasy popcorn...
it's like no time
has passed at all!
[grunting]
Ooh! Ooh! It's
your favorite part!
♪♪
Banana peels are so
very, very slippery!
It's funny because
it's true!
[forced laugh]
[groan]
What's the matter, darling?
I um, guess I just prefer black
box experimental theater.
What? Since when?
I don't know. It's no
big deal. This is great.
[jingle]
OK, we're here!
♪ Ta-da! ♪
[giggle]
Aren't you excited to
be back here again?
Do I know my baby sister,
or do I know my baby sister?
Uh... yeah. Where
is "here," exactly?
Oh! Stop being so silly.
You know this is your
favorite ice cream shop!
Oh, right. From when
I was a little filly.
And I convinced the original
owner to come out of retirement
to make you your all-time
favorite dessert!
♪♪
Huh. I remember it
being much bigger.
Well, go ahead. I know
you're dying to dig in.
Well?
That was... uh...
one tasty bite.
Still a little hungry though.
We can get another sundae!
Chocolate with rainbow
sprinkles perhaps?
I was thinking something
more like a salad.
A salad? When did
you get so practical?
Oh, um. I guess another
scoop would be fine!
One more filly clown
surprise, please!
[groan]
Hey, Ripley!
Look at me, over here!
♪♪
I know you must
be bored, darling.
This is a very long line for
one of Twisty Pop's balloons!
[groan]
But just be patient; we'll
get you your favorite
balloon bouquet and
it'll all be worth it!
♪♪
Who's a good puppy? Who's a good
puppy? You're the good puppy!
Now come on, puppy-wuppy.
Get the bally-wally.
Come on, Ripley!
Like this!
Good, Scootaloo! See?
[barking]
It's not working.
Maybe if the ball
tasted better?
I don't think
that's it, Scoot.
Doesn't look like
it's going so well.
I'm just gonna do a quick
check with the CMC's.
Well, I guess duty calls
and you have that now.
What?
Nothing, nothing, go on.
Hey Sweetie Belle, how's
your day with Rarity going?
Well, it's not exactly great.
What do you mean?
I don't know, it's like Rarity
doesn't even know me anymore.
I wish we could say our
day is going better--
[barking]
--but we can't.
Seems like Zipporwhill's puppy
doesn't want anything
to do with her!
Hmmm. I see what you mean.
Ya know, it's an
awfully big puppy.
Sweetie Belle! Hurry;
he's making it!
Gotta go.
I know just what
to do with this!
♪♪
And pose!
Love the camera!
Hate the camera.
Love it again!
Sweetie Belle, you did "hate the
camera" for all these shots!
Let's do it again.
No!
[gasp]
C'mon Zipporwhill,
you can do this!
♪♪
What do you mean no?
Rarity, this is hard for
me to say, but... um...
Sweetie Belle, what is it?
You've been acting
weird all day.
You used to love doing
these things with me!
That's just it! I used to!
That's not who I am anymore.
This isn't who I am. My cutie
mark must be for something else
because my puppy just
doesn't love me anymore!
But it is you. You love
puppet shows and dressing up
and taking silly photos and tiny
little clown-shaped ice creams!
Really?! If you still think
I like doing this stuff,
then maybe you don't
know me at all.
[whimper]
[sobbing]
I can't believe Sweetie Belle
talked to me like that.
And after everything I
did to set up a whole day of
doing her favorite things!
I mean, accusing me
of not knowing her!
I know her better than anypony!
Thank you, Twisty, but the
hard truth is my sister
is being unappreciative
right now.
And I'm going to go and give
her a piece of my mind!
Hey, Zipporwhill. What
are you doing here?
Where are Apple
Bloom and Scootaloo?
They're with my puppy.
He seems to like them
better than me anyway.
Now I'm sure that's not true.
It is. He doesn't like doing
anything with me anymore.
[sigh]
He didn't even want
to play with this.
And all puppies love these.
[sobbing]
I think that might be your
problem right there. Come on!
♪♪
Find Zipporwhill, Ripley.
Woof woof. Zipporwhill woof?
It's hopeless.
Sweetie Belle!
Zipporwhill! We're sorry we
haven't figured this out yet.
Don't worry, girls; I
think I cracked this one.
There she is! Oh, dear.
Really should have changed.
No matter. I'm going to give
her quite the talking to!
Right after she's done
with her conversation.
Anger is no excuse for
poor manners, after all.
OK. Zipporwhill,
what do you see?
My puppy?
That's not what I see.
I see a full grown dog.
He did get bigger, I guess.
He's not just bigger,
he's older too.
You don't still play
with the same toys
from when you were
a foal, do you?
Oh. Ohhh! This squeaker is
a little small for him now.
It's just hard for me to
believe he's not the same
adorable little guy
I found anymore.
I understand. But doing
things like you used to
won't turn him
back into a puppy.
So what do I do?
Treat him like the dog he is
and find new favorite
things to do together.
You think so?
I know so!
Rarity!?
Oh, Sweetie Belle. I heard what
you said and you are so right.
About the dog?
Yes, but about us, too!
The truth is, I know you're
not a little filly anymore.
But it's just the
last time we did
all of those things together,
I... I didn't realize
it was going to be
the last, last time.
I loved doing those
things with you;
it's hard for me to
let that go.
Aw, Rarity. I love being with
you too. That will never change!
But maybe we could just try to
do different things together?
♪♪
What is it, puppy?
I mean, Ripley?
I love you too, Ripley.
♪♪
Thank you, Crusaders!
No problem!
[laughter]
Sweetie Belle, I
am so very proud
of the pony
you've grown into.
And I'm proud that
no matter what,
I'll always be
your little sister.
I uhh, have a little bit of time
before I have to
head to Canterlot.
Could we spend it together?
What would a grown pony
like you want to do?
Well, I do have one idea.
♪♪
I didn't realize your idea
would be such a delicious one.
I don't know how I'm
going to finish this.
Oh, I'll help you!
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ friends ♪