♪♪
[grunts]
Get-- get over here!
Tents are lookin' good.
And we made good time today.
At this rate, we'll be at
Winsome Falls by tomorrow!
We should do the annual big
sister little sister
camping trip every weekend!
Then it wouldn't be annual.
And if we did it
every weekend,
it probably wouldn't
be as special.
But the more we do it, the
better we get at camping!
Remember the first
time we came here
and Rarity had that
gi-normous tent?
I heard that!
[giggle]
I've gotten much better at
roughing it, haven't I?
Yup. This time you only
packed three suitcases!
I know what you're
thinking, but I promise...
I only brought
the essentials.
Like those light thingies?
Of course!
What is life if you
can't make it beautiful?
Mmm. These berries look
good enough to eat.
DON'T!
According to my book, they're
extremely poisonous!
[sigh]
[scream]
What!
I heard something; I
stepped on something
and I saw that
creepy cave.
I guess I still get
a little bit scared
out here,
even after the
last camping trip.
Don't worry, kid, you've
got a big sister this time!
[Apple Bloom]
This looks amazing!
This is going to be the best
big sister/little sister
camping trip ever!
[splat]
[buzzing]
Aaaahhhhhh!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[panicked chattering]
Ow! What are these things?
Fly-ders!
Everypony run for cover!
Don't get stuck
in their...
[thud]
web!
[squealing]
Agh! Now what?
Follow me, everypony!
♪♪
Agh!
Not the scary cave!
[buzzing]
Where did those
terrible bugs come from?
And why did they
destroy our camp?
Fly-ders are from
the Luna Bay Area.
Never seen 'em this
far east though.
Probably attracted
to the food.
Best wait here
until they're gone.
Oh, apple rot!
What are we supposed to do now?
We had games to play and
marshmallows to roast at camp!
In here we got nothin'.
That's not entirely true.
We have each other.
That's right.
And if you girls want to,
maybe we could tell some stories
to pass the time.
You want stories?
I've got a ton of stories.
Spoiler alert, they're all
about me and how awesome I am.
I was thinking more
like campfire stories.
But we don't even
have a campfire.
I got this!
Wow. That was brave.
Eh, it was no biggie.
[cough]
We aren't gonna
tell scary stories
like our last camping
trip, are we?
It's bad enough
just being in here.
Don't worry, Scootaloo.
I was gonna tell you mine and
Apple Bloom's favorite legend!
Oh! You mean Rockhoof?
I love that one!
He was so strong and when he...
Apple Bloom! Shhh. We
haven't heard it yet.
Oh. OK.
But it's so good!
Well, it's true.
Rockhoof was known far and wide
for his incredible strength
but he didn't start
out that way.
You see, Rockhoof was
a tiny little fella,
the son of a farmer.
Just like us!
Heh heh heh.
They lived in a village
that sat at the foot
of a gigantic volcano.
♪♪
And the village was protected by
an elite group of Guard Ponies
called the Mighty Helm.
Ha ha ha ha!
Young Rockhoof wanted nothing
more than to be part
of the Mighty Helm...
Ha ha ha ha ha!
but he was told that
he was too scrawny
and weak to protect
the village.
[mocking laughter]
[thud]
But Rockhoof wouldn't
take "no" for an answer.
♪♪
Then one fateful day...
The volcano erupted!
[explosion]
Eeeeeeeee!!
This is my favorite part!
What happened next?
The molten lava poured down
the side of the volcano...
and try as they might, the
Mighty Helm couldn't figure out
a way to save the village.
They had to evacuate.
But the village ponies didn't
want to leave their homes!
They spent their
entire lives there.
They had nowhere else to go!
So Rockhoof decided
to do something crazy.
♪♪
He thought if he could
divert the flow of the lava,
he might be able to
save his village!
He started digging a trench.
[Sweetie Belle] Wait a minute.
All by himself?
It'd be impossible for one pony
to dig a trench fast enough
to stop the lava!
I mean, even I couldn't do that!
[shriek]
Good thing Rockhoof
didn't believe
in the word "impossible".
He continued to work, knowing
the odds were against him
but determined to push through.
Then... something
magical happened.
♪♪
Rockhoof got visibly stronger!
But the lava was
getting closer...
♪♪
[crash]
[cheers]
Through his extraordinary
determination
and sheer force of will,
Rockhoof more than earned
his place in the Mighty Helm.
[laughter]
[whoops]
Yeah!
Good story,
Applejack!
Even if it
wasn't about me.
[giggles]
I love that story, no matter
how many times I hear it.
Why don't we see if it's
safe to head back to camp?
Uh, girls?
There is no camp to go back to.
[buzzing]
[gasps]
♪♪
All our hard work is ruined.
There, there. Sweetie Belle.
Not to worry.
How? Our camp was so pretty and
this cave is sooo...
not.
Oh, nononono no, not true!
There's beauty in everything.
Even these blah rocks
aren't really blah!
If you look closely, you can
see flecks of gold in them.
And the way the firelight
dances on the cave wall...
shadow and light!
Ooooh, it's so gorgeous!
Sweetie Belle, have I ever told
you about my favorite legend?
No. I didn't know you had one.
Her name was Mistmane.
Mistmane?
Isn't she the old wrinkly
sorceress with the flower?
Yes. But did you
know she used to be
the most beautiful
unicorn in all the land?
No.
So what happened to her?
Well, Mistmane was a very
promising young sorceress.
She was as talented as she
was beautiful and kind.
Everypony loved her
and missed her
when she was sent to the
finest magic school.
While she was gone, she was
delighted to find out
that her best friend, Sable
Spirit, was crowned Empress.
She couldn't wait to return home
once she finished her studies.
But once she arrived, she was
devastated by what she saw.
♪♪
What happened here?
The Empress happened.
She makes everypony work
day and night on her palace.
We don't have time to take
care of anything else.
Well, that can't be.
I know her.
She would never do this.
But there was no denying
what was in front of her.
Sable Spirit took everything
that was beautiful
away from anypony else.
But Mistmane was sure there
had to be some explanation.
I'd assume there was
too, if somepony told me
either one of you
two'd gone evil.
Yeah, I'd never believe it.
I dunno.
I've seen the way you two
get when you miss breakfast.
Ha! Just kidding!
But I'd want answers, too.
So did Mistmane.
She went to confront her friend.
♪♪
Sable? Is that you?
Don't tell me you don't
recognize your old friend.
I don't. My friend would never
work our families and friends
to the bone for something
as silly as a palace.
Silly? My palace is
a beacon of beauty.
Anypony who passes will
be in awe of its majesty.
What good is a pretty palace if
it just hides the misery
of its ponies?
Beauty is everything.
You taught me that.
What?
You were always
the pretty one.
You got to go to the
best magic school.
Everypony missed you.
Everypony loved you.
I admit, I was jealous.
So I tried to perform a spell
that would make me beautiful.
You can see how that went.
[gasp]
I vowed if I couldn't have
beauty, I would take it.
I wasn't chosen to
be Empress, you know.
I took it.
Just like I'm going to
take everything else.
[Mistmane] I can't
let you do that.
Let me? [laughter]
[zapping]
♪♪
[screech]
[whoosh]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪♪
Agh!
[cheers]
[Rarity] Everypony thought
Sable Spirit was defeated
and that was that.
But Mistmane knew there was
more she could do to help.
Beauty isn't everything, but
Mistmane knew that it does have
the power to make ponies smile.
♪♪
She made a huge sacrifice to
bring that smile back
to her friends' and
families' faces.
♪♪
Including Sable Spirit's.
You did this for me?
Even after I was so cruel?
Sable Spirit was so touched
that she vowed to be
more like her friend
in the ways that mattered.
From then on, she ruled with
kindness and compassion.
[cheers]
Even though she gave
away her physical beauty,
she dedicated her life to
spreading beauty
all over Equestria.
Anytime you go out of your way
to brighten somepony's day
by doing something nice
like giving them flowers,
you're following in the
hoofsteps of Mistmane.
I think she's my
favorite legend, too.
[hiss]
Ahhh!!!!
Ugh!
These Fly-ders won't quit!
What do they want from us now?
Well, like it or
not, we're food too.
And I've got the
bites to prove it!
What are we going to do?
They're almost here!
[crashing]
What?
Now those bugs can't get in.
[panicked gasps]
And we can't get out !
Ah!
[panting]
Let's all just stay calm.
Lemme re-light this fire.
[whoosh]
We just have to wait
until the swarm moves on.
Then we'll think of a way out.
How long will
that be?
Don't bears live in caves?
Whoa, whoa.
Scootaloo, you're focusing
on the wrong things.
You have a plan?
Close.
I have a story!
Let me guess,
it's about you?
Practically.
It's about my favorite
legend, Flash Magnus.
Wasn't he the pony who
took on the Dragons?
Dragons?
Big, scary mean
ones or like Spike?
Oh, these were definitely
the big scary mean kind.
But not too scary.
You can sit closer
to me if you want.
A long time ago, before the
Wonderbolts were even founded,
Flash Magnus was a lowly
cadet in the Royal Legion.
And the Legion needed to
fly over the Dragon Lands
to get to their comrades
on the other side.
But as they got closer
to the Dragons...
[growl]
...The Dragons attacked!
You said this wasn't too scary!
[muffled] Scootaloo, if you
just hang in there...
What?
I said, if you
just hang in there,
I promise you'll
like the ending.
So, like I way saying, Flash
Magnus and the Royal Legion
tried to get past the dragons...
but the Dragons
wouldn't let them.
Everypony, RETREAT!
Flash Magnus and a few other
cadets were separated
from the battalion.
He managed to get away but the
dragons captured his friends
and took them back
to their lair.
[scream]
♪♪
Commander!
We need to save our
captured comrades.
I appreciate your
loyalty, Flash Magnus,
but getting past those dragons
is going to be impossible!
Nothing will work.
The Commander was right.
You can't
out-fight Dragons.
But you can out-think them.
Commander Ironhead, I'm pretty
sure I can out-fly the Dragons.
If I can lure them
into chasing me,
you can all sneak into the
lair and retrieve our friends
before they get back.
Are you really willing to
take that chance, Soldier?
I am, Sir.
It's a very brave
thing you're doing.
You'll need all the
help you can get.
Is this... Netitus?
The fireproof shield?
It has protected legion
heroes for generations
and today I can't think
of a worthier flank
for Netitus to protect!
Good luck, soldier.
♪ [military theme] ♪
♪♪
Hey! Come and get me,
fire breath! If you can!
Hey! Hey! Come and get me!
Hey! I'm over here!
[whoosh]
While Flash Magnus
bravely flew for his life,
Commander Ironhead was able
to get his soldiers back.
♪♪
Flash Magnus flew like the wind.
[whoosh]
Faster than the dragons!
♪♪
But he knew he couldn't
do this forever.
Luckily, he had a plan.
[thunderclap]
♪♪
[whistle]
[whoosh]
He led the dragons
straight into a storm
that the Legion had planted.
[thunderclap]
One taste of the lightning
and the dragons retreated!
[cough]
Flash Magnus' plan worked!
[cheers]
♪♪
Wow!
I did like that ending.
Told ya!
He always inspired me to be
my brave and awesome self.
Mmhmm!
Yeah, I guess he kinda
reminds me of you.
You guess?
Come on!
I'm just like him.
[laughter]
Hey, d'you hear that?
I don't hear anything.
Exactly.
Those gosh darn
fly-ders are gone!
We can get out!
Whoa!
Or not.
We're gonna have to see if we
can get out the other way.
You mean go further into
the dark, spooky cave?
Scootaloo, just
remember the story.
You've gotta be brave like
me and Flash Magnus. OK?
♪♪
I hear water!
And if there's
flowing water, then...
It might lead to the way out!
Ohhh!
OK on three!
One.
Two.
THREE!
[splashes]
Woohoo!
Yeah!
♪♪
Well, whaddaya know?
We found ourselves a
shortcut to Winsome Falls!
[Scootaloo] It's never
looked so beautiful!
Well, almost...
We sure are sorry
that our camping trip
wasn't what we
hoped it would be.
Are you kidding?
This trip is awesome!
It is?
We got to hear legendary stories
and go on an adventure.
Wait, you three want to stay?
Of course we do!
We could turn those trees
into a nice little shelter.
We can get you some big logs
and branches to help build it.
And I bet we can find
some more berries.
Come on!
I can't wait to see
what happens next year!