♪♪
Oh, Princess Twilight,
everypony at the
hospital is so excited
for your visit today!
I'm never too busy to visit
sick foals! I can't believe
a whole class just came
down with the Horsey Hives.
...on school
picture day, too!
Oh! The poor dears really
do need cheering up.
We'll do our best!
We'll bring snacks; I'll read
to them and get them gifts.
Food and presents
always cheer me up!
We'll see you soon.
OK, if we want to be at
the hospital by lunch,
then we have three hours
to buy get-well presents,
borrow a book from
the schoolhouse
and pick up treats.
It's a lot, but if we
stick to the schedule,
I know we can get
it all done.
Yeah, knock on wood!
[knock at door]
Surprise!
[baby giggle]
Oh, my gosh!
How's my
favorite niece?
[high voice] I'm good! I was
hoping my favorite aunt
could watch me for
a few hours!
I hope you're
not too busy!
Actually, we kind of are--
Busy? Psh! Would the Best
Aunt Ever be "too busy"
to spend time with this
adorable little one?
No!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[kissing sounds]
[giggles]
Flur-ry, I've got
a surprise for you!
Just a couple of toys that
reminded me of Flurry!
[clatter]
[Flurry gurgles with excitement]
I'm excited to show you
I've done some shopping
for Flurry Heart!
You're so sweet. You
didn't have to do all that!
I know, but I
can't help myself!
Best! Aunt! Ever!
Open this one, Flurry!
[baby talk]
[growl]
[laugh]
Exactly! They're bears!
You're one smart cookie!
♪♪
[excited chatter]
We'll just put Flurry's
things over here, Twiley!
Uh huh, totally!
Mashed peas:
her favorite.
And diapers, extra diapers,
oh and backup extra diapers.
Mashed peas: her favorite.
Wait. Did I say that already?
Uh-huh.
Whoops.
Oh! And this is the most
important thing of all!
Her "whammy."
I take it Flurry named it?
Yup. If she gets fussy,
just give her the whammy
and she'll calm
right down.
You getting all
this, Twiley?
Whammy! Got it!
Where are you guys
headed anyway?
You remember my friend from
the royal guard, Spearhead?
Honestly, all of your friends'
names are very similar.
Well, he has a pop-up art
show at the Ponyville Cafe
and we decided to go
at the last minute.
We're not exactly
art enthusiasts
but we could really
use a night out.
You mean day?
That's what I said.
Isn't that what I said?
Either way, are you
sure you can watch her?
Uh uh uh!
Have no fear! The Best-Aunt-Ever
has everything under control!
♪♪
[kiss]
Thanks again, Twiley!
OK, let's grab that
wharmmy thing and go!
Ooh, you wanna pretend
we're the bears?
I suppose we have
time for a quick game.
Do we though?
Hey!
All right, rawr!
I'm gonna getcha!
[squeak]
Agh!
[sigh]
You should catch her soon
cause we've got lots to do!
Horsey-hive covered foals
counting on us, remember?
Got it. Rawr, rawr!
I'm catching up! Rawr!
RAWWWWWR!
[squeal]
Uh oh. Sorry, bug.
Did that scare you?
[knock knock]
It's OK! It's just
Auntie Twiley!
You know, that was a
very advanced spell
for somepony your age.
Looks like you're already taking
after your Auntie Twiley!
All right, that was pretty
adorable. But now--
I know, Spike. We're leaving.
[stomach growls]
I just have to feed
her real quick.
Is this art...
or a mistake?
I have no idea.
But who cares? We're
not changing diapers.
Shining Armor! Cadance!
How are the new 'rents?!
Give me some hoof!
It is so! Good! To see you
dudes! Thanks for coming!
Of course! We're
having a great time!
Loving all the art!
Uh, that's a trash can.
So it is. I knew that!
But hey, who's to
say it's not art?
Art can be anything
that speaks to you.
It changed my world.
This is my latest piece: A
Thousand Nights in a Hallway.
Wow, I guess nighttime in a
hallway can be pretty dark.
There is none more dark.
Yeah. Totally.
We're just so happy to be here!
Usually we're covered
in mashed peas by now.
When they said mashed
peas were her favorite--
[splat]
[giggle]
--did they mean her favorite
thing to decorate a room with?
[giggle]
Aw, come on, Spike.
That wasn't too bad!
Yeah and we're only twenty
minutes behind schedule.
Twenty minutes? It's fine.
We can totally do this.
[splat]
[weak laugh]
OK, we just need to grab some
toys and we are out of here!
Rawrr!
You want to play, don't you?
Well, I know a game
that's even more fun...
and more efficient.
Playing race cart! Ha ha!
[excited shouts]
Woohoo!
[baby giggles]
[panting]
Hey, nice thinking, Twilight!
Best-Aunt-Ever!
Hang on, Flurry. The race
cart's taking a pit-stop.
[giggling and happy shouts]
[crash]
I'm not a detective, but
I think we've got a suspect.
Ah!
[sigh]
Well, we'd better
get to cleaning.
We've got no
time to waste!
Thanks, but they were
organized by color.
[sigh]
Yes! We gained back a whole
five minutes from running here!
Yeah, but if you add
that to the 40 minutes
we were already behind, we're
still... 55 minutes behind.
I mean... yay, team?
Mmhmm!
Thanks for helping us out,
Cheerilee! Sorry we were late.
Oh, no problem!
But I gotta say, I'm
surprised you came to me
for a book. Don't you
have a huge collection?
Yes, but...
sorry, one second--
[fussing]
[happy shouts]
I didn't think the
foals would be interested
in The Unabridged History
of Amulets in Pony Latin.
Yeah. It was good
you came to me.
How about the
complete collection
of "Ponyville
Fables and Stables"
Mm, too long.
"Alien Alicorns
vs. Space Pirates?"
Well, the science
there is preposterous.
How about Burnferno:
Warrior from Within?!
It's about a handsome dragon
warrior who slays evildoers
with his breath and
his snappy comebacks!
[giggle]
Let's borrow that for you
and keep looking. What else?
♪♪
How about "Gusty
the Great"?
Ooh! That was one
of my favorites
when I was a filly!
We'll take it!
Um... should I go with
something more current?
[gasp]
♪ Ta da! ♪
Cheerilee! I am so, so sorry.
I didn't even hear her leave.
There! All clean!
Great. Now I'll just write
it up again. With my mouth.
[groan]
Feast your eyes.
This one's called 'A
Kitchen Guard's journey'.
Oh...
This reminds me
of the time
Flurry got into the
chocolate pudding
and we found little chocolate
hoofprints all over the carpet.
That took forever
to clean up!
But remember how cute
her little face looked
when we caught her?
Yeah she was
like... uh oh!
[laughter]
Whoa! Art is
so evocative.
I wasn't even going
for that memory! Score!
Honestly, Twilight, I
don't even want to tell you
how late we are.
Should I just cancel our
visit to the hospital?
What? Cancel? We
can't cancel, Spike!
The sick foals are
counting on us!
And the B.A.E. would never
throw in the towel like that!
B.A.E.?
Best-Aunt-Ever!
Besides, this errand is
going to be different!
How do you figure that?
Because Flurry can play
with the Cake twins
and stay out of
trouble! Best Aunt Ever!
♪♪
[baby cooing]
Wonderful, they're
friends already!
Huh! I shouldn't
have doubted you.
Thanks. Wait,
you doubted me?
Spike, you watch Flurry; I'll
take care of everything else.
Hi Pinkie, how's it going? I
need to pick up the cupcakes
for the foals at the hospital
and can you do apology treats?
I'm good. Here they
are. Of course I can!
Do you still have a giant file
of everypony's favorite treat?
In my secret party
planning cave.
[ding]
BRB!
He he! Remind me to tell you
later how amazing you are.
Cheerilee?
I am pretty awesome.
Cherry oatmeal cookies
with yellow sprinkles.
Great! Can you write
"sorry" on them?
I've got a stamp for that.
[angry sounds]
Hey, you guys.
no need to fight.
Hang on! I'm sure
there's another one!
Hold on, sweetie!
We'll play in a second!
The salespony at
the toy store.
Apple strudel cupcake
with caramel drizzle!
Oh, no. You're making the
same face Cheerilee made.
♪ [horror movie stings] ♪
Pinkie, remind me what
your favorite treat is.
The sampler platter.
We'll take
three of those.
A-ha! told you I'd
find another one.
Heh heh.
[splat]
♪♪
Uh, Twilight!
Out of the question! We
are NOT cancelling!
It's going to be
OK! It has to be OK!
It's been so
terrible so far
that it can't possibly
end up [splat]
Sorry.
No, I needed it.
I was just gonna
say... we're here.
And we're only
four-and-a-half minutes late!
Four-and-a-half?
"And while nopony had ever
tried to reach Cloudsdale
on hoof, Gusty the
Great was not deterred.
She and her unicorn warriors
marched up the hill--
but suddenly they encountered--"
What?! What was it?!
"It was the
treacherous Grogar!
And Gusty could tell he
was ready for battle.
Gusty called out to
the unicorn warriors--"
OW!
Not right now, Flurry, these
foals really want to hear this.
[crying]
"'We can fight
Grogar... TOGETHER!'
And the unicorn warriors shot
magical beams into the clouds
that wove into one.
The beam, stronger than a
thousand armies, shined down.
It wrapped around Grogar and
pulled him to the ground.
Don't let him escape!'
yelled Gusty!"--
♪♪
Say aaaaah!
Aaah!
♪♪
"Grogar was strong,
for fear gave him power
and he broke
through the bonds--"
[whimpering]
[alarmed sounds]
I know! So good, right?!
[Spike] Twilight! Look up!
Spike! You're floating!
YOU'RE FLOATING!
So are you!
Flurry, honey, you
need to stop this.
Get us down, please!
Twilight, look out!
[gasp]
[scream]
Nopony panic! Everything's
going to be OK!
♪♪
Ah! I can't keep up with her!
Oh, yeah! Where's her snoozal?
Her what?
You know her, whacky,
wompy-thing, the snail!
Where is it? Cadance
said it calms her down!
I don't see it!
♪♪
FLURRY HEART! PUT US
ALL DOWN THIS INSTANT!
[screams]
Is everypony OK?
Flurry that was
very, very bad!
You could have
hurt somepony.
[bawling]
Oh, Flurry, I didn't mean to--
Sweetie, you don't have to be
scared; it's just me. See?
Oh. You're scared of me.
Because I yelled at you.
Like a big scary bear.
Flurry, I'm so sorry. I've
been a terrible aunt today.
All you wanted to do was play
and I've barely been able to
pay attention to you.
None of this is your
fault. It's mine.
So much for being
the Best Aunt Ever.
But I hope you know
how much I love you.
[giggle]
I take it you forgive me?
Thanks, Flurry. How
about we head home?
After we find your
whammy, of course!
Ahem!
And clean up.
This one kind of reminds
me of Flurry's hair.
And this one reminds
me of Flurry, too.
How so?
It's small, like her.
I can't do this
anymore.
Spearhead, this has
been great but--
Say no more.
My art has always spoken
to me about what I love,
but knowing that it spoke
to you about what you love,
speaks to me.
What?
Go to her!
[laughter]
♪♪
[baby giggle]
Flurry? Where's our
little foal?
♪♪
We missed you so much!
But it looks like you had
a great time without us.
Actually, not so much. Flurry
got into some mischief.
But it wasn't her fault.
I shouldn't have
agreed to watch her
with such a
jam-packed schedule.
It was too much
to juggle.
But Flurry taught me an
important lesson today.
It turns out being the
Best Aunt Ever
isn't about spending the
most time with your niece,
but spending quality
time with her.
And she taught me a
really cool "bear" game,
so I guess I learned two things.
[laughter]
Well, we definitely
should have given you
more of a head's up.
Yes! From now on, we'll
give you plenty of notice.
That would be great!
Hey, what are you doing
next Tuesday?
For dinner! Not to babysit.
I'll have to check with Spike,
but I think we're free.
Where is Spike, anyway?
"...the dashing dragon warrior
breathed a scorching
flame from his snout
then chuckled to himself
as he flew into the sunset.
'If you can't stand the heat,
don't fight a dragon.'"
Hey, you kinda
look like him!
Thank you.
OK. Now who wants more cake?!
[cheers]
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ friends ♪