NOW, WHAT HAVE WE LEARNED?
LOTS OF CONTROL...
GOOD.
...SCREAMING
AND HOLLERING.
YES.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY...
...PASSION.
RIGHT.
SO, NOW THAT YOU KNOW
THE ELEMENTS OF A GOOD CHEER,
LET'S HEAR ONE!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
Yay.
UGH!
YOU'RE GONNA CHEER FOR ME
LIKE THAT?
LOUDER.
YAY.
LOUDER!
LOUDER!!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ Meekly ] YA-A-A-Y.
UGH!
TOO LOUD?
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
THIS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
YAY.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ BOING! BOING!]
[ ZOOM! ]
AND NOW PHASE ONE
OF MY ROUTINE.
[ ZOOM! ]
OOH.
PHASE TWO.
[ ZOOM! ]
[ WHIRL! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
WAY TO GO.
HERE WE GO -- PHASE THREE,
THE SONIC RAINBOOM.
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
COME ON!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREECH! ]
UH-OH.
WH-O-O-OA!
Twilight Sparkle:
[ SIGHS ] LAST ONE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
HELPING ME CLEAN UP
ALL THESE BOOKS, GUYS.
IT WAS A CRAZY WEEKEND
OF STUDYING.
[ WHISTLE! ]
WH-O-O-O-OA!
AAH!
[ CRASH! ]
[ ALL GROANING ]
RAINBOW DASH,
YOU ROCK.
WHOO-HOO.
[ GASPS ]
DID MY CHEERING DO THAT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
SORRY ABOUT THAT,
LADIES.
THAT WAS A TRULY FEEBLE
PERFORMANCE.
ACTUALLY,
IT WASN'T ALL BAD.
I PARTICULARLY LIKED IT
WHEN YOU MADE THE CLOUDS SPIN.
UGH. I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT MY PERFORMANCE --
I'M TALKING ABOUT YOURS --
THAT FEEBLE CHEERING.
WHAT ARE YOU TWO
ARGUING ABOUT?
WERE WE ARGUING?
I'M SORRY.
UGH. I WISH YOU GUYS
COULD COME TO CLOUDSDALE
TO SEE ME COMPETE IN THE
BEST YOUNG FLIER COMPETITION.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S WHERE ALL THE GREATEST
PEGASUS FLIERS GET TOGETHER
AND SHOW OFF
THEIR DIFFERENT FLYING STYLES.
SOME ARE FAST!
[ ZOOM! ]
EEEEEEEE!
AND SOME ARE GRACEFUL.
WHOA! WHOA!
WH-O-O-OA!
OOH!
GOLLY.
I'D LOVE TO SEE YOU STRUT
YOUR STUFF IN THAT COMPETITION.
YEAH. I WISH YOU GUYS
COULD BE THERE.
FLUTTERSHY'S
A GREAT SUPPORT,
BUT HER CHEERING
ISN'T EXACTLY INSPIRATIONAL.
OOH! I'D LOVE TO SEE YOU MAKE
A SONIC RAINBOOM!
IT'S, LIKE,
THE MOST COOLEST THING EVER,
EVEN THOUGH
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY SEEN IT,
BUT, I MEAN, COME ON!
IT'S A SONIC RAINBOOM!
HOW N COOL COULD IT
POSSIBLY NOT BE?
WHAT'S A SONIC RAINBOOM?
YOU REALLY NEED TO
GET OUT MORE.
THE SONIC RAINBOOM
IS LEGENDARY!
WHEN A PEGASUS LIKE RAINBOW DASH
GETS GOING SO FAST --
BOOM! --
A SONIC BOOM AND A RAINBOW
CAN HAPPEN ALL AT ONCE!
AND RAINBOW DASH HERE'S
THE ONLY PONY
TO EVER PULL IT OFF.
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
I-I WAS JUST A FILLY.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE GONNA DO IT
AGAIN, RIGHT?
A-ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'M THE GREATEST FLIER
TO EVER COME OUT OF CLOUDSDALE.
I COULD DO SONIC RAINBOOMS
IN MY SLEEP.
WOW.
IF YOU PULL THAT OFF,
YOU'LL WIN THE CROWN FOR SURE.
THE GRAND PRIZE IS AN ENTIRE DAY
WITH THE WONDERBOLTS --
A WHOLE DAY OF FLYING
WITH MY LIFELONG HEROES.
IT'LL BE A DREAM COME TRUE!
YAY.
I'M GONNA GO REST UP.
DON'T WANT TO OVERPREPARE
MYSELF, YOU KNOW?
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND,
BETTER KEEP PRACTICING.
I NEED
A CHEERING SECTION
TO MATCH MY SPECTACULAR
PERFORMANCE.
SHE'S PRACTICED THAT MOVE
A HUNDRED TIMES,
AND SHE'S NEVER EVEN COME CLOSE
TO DOING IT.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN CHEER
LOUD ENOUGH TO HELP HER.
WELL, GUESS WE BETTER GET THIS
CLEANED UP...
AGAIN.
GO ON. GO ON.
[ PLOINK! ]
"GO ON" WHAT?
FIND A SPELL THAT WILL GET US
WINGLESS PONIES INTO CLOUDSDALE.
DIDN'T YOU SEE
HOW NERVOUS SHE WAS?
NERVOUS?
HAVE YOU SPIT YOUR BIT
OR SOMETHING?
SHE WAS TOOTING
HER OWN HORN
LOUDER THAN THE BRASS SECTION
OF A MARCHING BAND.
OH, PUH-LEASE.
I HAVE PUT ON
ENOUGH FASHION SHOWS
TO RECOGNIZE STAGE FRIGHT
WHEN I SEE IT.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO BE THERE FOR HER.
NOW, GO ON!
AAH!
UGH!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO FIND
A FLIGHT SPELL IN THIS MESS?
A FLIGHT SPELL?
ONE SEC.
[ ZOOM! ]
PAGE 27.
[ TINKLING ]
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
IT LANDED ON MY FACE
WHEN RAINBOW DASH
KNOCKED ME INTO THE BOOKCASE.
HERE IT IS -- A SPELL
THAT WILL ALLOW EARTH PONIES
TO FLY FOR THREE DAYS.
OHH, IT LOOKS REALLY
DIFFICULT.
I'M NOT SURE I CAN DO IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO TRY.
OKAY, BUT WHO'S GONNA VOLUNTEER
TO BE THE TEST SUBJECT?
I WILL!
FOR RAINBOW DASH,
I WILL GO FIRST.
HERE GOES.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ GROANS ]
AAH!
[ ZAP! ]
[ GASPS ]
I THINK IT WORKED.
YOU'VE GOT TO LEARN
TO BE ASSERTIVE, FLUTTERSHY.
DON'T BE AFRAID
TO SPEAK UP.
WELL, WELL, WELL.
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
IT'S OUR OLD FRIEND
RAINBOW CRASH.
GET KICKED OUT
OF ANY FLIGHT SCHOOLS LATELY?
[ LAUGHTER ]
I DIDN'T GET KICKED OUT.
FACE IT,
RAINBOW CRASH --
FLIGHT SCHOOL
HAD TOO MANY RULES
AND NOT ENOUGH NAPTIMES
FOR YOU.
[ SCOFFS ] ASK HER ABOUT
THE SONIC RAINBOOM.
THAT'S NOTHING
BUT AN OLD MARE'S TAIL.
YOU DON'T HAVE THE SKILLS
TO TRY SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
Fluttershy:
NOW, WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I'M TRYING TO BE
MORE ASSERTIVE.
ANYHOW, SHE IS GOING TO DO
A SONIC RAINBOOM.
NO, SHE'S NOT,
'CAUSE THERE'S NO SUCH THING.
THEN SHOW UP AT THE CLOUDISEUM
AND SEE FOR YOURSELF.
[ BLINK! ]
UH, IF YOU'RE FREE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'LL BE FREE.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL BE THERE.
SEE YOU THEN,
RAINBOW CRASH.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
I WAS SO ASSERTIVE.
[ SIGHS ]
THOSE GUYS ARE RIGHT.
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO DO IT.
BUT, RAINBOW DASH,
JUST BECAUSE YOU FAILED
THE SONIC RAINBOOM
100,000 TIMES
IN PRACTICE
DOESN'T MEAN
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO DO IT
IN FRONT OF AN ENTIRE STADIUM
FULL OF IMPATIENT,
SUPERCRITICAL,
SPORTS-FAN PONIES.
AAAH!
WHAT DO I DO?!
EVERYPONY'S
GONNA SEE ME FAIL!
THE WONDERBOLTS WILL NEVER LET
A LOSER LIKE ME JOIN!
PRINCESS CELESTIA
WILL PROBABLY BANISH ME
TO THE EVERFREE FOREST!
MY LIFE IS RUINED!!
RAR--
RARE?
THE SONIC RAINBOOM
IS WAY MORE THAN RARE!
R-RARITY?
RARITY, ARE YOU...
FLYING?
I MOST CERTAINLY AM!
AREN'T MY WINGS
SMASHING?
TWILIGHT
MADE THEM FOR ME.
I JUST ADORE THEM.
[ BLINK! ]
WHY SO SHOCKED?
WE COULDN'T LEAVE
OUR FAVORITE FLIER
WITHOUT A BIG
CHEERING SECTION.
"WE"?
I-I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
IT'S INCREDIBLE!
THIS IS SO COOL!
YOU GUYS MADE IT!
SURE DID!
WAIT!
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
ONLY PEGASUS PONIES
CAN WALK ON CLOUDS.
[ LAUGHS ]
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
I FOUND A SPELL THAT MAKES
TEMPORARY WINGS,
BUT IT WAS TOO DIFFICULT
TO DO MORE THAN ONCE,
SO I FOUND
AN EASIER SPELL
THAT LETS THE REST OF US
WALK ON CLOUDS.
AND WE CAME
TO CHEER YOU TO VICTORY.
TO BE HONEST,
I WAS STARTING TO GET
JUST THE TEENIEST,
TINIEST BIT NERVOUS,
BUT I FEEL A LOT BETTER
NOW THAT YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
HEY, WE'VE GOT SOME TIME
BEFORE THE COMPETITION.
WHY DON'T FLUTTERSHY AND I
SHOW YOU AROUND CLOUDSDALE?
YEAH!
ALL RIGHT!
THAT SOUNDS LOVELY.
GREAT!
WONDERFUL.
HERE IT IS -- THE GREATEST CITY
IN THE SKY.
WHOA!
WHOA!WHOA!
AHH!
AHH!AHH!
Rarity: OOH!
AHH!
UH...
SOME OF THE GREATEST PEGASI
IN HISTORY CAME FROM CLOUDSDALE.
OH, WAIT FOR ME!
[ DRILLING ]
THOSE WINGS
ARE GORGEOUS.
WHY, THANK YOU.
BE CAREFUL
WITH THOSE WINGS, RARITY.
THEY'RE MADE
FROM GOSSAMER AND MORNING DEW,
AND THEY'RE
INCREDIBLY DELICATE.
DON'T WORRY, TWILIGHT.
I'M SURE THEY CAN'T GET WORN OUT
FROM TOO MUCH ATTENTION.
SINCE WE'RE UP HERE,
I'D SURE LIKE TO GET A LOOK
AT WHERE THE WEATHER'S MADE.
GREAT IDEA.
COME ON, GIRLS --
TO THE WEATHER FACTORY!
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
THIS IS WHERE THEY MAKE
THE SNOWFLAKES.
EACH ONE IS HOOFMADE.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
IT'S A DELICATE OPERATION.
[ GASPS ]
OOH, THE SNOWFLAKES
LOOK EVEN BETTER FROM UP HERE.
OH, COME ON!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
WE'D BETTER MOVE ON
BEFORE RARITY RUINS WINTER
AND CAUSES A DROUGHT.
[ SHATTER! ]
AND HERE'S
WHERE THEY MAKE THE RAINBOWS.
[ SLURPS ]
[ GASPING ]
[ PANTING ]
SPICY!
YEAH.
[ LAUGHS ]
RAINBOWS AREN'T REALLY KNOWN
FOR THEIR FLAVOR.
Pony: WHOA!
OH, WHERE'D YOU GET
THOSE AMAZING WINGS?
I WANT A PAIR.
HMM.
YEAH, I GUESS
I COULD SEE THAT.
OH, HEY, LOOK.
IT'S RAINBOW CRASH AGAIN.
[ Laughing ] YEAH.
RAINBOW, UH...
CRASH!
RARITY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TALKING TO THESE GUYS?
OH, THEY WERE JUST ADMIRING
MY WINGS, RAINBOW DASH.
YEAH. YOU SHOULD FORGET
THE SONIC RAINBOOM
AND JUST GET YOURSELF
SOME WINGS LIKE THESE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OHH.
OH, COME ON, GIRLS.
WHY DON'T WE GO SEE
HOW CLOUDS ARE MADE?
DON'T LISTEN TO THEM.
YOU'RE GONNA WIN
THAT COMPETITION FOR SURE.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I CAN'T DO
THE SONIC RAINBOOM.
AND JUST LOOK AT THESE BORING,
PLAIN OLD FEATHERED WINGS.
I'M DOOMED.
[ STEAM HISSING, CHURNING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
OOH!
WOW.
WHAT? THESE OLD THINGS?
GO AHEAD, EVERYPONY.
PHOTOS ARE ENCOURAGED.
RARITY, WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE HELPING
RAINBOW DASH RELAX,
REMEMBER?
PUT YOUR WINGS AWAY
AND STOP SHOWING OFF.
OH, HOW CAN YOU ASK ME
TO PUT AWAY PERFECTION?
OOH!
OOH!OOH!
[ LAUGHS ]
RAINBOW DASH,
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD.
OF COURSE!
WHY WOULDN'T I BE OKAY?
EVERYONE'S SO IN LOVE
WITH RARITY'S WINGS
THAT THEY WON'T EVEN NOTICE
WHEN I TOTALLY BLOW IT
IN THE BEST YOUNG FLIERS
COMPETITION.
HEY, THERE'S AN IDEA --
YOU SHOULD ENTER
THE COMPETITION.
YEAH.
I COULD WATCH YOU FLY
ALL DAY LONG.
THERE REALLY ISN'T ANYPONY
WHO USES THEIR WINGS
QUITE LIKE ME.
PERHAPS I SHOULD COMPETE.
WHAT?!
OOOH!
OOOH!OOOH!
THAT'S AMAZING!
WOW!
OOH!
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I'LL NEVER WIN
THE COMPETITION NOW.
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS,
LAUGHTER ]
I'M GOING TO BE
AWHILE.
[ BLOWS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GULPS ]
FILLIES AND GENTLECOLTS,
PLEASE RISE AND JOIN ME
IN WELCOMING OUR BELOVED
PRINCESS CELESTIA.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
PLEASE WELCOME
OUR CELEBRITY JUDGES
FOR THE BEST YOUNG FLIER
COMPETITION,
THE WONDERBOLTS!
[ ZOOM! ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND NOW LET'S FIND OUT
WHO WILL TAKE THE PRIZE
AS THIS YEAR'S BEST YOUNG FLIER.
OKAY, CONTESTANT NUMBER 1.
YOU'RE UP.
AAH!
OKAY, NUMBER 2.
LET'S GO.
UM...
COME ON. COME ON.
WE AIN'T GOT ALL DAY.
SHE'S TALKING TO YOU.
OH, UH...
OH, I GUESS THAT'S ME.
OKAY, NUMBER 4.
TIME TO GO.
I'M NUMBER 4,
AND I NEED JUST ONE MORE
ITSY-BITSY MINUTE.
BE A DEAR AND HAVE SOMEPONY
GO AHEAD OF ME, HMM?
LOOK, I DON'T CARE WHO IT IS,
BUT SOMEPONY'S GOT TO GO ON.
LET'S DO THIS!
UH...
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
I LOVE NUMBER 7.
DOING 15 BARREL ROLLS IN A ROW
CAN'T BE EASY.
MY FAVORITE IS NUMBER 10.
SHE JUST LOOKED LIKE
SUCH A NICE PONY.
[ SCOFFS ]
WONDER HOW COME WE HAVEN'T SEEN
RAINBOW DASH OR RARITY YET.
THE COMPETITION'S
ALMOST OVER.
[ CHATTER! ]
NUMBER 15, LET'S GO.
[ DOOR OPENS,
STEAM HISSES ]
RARITY...IS READY.
LOOK, LADIES, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL YOU.
THERE'S ONLY TIME
FOR ONE MORE PERFORMANCE.
IF YOU BOTH
WANT TO COMPETE,
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO GO OUT THERE
TOGETHER.
WELL, RAINBOW DASH,
SHALL WE?
UH...UH...
HEH...HEH.
AND NOW FOR OUR FINAL
COMPETITOR OF THE DAY,
CONTESTANT NUMBER 15!
UH, AND, APPARENTLY,
CONTESTANT NUMBER 4.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
GOOD LUCK, RAINBOW DASH.
JUST DO YOUR BEST.
[ WHIMPERING ]
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND,
BUT I TOOK THE LIBERTY
OF CHANGING OUR MUSIC.
THAT ROCK 'N' ROLL
DOESN'T REALLY MATCH
MY WINGS.
[ GULPS ]
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
COME ON, RAINBOW DASH.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
JUST REMEMBER THE ROUTINE.
PHASE ONE.
[ ZOOM! ]
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
AAH!
NICE WORK,
RAINBOW CRASH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ WHIRL! ]
TIME FOR PHASE TWO.
[ ZOOM! ]
[ WHIRL! ]
LOOK.
PHASE TWO IS WORKING.
[ CHEERING ]
[ GASPS ]
AND NOW
FOR MY GRAND FINALE --
I WILL FLY
RIGHT UP TO THE SUN
AND BEAM MY BEAUTIFUL WINGS OVER
THE WHOLE CITY OF CLOUDSDALE.
OH, THEY'LL BE TALKING ABOUT IT
FOR YEARS!
LOOKS LIKE THIS IS MY LAST
CHANCE TO TURN THINGS AROUND.
PHASE THREE --
THE SONIC [GULPS] RAINBOOM.
WINGS, DON'T FAIL ME NOW.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ GRUNTING ]
LOOK UPON ME, EQUESTRIA,
FOR I AM RARITY!
[ TINKLING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ SIZZLE! ]
UH-OH.
AAH!
Twilight Sparkle: OH, NO!
HER WINGS EVAPORATED
INTO THIN AIR!
AAH!
[ CROWD GASPING ]
[ ZOOM! ]
AAAAAH!
OHH!
AAH!
[ TWEET! ]
AAAAAAAH!
[ GASPS ]
HOLD ON, RARITY!
I'M COMING!
[ ZOOM! ]
AAAAH!
[ GASPS ]
I CAN'T LOOK.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ CRACKLING ]
[ ZOOM! ]
A SONIC RAINBOOM!
SHE DID IT!
WHOO!!
[ ZOOM! ]
WHOA.
[ TINKLING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
A SONIC RAINBOOM!
WHOO!! YEAH!!
I DID IT.
I DID IT!
YOU SURE DID.
OH, THANK YOU,
RAINBOW DASH.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
WELL, YEAH.
I DID THAT, TOO.
[ CHUCKLES ]
BEST DAY EVER!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE CONTINUE ]
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
TO ALL OF YOU
FOR GETTING SO CARRIED AWAY
WITH MY BEAUTIFUL WINGS.
I GUESS
I JUST LOST MY HEAD.
IT'S OKAY, RARITY.
OH, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, KIDDO.
WE STILL LOVE YOU.
AND I'M ESPECIALLY SORRY
THAT I WAS SO THOUGHTLESS
AS TO JUMP INTO THE CONTEST
AT THE LAST MINUTE
AFTER YOU HAD WORKED
SO HARD TO WIN IT.
CAN YOU EVER, EVER
FORGIVE ME?
AWW, IT'S OKAY.
EVERYTHING TURNED OUT
ALL RIGHT, RIGHT?
I JUST WISH I COULD HAVE
MET THE WONDERBOLTS
WHEN THEY WERE AWAKE.
[ POINK! POINK! ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, MY GOSH!
SO, YOU'RE THE LITTLE PONY
WHO SAVED OUR LIVES.
WE REALLY WANTED TO MEET YOU
AND SAY THANKS.
OH, MY GOSH!
Twilight Sparkle:
PRINCESS.
HELLO,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE,
AND HELLO
TO YOUR FRIENDS, TOO.
PRINCESS CELESTIA...
I'M SORRY
I RUINED THE COMPETITION.
RAINBOW DASH HERE REALLY IS
THE BEST FLIER IN EQUESTRIA.
I KNOW SHE IS, MY DEAR.
THAT'S WHY, FOR HER
INCREDIBLE ACT OF BRAVERY
AND HER SPECTACULAR
SONIC RAINBOOM,
I'M PRESENTING THE GRAND PRIZE
FOR BEST YOUNG FLIER
TO THIS YEAR'S WINNER,
MS. RAINBOW DASH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, MY GOSH! OH, MY GOSH!
OH, MY GOSH!
SO, TWILIGHT SPARKLE,
DID YOU LEARN ANYTHING
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP
FROM THIS EXPERIENCE?
I DID, PRINCESS,
BUT I THINK RARITY LEARNED
EVEN MORE THAN ME.
I CERTAINLY DID.
I LEARNED
HOW IMPORTANT IT IS
TO KEEP YOUR HOOVES
ON THE GROUND
AND BE THERE
FOR YOUR FRIENDS.
EXCELLENT.
WELL DONE, RARITY.
THIS REALLY IS
THE BEST DAY EVER!
UH, HEY,
RAINBOW CRASH.
DASH!
OH, UH, SORRY.
RAINBOW DASH.
WE JUST WANTED
TO CONGRATULATE YOU
ON WINNING
THE COMPETITION.
THAT SONIC RAINBOOM
WAS AWESOME!
[ CHUCKLES ]
THANKS, GUYS.
UH, WE'RE REALLY SORRY
WE GAVE YOU
SUCH A HARD TIME BEFORE.
AWW, THAT'S OKAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
HEY, DO YOU WANT TO
HANG OUT WITH US?
MAYBE YOU COULD SHOW US HOW YOU
DID THAT INCREDIBLE TRICK.
SORRY, BOYS...
...BUT I'VE GOT PLANS.
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS