[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ CREAK! ]
OH, HI, PINKIE PIE.
* THIS IS
YOUR SINGING TELEGRAM *
* I HOPE IT FINDS YOU WELL
* YOU'RE INVITED TO A PARTY
* 'CAUSE WE THINK
YOU'RE REALLY SWELL *
* GUMMY'S TURNING 1 YEAR OLD
* SO HELP US CELEBRATE
* THE CAKE WILL BE DELICIOUS
* THE FESTIVITIES FIRST-RATE
* THERE WILL BE GAMES
AND DANCING *
* BOB FOR APPLES, CUT A RUG
* AND WHEN THE PARTY'S OVER
* WE'LL GATHER 'ROUND
FOR A GROUP HUG *
* NO NEED TO BRING A GIFT
* BEING THERE WILL BE ENOUGH
* BIRTHDAYS MEAN
HAVING FUN WITH FRIENDS *
* NOT GETTING LOTS OF STUFF
[ PANTING ]
* IT WON'T BE THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU *
* SO WE HOPE THAT YOU SAY YES
* SO PLEASE,
OH, PLEASE R.S.V.P. *
* AND COME AND BE OUR GUEST
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
NEXT TIME I THINK I'LL JUST PASS
OUT WRITTEN INVITATIONS.
[ THUD! ]
[ ZIP! ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ SPLASH! ]
[ SLOOP! CHOMP! ]
NICE ONE!
NOW LET ME SHOW YOU
HOW IT'S REALLY DONE.
HEY, GIRLS!
HEY, PINKIE PIE.
HOWDY.
JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
HOW HAPPY I AM
THAT YOU COULD MAKE IT
TO GUMMY'S PARTY!
ARE YOU KIDDIN'? I WOULDN'T HAVE
MISSED IT FOR THE WORLD.
ME NEITHER.
WHEN PINKIE PIE THROWS A PARTY,
I AM THERE!
[ SPLASH! ]
TA-DA!
AWW, JUST A BORING OLD APPLE.
DON'T WORRY.
THERE ARE PLENTY
OF OTHER SURPRISES IN THERE.
WHAT KIND OF SURPRISES?
I CAN'T TELL YOU THAT,
SILLY!
THEN IT WOULDN'T BE
A SURPRISE!
[ SPLASH! ]
[ CREAK! ]
UGH!
[ CHATTERS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ SLURP! ]
THIS PUNCH
IS SIMPLY DIVINE.
IS THIS
THE SAME RECIPE YOU USED
FOR YOUR
SPRING-HAS-SPRUNG PARTY?
NOPE, SOMETHING NEW.
[ SLURP! ]
IT'S GUMMY'S FAVORITE!
[ GULP! ]
[ SLURP! ]
[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
OOH!
THIS IS MY JAM!
[ ZOOM! ]
HAVING FUN?
A BLAST.
YOU ALWAYS THROW THE BEST
PARTIES, PINKIE PIE.
THEY'RE ALWAYS
THE BEST PARTIES
'CAUSE MY BEST FRIENDS
ARE ALWAYS THERE.
AAH!
OH!
COME ON, EVERYBODY!
[ TWEET! TWEET! ]
GUMMY WANTS TO DANCE!
GO, GUMMY!
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY!
WHOO-WHEE!
I AM BEAT.
I HAVEN'T DANCED
THAT MUCH SINCE --
WELL, SINCE
YOUR LAST PARTY.
THANKS AGAIN FOR THE INVITE.
SEE YOU LATER,
BIRTHDAY ALLIGATOR!
BRAVO FOR HOSTING YET ANOTHER
DELIGHTFUL SOIREE.
IT'S BEEN LOVELY.
Pinkie Pie: YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT TO STAY?
THERE'S STILL SOME CAKE LEFT.
UH, I THINK
I'M GONNA PASS.
GREAT PARTY, THOUGH.
WE SHOULD DO THIS AGAIN SOON.
[ GASPS ]
WE SHOULD DO THIS AGAIN SOON!
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ CREAK! ]
OH, HI, PINKIE.
IT'S SOON!
PARDON ME?
YOU SAID WE SHOULD HAVE ANOTHER
PARTY SOON, AND IT'S SOON.
HERE'S YOUR INVITATION.
[ TINKLING ]
"YOU'RE INVITED TO GUMMY'S
AFTER-BIRTHDAY PARTY
THIS AFTERNOON AT 3:00."
ALL OUR BESTEST FRIENDS
ARE INVITED,
AND THERE'S GONNA BE
DANCING AND GAMES AND CAKE
AND ICE CREAM AND PUNCH!
THIS AFTERNOON?
AS IN THIS AFTERNOON
YES, INDEEDY!
OH, GOSH.
I WISH I COULD MAKE IT,
BUT I'VE GOTTEN A BIT BEHIND
IN MY STUDIES.
[ TINKLING ]
[ WHOOSH! WHOOSH! WHOOSH! ]
I REALLY GOT
TO HIT THE BOOKS.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOUR STUDIES COME FIRST.
BUT DON'T WORRY. WE'LL BE SURE
TO SAVE YOU SOME CAKE.
[ TINK! ]
PLEASE DO.
OH, AND, TWILIGHT,
YOU SHOULDN'T HIT THE BOOKS.
YOU SHOULD REALLY
JUST READ THEM.
I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
[ POP! ]
HUH?
OH, HI, PINKIE PIE.
WHAT BRINGS YOU
'ROUND THESE PARTS?
WHO'S READY TO SHAKE
THEIR HOOF-THANG?
IT'S AN INVITATION TO GUMMY'S
AFTER-BIRTHDAY PARTY
THIS AFTERNOON.
THERE'S GONNA BE DANCING
AND GAMES
AND CAKE AND ICE CREAM
AND PUNCH!
THIS AFTERNOON?
AS IN THIS AFTERNOON
THAT'S FUNNY.
THAT'S JUST WHAT TWILIGHT SAID.
AND THE ANSWER IS, YES,
IT'S THIS AFTERNOON.
OH.
WELL, I -- UH, I DON'T THINK
I CAN MAKE IT,
'CAUSE I HAVE TO, UH...
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
UH, UH, PICK APPLES!
YEP, APPLES, 'CAUSE THAT'S
WHAT WE DO WITH, UH, APPLES.
WE, UH, PICK THEM.
[ TING! ]
[ CREAK! ]
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY,
GULPS ]
[ CREAK! ]
OKIE-DOKIE-LOKIE!
A PARTY IS
STILL A PARTY,
EVEN IF THERE ARE
ONLY THREE GUESTS.
WHEW!
[ GRUNTING ]
ANYTHING ELSE I CAN DO FOR YOU,
MOST BEAUTIFUL ONE?
[ SNIFFS, WHIMPERS ]
PERHAPS YOU COULD
TAKE A BATH.
HOW DO I PUT THIS
DELICATELY?
YOU SMELL LIKE
A ROTTEN APPLE CORE
THAT'S BEEN WRAPPED
IN MOLDY HAY
AND DIPPED
IN DRAGON PERSPIRATION.
[ SIGHS ]
[ THUNK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
OOH, LOVE THE NEW HAT.
VERY MODERN.
WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
GUMMY'S AFTER-BIRTHDAY PARTY
IS THIS AFTERNOON.
I'M DELIVERING
THE INVITATIONS.
THE PARTY
IS THIS AFTERNOON?
AS IN THIS AFTERNOON
THIS AFTERNOON?
IT'S SO STRANGE.
EVERYPONY KEEPS SAYING THAT.
OH. DO THEY?
I KNOW
IT'S SHORT NOTICE,
BUT WE HAD SUCH A GREAT TIME
AT HIS BIRTHDAY PARTY,
I THOUGHT WE COULD HAVE
EVEN MORE FUN
AT HIS
AFTER-BIRTHDAY PARTY.
AND I'M SURE
THAT WE WOULD,
BUT I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO DECLINE.
I HAVE TO...WASH MY HAIR.
[ GLEAM! ]
DON'T BE SILLY.
YOUR HAIR DOESN'T LOOK DIRTY.
IT DOESN'T?
NOPE.
[ ZING! ]
[ SQUISH! ]
SEE? [ GAGS ]
DIRTY.
I HAVE TO GO.
[ CREAK! ]
HUH.
NO TWILIGHT, NO APPLEJACK,
NO RARITY.
OH, WELL.
A PARTY IS STILL A PARTY,
EVEN WITH ONLY TWO GUESTS.
THIS AFTERNOON?
AS IN --
YES!
AS IN THIS AFTERNOON
THIS AFTERNOON!
OH, MAN, WE'D LOVE TO,
BUT WE'RE...HOUSE-SITTING
THIS AFTERNOON.
[ SIGHS ]
BOTH OF YOU?
IT'S, UH, A BIG HOUSE.
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
UH, LOOK AT THE TIME!
WE'D REALLY BETTER
GET GOING.
WAIT!
[ SCREECH! ]
MAYBE I COULD BRING YOU
SOME AFTER-BIRTHDAY CAKE
AND ICE CREAM!
WHO ARE YOU
HOUSE-SITTING FOR?
HARRY.
HARRY?
YEAH. I DON'T THINK
YOU KNOW HIM.
THAT'S STRANGE.
I KNOW JUST ABOUT EVERYPONY
AROUND HERE.
HE'S...A BEAR.
A BEAR?
[ TINK! ]
YEP. HE'S A BEAR,
ALL RIGHT.
AND HE'LL BE PRETTY UPSET
IF WE DON'T GET OVER
TO HIS HOUSE SOON.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WAIT!
[ SCREECH! ]
THERE'S A BEAR AROUND HERE
WHO LIVES IN A HOUSE?
IT'S, UH,
REALLY MORE OF A CAVE.
BUT HE'S FIXED
THE PLACE UP SO MUCH,
IT FEELS LIKE A HOUSE.
AND, UH, HE WANTS US
TO LOOK AFTER HIS HOUSE --
UH, CAVE --
WHILE HE'S, UH...
A-AT THE BEACH.
HE'S VACATIONING
AT THE BEACH?
YEP. HE LOVES TO...
COLLECT SEASHELLS!
PLAY BEACH VOLLEYBALL!
COLLECT VOLLEYBALLS!
PLAY SEASHELLS!
GOT TO GO!
[ WHOOSH! ]
SOMETHING STRANGE IS DEFINITELY
GOING ON AROUND HERE, GUMMY.
SURE, RAINBOW DASH
AND FLUTTERSHY
HAD TO HOUSE-SIT
FOR THAT VACATIONING BEAR,
BUT WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
ALL MY OTHER FRIENDS
WOULD HAVE PLANS
THIS AFTERNOON, TOO?
RARITY HAS TO WASH HER HAIR?
APPLEJACK HAS TO PICK APPLES?
TWILIGHT IS
BEHIND ON HER STUDIES
AND HAS TO HIT THE BOOKS?
THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT,
THE MORE THOSE ARE STARTING
TO SOUND LIKE...
[ GASPS ]
...EXCUSES!
[ ZIP! WHIP! ]
[ PITTER! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ SLINK! ]
[ CREAK! ]
THAT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE STUDYING...
OR HITTING.
[ BELL DINGS ]
OH, YOU MUST BE
HERE FOR --
Shh!
IS PINKIE PIE AROUND?
OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
GOOD.
I DON'T WANT HER TO KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS.
[ RATTLE! ]
YES, OF COURSE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
BUT WE'RE FRIENDS.
WHAT WOULDN'T TWILIGHT WANT ME
TO KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT?
[ GASPS ]
SHE'S COMING BACK.
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS. AND REMEMBER,
NOT A WORD TO PINKIE PIE.
HEY.
[ CLUNK! ]
WHAT'S WITH THE TIN CAN?
[ SNAP! CRASH! ]
AAH!
[ CRASH! RATTLE! ]
[ SLOOP! CRANK! ]
[ PITTER! ]
[ CRANK! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ PITTER! ]
[ SLOOP! WHIP! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
TIME TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THINGS.
[ PITTER! ]
[ CRACK! ]
[ WHIP! ]
[ PLOP! ]
[ CREAK! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
I THINK OUR COVER'S BEEN BLOWN.
WE'LL NEED
A NEW DISGUISE.
[ PITTER! ]
[ CHIMES PLAY ]
SHE DIDN'T SEE YOU
AT THE SWEET SHOP, DID SHE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, GOOD. I'D HATE FOR HER
TO RUIN EVERYTHING.
ME TOO.
[ SLOOP! PLOP! ]
[ CREAK! ]
[ BOING! ]
[ POP! ]
[ SQUEAKS ]
[ SNEEZES ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
RARITY:
Have you seen her?
FLUTTERSHY:
Not since this morning.
Me neither.
Can you believe she was
planning on throwing
an after-birthday party
today?
I'm just glad I was able
to come up with an excuse
for why I couldn't
be there.
Me too. This is obviously
going to be so much better.
As long as we keep her
from finding out about it,
it will.
See you later.
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ THUMP! ]
OH!
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SLOOP! ]
AAH!
[ ZOOM! ]
I THOUGHT EVERYPONY
LOVED MY PARTIES.
HI, PINKIE PIE.
[ TWANG! ]
UH-OH!
[ WHOOSH! ]
RAINBOW DASH, WAIT!
WHEW!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
AAH!
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ CLANG! ]
[ CREAK! ]
WHAT'S THE REAL REASON
YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO COME TO GUMMY'S PARTY?!
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT'S IN THAT BAG?!
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHOOSH! WHOOSH! ]
[ ZIP! WHOOSH! ]
APPLEJACK, WE HAVE A PROBLEM!
[ GASPS ]
[ SLAM! ]
[ CONK! CONK! CONK!
CONK! CONK! CONK! ]
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE!
OH, UH, HOWDY, PARTNER.
MIND IF I TAKE A LOOK
INSIDE THE BARN?
NO.
UH, I MEAN YES.
I MEAN
YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE.
RAINBOW DASH
JUST WENT IN THERE.
OH, WELL, SHE WAS JUST BRINGING
IN SOME...SUPPLIES, YEP.
SUPPLIES
FOR THE R-RENOVATION.
FIXING UP THE WHOLE THING,
TOP TO BOTTOM.
UH, LOTS OF CONSTRUCTION
GOING ON IN THERE RIGHT NOW!
YOU HEARD HER!
CONSTRUCTION!
[ PONIES IMITATING ANIMALS ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ SLINK! ]
[ WHIP! ]
[ CREAK! CREAK! CREAK! CREAK! ]
[ CREAK! ]
[ CREAK! CREAK! CREAK! ]
[ SMACK! ]
[ TINKLE! ]
YEP, CONSTRUCTION.
THAT'S MY STORY,
AND I'M STICKING TO IT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GULP! ]
OKIE-DOKIE-LOKIE.
[ SIGHS ]
[ WHIP! ]
[ ALL SIGH ]
SECRETS AND LIES.
IT'S ALL SECRETS AND LIES
WITH THOSE PONIES.
THEY'RE UP TO SOMETHING, GUMMY,
SOMETHING THEY DON'T WANT ME
TO KNOW ABOUT.
[ BOING! ]
WELL, I'M GONNA KNOW
ABOUT IT!
I'M GONNA KNOW ABOUT IT
BIG TIME!
AND I KNOW JUST WHO'S
GONNA TELL ME ALL ABOUT IT --
TELL ME ALL ABOUT IT
BIG TIME!
WOW! NICE SPREAD.
IT'S ALL YOURS, SPIKE.
[ CLINK! ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ CLANK! CLANK! ]
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS TALK.
THAT'S IT?
OH, YOU GOT IT.
OKAY. UH, BEAUTIFUL WEATHER
WE'RE HAVING, EH?
I LOVE A SUNNY SPRING DAY.
DON'T YOU?
THE BIRDS CHIRPING,
THE FLOWERS BLOOMING.
NO, NO, NO.
TALK ABOUT OUR FRIENDS.
OH, OKAY.
LET'S SEE.
THERE'S TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
SHE'S THE UNICORN.
GOOD WITH MAGIC,
REAL BRAINIAC.
AND THEN YOU GOT RARITY --
TOTAL KNOCKOUT.
TWILIGHT SEEMS TO THINK
I DON'T HAVE A CHANCE WITH HER,
BUT, EH,
WHAT DOES SHE KNOW?
LET'S SEE.
THERE'S -- THERE'S FLUTTERSHY,
A PEGASUS AFRAID OF HEIGHTS.
HUH!
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
UGH! NO!
YOU'RE NOT
UNDERSTANDING ME!
I WANT YOU TO CONFESS!
CONFESS?
CONFESS!
I'M THE ONE WHO SPILLED JUICE
ALL OVER TWILIGHT'S COPY
OF "MAGICAL MYSTERIES
AND PRACTICAL POTIONS"!
[ SQUEAK! ]
AND?
AND I'M THE ONE WHO USED UP
ALL THE HOT WATER
IN PONYVILLE YESTERDAY
WHEN I TOOK
A SEVEN-HOUR BUBBLE BATH!
[ SQUEAK! ]
AND?
AND SOMETIMES, WHEN NO ONE'S
AROUND, I DO THIS.
[ CREAK! WHIP! ]
[ CREAK! ]
LOOKIN' GOOD, SPIKE!
LOOKIN' REAL GOOD!
[ TINK! TINK! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
NO, NO, NO, NO!
W-WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO HEAR?
TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT ME TO SAY,
AND I'LL SAY IT!
TELL ME THAT MY FRIENDS ARE
LYING TO ME AND AVOIDING ME
BECAUSE THEY DON'T
LIKE MY PARTIES
AND THEY DON'T WANT TO
BE MY FRIENDS ANYMORE!
[ PANTING ]
YOUR FRIENDS ARE ALL LYING
TO YOU AND AVOIDING YOU
'CAUSE THEY DON'T
LIKE YOUR PARTIES
AND THEY DON'T WANT TO
BE YOUR FRIENDS ANYMORE!
AHA! I KNEW IT!
[ CREAK! ]
[ POP! GUST! ]
OH, NO!
MY FRIENDS DON'T
LIKE MY PARTIES,
AND THEY DON'T WANT TO
BE ME FRIENDS ANYMORE.
[ CLICK ]
UH, SO...
AW!
[ CHOMP! ]
MM-MMM!
[ SIGHS ]
THANK YOU ALL
SO MUCH FOR COMING.
IT MEANS SO MUCH TO GUMMY.
[ CHATTERS ]
[ Deep voice ]
COULD I HAVE SOME MORE PUNCH?
[ Normal voice ]
WELL, OF COURSE YOU CAN HAVE
SOME MORE PUNCH, MR. TURNIP.
[ ZIP! ]
[ BOING! ]
[ Deep voice ]
THIS IS ONE GREAT PARTY!
YOU'VE REALLY OUTDONE YOURSELF!
[ Normal voice ]
WHY, THANK YOU, ROCKY.
[ Deep voice ] I'M HAVING
A DELIGHTFUL TIME, AS WELL.
[ Normal voice ]
I'M SO GLAD, SIR LINTS-A-LOT.
[ BOING! ]
[ High-pitched voice ]
MIGHT I TROUBLE YOU FOR
ANOTHER SLICE OF CAKE?
[ Normal voice ] ANYTHING
FOR YOU, MADAM LE FLOUR.
[ Deep voice ] I'M JUST GLAD
NONE OF THEM PONIES SHOWED UP.
[ SLOOP! ]
[ Normal voice ]
OH, THEY'RE NOT SO BAD.
[ PLOP! PLOP! ]
[ SLUMP! ]
NOT SO BAD? PLEASE.
THEY'RE A BUNCH OF LOSERS.
OH, COME ON, NOW.
"LOSERS" MIGHT BE A LITTLE
STRONG, DON'T YOU THINK?
AFTER THE WAY
THEY TREATED YOU?
I SAY "LOSERS"
ISN'T STRONG ENOUGH.
WELL, IT WAS PRETTY RUDE.
PRETTY RUDE?
IT WAS DOWNRIGHT DESPICABLE!
IT WAS, WASN'T IT?
IF I WERE YOU, I WOULDN'T
SPEAK TO THEM EVER AGAIN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M NOT GONNA SPEAK TO THEM
EVER AGAIN,
AND I'M NOT GONNA INVITE THEM
TO ANOTHER PARTY
AS LONG AS I LIVE!
THEY DON'T DESERVE TO BE
INVITED TO MY PARTIES!
[ SCREECH! ]
NOT AFTER THE WAY
THEY'VE BEEN ACTING.
DESPICABLE!
BUNCH OF LOSERS!
[ High-pitched voice ]
YES, THAT'S RIGHT!
[ Deep voice ]
WELL DONE.
YEAH, YOU SHOW THEM!
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ TWANG! ]
WHO COULD THAT BE?
HEY THERE, PINKIE PIE.
SORRY I WAS IN
SUCH A RUSH EARLIER.
HAD SOMEPLACE TO BE AND COULDN'T
SLOW DOWN AND SAY HELLO.
YOU KNOW HOW IT GOES.
I KNOW HOW IT GOES,
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
SO, WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME
OVER TO SWEET APPLE ACRES?
NO, THANKS. I'M SPENDING TIME
WITH MY REAL FRIENDS.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
MADAM LE FLOUR?
[ High-pitched voice ]
OUI! THAT IS CORRECT, MADAM.
UH, PINKIE PIE?
[ Normal voice ]
ANOTHER SLICE OF CAKE,
SIR LINTS-A-LOT?
[ Deep voice ]
I'D LOVE ONE.
ALL RIGHTY.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GET ON
OUT OF CREEPY TOWN
AND HEAD OVER
TO APPLEJACK'S --
SHE'S NOT
GOING ANYWHERE.
[ Normal voice ]
I MOST CERTAINLY AM NOT.
I'M HAVING A WONDERFUL TIME
RIGHT HERE.
[ ZIP! ]
YOU SHOULD REALLY
JUST COME WITH ME.
[ SLOOP! ]
[ Deep voice ]
YOU HEARD THE LADY!
SHE AIN'T GOIN' NOWHERES,
CHUMP!
WHO YOU CALLIN'
A CHUMP, CHUMP?
[ SIGHS ]
THAT'S IT.
PARTY'S OVER.
COME ON, PINKIE PIE.
NO!
PINKIE PIE, LET'S GO!
I SAID NO!
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ CREAK! ]
YOU...HAVE TO...
COME WITH...ME!
NO...I...DON'T!
[ CLANG! ]
[ ZIP! CRASH! ]
OH, YOU WANT TO DO THIS
THE HARD WAY?
WE'LL DO THIS
THE HARD WAY!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ PANTING ]
WE'RE...HERE.
SURPRISE!
I REALLY THOUGHT
SHE'D BE MORE EXCITED.
EXCITED?! EXCITED?!
WHY WOULD I BE EXCITED TO ATTEND
MY OWN FAREWELL PARTY?!
FAREWELL PARTY?
YES!
YOU DON'T LIKE ME ANYMORE,
SO YOU DECIDED TO KICK ME
OUT OF THE GROUP
AND THROW A GREAT BIG PARTY
TO CELEBRATE,
A-FAREWELL-TO-PINKIE PIE
PARTY!
WHY IN THE WORLD
WOULD YOU THINK
WE DIDN'T LIKE YOU ANYMORE,
SUGAR CUBE?
WHY?
WHY?!
OH!
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN LYING TO ME
AND AVOIDING ME ALL DAY!
THAT'S WHY!
UH, YEAH, BECAUSE WE WANTED
YOUR PARTY TO BE A SURPRISE.
WE'VE BEEN PLANNING THIS PARTY
FOR SUCH A LONG TIME.
WE HAD TO MAKE EXCUSES FOR WHY
WE COULDN'T ATTEND GUMMY'S PARTY
SO THAT WE COULD GET
EVERYTHING READY FOR YOURS.
Twilight: IF THIS IS
A FAREWELL PARTY,
WHY DOES THE CAKE I PICKED UP
FROM SUGAR CUBE CORNER
SAY "HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
PINKIE PIE"?
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
BECAUSE IT'S MY BIRTHDAY!
OH, HOW COULD I HAVE FORGOTTEN
MY OWN BIRTHDAY?
[ ALL SIGH ]
[ THUD! ]
AND YOU LIKE ME SO MUCH,
YOU DECIDED TO THROW ME
A SURPRISE PARTY!
THAT'S WHAT WE'VE BEEN TRYING
TO TELL YOU, DARLING.
YOU GIRLS ARE
THE BEST FRIENDS EVER!
HOW COULD I HAVE
EVER DOUBTED YOU?
IT'S OKAY, PINKIE PIE.
IT COULD'VE HAPPENED
TO ANY OF US.
[ LAUGHTER ]
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
I'M JUST GLAD I HAVEN'T BEEN
REPLACED BY A BUCKET OF TURNIPS.
HUH?
YOU DON'T WANT
TO KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS.
ENOUGH OF THIS GABBIN'.
[ RECORD SCRATCHES ]
LET'S PARTY!
[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
Twilight:
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
I AM WRITING TO YOU FROM
THE MOST DELIGHTFUL PARTY.
I AM NOT ONLY HAVING A GREAT
TIME WITH MY FRIENDS
BUT ALSO WAS GIVEN
THE OPPORTUNITY
TO LEARN A VALUABLE LESSON
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
ALWAYS EXPECT THE BEST
FROM YOUR FRIENDS
AND NEVER ASSUME THE WORST.
REST ASSURED THAT A GOOD FRIEND
ALWAYS HAS YOUR BEST INTERESTS
AT HEART.
YOUR FAITHFUL STUDENT,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
YOU GIRLS WOULDN'T MIND
IF WE CELEBRATED
GUMMY'S AFTER-BIRTHDAY PARTY,
TOO, WOULD YOU?
HIS PARTY WAS CUT SHORT,
AND HE'S PRETTY UPSET ABOUT IT.
Rainbow: OH, SURE!
Rarity: OH, DEFINITELY.
WE MUST HAVE A PARTY.
LET'S HAVE A PARTY
FOR GUMMY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS