[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
THERE YOU GO,
MR. MOUSEY.
[ WHEELCHAIR SQUEAKING ]
[ BOING! BOING! ]
NOW, YOU STAY OFF THAT LEG
AND DO EVERYTHING I TOLD YOU,
AND IT WILL BE JUST LIKE NEW
IN NO TIME AT ALL.
[ SQUEAKS ]
OH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
HAPPY TO BE ABLE
TO HELP.
[ PANTING ]
[ GASPS ]
OOH!
[ ZIP! ]
[ CREAK! ]
YOU...FOUND A WATCH?
[ WHIFFLE! ]
YOU...
WHAT TO BE A WATCH?
YOU'RE RUNNING.
RUNNING OUT OF TIME?
NO. YOU'RE LATE?
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ BELL TOLLING ]
[ GASPS ]
I'M LATE
FOR A VERY IMPORTANT DATE!
THE BIG BRUNCH
FOR PRINCESS CELESTIA
AT SUGARCUBE CORNER.
[ POINK! POINK! POINK! ]
[ SIGHS ]
OH, THE PRINCES IS HERE
IN PONYVILLE FOR A PARTY,
AND WE ALL PROMISED WE'D BE
THERE, BUT I'M NOT THERE!
OH, DO I LOOK ALL RIGHT?
DO I NEED TO BRING ANYTHING?
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T GO.
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
AH!
IT'S STARTING!
I'M MISSING IT!
[ SIGHS ]
OH, THANKS, ANGEL.
[ SPROING! SPROING! ]
I MEAN, IF YOU HADN'T
REMINDED ME,
I MIGHT HAVE NOT REMEMBERED,
AND THEN I WOULDN'T BE THERE
AND EVERYPONY WOULD BE WONDERING
WHERE I WAS AND --
OH, RIGHT.
I'M LATE.
[ RATTLING ]
OH, OKAY, THEN.
SEE YOU LATER.
[ SIGHS ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
* FAITHFUL AND STRONG
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
SO, WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO
TO GET TO BE ONE OF THE
PRINCESS'S ROYAL GUARDS, ANYWAY?
IS THE PAY GOOD?
HELLO?!
ANYBODY HOME?
BLBLBLBLBL!
WAH-WAH!
PBHT!
BLBLBLBLBLBL!
OOH, YOU'RE GOOD.
TOO GOOD.
I'M BORED.
[ PANTING ]
PHEW! MADE IT.
[ SHING! ]
[ GASPS ]
HALT!
WHO GOES THERE?
[ GULPS ]
NO ONE. NEVER MIND.
I'LL GO HOME.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, SIRS.
SHE'S ON THE LIST.
THANKS, TWILIGHT.
I'M SO GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT,
FLUTTERSHY.
IT WOULDN'T BE THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU.
[ BELL DINGS ]
HOW'S EVERYPONY DOING?
GOOD? GOOD.
ANYTHING ELSE WE CAN GET
FOR YOU, DEARIES --
OOH!
I-I MEAN, ESTEEMED GUEST.
EVERYTHING IS FINE,
MR. AND MRS. CAKE.
SORRY I'M LATE.
I HAD TO FINISH TAKING CARE
OF A PATIENT FIRST.
OH, YOU AND YOUR TENDER-LOVING
CARE OF LITTLE ANIMALS.
I JUST KNOW PRINCESS CELESTIA'S
GONNA LOVE THAT ABOUT YOU.
I MEAN,
I HOPE SHE WILL.
I MEAN [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
OF COURSE SHE WILL.
WOW, TWILIGHT,
I THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO GOT NERVOUS
AT SOCIAL GATHERINGS.
OH, IT'S NOT THAT.
I JUST WANT THE PRINCESS
TO APPROVE OF MY FRIENDS.
BUT SHE'S MET US
ALL BEFORE.
AND READ ABOUT YOU
IN MY LETTERS.
BUT THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME SHE'S SPENT ANY
REAL TIME WITH YOU.
I WANT EVERYPONY
TO MAKE A GOOD IMPRESSION.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU HAVE
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
BESIDES, IT'S JUST
A CASUAL GET-TOGETHER, RIGHT?
DON'T TOUCH ME!
WATCH THE DRESS!
CAREFUL!
YOU'RE GONNA SPILL THAT ON ME!
OH, OOH,
THAT LOOKS DELICIOUS.
WHAT IS IT?
OHH!
DOES IT STAIN?!
KEEP IT AWAY FROM ME!
OR PERHAPS
NOT THAT CASUAL.
UH, WHICH IS THE SALAD AND
WHICH IS THE APPETIZER AGAIN?
AND WHICH AM I SUPPOSED
TO EAT FIRST?
AW, NEVER MIND.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
IT'S OKAY, TWILIGHT.
SO OUR FRIENDS' MANNERS
AREN'T PERFECT.
I DOUBT THE PRINCESS
WILL EVEN NOTICE.
[ GIGGLES, SNORTS ]
WHOO-HOO!
COOKIES, CANDIES, AND PIES!
OH, MY!
[ SPLAT! ]
OHH, CHOCOLATE FOUNTAINY
GOODNESS!
[ SPLAT! ]
[ CRACKLING ]
MMM!
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
YOU GONNA EAT THAT?!
[ GULPS ]
[ GASPS ]
HEY!
A THOUSAND PARDONS,
YOUR MAJESTY.
THAT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ SLURPS ]
EMPTY TEACUP AT 4:00!
I SEE IT, HONEY BUN!
OH! UM, THANK YOU.
NOT AT ALL,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
[ SLURPS ]
THANK YOU AGAIN.
OH, BUT OF COURSE,
YOUR MAJESTY.
[ SLURPS ]
GOTCHA!
OH!
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU, DEAR?
FLUTTERSHY, IS IT?
ME?
OH, YES, YOUR HIGHNESS.
I UNDERSTAND
FROM TWILIGHT SPARKLE'S LETTERS
THAT YOU ENJOY TENDING TO
THE NEEDS OF WOODLAND CREATURES.
YES, I LOVE TO TAKE CARE
OF ANIMALS.
AS DO I.
AS PRINCESS,
I CARE DEEPLY
ABOUT ALL CREATURES
GREAT AND SMALL.
[ COUGHS ]
NOTHING MEANS MORE TO ME
THAN THE WELL-BEING
OF ALL MY SUBJECTS.
[ COUGHS ]
[ SPITS ]
AH, PHILOMENA, MY PET.
YOU'RE AWAKE.
DO SAY HELLO
TO OUR GRACIOUS HOSTS.
[ COUGHS ]
[ GAGGING ]
[ SPITS ]
[ SIGHS ]
OH...MY.
SHE IS QUITE A SIGHT,
ISN'T SHE?
I...I...
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
[ COUGHS ]
[ SPITS ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY ]
REALLY?
WELL, IF I MUST.
I'M SORRY, EVERYPONY.
I'M AFRAID I HAVE
TO CUT THE PARTY SHORT.
THE MAYOR HAS REQUESTED
AN AUDIENCE WITH ME.
ROYAL DUTY CALLS.
THANK YOU FOR A WONDERFUL TIME.
IT'S BEEN A JOY
GETTING TO KNOW YOU ALL BETTER.
[ SQUEAK! ]
PHEW!
NOW I CAN EAT SOMETHING!
I'M STARVED!
[ CLATTER! CLATTER! ]
[ GROANS ]
WHOO!
HA HA! WHOO! HA HA!
STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE!
ALL I WANT IS A CLEAR PATH
TO THE EXIT.
NOBODY MOVE,
AND MY DRESS WON'T GET HURT!
STAY BACK!
BACK, I SAY!
[ SLURPS ]
[ SIGHS ]
WELL, SPIKE,
I DON'T KNOW FOR SURE
HOW THINGS WENT
WITH THE PRINCESS,
BUT AT LEAST NO BIG DISASTERS
HAPPENED.
[ DOOR SQUEAKS ]
OH, YOU POOR, LITTLE THING.
HOW DID YOU EVER GET IN
SUCH BAD CONDITION?
DON'T YOU WORRY,
PHILOMENA.
I'LL NURSE YOU BACK TO HEALTH
AS A FAVOR TO THE PRINCESS,
WHO'S OBVIOUSLY JUST FAR TOO
BUSY TO CARE FOR YOU PROPERLY.
[ COUGHS ]
I'M SURE THE PRINCESS
WILL APPRECIATE THE HELP.
[ WARBLE! ]
OH, MY!
WE'D BETTER GET YOU TO BED
RIGHT AWAY.
THERE.
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SHIVER! CHATTER! ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ SHIVER! ]
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
THIS IS FAR WORSE
THAN I THOUGHT.
WHAT YOU NEED
IS SOME MEDICINE STAT!
[ COUGHS ]
[ SIGHS ]
HERE YOU GO, PHILOMENA.
THIS WILL FIX YOU RIGHT UP.
[ SNIFFS ]
BLAH!
DR. FLUTTERSHY
EXPECTED THAT.
[ WARBLE! ]
[ BOING!
HAMMER! HAMMER! HAMMER!]
ALWAYS WORKS.
[ GASP ]
OH.
ALMOST ALWAYS.
[ COUGHS ]
[ BLOWS ]
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE HOMEMADE
SOUP TO CURE WHAT AILS YOU.
COME ON, NOW.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET BETTER
IF YOU DON'T COOPERATE.
MMM. SEE?
IT'S DELICIOUS.
GOOD
AND GOOD FOR YOU.
HERE COMES
THE CHOO-CHOO TRAIN.
CHUGGA-CHUGGA, CHUGGA-CHUGGA,
WHOO-WHOO!
[ SLOOP! SLOOP! SLOOP! ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ WHIRL! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
OH, DEAR.
DON'T WORRY, PHILOMENA.
I KNOW WHAT'LL MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
WAIT RIGHT HERE.
I HAVE JUST THE THING.
[ COUGHS ]
[ BUBBLE! ]
LOOK, PHILOMENA.
I BROUGHT A FELLOW FEATHERED
FRIEND BY TO CHEER YOU UP.
HUMMINGWAY HERE
WAS SICK ONCE, TOO,
BUT HE LET ME HELP HIM
AND GOT BETTER IN NO TIME.
DIDN'T YOU, BOY?
[ CHIRPS ]
SAY HELLO TO YOUR NEW FRIEND,
PHILOMENA.
[ CHIRPING ]
AW, LOOK.
I THINK HE LIKES YOU.
* AH-H-H-H
* M-M-M-M-M
YOUR TURN NOW,
PHILOMENA.
GO AHEAD.
YOU CAN DO IT.
* AH-H-H-H
[ COUGHS ]
OH!
UM, GOOD TRY?
I KNOW WHAT'LL CLEAR UP
THAT TICKLE IN YOUR THROAT --
A HUMIDIFIER.
[ STEAM HISSES ]
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
REFRESHING.
HOW'S THAT FEELING NOW FOR YOU,
PHILOMENA?
BETTER?
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ COUGHS ]
OH.
[ BOING! ]
THAT'S OKAY.
I KNOW LOTS OF OTHER WAYS
TO TAKE CARE OF YOU.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE GONNA GET BETTER.
HOW ABOUT...
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
...AROMATHERAPY?
[ SNIFFS ]
AH-CHOO!
[ BOING! ]
WARM BATH?
OINTMENT?
[ SQUISH! ]
[ POP! POP! POP! ]
[ POP! POP! POP! POP! ]
[ BOING! ]
SCALPEL.
SURGICAL TAPE.
[ TAPE RIPS ]
FEATHERS.
[ BOING! ]
[ DRIP! DRIP! DRIP! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ COUGHS ]
OH, PHILOMENA,
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE EASY
TO NURSE YOU BACK TO HEALTH.
I'VE TRIED EVERYTHING I KNOW,
AND LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE WORSE THAN EVER.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ ZOOM! ]
HI, FLUTTERSHY.
I JUST WANTED TO DROP BY
AND SAY THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH
FOR MAKING SUCH A
GOOD IMPRESSION ON
THE PRINCESS TODAY.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT IS CELESTIA'S PET
DOING HERE?!
I COULDN'T LEAVE THE POOR THING
THERE.
SHE NEEDED MY HELP.
OH, NO!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
THIS IS BAD!
HOW COULD I JUST WALK AWAY
AND NOT DO ANYTHING?
BUT -- BUT --
SHE DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU!
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
WITHOUT TELLING ANYPONY?!
WITHOUT ASKING PERMISSION?!
BUT --
[ COUGHS ]
I KNOW YOU HAD
GOOD INTENTIONS,
BUT YOU HAVE GOT TO RETURN
THE PRINCESS'S PET!
BUT --
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OKAY, LET'S...
[ COUGHS ]
...GO.
[ STRETCH! ]
[ THUNK! ]
IF WE HURRY,
WE CAN PUT HER BACK
BEFORE ANYPONY
EVEN REALIZES SHE'S MISSING.
[ GASPS ]
WE WERE TOLD WE COULD FIND
TWILIGHT SPARKLE HERE.
WE REGRET TO INFORM YOU,
MISS,
THAT THE ROYAL PET
HAS GONE MISSING.
REALLY?
YOU DON'T SAY.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
[ COUGHS ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ BOTH COUGHING ]
[ Hoarsely ]
IT'S THAT DRY NIGHT AIR.
BUT IT'S DAYTIME.
WELL, DAY AIR'S EVEN DRIER.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
YOU GUARDS BETTER BE
ON YOUR WAY
IF YOU'RE GONNA FIND
THE PRINCESS'S MISSING PET.
PHILOMENA, WAS IT?
THANK YOU EVER SO MUCH
FOR KEEPING ME IN THE LOOP.
BYE!
[ PANTING ]
PHEW!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
GOING TO RETURN PHILOMENA,
REMEMBER?
WE CAN'T NOW!
WHY NOT?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THE PRINCESS IS GONNA DO
IF SHE FINDS YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO TOOK HER PET, DO YOU?!
DO YOU?
WELL...NO.
BUT IT CAN'T BE
ANYTHING GOOD.
SHE MIGHT BANISH YOU
FROM EQUESTRIA...
OR THROW YOU
IN A DUNGEON...
[ GASPS ]
...OR BANISH YOU
AND THEN THROW YOU IN A DUNGEON
IN THE PLACE
THAT SHE BANISHES YOU TO.
YOU REALLY THINK
THE PRINCESS WOULD DO THAT?
OKAY, GRANTED THAT PROBABLY
WON'T HAPPEN,
BUT DO YOU WANT TO TAKE
ANY CHANCES?
ALL THAT REALLY MATTERS
TO ME
IS THAT POOR LITTLE PHILOMENA
HERE GETS WELL.
[ COUGHS ]
THAT'S VERY NOBLE OF YOU.
I'LL WRITE TO YOU
WHEN YOU'RE BANISHED,
UNLESS I'M BANISHED
TO SOMEWHERE THERE'S
NO POST OFFICE.
THEN YOU'LL HAVE
TO WRITE TO ME.
DEAL?
PLEASE, TWILIGHT.
YOU JUST HAVE TO HELP ME
GET PHILOMENA HEALTHY,
AND THEN WE CAN RETURN HER
TO THE PRINCESS,
AND EVERYTHING
WILL BE FINE.
DID YOU GIVE HER
ANY KIND OF MEDICINE?
I TRIED TO,
BUT SHE WOULDN'T TAKE IT.
UGH!
THEN YOU HAVE
TO MAK HER TAKE IT.
YOU CAN'T BE SUCH A PUSHOVER,
FLUTTERSHY.
YOU NEED TO SHOW THIS PATIENT
WHO'S THE BOSS.
MAKE HER STRAIGHTEN UP
AND FLY RIGHT!
SHE CAN'T FLY.
NO EXCUSES!
[ GULPS ]
DONE.
OKAY, WHAT ELSE?
UH, WELL, SHE KEEPS PULLING
HER FEATHERS OFF,
THE ONES THAT HAVEN'T
FALLEN OUT YET
FROM ALL HER COUGHING,
I MEAN.
[ COUGHS ]
THERE YOU GO.
[ THUNK! ]
[ STRETCH! ]
I DON'T THINK
SHE LIKES IT.
TOUGH LOVE, BABY.
YOU WANT HER TO GET WELL,
DON'T YOU?
OF COURSE, BUT --
NEXT!
WELL, SHE DESPERATELY NEEDS
SOME BED REST,
BUT I CAN'T GET HER
TO STAY PUT.
[ HONK! ]
[ Echoing ]
ONE STEP AHEAD OF YOU.
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD,
PHILOMENA, I PROMISE.
PLEASE JUST RELAX
AND TRY TO GET SOME SLEEP.
WHAT'S THIS SOUP
OVER HERE?
SMELLS DELICIOUS.
I MADE IT FOR PHILOMENA,
BUT SHE WOULDN'T EAT IT.
OH, SHE'LL EAT IT,
ALL RIGHT.
[ TINKLING ]
[ SQUAWKS ]
HEY!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
NO, PHILOMENA!
COME BACK!
[ SCREECH! ]
[ BOTH COUGH ]
[ PITTER! PITTER! PITTER!
PITTER! PITTER! PITTER! ]
[ ZIP! ]
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING?
ARE YOU HAVING A RACE?
OH, CAN I PLAY?
1, 2, 3, GO!
MMM!
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
EXCUSE ME.
HI!
BEG YOUR PARDON.
PUT ME DOWN!
WHAT IN TARNATION?
SORRY,
BUT WE'VE GOT TO FIND --
THE PRINCESS'S PET BIRD!
[ COUGHS ]
PHILOMENA,
COME DOWN FROM THERE.
YOU'LL HURT YOURSELF.
[ WARBLE! BOING! ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ GAGGING ]
[ BOING! ]
[ COUGHING ]
I'LL CATCH YOU.
[ GASPS ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
TWILIGHT.
YES, YOUR MAJESTY.
THERE'S BEEN
A TERRIBLE ACCIDENT.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
NO, PRINCESS.
FLUTTERSHY
DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER.
IT WAS MY FAULT.
I'M THE ONE WHO DID IT.
BUT YOU WERE ONLY
TRYING TO HELP.
SOME HELP I WAS.
WILL YOU LET ME DO THIS?
SHE'LL GO EASIER ON ME.
BUT IT'S MY FAULT.
NO, IT'S MY FAULT.
WAIT.
WHAT ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
THANKS FOR TRYING
TO PROTECT ME, TWILIGHT,
BUT, PRINCESS CELESTIA, I'M
THE ONE WHO TOOK YOUR PET BIRD.
I REALLY WAS ONLY TRYING TO HELP
THE POOR LITTLE THING.
THEN I WAS GONNA BRING IT
RIGHT BACK TO YOU, HONEST.
SO, IF YOU WANT TO BANISH ME
AND THEN THROW ME IN A DUNGEON
IN THE PLACE
THAT YOU BANISH ME TO,
THEN THAT'S
WHAT I DESERVE.
OH, STOP FOOLING AROUND,
PHILOMENA.
YOU'RE SCARING EVERYPONY.
[ TINKLING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
WOW!
WOW!WOW!
I-I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT IS THAT THING?
WHAT HAPPENED
TO PHILOMENA?
THIS IS PHILOMENA.
SHE'S QUITE A SIGHT,
AS I SAID,
BUT NOTHING UNUSUAL
FOR A PHOENIX.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
PHILOMENA?
[ SQUAWKS ]
A-A PHOENIX?
A PHOENIX IS A MAJESTIC
AND MAGICAL BIRD.
WHILE IT APPEARS HEALTHY
AND HAPPY MOST OF THE TIME...
EVERY SO OFTEN,
IT MUST RENEW ITSELF
BY SHEDDING ALL OF ITS FEATHERS
AND BURSTING INTO FLAME.
Rather melodramatic,
if you ask me.
IT THEN RISES FROM THE ASHES
FRESH AS A DAISY.
ALL JUST A NORMAL PART
OF THE LIFE CYCLE OF A PHOENIX.
I'M AFRAID MISCHIEVOUS
LITTLE PHILOMENA HERE
TOOK THE OCCASION TO HAVE A
LITTLE FUN WITH YOU, FLUTTERSHY.
SAY YOU'RE SORRY,
YOUNG LADY.
[ WHIMPERS ]
SO, AREN'T YOU GONNA BANISH ME
OR THROW ME IN A DUNGEON
OR BANISH ME THEN THROW ME
IN A DUNGEON
IN THE PLACE
THAT YOU BANISH ME TO?
OF COURSE NOT,
MY LITTLE PONY.
WHERE ON EARTH
WOULD YOU GET SUCH AN IDEA?
I GUESS I HAVE
SOME IMAGINATION.
FLUTTERSHY REALLY DID DO
EVERYTHING SHE COULD
TO TRY TO TAKE CARE OF PHILOMENA
FOR YOU.
AND I DO APPRECIATE
THAT YOUR HEART WAS IN
THE RIGHT PLACE, CHILD,
BUT ALL YOU HAD TO DO
WAS ASK ME,
AND I COULD HAVE TOLD YOU
PHILOMENA WAS A PHOENIX
AND SAVED YOU
ALL THIS TROUBLE.
I KNOW.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE JUMPED
TO CONCLUSIONS.
NEXT TIME, I'LL ASK
BEFORE TAKING MATTERS
INTO MY OWN HOOVES.
[ POP! ]
SHOULD I WRITE YOU A LETTER
ABOUT THAT LESSON, PRINCESS?
NO, THAT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
I THINK I CAN REMEMBER.
[ COOS ]
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU, PHILOMENA.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
HMM.
Hey, you know
what you should do?
You should go over
and tickle.
[ WARBLE! WARBLE! WARBLE! ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
YEAH!
[ SQUAWKS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS