THIS METEOR SHOWER TONIGHT
IS GONNA BE AMAZING!
AWESOME!
[ WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! ]
YOU KNOW, THIS SHOWER ONLY
HAPPENS ONCE EVERY 100 YEARS.
A CENTENNIAL CELEBRATION!
[ WARBLE! ]
UH, UNH!
WE BETTER
GET A MOVE ON.
DON'T WANT TO BE LATE!
[ SLOSHING ]
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
AHH! THERE.
SPIKE, DID YOU GRAB
MY QUILL AND INK?
Spike: CHECK!
SCROLLS?
CHECK!
I'VE ALSO PACKED A TELESCOPE,
APPLES, BANANAS, FRUIT PUNCH,
AND MY FRESHLY BAKED,
HOMEMADE,
TRIPLE-DECKER, NUT-CRAZY
VANILLA-CREAM COOKIES!
[ CHUCKLES ]
I CAN SEE THAT.
[ SLURP! ]
ONCE AGAIN,
YOU'VE READ MY MIND, SPIKE.
AND THAT IS WHY YOU ARE
MY NUMBER-ONE ASSISTANT.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T HEAR YOU.
THAT IS WHY YOU ARE
MY NUMBER-ONE ASSISTANT.
MISSED THAT. HUH?
I SAID...
[ POINK! ]
[ CHUCKLES ] COME ON.
LET'S GET GOING.
WAIT! I ALMOST FORGOT!
I WANT TO BRING
"THE ASTRONOMICAL ASTRONOMERS'
ALMANAC TO ALL THINGS
ASTRONOMY."
THE ASTRO NOMO LOMO--
HUMMANUH WHAT?
YOU KNOW, THAT REALLY OLD,
BIG, BLUE BOOK
ON STARS, MOONS, PLANETS,
THE UNIVERSE?
RIGHT. CHECK!
AH...AH...AH!
AH!
[ SIGHS ]
A-A-A-A-H-CHOO!
Twilight Sparkle: HEY!
WHAT'S TAKING MY NUMBER-ONE
ASSISTANT SO LONG?
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
I WAS SURE I PUT "THE
ASTRONOMERS' GUIDE" BACK.
THE BOOK WOULD HAVE
HELPED ME IDENTIFY
DIFFERENT PLANETS
AND STARS TONIGHT.
WELL, MAYBE
SOMEONE BORROWED IT.
BESIDES,
YOU DON'T NEED THAT BOOK.
YOU CAN ALREADY NAME
ALL THE PLANETS AND STARS
'CAUSE YOU'RE SUPER SMART
AND ASTRONOMICALLY AWESOME!
THANKS, SPIKE.
YOU'RE SUCH A FLATTERER.
YEAH, I'M A SWEET-TALKER.
AND A NUMBER-ONE ASSISTANT.
RIGHT?
CHECK!
[ ZIP! ZIP! ZIP!
ZIP! ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! GULP! ]
WOW, TWILIGHT!
YOU'RE LUCKY TO HAVE
SUCH A RAD ASSISTANT.
I WISH I HAD SOMEONE
TO DO WHATEVER I TOLD THEM.
[ POINK! ]
OOH! OOH! ME! ME! ME!
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU WANT,
RAINBOW DASH!
OH, YEAH, PIPSQUEAK?
HOW ABOUT
TAKING OUT THE TRASH?
YES, MA'AM!
DO WE HAVE SPIKE TO THANK AGAIN
FOR THIS AMAZING SPREAD?
ISN'T HE
SIMPLY AMAZING?
AW, COME ON.
[ POINK! ]
I SAID, "COME ON."
LITTLE SPIKEY-WIKEY,
WHO KNEW THAT BIG,
FEROCIOUS DRAGONS
STARTED OFF
SO CUTESY-WOOTSY?
SPIKE, YOU ARE SUCH
A LITTLE STAR
THAT I HAD TO MAKE
THIS LITTLE BOW TIE FOR YOU.
[ TWINKLE! ]
GOSH, YOU GUYS
ARE EMBARRASSING ME.
STOP IT!
TWILIGHT, YOUR TURN.
SPIKE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
OH, RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
HEY, EVERYPONY,
THE SHOW IS STARTING!
[ HOOFBEATS,
INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
WOW!
COOL!
WOW! THAT'S AMAZING!
WHOA!
SO COOL!
THAT'S AMAZING!
WHOA!
[ YAWNS ]
HUH?
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ GULP! ]
[ WHIP! ]
MMM!
[ GULP! ]
MMM, WOW!
THESE COOKIES ARE DELISH!
SPIKE MADE THEM.
SPEAKING OF...
SPIKE?
CAN YOU BRING US SOME PUNCH?
[ POINK! ]
SPIKE?
[ SNORING ]
OOH, POOR LITTLE THING.
AWW, HE'S WORKED HIMSELF
TO THE BONE.
AND NOW THE PUNCH
HAS BEEN...
SPIKED!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SPIKE SNORING ]
GOOD NIGHT, SPIKE.
[ SNORING CONTINUES ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
SWEET DREAMS,
NUMBER-ONE ASSISTANT.
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ SIGHS ]
"THE STUDY OF COMETS.
"COMETS ARE SMALL,
IRREGULARLY SHAPED BODIES
"THAT ARE MADE OF NONVOLATILE
GRAINS AND FROZEN GASES.
[ CREAKING ]
THEY --"
[ HINGES CREAK ]
HMM.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ HINGES CREAK ]
[ CLANG ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
"...HAVE BODY STRUCTURES
THAT ARE FRAGILE AND DIVERSE."
[ CREAKING ]
[ HINGES CREAK ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
OOH, SHOOT!
[ WHOOSH! ]
OOH, THIS IS A JOB FOR SPIKE.
IF ONLY HE WERE AWAKE!
Owl: HOOT!
WAIT! DON'T GO!
DON'T BE AFRAID.
THANK YOU FOR RETURNING
MY SCROLL.
HOOT! HOOT!
[ WIND HOWLING ]
GOSH, IT'S COLD TONIGHT.
SAY, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO RELAX IN HERE
AND KEEP ME COMPANY
WHILE I WORK?
HOOT! HOOT!
NOW, WHERE WAS I?
OH, YES --
"...FRAGILE AND DIVERSE
WITH A SURROUNDING CLOUD
"OF MATERIAL CALLED A COMA
THAT GROWS IN SIZE
AND BRIGHTENS
AS THE COMET..."
[ SNORING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
AAH! I OVERSLEPT!
I KNOW IT'S ALREADY 10:00,
BUT I'M SCALY-TAILED
AND BRIGHT-EYED
AND READY TO WORK
TWICE AS FAST!
OH, PLEASE DON'T BE UPSET,
TWILIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT FOR BREAKFAST?
OATMEAL?
HOW ABOUT A SUNFLOWER SMOOTHIE?
GRASS PANCAKES?
SPIKE, DON'T WORRY.
BUT MY MORNING CHORES.
IT'S OKAY.
ALOYSIUS DID THEM FOR YOU.
WHO?
HE'S OUR NEW
JUNIOR ASSISTANT.
HE'S GONNA HELP OUT
WITH YOUR CHORES
SO YOU WON'T BE SO TIRED
ALL THE TIME.
[ RATTLE! ]
WH --
WH-WHAT DO WE NEED
A JUNIOR ASSISTANT FOR?
I'M NOT TIRED.
I DO FINE ON MY OWN.
I DON'T NEED SLEEP. I --
SPIKE, DON'T WORRY.
HE'S JUST HERE
TO HELP OUT A LITTLE.
NOW, I HAVE TO GO OUT.
SO WHY DON'T YOU INTRODUCE
YOURSELF TO ALOYSIUS?
HE'S IN THE LIBRARY.
WORRIED? DO I LOOK WORRIED?
I'M NOT WORRIED.
WHO'S WORRIED?
HELLO?
HELLO?!
[ CREEEAK! ]
WHOA!
DUDE, THAT'S CREEPY.
UH, HI, THERE.
I'M SPIKE.
I'M SURE TWILIGHT HAS TOLD YOU
ALL ABOUT ME.
HOOT.
UH, SPIKE?
YOU KNOW, ASSISTANT NUMBER ONE?
HOOT?
I'M SPIKE!
AND WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU?
HOO.
WHO?
HOO!
I THOUGHT YOUR NAME
WAS ALOYSIUS!
HOO?
OKAY, WHO, ALOYSIUS,
WHATEVER!
I'M SPIKE, OKAY?
LOOK, ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW
IS THAT I'M NUMBER ONE
AND YOU'RE NUMBER TWO!
GOT IT?
HOO?
SO, A MAN OF MYSTERY, HUH?
I'M KEEPING MY EYE ON YOU.
I'VE GOT EYES IN THE BACK
OF M HEAD, TOO, YOU KNOW!
[ SLUMP! ]
[ TWEET! ]
UNH, WELL, NOT REALLY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN!
[ SLAM! ]
THAT BIRD IS OUT FOR MY JOB.
HE WANTS TO BE NUMBER ONE.
WELL, I'LL PROVE TO TWILIGHT
THAT I DESERVE TO BE NUMBER ONE,
NOT FREAKY FEATHERS OVER THERE.
I WON'T LET HIM HAVE MY JOB
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO!
[ BLOP! ]
OH, WHAT A FANTASTICAL,
FLUFFALICIOUS,
FEATHERY, LITTLE FRIEND!
I'M HOO-KED!
[ LAUGHTER ]
HE'S JUST WONDERFUL.
[ Mockingly ]
"HE'S JUST WONDERFUL!"
[ POINK! ]
UH, YES, WONDERFUL.
HE IS QUITE...
THE CHARMER.
AND ALOYSIUS,
YOU'RE SUCH A STAR.
I JUST HAD TO MAKE
THIS LITTLE BOW FOR YOU.
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
UGH!
[ SLAM! ]
WHAT'S HE ALL
SADDLE-SORE ABOUT?
HE'S PROBABLY JUST JEALOUS
OF ALOYSIUS.
MAYBE SPIKE FEELS THREATENED
OR WORRIED
THAT ALOYSIUS WILL REPLACE HIM.
REPLACE HIM?
HA! THAT'S CRAZY.
SPIKE KNOWS
HE CAN'T BE REPLACED.
THEY'RE TRYING TO REPLACE ME!
I BETTER STEP IT UP
AND MAKE SURE
THAT TWILIGHT AND ALOYSIUS KNOW
THAT I'M STILL NUMBER ONE!
[ POINK! ]
HEY, SPIKE, CAN YOU FETCH ME
THAT BOOK CALLED
"TWO HEADED MYTH--"
"MYTHOLOGICAL MYSTERIES"!
I KNOW WHERE IT IS.
[ POINK! ]
Twilight Sparkle:
THANKS, ALOYSIUS.
HEY, SPIKE, NO WORRIES.
ALOYSIUS FLEW UP
AND GOT THE BOOK FOR ME.
O-M-G, I GUESS I NEED
"FERRETS OF FAIRYLAND," TOO.
[ YOINK! ]
Spike: HEY!
WHOA! WHOA!
CLIMB DOWN FROM THERE
BEFORE YOU FALL.
Spike: WHOA!
[ CRASH! ]
UGH!
[ SNAP! ]
SHOOT!
[ ZIP! ]
YES, SIR!
MY LAST WRITING QUILL --
IT'S BROKEN.
NEVER FEAR. SPIKE, YOUR
NUMBER-ONE ASSISTANT, IS HERE!
[ ZIP! ]
QUILL, QUILL.
WHERE IS IT?
NOT HERE.
QUILL...
[ WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! ]
QUILL. WHERE IS IT?!
HOO.
[ YOINK! ]
WHERE AM I GONNA
GET A QUILL?
SPIKE! WAIT! WAIT!
BUT THE STORE IS CALLED
"QUILLS AND SOFAS."
YOU ONLY SELL TWO THINGS!
SORRY, JUNIOR. ALL OUT OF QUILLS
UNTIL MONDAY.
NEED A SOFA?
UGH!
I SWORE I HAD ONE
HERE SOMEWHERE.
AH! HERE IT IS.
A QUINCE!
NOT A QUINCE.
A QUILL!
RIGHT! A QUAIL?
[ FLUTTER! ]
A QUILT!
A QUESADILLA?
UGH.
AHA! A QUICHE.
NOT A QUICHE. A QUILL!
NOPE, SORRY.
ALL OUT OF QUILLS.
AW, SHOOT.
[ CLUCKING ]
COME ON, CHICKEN!
HERE, CHICKY, CHICKY, CHICKY!
HERE, CHICK, CHICK,
CHICK, CHICKY!
COME HERE!
[ BANG! ]
UNH!
[ CLUCKING ]
COME HERE!
NO! WAIT! NO! WAIT!
STOP! QUIT IT!
[ DING! ]
[ Panting ] SPIKE...
TO THE RESCUE!
[ WARBLE! ]
Twilight Sparkle:
OH. SPIKE.
I WAS CALLING OUT FOR YOU
WHEN YOU WERE TURNING
THIS PLACE UPSIDE DOWN.
ALOYSIUS GAVE ME ONE OF HIS
FEATHERS TO USE AS A QUILL.
[ POINK! ]
THAT'S JUST GREAT.
PERFECT!
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
SWEET!
I THINK I'LL JUST, UH, FINISH UP
THE REST OF MY CHORES.
OR DID ALOYSIUS
ALREADY DO THEM?
OH, NO, NO.
THERE ARE QUITE A LOT OF THEM.
WELL, THAT'S FINE
BECAUSE I CAN JUST STAY UP
ALL NIGHT AND FINISH --
[ SNORING ]
POOR SPIKE.
HE'LL COME AROUND.
HE'S GENUINELY
A GOOD, LITTLE GUY.
[ SLAM! ]
HUH?
Twilight Sparkle:
SPIKE, WHAT IS THIS?
YOU SAID
THIS BOOK WAS MISSING.
WELL, ALOYSIUS FOUND IT
RIGHT WHERE IT BELONGS,
BUT LIKE THIS.
HOW DID IT GET THIS WAY?
UH, WELL, UM, YOU SEE,
I-I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT YOU, AND, UH --
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
A DRAGON SNEEZE?
I'VE SEEN A DRAGON LIE.
I'M VERY DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU, SPIKE.
YOU SET ME UP!
WELL, TWO CAN PLAY
THAT GAME.
HOO!
NOT "HOO." TWO!
UGH!
ALOYSIUS IS OUT
TO TAKE MY PLACE.
I JUST KNOW IT!
I'VE GOT TO STOP HIM. BUT HOW?
[ MOUSE SQUEAKING ]
AHHHHH.
[ ZIP! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
COME ALONG, OPAL.
LET'S HURRY UP AND GET
TO FLUTTERSHY'S TEA PARTY.
[ POINK! ]
[ PITTER! PITTER! PITTER! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ PLING! ]
SO LIFELIKE.
AND WHEN TWILIGHT DISCOVERS
IT SHREDDED UP ON HER FLOOR,
SHE'LL THINK MOUSE-EATING
ALOYSIUS IS TO BLAME,
AND I'LL BE NUMBER ONE AGAIN!
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
[ PITTER! PITTER! PITTER! ]
[ SPROING! SNAP! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ WHOOSH! BOING! ]
[ WHIP! ]
[ PITTER! PITTER! PITTER! ]
[ YOINK! ]
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ SMASH! ZIP! ]
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
[ ZIP! ]
THAT POOR LITTLE
FIELD MOUSE --
TORN TO PIECES!
IT MUST HAVE BEEN ALOYSIUS!
YOU KNOW, SINCE OWLS EAT,
YOU KNOW, MICE.
WHAT A TERRIBLE,
TERRIBLE BIRD!
HE MUST BE PUNISHED!
RIGHT?
SPIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT UPSETS ME MORE --
THAT YOU DELIBERATELY TRIED
TO SET UP ALOYSIUS
OR THAT
YOU ACTUALLY THOUGHT
THIS PATHETIC ATTEMPT
WOULD WORK.
YOU'VE LET YOUR JEALOUSY
GET THE BEST OF YOU, SPIKE.
I AM TRULY DISAPPOINTED.
THIS IS NOT THE SPIKE
I KNOW AND LOVE!
[ CREEEAK! ]
SHE --
SHE DOESN'T LOVE ME ANYMORE.
[ BLINK! BLINK! BLINK! ]
TWILIGHT HATES ME.
AND I'M COLD, HUNGRY,
TIRED, AND LONELY.
COULD IT GET ANY WORSE?
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
[ GASPS ]
I GUESS THAT'S A "YES."
[ POINK! ]
[ Echoing ] HELLO?
HELLO?!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
WHAT IS THAT?!
[ TWINKLING ]
WOW! IF THIS IS WHAT
RUNNING AWAY IS ALL ABOUT,
I NEVER WANT TO GO HOME!
[ ZIP! ]
GEMS! MMM! WHOO-HOO!
[ CHOMP! CHOMP! ]
[ HICCUPS ]
[ GROANS ]
EVEN IF MY TUMMY'S FULL,
THE REST OF ME IS STILL EMPTY.
I MISS TWILIGHT
AND THE PONY GANG.
BUT SHE DOESN'T LOVE ME ANYMORE,
SO I'M BETTER OFF HERE --
ALL BY MYSELF.
WOW, IT SEEMS
TO BE GETTING WARMER.
THIS STEAM IS GREAT
FOR MY COMPLEXION,
BUT IT'S SURE GETTING HOT
IN HERE.
[ RUMBLING ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY CAVE?
AND WHY ARE YOU EATING
MY GEMS?
[ PTOO! ]
UH, HEY, ABOO.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THIS WAS YOUR CAVE.
AND I DIDN'T KNOW
THESE WERE YOUR GEMS,
BUT WE'RE COOL, RIGHT?
[ GROWLING ]
WHOA, WHOA!
HEY, UH, WE'RE LIKE BROTHERS,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YOU'RE A DRAGON
AND I'M A DRAGON.
IT'S US AGAINST THE WORLD,
RIGHT?
[ GROWLS ]
AAH!
UH, YOU DON'T SCARE ME!
SO YOU'RE BIG.
[ GROWLING ]
REALLY BIG.
[ SHING! ]
AND YOUR CLAWS
ARE SUPER SHARP.
TAIL...
[ SHING! ]
...EXTRA SPIKY.
BUT, UH,
YOU DON'T SCARE ME!
HA!
[ FIZZLE! ]
HOW'D YOU LIKE THAT?
[ ROARS ]
UH, I'D LOVE TO STAY,
BUT GOT TO GO!
SEE YA!
WOULDN'T WANT TO BE YA!
[ ROARING ]
AAH!
[ SCREECH! ]
[ SNARLING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
Aloysius: HOO! HOO!
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ SNARLS ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ BOINK! ]
SPIKE, OVER HERE!
AM I GLAD TO SEE YOU!
HURRY! HOP ON!
[ ROARING ]
IT'S TOO DARK!
I CAN'T SEE!
HOO! HOO, HOO!
[ ROARING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ SCREECH! ]
[ PANTING ]
SPIKE, WE WERE
SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I WAS SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU!
WHY DID YOU RUN AWAY?
I THOUGHT
YOU DIDN'T NEED ME ANYMORE
AND THAT YOU DIDN'T
LOVE ME ANYMORE.
SPIKE,
SURE, I WAS DISAPPOINTED,
BUT YOU ARE
MY NUMBER-ONE ASSISTANT
AND FRIEND,
AND YOU ALWAYS WILL BE.
IT'S JUST THAT SOMETIMES
I NEED SOME HELP AT NIGHT.
I CAN'T ASK YOU
TO STAY UP LATE.
YOU'RE A BABY DRAGON,
AND YOU NEED YOUR REST.
OWLS ARE NOCTURNAL,
SO I ASKED ALOYSIUS TO HELP,
BUT NOT TO TAKE YOUR PLACE.
NO ONE COULD
EVER REPLACE YOU, SPIKE,
NOT EVEN WHEN YOU ARE BEING
A JEALOUS NUMBSKULL.
I'M SORRY, TWILIGHT.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
BEEN SO JEALOUS.
AND I'M SORRY, TOO, SPIKE.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
MORE SENSITIVE.
AND, ALOYSIUS, I KNOW NOW THAT
YOU WEREN'T OUT TO TAKE MY JOB.
FORGIVE ME?
HOO?
ME. FORGIVE ME -- SPIKE.
HOO!
[ CHUCKLES ]
HE FORGIVES YOU, SPIKE.
HEY, HOW DID YOU GUYS KNOW
WHERE I WAS?
IT WAS YOUR
KETCHUP-COVERED FEET.
ALOYSIUS DISCOVERED
YOUR FOOTPRINTS,
AND WE FOLLOWED THEM
ALL THE WAY TO THE CAVE.
OH, YEAH, THE KETCHUP.
IT LOOKED PRETTY REAL, THOUGH,
DIDN'T IT?
UH...
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
I KNOW PRINCESS CELESTIA
WILL WANT TO READ ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY.
I'M READY WHEN YOU ARE.
[ DING! ]
HEY, SPIKE, WHY DON'T YOU
WRITE TO PRINCESS CELESTIA
AND TELL HER
WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED?
REALLY?
WHY, THAT'S
A BIG RESPONSIBILITY.
I KNOW.
BUT NOTHING MY NUMBER-ONE
ASSISTANT CAN'T HANDLE.
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA...
"THIS IS SPIKE WRITING TO YOU
ABOUT MY ADVENTURES.
"THIS WEEK, I LEARNED THAT
BEING JEALOUS AND TELLING LIES
"GETS YOU NOWHERE
IN FRIENDSHIP.
"I ALSO LEARNED
"THAT THERE'S PLENTY OF LOVE
FOR EVERY FRIEND TO SHARE.
SO FROM HERE ON OUT, I PROMISE
THAT I, SPIKE, WILL --"
[ THUD ]
[ SNORING ]
[ POINK! ]
OH, SPIKE.
HOO?
[ POINK! ]
"WHO?"
SPIKE. YOU KN--
OHHHH! [ CHUCKLES ]
[ TINK! ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS