[ BELL RINGING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
LET'S QUIET DOWN, PLEASE.
WE HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT LESSON
TO GET TO.
THANK YOU.
TODAY, WE ARE GOING TO BE
TALKING ABOUT CUTIE MARKS.
BORING.
YOU CAN ALL SEE MY CUTIE MARK,
CAN'T YOU?
LIKE ALL PONIES,
I WASN'T BORN WITH A CUTIE MARK.
MY FLANK WAS BLANK.
AWW...
SHE'S SO PRECIOUS.
THEN ONE DAY
WHEN I WAS ABOUT YOUR AGE,
I WOKE UP TO FIND
THAT A CUTIE MARK HAD APPEARED.
Pony:
LOOK AT HER HAIR!
[ LAUGHTER ]
YES, I KNOW, BUT, HONESTLY,
THAT'S HOW EVERYPONY WAS WEARING
THEIR MANE BACK THEN.
I HAD DECIDED TO BECOME
A TEACHER,
AND THE FLOWERS
SYMBOLIZE MY HOPE
THAT I COULD HELP
MY FUTURE STUDENTS BLOOM
IF I NURTURED THEM
WITH KNOWLEDGE.
THE SMILES REPRESENTED
THE CHEER I HOPED TO BRING
TO MY LITTLE PONIES
WHILE THEY WERE LEARNING.
NOW, CAN ANYONE TELL ME WHEN A
PONY GETS HIS OR HER CUTIE MARK?
OH! OH! OH!
WHEN SHE DISCOVERS
THAT CERTAIN SOMETHING
THAT MAKES HER SPECIAL.
THAT'S RIGHT, TWIST.
A CUTIE MARK
APPEARS ON A PONY'S FLANK
WHEN HE OR SHE FINDS
THAT CERTAIN SOMETHING
THAT MAKES THEM DIFFERENT
FROM EVERY OTHER PONY.
DISCOVERING
WHAT MAKES YOU UNIQUE
ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENS OVERNIGHT.
PSST!
AND NO AMOUNT OF HOPING,
WISHING, OR BEGGING...
PSST!
...WILL MAKE A CUTIE MARK APPEAR
BEFORE ITS TIME.
PSST!
WHAT?!
APPLE BLOOM!
ARE YOU PASSING A NOTE?
UH...UM...
WHAT COULD BE SO IMPORTANT
THAT IT COULDN'T WAIT
UNTIL AFTER CLASS?
[ GASPS ]
IT'S BLANK.
[ LAUGHS ]
REMIND YOU
OF ANYPONY?
[ LAUGHTER ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
WANT SOMETHING SWEET?
I'VE GOT
SOME PEPPERMINT STICKS.
I MADE THEM MYSELF.
MNH-MNH.
THEY'LL MAKE YOU SMILE.
NO.
I DON'T KNOW WHY WE HAD TO
SIT THROUGH A LECTURE
ABOUT GETTING A CUTIE MARK.
I MEAN, WAITING
FOR YOUR CUTIE MARK
IS SO LAST WEEK.
YOU'VE GOT YOURS.
I JUST GOT MINE.
WE ALL HAVE THEM ALREADY.
[ GASPS ]
I MEAN, ALMOST ALL OF US
HAVE THEM ALREADY.
DON'T WORRY, YOU TWO,
YOU'RE STILL TOTALLY INVITED
TO MY CUTE-CEAÑERA THIS WEEKEND.
IT'S GOING TO BE
AMAZING.
IT'S A PARTY CELEBRATING ME
AND MY FANTASTIC CUTIE MARK.
HOW CAN IT NOT BE?
BUMP, BUMP,
SUGAR LUMP, RUMP!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
GIVE ME A BREAK.
SEE YOU
THIS WEEKEND...
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
Both:
...BLANK FLANKS!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
IT'S NOT FAIR!
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR!
DON'T GET YOUR MANE
IN A TANGLE.
YOU'LL GET YOUR CUTIE MARK.
EVERYPONY GETS ONE
EVENTUALLY.
BUT I DON'T WANT ONE
I WANT ONE RIGHT NOW!
I CAN'T GO TO DIAMOND TIARA'S
CUTE-CEAÑERA WITHOUT ONE.
I JUST CAN'T!
'COURSE YOU CAN.
YOU KNOW, I WAS THE LAST PONY
IN MY CLASS TO GET A CUTIE MARK,
AND I COULDN'T BE PROUDER
OF IT.
I KNEW MY FUTURE
WAS TO RUN SWEET APPLE ACRES,
AND THESE BRIGHT, SHINY APPLES
SEALED THE DEAL.
[ GASPS ]
COME TO THINK OF IT,
GRANNY SMITH WAS THE LAST ONE
IN HER CLASS, TOO.
HUH.
SAME WITH BIG McINTOSH.
I REALLY DON'T SEE HOW THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
IT PROBABLY MEANS THAT BEING
THE LAST ONE IN YOUR CLASS
TO GET A CUTIE MARK
RUNS IN THE FAMILY.
"RUNS IN THE FAMILY"?
"RUNS IN THE FAMILY"!
YOU'VE GOT APPLES
FOR YOUR CUTIE MARK.
GRANNY SMITH
HAS AN APPLE PIE.
BIG McINTOSH
HAS AN APPLE HALF.
MY UNIQUE TALENT MUST HAVE
SOMETHING TO DO WITH APPLES!
APPLES, APPLES, APPLES!
[ CRASH! ]
[ SIGHS ]
APPLES.
GET YOUR DELICIOUS,
NUTRITIOUS APPLES HERE.
DELICIOUS AND NUTRITIOUS
AND SO MANY USES.
[ CHOMP! ]
YOU CAN EAT 'EM,
PLAY WITH 'EM...
[ CRASH! ]
Pony:
HEY! WATCH IT!
...CREATE FINE ART
FOR YOUR HOME WITH 'EM.
YOU'D HAVE TO BE CRAZY NOT TO
GET A BUSHEL OF YOUR VERY OWN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SHE'S SO CREATIVE.
YOU, SIR!
CARE TO BUY
SOME APPLES?
UH, NO, THANKS.
WHY NOT?
I HAVE PLENTY AT HOME.
ARE YOU SURE?
YES, I'M PRETTY SURE.
YOU'RE PRETTY SURE,
BUT YOU'RE NOT ABSOLUTELY,
POSITIVELY,
COMPLETELY, SUPERDUPER SURE,
ARE YOU?
UH, IF I BUY SOME APPLES,
WILL YOU PLEASE LEAVE ME ALONE?
ALL RIGHT!
YOU FORGOT YOUR CHANGE!
Apple Bloom:
WHOO-HOO!
THERE'S HOW YOU SELL SOME APPLES
AND GET A CUTIE MARK.
SO, WHAT DOES MY CUTIE MARK
LOOK LIKE --
A SHOPPING BAG
FULL OF APPLES?
A SATISFIED CUSTOMER
EATING AN APPLE?
HMM.
MAYBE I GOT TO INCREASE
MY SALES FIGURES FIRST.
YOU TOUCH IT,
YOU BUY IT!
WE TAKE CASH OR CREDIT.
I'M SORRY, MA'AM.
MA'AM!
[ SIGHS ]
NOW, APPLE BLOOM,
YOU CAN'T JUST...
THAT'LL BE FOUR BITS.
I DIDN'T PUT THOSE
IN MY BAG.
LIKELY STORY.
FOUR BITS, LADY.
APPLE BLOOM!
I AM REALLY, REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
SHE'S NEW.
HERE. TAKE THESE.
NO CHARGE.
AND THESE.
[ GRUNTS ]
Y'ALL COME BACK NOW,
YOU HEAR?
WHAT?
SORRY, LITTLE SIS, BUT YOUR
APPLE-SELLING DAYS ARE OVER.
WHAT?!
BUT HOW ELSE AM I GONNA GET
MY CUTIE MARK?
HOME. NOW!
PBHT!
HMPH.
[ SIGHS ]
LISTEN, SUGAR CUBE,
I KNOW IT'S HARD TO WAIT
FOR YOUR VERY OWN CUTIE MARK,
BUT YOU JUST CAN'T
FORCE IT.
BESIDES, YOU'RE NOT
THAT GROWN UP JUST YET.
AIN'T THERE OTHER FILLIES
IN YOUR CLASS WITHOUT ONE?
WELL, TWIST
DOESN'T HAVE HERS YET.
DO YOU THINK
YOU'D FEEL BETTER
IF YOU WENT TO THE PARTY
WITH HER?
MM-HMM.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
BET YOU AND TWIST WOULD HAVE
A GREAT TIME TOGETHER.
NOW, RUN ALONG
AND FIND YOUR FRIEND.
YOU'RE SURE YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO STICK AROUND
TILL THE END OF THE MARKET?
HEY, WHO'S BEEN USING
MY RACKET?!
YEAH, I'M SURE.
OH, WHAT'S UP,
APPLE BLOOM?
SO, I WAS THINKING.
MAYBE WE COULD GO TO DIAMOND
TIARA'S CUTE-CEAÑERA TOGETHER.
I-I DON'T HAVE
A CUTIE MARK.
YOU DON'T HAVE
WELL, UM...
[ LOCK UNLATCHES ]
[ GASPS ]
ISN'T MY CUTIE MARK
SWELL?
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED
MAKING MY OWN SAVORY SWEETS,
BUT IT TOOK ME SOME TIME
TO DISCOVER
THAT IT WAS
MY SUPER-SPECIAL TALENT.
PRETTY SWEET, HUH?
YEAH.
PRETTY...SWEET.
HEY...
THIS DOESN'T MEAN WE CAN'T GO
TO THE CUTE-CEAÑERA TOGETHER.
YOU'RE STILL GONNA COME
TO THE PARTY, AREN'T YOU?
OF COURSE SHE WILL.
IT'S NOT LIKE BEING THE ONLY
PONY THERE WITHOUT A CUTIE MARK
WILL BE, LIKE, THE MOST
EMBARRASSING THING EVER.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
WHOA.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEPONY'S GOT A DARK
CLOUD HANGING OVER HER HEAD.
LET ME DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
KID?
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ Rapidly ] THERE'S
A CUTE-CEAÑERA THIS AFTERNOON,
AND EVERYPONY IN MY CLASS
WILL BE THERE,
AND THEY'LL ALL HAVE
THEIR CUTIE MARKS,
AND I WANT TO GET MY
CUTIE MARK, BUT I'M NO
GOOD AT SELLING APPLES,
BUT I REALLY
WANT TO GO TO THE PARTY,
BUT HOW COULD I GO TO
THE PARTY IF I DON'T
HAVE MY CUTIE MARK,
WHICH MY BIG SISTER SAYS
I'M GONNA GET EVENTUALLY,
[ Deliberately ]
BUT I WANT IT NOW!
CUTIE MARK?
I CAN GET YOU A CUTIE MARK
LIKE THAT.
APPLEJACK SAYS THESE THINGS
TAKE TIME.
I HAVE TO JUST WAIT FOR IT
TO HAPPEN.
WHY WAIT FOR SOMETHING TO HAPPEN
WHEN YOU CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN?
BUT APPLEJACK
SAYS THAT --
HEY, WHO ARE YOU
GONNA LISTEN TO --
APPLEJACK OR THE PONY
WHO WAS FIRST IN HER CLASS
TO GET A CUTIE MARK?
I ALWAYS LIKED FLYING
AND ALL,
BUT I WAS GOING NOWHERE
IN A HURRY.
IT WASN'T UNTIL
MY VERY FIRST RACE
THAT I DISCOVERED
A SERIOUS NEED FOR SPEED,
AND -- KAZAAM! --
THIS SWEET BABY APPEARED
AS FAST AS LIGHTNING.
[ GRUNTING ]
THAT'S RIGHT.
STRETCH OUT THOSE LEGS.
GOT TO BE
NICE AND LOOSE.
THE KEY HERE IS TO TRY
AS MANY THINGS AS POSSIBLE
AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
ONE OF THEM IS BOUND TO LEAD
TO YOUR CUTIE MARK.
ARE YOU READY?
I'M READY!
I SAID,
ARE YOU READY?!
I'M READY!
JUGGLING -- GO!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
UHH!
HANG GLIDING -- GO!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
WHOA! UNH!
KARATE -- GO!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
HYAH!
[ THUD! ]
KITE FLYING -- GO!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
ULTRA PONY
ROLLER DERBY -- GO!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ GROWLING ]
WHA! WHOA!
[ SCREECH! ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ WHEELS SQUEAKING ]
TRIED THAT ONE.
[ BOTH GIGGLING ]
YOUR NEW OUTFIT IS, LIKE,
PERFECT FOR THE PARTY.
Diamond Tiara:
I KNOW.
[ GASPS ]
IT TOTALLY SHOWS OFF
MY NEW CUTIE MARK.
I LOVE BEING SPECIAL.
CAN YOU IMAGINE HOW EMBARRASSING
IT MUST BE TO BE...
NOT SPECIAL?
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO, LIKE,
THINK ABOUT IT.
TRIED THAT ONE.
[ GROANS ]
I'M DOOMED -- DOOMED!
I'LL NEVER FIND SOMETHING
I'M GOOD AT!
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'D BE GOOD
AT EATING CUPCAKES.
EATING CUPCAKES?
EATING CUPCAKES!
I REALLY APPRECIATE
ALL YOUR HELP, RAINBOW DASH.
YOU'RE A REALLY GREAT COACH,
AND I'VE REALLY
LEARNED A LOT FROM YOU,
AND I'M SURE
I CAN LEARN A LOT MORE,
BUT I'VE GOT
SOME CUPCAKES TO EAT!
SEE YOU
AT THE CUTE-CEAÑERA!
HOLD ON, PINKIE PIE,
I'M COMING!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DIDN'T THINK OF THIS --
A CUPCAKE-EATING
CUTIE MARK.
IT'S SO OBVIOUS.
NOW,
WHERE ARE THOSE CUPCAKES?
I'M READY TO CHOW DOWN!
I DON'T HAVE
ANY CUPCAKES.
OH.
[ GASPS ]
BUT YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'D BE GOOD
AT HELPING ME MAKE SOME!
I GUESS A MAKING-CUPCAKES
CUTIE MARK COULD WORK, TOO.
* ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS TAKE A CUP OF FLOUR *
* ADD IT TO THE MIX
* NOW JUST TAKE A LITTLE
SOMETHING SWEET, NOT SOUR *
* A BIT OF SALT,
JUST A PINCH *
* BAKING THESE TREATS
IS SUCH A CINCH *
* ADD A TEASPOON OF VANILLA
* ADD A LITTLE MORE,
AND YOU COUNT TO FOUR, *
* AND YOU NEVER GET
YOUR FILL-A *
* CUPCAKES,
SO SWEET AND TASTY *
DON'T BE TOO HASTY *
* CUPCAKES,
CUPCAKES, CUPCAKES, CUPCAKES! *
[ MIXER WHIRRING ]
[ SMOKE HISSES ]
[ COUGHS ]
[ SIZZLING ]
HOT! HOT! HOT!
OOH! THOSE LOOK MUCH BETTER
THAN THE LAST BATCH.
[ MUNCHING ]
YUCK!
GUESS I'M NOT CUT OUT TO BE
A BAKER, EITHER.
I JUST HAVE TO FACE IT.
I'M GONNA HAVE
A BLANK FLANK FOREVER!
WHAT ABOUT THAT?
WHAT ABOUT WHAT?
IS THERE SOMETHING
ON MY FLANK?
IS THERE? IS THERE?
IS THERE?
[ GASPS ]
A CUTIE MARK!
IT'S A...
A MEASURING CUP? NO.
A MIXING BOWL? NO.
ARE THOSE CUPCAKES?
A TOWER OF CUPCAKES, MAYBE.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
FLOUR! IT'S FLOUR!
YAY!
I GUESSED IT!
WHAT GAME
DO YOU WANT TO PLAY NEXT?
PLEASE SAY BINGO.
WHOA! WHAT'S BEEN
GOING ON IN HERE?
WE'VE BEEN MAKING CUPCAKES.
WANT TO TRY ONE?
NO, THANK YOU,
NOT THAT THEY DON'T LOOK
[SIGHS] DELICIOUS.
TWILIGHT,
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
TIARA'S CUTE-CEAÑERA IS
TODAY, AND EVERYPONY IN
MY CLASS WILL BE THERE,
AND THEY ALL HAVE
THEIR CUTIE MARKS,
AND I WANT TO GET MY CUTIE MARK,
BUT I'M NO GOOD AT SELLING
APPLES OR HANG-GLIDING
OR MAKING CUPCAKES,
BUT I WANT TO GO TO THE PARTY,
BUT HOW CAN I GO TO THE PARTY
IF I DON'T HAVE MY CUTIE MARK,
WHICH PINKIE PIE SAYS
I CAN'T JUST MAKE APPEAR,
BUT I NEED IT TO APPEAR
[Deliberately]
RIGHT NOW!
UH...I DON'T FOLLOW.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
YOU CAN USE YOUR MAGIC
TO MAKE MY CUTIE MARK APPEAR.
OH, NO, APPLE BLOOM.
A CUTIE MARK IS SOMETHING
THAT A PONY HAS TO DISCOVER
FOR HERSELF.
PLEASE, TWILIGHT,
JUST TRY.
I'M SORRY, BUT --
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT!
OH, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
[ TINKLING ]
YES!
I KNEW YOU COULD DO...IT.
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE,
BUT I TOLD YOU.
TRY AGAIN!
[ SIGHS ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ GASPS ]
TOLD YOU
THAT NOT EVEN MAGIC
CAN MAKE A CUTIE MARK APPEAR
BEFORE ITS TIME.
IT'S HOPELESS --
HOPELESS!
I JUST WON'T GO
TO THE PARTY.
I CAN'T GO.
EVERYONE
WILL JUST LAUGH AT ME
AND MAKE FUN OF ME
AND CALL ME NAMES.
IT WILL BE THE WORST NIGHT
OF MY LIFE.
I'M SURE IT WON'T BE
AS BAD AS ALL THAT.
FORGET IT.
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GOING TO THAT...
[ GULPS ]
...PARTY.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
HOW COULD I HAVE FORGOTTEN
THE TIME?
PINKIE PIE
WAS HOSTING THE PARTY?
HOW COULD I HAVE FORGOTTEN
IT WAS AT SUGAR CUBE CORNER?
DON'T FORGET YOUR PARTY HAT,
FORGETTY FORGETERSON.
I HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE ANYPONY SEES ME.
Diamond Tiara: HEY!
IT'S MY CUTE-CEAÑERA!
I'M SUPPOSED TO GET
THE FIRST BITE OF CAKE!
[ POPPING LOUDLY ]
OKAY, APPLE BLOOM,
ALMOST THERE.
[ PITTER! ]
[ SLURPS ]
APPLE BLOOM,
YOU MADE IT!
AFTER I HEARD ABOUT TWIST,
I WAS AFRAID
YOU WOULDN'T SHOW UP.
I SURE AM GLAD
YOU CAME TO YOUR SENSES
ABOUT THIS WHOLE
CUTIE-MARK THING.
THESE THINGS HAPPEN WHEN THESE
THINGS ARE SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
TRYING TO RUSH IT
WILL JUST DRIVE YOU CRAZY.
I'LL LET YOU BE.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR FRIENDS
WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
[ GRUNTS ]
WELL, WELL, WELL,
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
NICE OUTFIT.
JUST SOMETHING I, UH,
PULLED TOGETHER LAST MINUTE.
I REALLY SHOWS OFF
YOUR CUTIE MARK.
OH, WAIT. THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE ONE.
I HAVE A CUTIE MARK.
WHAT? SINCE WHEN?
SINCE, UM, EARLIER TODAY.
OH, REALLY?
LET'S SEE IT.
I-I SHOULDN'T.
I-I COULDN'T.
MY CUTIE MARK
IS SO UNBELIEVABLY AMAZING.
I'M AFRAID
THAT IF I SHOW IT OFF,
EVERYONE WILL START PAYING
ATTENTION TO ME INSTEAD OF YOU.
OUTSHINED AT YOUR OWN
CUTE-CEAÑERA?
CAN YOU IMAGINE
HOW EMBARRASSING THAT WOULD BE?
UH, FORGET IT.
I DIDN'T REALLY
WANT TO SEE IT ANYWAY.
OKAY.
WELL, I'M GONNA GO MINGLE.
ENJOY YOUR PARTY.
[ SIGHS ]
[ RECORD SCRATCHES ]
[ ALL GASP ]
OH, NO!
[ LAUGHS ]
WOW!
THAT IS AN AMAZING
CUTIE MARK.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
NICE TRY...
BLANK FLANK!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
[ SCATTERED LAUGHTER ]
BLANK FLANK.
DOES ONE OF YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH BLANK FLANKS?
[ ALL GASP ]
I SAID, YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH BLANK FLANKS?
THE PROBLEM IS, I MEAN, SHE'S,
LIKE, TOTALLY NOT SPECIAL.
NO, IT MEANS
SHE'S FULL OF POTENTIAL.
IT MEANS SHE COULD BE GREAT
AT ANYTHING.
THE POSSIBILITIES
ARE, LIKE, ENDLESS.
SHE COULD BE A GREAT SCIENTIST
OR AN AMAZING ARTIST
OR A FAMOUS WRITER.
SHE COULD EVEN BE MAYOR
OF PONYVILLE SOMEDAY.
AND SHE'S NOT STUCK
BEING STUCK-UP LIKE YOU TWO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
HEY!
THIS IS MY PARTY.
WHY ARE TWO ON HER SIDE?
BECAUSE...
[ GASPS ]
YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY CUTIE MARKS, EITHER?!
I THOUGHT
I WAS THE ONLY ONE.
WE THOUGHT
WE WERE THE ONLY TWO.
I, FOR ONE, THINK YOU ARE THREE
VERY LUCKY FILLIES.
LUCKY?
HOW CAN THEY BE LUCKY?
THEY STILL GET TO EXPERIENCE
THE THRILL
OF DISCOVERING WHO THEY ARE
AND WHAT THEY'RE MEANT TO BE.
AND THEY'VE GOT ALL THE TIME
IN THE WORLD TO FIGURE IT OUT,
NOT JUST AN AFTERNOON.
[ INDISTINCT AGREEING ]
WOW! APPLE BLOOM!
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN BE ANYTHING?
I WISH
I COULD BE A SCIENTIST!
MAYBE I GOT MY CUTIE MARK
TOO SOON.
HEY,
WHAT'S EVERYPONY DOING?
THIS IS MY PARTY.
EVERYPONY IS SUPPOSED TO BE
PAYING ATTENTION TO ME!
WHATEVER.
WE STILL THINK YOU'RE LOSERS,
RIGHT, DIAMOND TIARA?
BUMP, BUMP,
SUGAR...RUMP?
NOT NOW, SILVER SPOON.
NAME'S SCOOTALOO.
AND I'M SWEETIE BELLE.
APPLE BLOOM.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
THIS SONG IS SO SUPER!
[ GLASSES CLINK ]
[ SLURPING ]
SO, I WAS THINKING,
NOW THAT WE'RE FRIENDS --
I MEAN,
WE ARE FRIENDS, RIGHT?
HOW COULD WE NOT BE?
WE'RE TOTALLY ALIKE.
WE DON'T HAVE
CUTIE MARKS,
DIAMOND TIARA AND SILVER SPOON
DRIVE US CRAZY.
TOTALLY CRAZY!
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL,
NOW THAT WE'RE FRIENDS,
WHAT IF THE THREE OF US
WORK TOGETHER
TO FIND OUT WHO WE ARE
AND WHAT WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE?
OOH! OOH!
WE COULD FORM
OUR OWN SECRET SOCIETY.
I'M LIKING THIS IDEA.
A SECRET SOCIETY.
YEAH.
WE'LL NEED A NAME FOR IT,
THOUGH.
THE CUTIE-MARK THREE?
THE CUTE-TASTICALLY
FANTASTICS?
HOW ABOUT...
THE CUTIE-MARK CRUSADERS?
IT'S PERFECT!
THIS IS GONNA BE
SO GREAT!
WE'RE GONNA BE
UNSTOPPABLE!
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE CELEBRATE
WITH SOME OF THESE
DELICIOUS CUPCAKES?
NOT THE CUPCAKES!
TRUST ME.
LET'S SEE IF THERE ARE
ANY COOKIES.
YEAH!
COME ON.
Twilight Sparkle:
"DEAREST PRINCESS CELESTIA,
"I AM HAPPY TO REPORT THAT ONE
OF YOUR YOUNGEST SUBJECTS
"HAS LEARNED A VALUABLE LESSON
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
"SOMETIMES THE THING YOU THINK
WILL CAUSE YOU TO LOSE FRIENDS
AND FEEL LEFT OUT..."
"...CAN ACTUALLY BE THE THING
"THAT HELPS YOU MAKE
YOUR CLOSEST FRIENDS
AND REALIZE HOW SPECIAL
YOU ARE."
HMM.
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS