Pinkie Pie:
HOOF-FIGHTING ACTION OVERLOAD!
SHE WAS LIKE A STUNT SUPERSTAR,
FLYING HIGHER AND HIGHER,
AND THEN RAINBOW DASH
SWOOPED DOWN -- SWOOSH!
AND RIGHT BEFORE
SHE HIT THE GROUND --
SHOOM! --
SHE PULLED UP!
VROOM!
UH-HUH.
AND THEN SHE LOOKED AROUND
AND AROUND,
LIKE WHOO! WHOO! WHOO!
WHOO! WHOO! WHOO! WHOO!
UH-HUH.
[ AIR RUSHING ]
WHEW!
Pinkie Pie:
OH, RAINBOW DASH!
[ GROANS ]
PINKIE PIE? NOT AGAIN.
RAINBOW DASH!
NOT NOW, PINKIE PIE.
BUT -- BUT,
RAINBOW DASH!
I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOMETHING.
BUT --
I SAID, "NOT NOW"!
UNH!
I WAS GONNA TELL YOU
TO LOOK OUT FOR THAT MOUNTAIN.
[ GROANS ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
THIS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
[ PINKIE PIE HUMMING ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING!
BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ BOING! BOING! ]
[ HUMMING CONTINUES ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
HI! I'M LOOKING
FOR RAINBOW DASH.
HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
HI, THERE.
HAVE YOU SEEN RAINBOW DASH?
OKAY.
THANKS, ANYWAY.
TWILIGHT, HAVE YOU SEEN
RAINBOW DASH ANYWHERE?
ISN'T SHE
RIGHT UP THERE?
RAINBOW DASH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
WHEW!
THAT WAS CLOSE.
HI!
AAH!
[ ZOOM! ]
[ BOING! BOING! ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HI, AGAIN!
AAH!
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ BOING! BOING!
BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ PITTER! ]
[ SPITS ]
I NEED A FAVOR, RAINBOW DASH.
AAH!
OH, FORGET IT.
I TOTALLY PROMISE,
IT'LL BE TOTALLY FUN!
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY.
OVER TO THE RIGHT.
NO, NO,
A LITTLE TO THE LEFT.
OH, WAIT,
BACK TO THE RIGHT.
[ CREAK! ]
NOW A LITTLE LEFT-ISH
WHILE STAYING RIGHTLY.
STOP!
HMM.
MAYBE A FEW INCHES
TO THE SOUTH.
NOW A COUPLE CENTIMETERS
NORTH.
OKAY...
ONE MORE SMIDGIMETER
TO THE --
PINKIE PIE!
UH, I MEAN, PERFECT.
NOW WAIT FOR MY SIGNAL.
[ HUMMING ]
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
AAH!
[ HICCUPING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
OH, RAINBOW DASH,
WE STARTLED SPIKE
INTO GETTING THE HICCUPS!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
GOOD ONE, PINKIE [HICCUPS] PIE.
[ HICCUPS ]
YOU'RE ALWAYS PULLING A FAST ONE
[HICCUPS] ON ME.
[ HICCUPS ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
YOU'RE NOT HURT, ARE YOU?
NAH. [ HICCUPS ]
DON'T BE [HICCUPS] SILLY.
DRAGONS ARE [HICCUPS] FIREPROOF.
OH, OKAY.
GOOD.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
[ HICCUPS ]
I WISH THE SAME THING [HICCUPS]
WERE TRUE OF SCROLLS.
[ GASPS ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
[ HICCUPING ]
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ANYTHING
MORE HILARIOUS?
[ LAUGHS ]
I CAN THINK OF ONE THING.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
AAH!
[ HICCUPS, LAUGHS ]
[ HICCUPS ]
I DIDN'T TAKE YOU
FOR A PRANKSTER, PINKIE PIE.
ARE YOU [HICCUPS] KIDDING?
[ HICCUPS ]
I LOVE TO PULL PRANKS.
IT'S ALL [HICCUPS]
IN GOOD FUN,
AND PINKIE PIE LO-- [HICCUPS]
--OVES TO HAVE [HICCUPS] FUN!
[ HICCUPS ]
YOU KNOW, PINKIE PIE, YOU'RE NOT
AS ANNOYING AS I THOUGHT.
[ HICCUPS ]
YOU WANT TO HANG OUT?
THAT'D BE [HICCUPS]
I'D REALLY --
[HICCUPS]
WHEN DO --
I MEAN [HICCUPS]
WHEN WOULD YOU [HICCUPS]
[ HONK! ]
A SIMPLE NOD WILL DO.
MM-HMM.
[ BOING! BOING!
BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
IS SHE EVEN HOME?
I don't know.
This is gonna be gold!
Shh! Shh!
[ LAUGHS ]
There she is!
MMM!
[ SNIFFS ]
AH...AH...AH...
AH-CHOO! AH-CHOO!
AH-AH-CHOO!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
AH-CHOOOO!
HMM?
[ POOF! ]
[ PINKIE PIE AND RAINBOW DASH
LAUGHING ]
[ GASPS ]
LAND SAKES!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
IS SOMEONE OVER THERE?
WHO WE GONNA SQUIRT?
[ SNICKERS ]
FLUTTERSHY.
WHAT?! [ SPITS ]
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WE CAN'T PRANK FLUTTERSHY.
I MEAN,
SHE'S SO SENSITIVE.
IT'LL HURT HER FEELINGS,
EVEN OUR MOST HARMLESS PRANK.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
PBHT! HUH.
WE NEED ANOTHER VICTIM
WHO'S MADE OF TOUGHER STUFF.
SO, WHO'S IT GONNA BE?
OH!
[ LAUGHS ]
I'VE GOT SOMEONE IN MIND.
THE TOUGHEST AROUND.
OH, AWESOME!
WHO? WHO?
DO I KNOW THEM?
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, YES.
YOU'RE VERY CLOSE.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
GOOD ONE, PINKIE PIE.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SWISH! SWOOSH! ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
RIDICULOUS!
[ BOING! WHIFFLE! ]
[ HONK! ]
[ HONK! HONK! HONK! HONK! ]
RISE AND SHINE,
RAINBOW DASH!
IT'S A BRAND-NEW DAY,
AND WE GOT A LOT
OF PRANKING TO --
OOH!
MORNING, PINKS.
GILDA, THIS IS MY GAL PAL
PINKIE PIE.
[ SHRIEKS ]
HEY. WHAT'S UP?
PINKIE, THIS IS
MY GRIFFON FRIEND GILDA.
WHAT'S A GRIFFON?
SHE'S HALF EAGLE,
HALF LION...
AND ALL AWESOME!
[ ROARS ]
[ LAUGHS ] YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
GILDA'S MY BEST FRIEND
FROM MY DAYS
AT JUNIOR SPEEDSTER FLIGHT CAMP.
HEY, REMEMBER THE CHANT?
CHYEAH. THEY MADE US
RECITE IT EVERY MORNING.
I'LL NEVER GET THAT LAME THING
OUT OF MY HEAD.
SO...
[ GROANS ]
ONLY FOR YOU, DASH.
Both: [ Chanting ]
JUNIOR SPEEDSTERS ARE OUR LIVES.
SKY BOMBS, SOARS,
AND DARING DIVES.
JUNIOR SPEEDSTERS,
IT'S OUR QUEST
TO SOMEDAY BE THE VERY BEST.
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, THAT WAS AWESOME!
AND IT GAVE ME A GREAT IDEA
FOR A PRANK.
[ SQUEAK! ]
GILDA, YOU GAME?
HUH.
WELL, I GROOVE ON A GOOD PRANK
AS MUCH AS THE NEXT GRIFFON.
BUT, DASH, YOU PROMISED ME
WE'D GET A FLYING SESSION IN
THIS MORNING.
YEAH, UH, WELL...
PINKIE PIE,
YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU?
GILDA JUST GOT HERE.
WE'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU LATER.
OH, UM...
WELL, SURE -- NO PROBLEM!
HAVE FUN, YOU GUYS.
I'LL, UH, JUST CATCH UP
WITH YOU...
[ SIGHS ]
...LATER.
[ HONKS SADLY ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
WHOA! THAT WAS SWEET!
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES.
YEAH, ONLY FASTER!
SO, NOW WHAT?
HEY, THERE!
HUH?
IT'S LATER!
AND I CAUGHT UP!
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
PINKIE PIE...
YOU ARE SO RANDOM.
HEY, DASH, THINK YOU GOT
ENOUGH GAS LEFT
TO BEAT ME TO THAT CLOUD?
A RACE?
YOU ARE SO ON!
1, 2, 3 -- GO!
HEY!
I WIN!
AS IF!
I WON, DUDE!
NO WAY!
YES WAY!
OH, COME ON!
I WAS WAY AHEAD OF YOU!
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, GEEZ, DREAM ON!
REMEMBER BACK AT CAMP?
THERE IS NO WAY
YOU BEAT ME!
WHATEVER!
WOW, GUYS,
THAT WAS REALLY CLOSE!
BUT I THINK
RAINBOW DASH BEAT YOU
BY A TEENY, WEENY,
ITTY-BITTY HAIR
OR A TEENY, WEENY,
ITTY-BITTY FEATHER.
HA! SEE?
GOOD THING PINKIE PIE'S HERE
TO KEEP YOU HONEST, "G."
OKAY, DASH...
LAST ONE TO THAT CLOUD UP THERE
IS A GNARLY DRAGON EGG.
GO!
I THINK THE HIGH ALTITUDE
IS MAKING YOU DIZZY.
[ POP! POP! POP! POP! POP! ]
WAIT! GUYS!
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
WOW! YOU GUYS ALMOST
GOT AWAY FROM ME THAT TIME!
[ CHOPPER CLUNKING,
SQUEAKING ]
SO, DASH, GOT ANY NEW MOVES
IN YOUR TRICK-TIONARY,
OR ARE YOU
100% OLD-SCHOOL?
NEW MOVES? HA!
SIT BACK, "G."
THIS IS GONNA
TAKE A WHILE.
HEY, PINKIE, COME HERE.
YEAH?
DON'T YOU KNOW HOW TO TAKE
"GET LOST" FOR AN ANSWER?
DASH DOESN'T NEED TO HANG
WITH A DWEEB LIKE YOU
NOW THAT I'M AROUND.
YOU'RE DORKING UP THE SKY,
STINKY PIE.
SO, MAKE LIKE A BEE
AND BUZZ OFF!
AAH! WHOA-OA!
WHOA!
TRY MATCHING THAT!
HEY, WHERE'S PINKIE PIE
AND HER CRAZY CONTRAPTION?
EH, SHE LEFT --
SOMETHING ABOUT BEING
AS BUSY AS A BEE.
[ CHOPPER SQUEAKS ]
HMPH!
SO, PINKIE PIE, ARE YOU SURE
THAT THIS FRIEND OF RAINBOW DASH
IS REALLY SO MEAN?
UM, YEAH!
SHE KEEPS STEALING
RAINBOW DASH AWAY,
SHE POPPED MY BALLOONS,
AND SHE TOLD ME TO BUZZ OFF!
I NEVER MET A GRIFFON
THIS MEAN.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I'VE NEVER MET A GRIFFON AT ALL.
BUT I BET IF I HAD,
SHE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
AS MEAN AND GRUMPY AS GILDA!
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK,
PINKIE PIE?
HMM?
WELL, I THINK...
YOU'RE JEALOUS.
JEALOUS?!
GREEN WITH ENVY --
WELL, IN YOUR CASE,
PINK WITH ENVY.
WELL, YES, JEALOUS.
LISTEN, PINKIE,
I DON'T WANT TO UPSET YOU,
BUT JUST BECAUSE
RAINBOW DASH HAS ANOTHER FRIEND
DOESN'T MAKE GILDA
A GRUMP.
I MEAN, PERHAPS IT'S YOU,
PINKIE,
WHO NEEDS TO IMPROVE
HER ATTITUDE.
IMPROVE MY ATTITUDE?!
BUT I -- BUT IT'S GILDA THAT --
ARE YOU SERI--
[ SHRIEKS ]
[ DOOR OPENS, SLAMS ]
[ SIGHS ]
MAYBE TWILIGHT IS RIGHT.
MAYBE GILDA ISN'T A BIG, MEAN,
GRUMPY, MEAN, MEANY PANTS.
MAYBE I'M JUST A BIG, JEALOUS,
JUDGMENTAL,
JEALOUS, JEALOUSY PANTS.
[ SIGHS ]
[ SLURPING ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ GILDA AND RAINBOW DASH LAUGH ]
Rainbow Dash: THAT WAS SWEET!
[ GRUNTS ]
I GOT TO TAKE CARE OF
A FEW WEATHER JOBS AROUND HERE.
SHOULDN'T TAKE LONG.
JUST, UH, HANG OUT IN TOWN,
AND I'LL COME FIND YOU.
THAT'S COOL, I GUESS.
I'M GONNA GO CHOW DOWN!
LATER!
[ SNIFFS ]
AAH! A RATTLER!
A RATTLER!
RUN FOR THE HILLS!
EVERYBODY, RUN!
SAVE YOURSELVES!
THIS STUFF
AIN'T FRESH, DUDE.
AW, POOR GRANNY SMITH!
SHE DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS A JOKE!
HOW MEAN!
NO, NO.
I CAN'T MISJUDGE HER.
IT WAS KIND OF A FUNNY PRANK,
I GUESS.
[ CRUNCH! ]
[ GASPS ]
I DID MISJUDGE HER!
SHE'S NOT ONLY A MEANY, MEAN
PANTS, SHE'S ALSO A THIEF!
NO, NO, NO, NO.
SHE MIGHT GIVE IT BACK.
IT'S JUST A JOKE.
ALL RIGHT, LITTLE ONES,
THIS WAY, THIS WAY.
MAMA DUCK...
YOU'RE FREE AND CLEAR.
HEY!
PLEASE EXCUSE ME.
I'M WALKING HERE!
OH, UM, I'M SORRY.
I-I-I WAS JUST TRYING TO --
"I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY."
WHY DON'T YOU JUST WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOING, DOOFUS?!
B-B-B-BUT I...
I...
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ ROARS ]
[ CRYING ]
UGH! PLEASE.
ALL THESE LAME PONIES
ARE DRIVING ME BUGGY.
I GOT TO BAIL.
SHE'S A GRUMP AND A THIEF
AND A BULLY --
THE MEANEST KIND
OF MEAN, MEANY PANTS THERE IS!
I CAN TAKE IT, BUT NO ONE
TREATS FLUTTERSHY LIKE THAT!
NO ONE!
THIS CALLS
FOR EXTREME MEASURES,
PINKIE PIE-STYLE!
WELCOME! WELCOME!
WELCOME!
WHO'S THIS GILDA
I'VE HEARD NOTHING ABOUT?
I HEAR SHE'S AN OLD FRIEND
OF RAINBOW DASH.
A GRIFFON --
SO RARE!
YOU'VE MET GILDA, RIGHT?
WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
OH, UM, WELL...
I'LL TELL YOU LATER,
TWILIGHT.
WELCOME! WELCOME!
UM, PINKIE PIE,
ABOUT THIS PARTY FOR GILDA,
UM, DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA?
I MEAN --
DON'T WORRY YOUR PRETTY, LITTLE
HEAD ABOUT MEAN, OLD GILDA.
YOUR AUNTIE PINKIE PIE'S
GOT IT ALL TAKEN CARE OF.
I'M A YEAR
OLDER THAN YOU.
GILDA!
I'M SO HONORED
TO THROW YOU
ONE OF MY SIGNATURE
PINKIE PIE PARTIES,
AND I REALLY, TRULY,
SINCERELY HOPE
YOU FEEL WELCOME HERE
AMONGST ALL US PONY FOLK.
[ ZAP! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, PINKIE PIE,
THE OLD HOOF-SHAKE BUZZER!
YOU ARE A SCREAM!
YEAH.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
GOOD ONE, PINKIE PIE.
COME ON, "G,"
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU
TO SOME OF MY OTHER FRIENDS.
RIGHT BEHIND YOU, DASH!
I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE UP TO.
GREAT!
[ GROANS ]
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLANNING.
[ LAUGHS, SNORTS ]
WELL, I HOPE SO.
THIS WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO BE A SURPRISE PARTY.
I MEAN,
I'VE GOT MY EYE ON YOU.
AND I...GOT MY EYE ON YOU!
EVERYONE, I'D LIKE YOU ALL
TO MEET GILDA,
A LONGTIME, DEAR FRIEND
OF RAINBOW DASH.
LET'S HONOR HER
AND WELCOME HER TO PONYVILLE.
Pony: YAY, GILDA!
WELCOME!
[ INDISTINCT EXCLAMATIONS ]
PLEASE HELP YOURSELF.
VANILLA LEMON DROPS --
DON'T MIND IF I DO.
[ WHIP! ]
[ GULPS ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ GASPING ]
HOT!
"G," THE PUNCH!
[ SIREN WAILING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GULPING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
HUH?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
PEPPER IN THE VANILLA
LEMON DROPS
AND THE PUNCH SERVED
IN A DRIBBLE GLASS!
HA! PRICELESS!
PRICELESS!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GULPS, BREATHING HEAVILY ]
YEAH, HILARIOUS.
HEY, "G," LOOK --
PRESENTS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
SPITTIN' SNAKES.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SOMEPONY PULLED THAT PRANK
ON ME LAST MONTH.
HA, HA.
I BET I KNOW WHO THAT WAS!
YOU DO?
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
CAKE TIME, EVERYPONY!
HEY, CAN I BLOW OUT
THE CANDLES?
WHY DON'T WE LET GILDA
BLOW OUT THE CANDLES, SPIKE?
SHE IS THE GUEST OF HONOR,
AFTER ALL.
UNH!
EXACTLY!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ BLOWS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ BLOWING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
RELIGHTING BIRTHDAY CANDLES --
I LOVE THAT PRANK!
WHAT A CLASSIC!
NOW, I WONDER WHO
COULD HAVE DONE THAT?
YEAH.
I WONDER.
Spike: MMM! MMM!
WHO CARES?
THIS CAKE IS AMAZING!
SPIKE!
WHAT? IT'S GREAT.
TRY SOME.
HEY, "G,"
YOU'RE NOT UPSET
ABOUT SOME SILLY CANDLES,
ARE YOU?
NO WAY, DASH.
LIKE I SAID,
I'M DOWN WITH A GOOD PRANK.
COME ON, THEN.
LET'S HAVE SOME CAKE.
[ SQUEAK! ]
HEY. I'M WATCHING YOU
LIKE A HAWK.
WHY? CAN'T YOU WATCH ME
LIKE A GRIFFON?
Applejack: HEY, Y'ALL.
IT'S PIN THE TAIL ON THE PONY.
LET'S PLAY.
OH, MY FAVORITE GAME!
CAN I GO FIRST?
CAN I HAVE THE PURPLE TAIL?
[ GRUNTS ]
WELL, I AM THE GUEST
OF HONOR.
AND I' HAVE
THE PURPLE TAIL.
YEAH, GILDA SHOULD
DEFINITELY GO FIRST.
LET'S GET YOU
BLINDFOLDED.
HEY, WH-WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?!
[ GRUNTS ]
WE'RE SPINNING YOU
AROUND AND AROUND,
AND THEN YOU CAN PIN THE TAIL
ON THE PONY.
NOW JUST WALK STRAIGHT AHEAD
AND PIN THE TAIL.
"NOW, JUST WALK STRAIGHT AHEAD
AND PIN THE TAIL."
HMPH! YEAH, RIGHT.
THIS IS ANOTHER PRANK, ISN'T IT?
I'M GOING THIS WAY!
WAIT!
THE POSTER IS THIS --
WHOA! AH! AH! AH!
AAH! UNH!
UH, GILDA?
YOU PINNED THE TAIL
ON THE WRONG END.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ ROARS ]
THIS IS YOUR IDEA
OF A GOOD TIME?!
I'VE NEVER MET A LAMER BUNCH
OF DWEEBS IN ALL MY LIFE!
AND, PINKIE PIE...
YOU --
YOU ARE QUEEN LAME-O
WITH YOUR WEAK,
LITTLE PARTY PRANKS!
DID YOU REALLY THINK
YOU COULD MAKE ME LOSE MY COOL?!
WELL, DASH AND I HAVE
10 TIMES AS MUCH COOL
AS THE REST OF YOU
PUT TOGETHER!
COME ON, DASH, WE'RE BAILING
ON THIS PATHETIC SCENE!
COME ON, RAINBOW DASH!
I SAID WE'RE LEAVING!
YOU KNOW, GILDA...
I WAS THE ONE WHO SET UP ALL
THOSE WEAK PRANKS AT THIS PARTY.
[ GASPS ] WHAT?!
OOH.
SO I GUESS
I'M QUEEN LAME-O.
COME ON, DASH,
YOU'RE JOSHING ME.
THEY WEREN'T ALL MEANT
FOR YOU SPECIFICALLY.
IT WAS JUST DUMB LUCK
THAT YOU SET THEM ALL OFF.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
THAT DRIBBLE CUP
HAD RAINBOW DASH
WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.
NO WAY!
I-IT WAS PINKIE PIE!
SHE SET UP THIS PARTY
TO TRIP ME UP,
TO MAKE A FOOL OF ME!
ME? I THREW THIS PARTY
TO IMPROVE YOUR ATTITUDE.
I THOUGHT A GOOD PARTY MIGHT
TURN THAT FROWN UPSIDE DOWN.
AND YOU SURE DIDN'T NEED ANY
HELP MAKING A FOOL OF YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS NOT
HOW I THOUGHT MY OLD FRIENDS
WOULD TREAT MY NEW FRIENDS.
IF BEING COOL
IS ALL YOU CARE ABOUT,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO FIND SOME
NEW COOL FRIENDS SOMEPLACE ELSE.
[ GROWLS ] YEAH?
WELL, YOU -- YOU --
YOU ARE SUCH A, UM, FLIP-FLOP,
COOL ONE MINUTE
AND LAME THE NEXT!
WHEN YOU DECIDE
NOT TO BE LAME ANYMORE,
GIVE ME A CALL.
[ SHRIEKS ]
NOT COOL.
WOW, TALK ABOUT
A PARTY POOPER.
[ ALL MURMURING ]
WOW, WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
YEAH.
REALLY AWKWARD!
I'M SORRY, EVERYPONY,
FOR BRINGING GILDA HERE.
I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW RUDE SHE WAS.
AND, PINKIE PIE,
I'M REALLY SORRY
SHE RUINED THAT AWESOME PARTY
YOU PUT ON FOR HER.
HEY, IF YOU WANT TO HANG OUT
WITH PARTY POOPERS,
THAT'S YOUR BUSINESS.
I'D RATHER HANG OUT
WITH YOU.
NO HARD FEELINGS?
NO HARD FEELINGS.
[ ZAP! ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
HEY, PINKIE, SORRY I ACCUSED YOU
OF MISJUDGING GILDA.
LOOKS LIKE I'M THE ONE
WHO MISJUDGED YOU.
IT'S OKAY, TWILIGHT.
EVEN YOU CAN'T BE
A SUPER-SMART,
SMARTY-SMART PANTS ALL THE TIME.
COME ON, EVERYPONY,
THERE'S STILL A WHOLE LOT
OF PARTY TO FINISH.
[ INDISTINCT TALKING, LAUGHTER ]
"DEAREST PRINCESS CELESTIA,
"TODAY, I LEARNED
THAT IT'S HARD TO ACCEPT
"WHEN SOMEPONY YOU LIKE
"WANTS TO SPEND TIME WITH
SOMEPONY WHO'S NOT SO NICE.
"THOUGH IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO CONTROL
"WHO YOUR FRIENDS
HANG OUT WITH,
"IT IS POSSIBLE
TO CONTROL YOUR OWN BEHAVIOR.
"JUST CONTINUE TO
BE A GOOD FRIEND.
"IN THE END, THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A FALSE FRIEND
"AND ONE WHO IS TRUE
WILL SURELY COME TO LIGHT.
YOUR FAITHFUL STUDENT,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE."
"DEAR TWILIGHT SPARKLE,
MY MOST FAITHFUL STUDENT."
OH! [ CHUCKLES ]
WRONG INK.
[ SIGHS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS