[ SNORING ]
[ GASPS ]
SPIKE, WAKE UP!
WAKE UP, WAKE UP!
IT'S WINTER WRAP-UP DAY!
[ ZIP! ]
HUH?
MOMMY?
WINTER WRAP-UP.
YOU'RE NOT MOMMY.
SPIKE, THE FIRST DAY
OF SPRING IS TOMORROW,
SO EVERY PONY IN PONYVILLE
NEEDS TO CLEAN UP WINTER.
IT'LL HELP ME GET READY.
CLEAN UP WINTER?
WHO CLEANS UP WINTER?
DON'T THEY JUST USE MAGIC
TO CHANGE THE SEASONS
LIKE WE DO IN CANTERWOT?
NO, SPIKE.
PONYVILLE WAS STARTED
BY EARTH PONIES,
SO FOR HUNDREDS OF YEARS,
THEY'VE NEVER USED MAGIC
TO CLEAN UP WINTER.
IT'S TRADITIONAL.
[ THUD ]
[ SIGHS ]
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
NO MAGIC. PAH!
OKAY, LET'S SEE.
SCARF, CHECK.
SADDLE, CHECK.
BOOTS, CHECK.
SPIKE REFUSING TO GET UP AND
GOING BACK TO SLEEP, CHECK.
IT'S A GOOD THING
I'M SO ORGANIZED. I'M READY.
BRIGHT AND EARLY.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
OH, MAYBE A LITTLE TOO EARLY.
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
THIS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
THOSE MUST BE THE TEAM VESTS
RARITY DESIGNED.
BLUE FOR THE WEATHER TEAM,
GREEN FOR THE PLANT TEAM,
AND TAN FOR THE ANIMAL TEAM.
I WONDER WHICH TEAM VEST
I'LL BE WEARING.
I'LL TAKE A BLUE VEST --
THE SAME COLOR
AS MY BLANKIE,
WHICH I THINK
I HEAR CALLING MY NAME.
"SPIKE,
SPIKE, COME TO BED!"
[ GROANS ]
IT'S TOO EARLY.
THANK YOU, EVERYPONY, FOR BEING
HERE BRIGHT AND EARLY.
WE NEED EVERY SINGLE PONY'S HELP
TO WRAP UP WINTER
AND BRING IN SPRING.
[ CHEERING ]
NOW, ALL OF YOU HAVE YOUR VESTS
AND HAVE BEEN ASSIGNED
TO YOUR TEAMS,
SO LET'S DO EVEN BETTER
THAN LAST YEAR
AND HAVE THE QUICKEST
WINTER WRAP-UP EVER.
[ CHEERING ]
OH,
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYPONY,
FIND YOUR TEAM LEADER
AND LET'S GET GALLOPING.
YEAH!
OH, GOSH,
WHERE SHOULD I GO?
I'M NOT SURE WHERE I'D FIT IN.
WHAT EXACTLY
DOES EVERYPONY DO?
* THREE MONTHS OF WINTER
COOLNESS AND AWESOME HOLIDAYS *
* WE'VE KEPT OUR HOOFSIES WARM
AT HOME *
* TIME OFF FROM WORK
TO PLAY *
* BUT THE FOOD WE'VE STORED
IS RUNNING OUT *
* AND WE CAN'T GROW
IN THIS COLD *
* AND EVEN THOUGH
I LOVE MY BOOTS *
* THIS FASHION'S
GETTING OLD *
* THE TIME HAS COME
TO WELCOME SPRING *
* AND ALL THINGS
WARM AND GREEN *
* BUT IT'S ALSO TIME
TO SAY GOODBYE *
* IT'S WINTER,
WE MUST CLEAN *
* HOW CAN I HELP?
I KNEW YOU'D SEE *
* WHAT DOES EVERYPONY DO?
* HOW DO I FIT IN
WITHOUT MAGIC? *
* I HAVEN'T GOT A CLUE
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* LET'S FINISH
OUR HOLIDAY CHEER *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* BRINGING HOME
THE SOUTHERN BIRDS *
* OUR PEGASUS' JOB BEGINS
* AND CLEARING ALL THE GLOOMY
SKIES TO LET THE SUNSHINE IN *
* WE THE CLOUDS
AND WE MELT THE WHITE SNOW *
* WHEN THE SUN COMES UP, ITS
WARMTH AND BEAUTY WILL GLOW *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* LET'S FINISH
OUR HOLIDAY CHEER *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* LITTLE CRITTERS HIBERNATE
UNDER THE SNOW AND ICE *
* WE WAKE UP ALL THE SLEEPYHEADS
SO QUIETLY AND NICE *
* WE HELP THEM GATHER UP THEIR
FOOD, FIX THEIR HOMES BELOW *
* WE WELCOME BACK
THE SOUTHERN BIRDS *
* SO THEIR FAMILIES
CAN GROW *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* LET'S FINISH
OUR HOLIDAY CHEER *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* NO EASY TASK TO CLEAR THE
GROUND, PLANT OUR TINY SEEDS *
* WITH PROPER CARE AND SUNSHINE,
EVERYONE IT FEEDS *
* APPLES, CARROTS, CELERY
STALKS, COLORFUL FLOWERS, TOO *
* WE MUST WORK SO VERY HARD,
IT'S JUST SO MUCH TO DO *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* LET'S FINISH
OUR HOLIDAY CHEER *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* NOW THAT I KNOW
WHAT THEY ALL DO *
* I HAVE TO FIND MY PLACE
* AND HELP
WITH ALL OF MY HEART *
* TOUGH TASK AHEAD I FACE
* HOW WILL I DO
WITHOUT MY MAGIC? *
* HELP THE EARTH PONY WAY?
* I WANT TO BELONG,
SO I MUST DO MY BEST TODAY *
* DO MY BEST TODAY
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* LET'S FINISH
OUR HOLIDAY CHEER *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
* WINTER WRAP-UP,
WINTER WRAP-UP *
* 'CAUSE TOMORROW
SPRING IS HERE *
SPRING IS HE-E-E-E-RE *
EVERYPONY
BELONGS TO A TEAM.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WHERE SHOULD I GO?
[ ZOOM! ]
ALL RIGHT, TEAM,
YOU'RE CLEARED FOR TAKEOFF.
RAINBOW DASH.
OH, HEY, TWILIGHT.
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SENDING OFF
ONE OF MY FLIGHT CREWS
TO RETRIEVE THE BIRDS THAT HAVE
FLOWN SOUTH FOR THE WINTER.
OH, CAN I HELP?
HOW ABOUT IF I HELP
CLEAR OUT THE CLOUDS?
UM...
RIGHT, NO WINGS.
SORRY, TWILIGHT.
[ ZOOM! ]
[ GASPS ]
GREAT.
NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I'M GONNA BE NAPPING.
[ SNORES ]
COME ON, SPIKE,
THIS IS SERIOUS BUSINESS!
WINTER NEEDS
TO BE WRAPPED UP,
AND I'M DETERMINED
TO DO MY PART...
SOMEHOW.
[ STRETCH! ]
[ SNAP! ]
RARITY, PLEASE TELL ME
THERE'S SOMETHING, ANYTHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH.
WELL, HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE TO HELP CREATE
PONYVILLE'S FINEST
BIRD'S NESTS?
WHY, YES.
WHEN THE WEATHER TEAM
GUIDES THE BIRDS
BACK NORTH FOR THE SPRING,
THEY'LL NEED A PLACE TO LIVE
AND LAY THEIR EGGS.
WOW, RARITY.
THAT ONE'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
OH, WHY, THANK YOU
MOST SINCERELY.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY YOUR HOOF
AT A NEST?
WOULD I? YES!
WHERE DO I BEGIN?
OKAY, NOW, TAKE SOME OF THAT
STRAW AND HAY OVER THERE
AND A LITTLE BIT OF BRANCH.
NOW, WEAVE THEM
THROUGH THERE.
YES! TAKE SOME RIBBON.
YES, OOH, N-NOT THERE.
YES, UH, TUCK IT IN OVER THERE,
BUT BE CAREFUL NOT TO...
NO, NO, NO,
I GUESS THAT WILL DO.
OH, DEAR.
THERE!
IT LOOKS
JUST LIKE...YOURS.
OH, MY.
THAT NEST
NEEDS TO BE CONDEMNED.
[ Laughing ] OH, SPIKE.
IT'S NOT SO BAD.
MAYBE THE BIRDS
CAN USE IT AS AN...
AN OUTHOUSE?
SPIKE, IT'S JUST FINE.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE ROUGH
AROUND THE EDGES.
LET ME LEND YOU A HOOF.
LET'S JUST UNTIE THIS RIBBON.
AND IF WE TAKE OUT THESE STICKS
HERE, RESHAPE THIS.
I THINK WE LOST HER.
AND WE NEED
TO WEAVE THIS STRING IN.
HELLO, TWILIGHT!
WHEEE!
WOW, PINKIE PIE,
YOU'RE QUITE THE SKATER.
PROBABLY THE BEST SKATER
I'VE EVER SEEN.
THANKS, TWILIGHT.
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS
SINCE I WAS AN ITTY-BITTY,
LITTLE, LITTLE TWINKIE PINKIE.
JUST COMES NATURALLY.
WHICH IS PROBABLY WHY THEY
DESIGNATED ME THE LAKE SCORER.
I CUT LINES IN THE LAKE
WITH MY SKATES.
THAT WAY, WHEN THE REST OF
THE WEATHER TEAM COMES HERE
TO BREAK THE ICE,
IT'LL BE EASY AS PIE.
HOW CLEVER.
WHEN THE THICK ICE
BEGINS TO MELT,
IT'LL BREAK ALONG THE LINES.
WELL, YOU SURE HAVE
A LOT OF WORK AHEAD OF YOU.
THERE'S QUITE A FEW LAKES
IN PONYVILLE.
TELL ME ABOUT IT!
HEY, TWILIGHT,
WANT TO HELP ME OUT?
WOULD I!
COME ON, PUT ON THOSE SKATES
OVER THERE.
I BET YOU'LL BE A NATURAL,
TOO.
OKAY.
[ WARBLE! ]
YAY!
UH, MAYBE
ON SECOND THOUGHT...
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO BE HELPFUL.
YIPPEE!
NOW GET OUT THERE.
[ GASPS ]
WHOA! WHOA!
TWILIGHT, STEER!
STEER!
YA!
OH, BOY!
WHAA!
[ CRASH! ]
[ PLINK! PLINK! PLINK! ]
UGH!
BRR!
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU ARE A NATURAL, TWILIGHT --
A NATURAL DISASTER!
[ LAUGHS ]
TWILIGHT, YOU DID A GREAT JOB
YOUR FIRST TIME AROUND.
I'M SURE MY FIRST TIME
WAS JUST AS WOBBLY AND BOBBLY
AND CRASHERRIFIC AS YOURS!
REALLY?
NO.
[ LAUGHS ]
BUT DID I MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER?
[ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, I GUESS.
I BET YOU'LL BE SUPER AWESOME
AT SOMETHING
THAT KEEPS YOUR HOOVES
ON THE GROUND.
I KNOW! FLUTTERSHY COULD
PROBABLY USE YOUR HELP
WITH THE CRITTERS.
WELL, I'M PRETTY GOOD
WITH LITTLE ANIMALS.
YEAH, I'LL GO HELP HER.
UH, IT'S, UH, THATAWAY.
YA!
[ THUNK! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ BELL RINGS ]
WAKE UP,
LITTLE SLEEPYHEADS.
HOPE YOU HAD SOME WONDERFUL
DREAMS AND RESTFUL HIBERNATION,
BUT IT'S TIME
TO GET UP NOW.
SPRING IS COMING.
[ YAWNING ]
AW, HOW CUTE.
AREN'T THEY?
THIS IS MY FAVORITE TASK
OF THE WHOLE SEASON,
WHEN I GET TO SEE ALL MY LITTLE
ANIMAL FRIENDS AGAIN.
UH, WHAT'S HIBERNATION?
IT'S LIKE A LONG SLEEP.
LONG SLEEP?
YES.
[ RINGS ]
WAKE UP, LITTLE PORCUPINES.
ANIMALS OFTEN HIBERNATE
THROUGH THE WINTER
TO SAVE THEIR ENERGY
AND EAT LESS FOOD.
I DEFINITELY LIKE THE IDEA
OF HIBERNATION,
EXCEPT FOR THE
"EAT LESS FOOD" PART.
[ BOTH YAWN ]
[ SPROING! ]
[ YELPS ]
OH, BUT JUST LOOK AT ALL THESE
WARRENS AND DENS.
I'M WORRIED THAT I WON'T BE ABLE
TO WAKE UP EVERY ANIMAL
BEFORE SPRING COMES.
WELL, I'LL HELP,
FLUTTERSHY.
OH, YOU WILL?
OH, THAT WOULD BE WONDERFUL.
OKAY.
LET'S START THERE.
[ BELL RINGS ]
HELLO?
WAKE UP, LITTLE FRIENDS,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
SPRING IS COMING.
[ RINGS ]
I WONDER WHICH CUTE, LITTLE,
FURRY CREATURES I'VE AWOKEN.
[ HISSING ]
AAH, SNAKES! SNAKES!
AAAAAAAH!
UGH!
OOH!
[ BUZZING ]
[ Muffled ] AAAAAH!
OOF!
GOOD MORNING, FRIENDS.
OH, ALL THIS
WINTER WRAP-UP STUFF
IS A LOT HARDER
THAN IT LOOKS.
RIGHT,
BECAUSE THERE'S NO MAGIC.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST USE MAGIC,
TWILIGHT,
AND GET IT DONE
THE RIGHT WAY?
NO, SPIKE.
I HAVE TO DO IT
THE TRADITIONAL WAY.
PONYVILLE HAS NEVER NEEDED MAGIC
TO WRAP UP WINTER.
BUT THEY NEVER HAD YOU HERE
BEFORE, EITHER.
THINK ABOUT HOW MUCH QUICKER
THEY COULD WRAP UP WINTER
WITH YOUR MAGIC.
NO, NO, NO!
I'M GONNA FIND SOME OTHER WAY
THAT I CAN HELP OUT
IF IT KILLS ME!
[ GROANS ]
KEEP PUSHING, CARAMEL.
THAT'S IT, BUMPKIN.
I KNOW IT'S HARD WORK,
BUT YOU GUYS ARE DOING GREAT.
YEEHAW!
HEY, APPLEJACK,
HOW'S EVERYTHING GOING?
OH, JUST DANDY.
LITTLE SLOW STARTING,
BUT PEACHY, ALL THE SAME.
THERE'S A LOT OF GROUND
TO CLEAR, YOU HEAR?
WE CAN'T EVEN START THE PLANTING
AND THE WATERING
UNTIL WE GET ALL THIS HEAP
OF SNOW HIGHTAILED OUT OF HERE.
WELL, I'D LIKE TO HELP.
WELL, I-I DON'T KNOW,
TWILIGHT.
JUST GIVE ME A CHANCE.
WELL, I NEVER TURN DOWN
A HARD WORKER, BUT...
[ GRUNTING ]
Spike: THINK OF HOW MUCH QUICKER
THEY COULD WRAP UP WINTER
WITH YOUR MAGIC?
I COULD USE
A COME-TO-LIFE SPELL.
OH, HERE GOES.
HMM, SHE'S AWFUL STRONG
FOR SUCH A LITTLE PONY.
THAT'S MY GIRL!
FOLLOWING MY ADVICE.
AND WHAT IN TARNATION
DOES THAT MEAN?
[ GASPS ]
UH-OH. SLOW DOWN.
SLOW DOWN!
[ SPLAT! ]
OH!
[ BOOM! ]
Both: WHOA-OH-OA!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'D YOU DO?
YOU USED MAGIC,
DIDN'T YOU?
[ BOOM! ]
[ RUMBLE! ]
[ POP! POP! ]
NUTS, TWILIGHT!
YOU USED MAGIC!
THE NERVE!
CAN YOU BELIEVE HER?
THAT'S NOT HOW WE DO IT
'ROUND HERE, TWILIGHT,
AND ESPECIALLY
NOT ON MY FARM!
WELL, SEE,
I JUST WANTED TO --
OH!
[ ZOOP! ]
COME ON, TWILIGHT,
COME ON OUT.
Twilight:
I'M A WINTER MESS UP.
WELL, YOU'RE GOOD
AT A LOT OF THINGS,
JUST NOT NEST MAKING,
ICE SKATING,
ANIMAL WAKING,
SNOW CLEARING.
THANKS A LOT FOR MAKING ME FEEL
SO MUCH BETTER.
THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE FOR,
SISTER.
RAINBOW DASH,
Y'ALL ON THE WEATHER TEAM
NEED TO MELT THE REST OF THIS
SNOW HERE ON THE GROUND
AND THE TREES PRONTO.
GOT IT!
YOU CAN'T.
MY POOR LITTLE ANIMALS' HOMES
WILL GET FLOODED
IF THE SNOW
MELTS TOO FAST.
GOT IT?
I'M TELLING YOU, RAINBOW,
YOU GOT TO MELT THAT SNOW NOW.
NO!
YOU SIMPLY MUST WAIT.
OKAY.
GO!
STOP!
UGH!
MAKE UP YOUR MINDS!
OH, WHAT IN EQUESTRIA
ARE ALL YOU ARGUING ABOUT?
THIS SORT OF SILLINESS IS WHY
WERE LATE FOR SPRING LAST YEAR,
AND THE YEAR BEFORE THAT,
AND THE YEAR BEFORE THAT!
DID SHE SAY LATE?
I WAS HOPING MY AMAZINGLY
INSPIRATIONAL SPEECH
WOULD URGE EVERYONE
TO DO BETTER THAN LAST YEAR,
BUT NOW IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
GOING TO BE LATER THAN EVER!
I MEAN, JUST LOOK
AT THIS CATASTROPHE!
THE ICE SCORERS MADE
THE ICE CHUNKS TOO BIG TO MELT.
THE NEST DESIGNER'S
HORRENDOUSLY BEHIND.
WE NEED SEVERAL HUNDRED,
AND SHE'S ONLY MADE ONE.
[ SOBS ]
AND DON'T GET ME STARTED ON ALL
THE CLOUDS STILL IN THE SKY,
THE ICICLES ON THE TREES.
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
NOT AT ALL!
AND IT'S GONNA BE ALL-TO-PIECES
DISASTROUS
IF WE CAN'T GET OUR SEEDS
ALL PLANTED.
CHILLAX, APPLEJACK!
WE'RE BUSTING OUR CHOPS
AS FAST AS WE CAN.
NO, NOT FAST.
YOU HAVE TO WAKE ANIMALS SLOWLY.
UH, A.J.?
OH, GOOD GRAVY!
CARAMEL LOST THE GRASS SEEDS
AGAIN, DIDN'T HE?
UH-YEP.
DITZY DOO ACCIDENTALLY WENT
NORTH TO GET THE SOUTHERN BIRDS.
OH, THAT FEATHERBRAIN!
DIDN'T SHE LEARN HER LESSON
LAST YEAR WHEN SHE WENT WEST?
[ ALL TALKING ]
STOP THIS AT ONCE!
WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO ARGUE!
IT'S ALMOST SUNDOWN.
SPRING IS GOING TO BE LATE
AGAIN.
ANOTHER YEAR
OF SCANDAL AND SHAME!
IF ONLY WE COULD BE
MORE ORGANIZED.
SPIKE, GET MY CHECKLIST
AND CLIPBOARD -- STAT!
YES, MA'AM.
STOP, EVERYPONY!
[ ALL TALKING ]
STOP!
[ WHISTLE! ]
Sorry.
I KNOW YOU ALL WANT
TO COMPLETE YOUR JOBS ON TIME,
BUT ARGUING
IS NO WAY TO GO ABOUT IT.
WHAT YOU NEED IS ORGANIZATION,
AND I'M JUST THE PONY
FOR THE JOB.
[ ZIP! ]
[ RINGS ]
[ BOING! BOING! ]
[ HISSING ]
[ CHIRPS ]
[ POOF! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING, CAWING ]
[ BUZZING ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
SPRING IS HERE
ON TIME!
AND WE HAVE YOU
TO THANK FOR IT.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOUR
ORGANIZING SKILLS,
WE WOULD
STILL BE ARGUING.
UH-YEP.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT WAS A TEAM EFFORT.
AND SINCE
YOU HELPED EVERY TEAM,
WE HAVE AN OFFICIAL VEST
FOR YOU.
WE GIVE YOU
THE TITLE ALL-TEAM ORGANIZER.
GOSH, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
THANK YOU, EVERYPONY.
AND HEREBY I DECLARE THAT WINTER
IS WRAPPED UP ON TIME!
[ CHEERING ]
SPIKE'S SURE GONNA BE IN
FOR A HOG-SIZED SURPRISE
WHEN THAT LAST PIECE
OF ICE MELTS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Twilight:
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
"WINTER WRAP-UP WAS ONE OF
THE MOST SPECIAL THINGS
"I'VE EVER BEEN A PART OF
HERE IN PONYVILLE.
"IT HELPED ME TO LEARN THAT
WE ALL HAVE HIDDEN TALENTS,
"AND IF WE'RE PATIENT
AND DILIGENT,
"WE'RE SURE TO FIND THEM.
"AND AS ALWAYS, WITH GOOD
FRIENDSHIP AND TEAMWORK,
PONIES CAN ACCOMPLISH ANYTHING."
HOW'S THAT, SPIKE?
SPIKE?
[ SNORING ]
OH, SPIKE.
[ LAUGHS ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS