[ TINKLING, DOORBELL RINGS ]
SO SORRY, FLUTTERSHY.
I HATE BEING LATE
FOR OUR WEEKLY GET-TOGETHER.
THE USUAL.
[ ZIP! ]
[ STEAM HISSING ]
BUT YOU WOULD NOT BELIEVE
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME!
IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT?
OH, IT'S MUCH MORE
THAN ALL RIGHT.
I WAS ON MY WAY HERE
WEARING MY LATEST HAT CREATION,
WHEN WHO SHOULD STOP ME
ON THE STREET BUT PHOTO FINISH!
PHOTO FINISH?
SHE'S THE MOST FAMOUS
FASHION PHOTOGRAPHER
IN ALL OF EQUESTRIA!
ANYHOO, SHE SAW MY HAT
AND SAID IT WAS
"ABSOLUTELY MARVELOUS!"
WHAT A LOVELY COMPLIMENT.
SHE WAS SO IMPRESSED
THAT SHE WANTS TO TAKE
SOME PICTURES AT MY SHOP,
FEATURING
SOME OF MY CLOTHES!
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
THAT'S WONDERFUL.
[ Shakily ] DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS COULD MEAN
FOR MY FASHION CAREER?
OH, RARITY,
I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
BUT I'M GOING TO NEED SOMEPONY
FABULOUS TO MODEL FOR ME.
SOMEPONY WITH BEAUTY,
SOMEPONY WITH GRACE,
SOMEPONY...
LIKE YOU?
OH, GOODNESS.
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, THIS IS
SUCH A HUGE OPPORTUNITY,
AND IT WOULD MEAN
SO MUCH TO ME.
I'M FLATTERED, REALLY.
NOPONY IS GOING TO HAVE
YOUR ELEGANCE AND POISE.
BUT --
NOPONY.
THERE HAS TO BE SOMEPONY
MORE QUALIF--
PLEASE?!
SOMEPONY
MORE INTO FASHION.
PLEASE?!
SOMEPONY MORE COMFORTABLE
IN THE SPOTLIGHT.
PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLE-E-E-ASE?!
[ TING! ]
OH, IF IT'S THAT IMPORTANT
TO YOU, OF COURSE I'LL DO IT.
[ GASPS ] OH, THANK YOU!
THANK YOU! THANK YOU! THANK YOU!
YOU ARE THE BEST FRIEND
A PONY COULD EVER HAVE!
[ SIGHS ] WHAT A WONDERFUL WAY
TO SPEND AN AFTERNOON.
ISN'T IT?
THOUGH, I WAS SO AFRAID YOU
WOULDN'T AGREE TO MODEL FOR ME
THAT I FELT
COMPLETELY FRAZZLED!
I THINK I FEEL A PIMPLE
COMING ON.
OH!
ONLY ONE SOLUTION.
[ TINKLING ]
THE USUAL.
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
HMM. SHE'S GOING TO WANT TO SEE
ATTITUDE AND PIZZAZZ.
A-A-ATTITUDE AND...
PIZZAZZ.
MORE LIGHT! IT HAS TO CATCH
THE SEQUINS JUST SO
[ TINKLING ]
OR THE WHOLE OUTFIT
IS JUST A DISASTER.
OOH, AND THE HEADDRESS
NEEDS MORE FEATHERS.
PINKIE PIE,
MORE FEATHERS!
[ SPROING! SPROING! SPROING! ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ POP! ]
[ GASPS ] AND SEQUINS!
MORE SEQUINS!
[ TINKLING ]
[ WINCES ]
AND MORE RIBBON!
[ ZIP! ]
OH, NO. LESS RIBBON.
NO! MORE RIBBON.
[ WINCES ]
OH, THIS HEM
IS COMPLETELY OFF.
PIN CUSHION!
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ TINKLING ]
THANK YOU ALL
FOR HELPING ME.
I'M SORRY TO BE SO SHORT WITH
YOU, BUT I'M JUST SO NERVOUS.
OOH,
DOESN'T THAT HURT?
THICK SCALES.
CAN'T FEEL A THING.
AND EVEN IF I COULD,
THERE IS NO PAIN THAT WOULD
KEEP ME FROM ASSISTING...
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL CREATURE
IN THE WORLD.
UGH!
I'M GONNA TELL YOU TWO
A SECRET,
BUT YOU HAVE TO PROMISE
NOT TO TELL ANYONE.
I PROMISE.
CROSS MY HEART
AND HOPE TO FLY.
STICK A CUPCAKE
IN MY EYE.
I have a crush
on Rarity.
[ GASPS ]
WE WON'T SAY A WORD.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
EVERYPONY ALREADY KNOWS
HOW YOU --
TWILIGHT! YOU PROMISED SPIKE
YOU WOULDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
HE TRUSTS YOU,
AND LOSING A FRIEND'S TRUST
IS THE FASTEST WAY
TO LOSE A FRIEND FOREVER!
BUT --
FOREVE-E-E-R!
MY LIPS ARE SEALED.
THOUGH I'M PRETTY SURE
RARITY IS GONNA PICK UP
ON YOUR FEELINGS.
[ DOOR OPENS, BELL JINGLES ]
[ Foreign accent ]
I, PHOTO FINISH...
HAVE AWWIVED.
LET ME JUST SAY,
WHAT AN HONOR.
WE BEGIN...
[ BOING! ]
...NOW.
ATTITUDE AND PIZZAZZ!
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
YES! SHOW PHOTO FINISH
SOMETHING!
NO!
[ WHIMPERS ]
YES.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
[ TING! ]
NO!
YES.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
NO!
YES.
ENOUGH!
SHE HARDLY TOOK
ANY PICTURES.
[ TINKLING ]
I'M SO SORRY.
I TRIED MY BEST.
WELL, THE HEADDRESS
IS TOO BIG FOR YOU,
AND THE CAPE
HAD TOO MUCH SPARKLE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I EVER THOUGHT
I COULD IMPRESS HER.
IT SEEMS THAT I,
PHOTO FINISH,
HAVE FOUND THE NEXT FASHION STAR
HERE IN PONYVILLE.
REALLY?
YES, REALLY.
AND I, PHOTO FINISH,
AM GOING TO HELP HER TO SHINE
ALL OVER EQVESTRIA!
TOMORROW,
A PHOTO SHOOT IN ZE PARK!
I GO!
[ ZIP! ]
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
I AM GOING TO
"SHINE ALL OVER EQUESTRIA!"
OH, RARITY, I WAS SO WORRIED
I'D RUINED EVERYTHING.
OH, NEVER.
I KNEW YOU'D BE PERFECT.
[ SQUEALING AND LAUGHING ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
NO. NO. NO.
YES!
[ TINKLING ]
THAT IS DEFINITELY
THE ONE.
PHOTO FINISH
IS GOING TO LOVE IT.
EVERYPONY
IS GOING TO LOVE IT!
OH, I AM SO EXCITED
FOR YOU.
JUST DON'T FORGET
US LITTLE PONIES
WHEN YOU BECOME THE MOST FAMOUS
DESIGNER IN ALL OF EQUESTRIA.
NEVER.
Photo Finish:
PUT ME DOWN HERE.
[ ZIP! ]
OH, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO. NO.
THE MODEL SHOULD BE
IN SOMETHING SIMPLE!
SOMETHING INSPIRED BY...
THE NATURE.
THAT'S JUST
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
UM, GIVE ME A MOMENT
AND I'LL, UH,
PUT A LITTLE SOMETHING
TOGETHER.
YES. THAT WILL NOT
BE NECESSARY.
BUT -- BUT --
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO HELP ME
"SHINE ACROSS EQUESTRIA"
IF I DON'T DESIGN SOMETHING NEW
FOR THESE PICTURES?
I AM NOT GOING TO HELP YOU
SHINE ACROSS EQUESTRIA!
I AM GOING TO HELP
HER SHINE.
SHE IS MY STAR!
YOU, GO.
[ GASPS ]
I CAN'T, RARITY.
OH, BUT YOU MUST,
FLUTTERSHY.
PHOTO FINISH
WANTS TO MAKE YOU A STAR.
THIS IS THE OPPORTUNITY
OF A LIFETIME.
I KNOW WE WERE BOTH HOPING
IT WOULD BE MY LIFETIME,
BUT NONETHELESS, YOU CAN'T
THROW AWAY THIS CHANCE.
YOU MUST DO THIS
FOR ME.
YOU MUST.
YOU MUST! YOU MUS-S-T!
Photo Finish:
FLOOTTERSHY!
IT IS TIME TO MAKE...
THE MAGICS!
[ TING! ]
OH, WUNDERBAR!
YOU ARE LIKE
A DELICATE FLOWER --
SO MUCH MORE ALLURING WITHOUT
ALL THOSE SPARKLES AND FEATHERS.
[ SIGHS ]
[ SEWING MACHINE WHIRRING ]
HOW'D IT GO?!
IT DIDN'T.
PHOTO FINISH WANTED TO WORK
WITH FLUTTERSHY, NOT ME.
OH, RARITY.
I'M SO SORRY.
IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO?
I JUST...VANT TO BE ALONE
RIGHT NOW.
YOU HEARD HER.
SHE "VANTS TO BE ALONE."
[ SPROING! SPROING! ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT? I DIDN'T THINK
SHE MEANT ALONE ALONE.
[ SNIFFS ]
[ WINCES ]
TOO MUCH BLUSH.
[ RATTLE! ]
NOT ENOUGH.
TOO MUCH.
[ WINCES ]
NOT ENOUGH.
PERFECT.
AH-AHHHHHH...
choo!
OH, YES!
EVEN HER SCHNEEZES
ARE GRACEFUL!
NOW GO!
[ ZIP! ]
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
EXCITED? OVERJOYED?
THRILLED BEYOND
YOUR WILDEST DREAMS?
N-NERVOUS.
NERVOUS?
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
YOU'RE ONLY FACING
A LARGE CROWD OF PONIES
WHO WILL BE WATCHING YOUR EVERY
MOVE AND SILENTLY JUDGING YOU.
[ ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
YOUR CUE! NOW GO!
[ YELPS ]
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
I CAN'T LET RARITY DOWN.
I MUST DO THIS.
MUST, MUST, MUST.
[ CHEERING, HOOVES STOMPING ]
SO GRACEFUL.
SO LOVELY.
Pony: SO PERFECT
FOR MY NEW ADVERTISEMENT.
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GROWLS ]
IT'S FLUTTERSHY!
[ PONIES SQUEALING ]
FLUTTERSHY!
OVER HERE!
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
FLUTTERSHY!
OVER HERE!
BEAUTIFUL, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
COME HERE!
RIGHT HERE, FLUTTERSHY!
OVER HERE!
FLUTTERSHY!
THERE YOU ARE.
[ SEWING MACHINE WHIRRING ]
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
HEY, OVER HERE, FLUTTERSHY!
LOOK OVER HERE!
FLUTTERSHY!
MORE PICTURES,
PLEASE.
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
WOW.
LOOK HOW POPULAR YOU ARE.
I'M SO EXCITED FOR YOU.
YOU MUST BE
HAVING THE BEST TIME EVER.
OH, YES.
BEST TIME EVER.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
Photo Finish:
FLOOTTERSHY!
I HAVE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU
EVERYWHERE.
WE HAVE THE THING
AT THE PLACE!
I'LL SEE YOU AT THE SPA,
OUR USUAL TIME?
OF COURSE!
I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR
ALL ABOUT THE...
THING AT THE PLACE.
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
I'M THE ONE WHO SHOULD BE MOBBED
BY STRANGERS WHEREVER I GO.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
WELCOME
TO CAROUSEL BOUTIQUE!
IS SHE STILL HERE?
WE HEARD FLUTTERSHY WAS HERE.
SORRY.
YOU JUST MISSED HER.
BUT YOU'RE
STILL IN LUCK.
I'M HAVING A HUGE SALE
ON SOME OF MY BEST DESIGNS.
AND YOU ARE?
RARITY, OF COURSE.
NEVER HEARD OF YOU.
[ GROWLS ]
OBVIOUSLY, I, PHOTO FINISH,
AM THRILLED TO HAVE FOUND HER.
PHOTO FINISH?
SHE'S A NATURAL
IN FRONT OF THE CAMERA.
UM, PHOTO FINISH?
I ONLY NEED
TO POINT AND SHOOT,
AND I CAPTURE...
THE MAGICS!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
PHOTO FINISH,
I'M SO SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
IT'S JUST
THAT I'M RUNNING LATE.
[ GASPS ]
HOW COULD I HAVE FORGOTTEN?!
YOUR APPEARANCE
AT THE BALLET OPENING --
EVERYPONY WHO IS ANYPONY
WILL BE THERE!
OH, ACTUALLY, I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
MEETING MY FRIEND --
WE GO!
[ GROANS ]
MY HOOVES ARE GETTING
POSITIVELY PRUNE-Y,
I'VE BEEN WAITING HERE
SO LONG.
OBVIOUSLY, FLUTTERSHY'S JUST
TOO BUSY WITH HER NEW CAREER
TO SPEND TIME
WITH HER BEST FRIEND.
I'M SURE
SHE JUST GOT TIED UP.
OF COURSE SHE DID.
SHE'S A BIG, BRIGHT,
SHINING STAR.
I WISH
THAT STAR WOULD BURN OUT!
RARITY, FLUTTERSHY
IS YOUR FRIEND.
I KNOW! I KNOW!
AND I SHOULD BE
HAPPY FOR HER,
BUT INSTEAD,
I'M JUST...UNH...JEALOUS!
OH, PLEASE PROMISE YOU WON'T
TELL HER I FEEL THIS WAY!
PLEASE? PLEASE?
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLE-E-ASE?
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
LOSING A FRIEND'S TRUST IS THE
FASTEST WAY TO LOSE A FRIEND.
FOREVER!
WOW!
YOU LOOK GREAT!
FLUTTERSHY MAY BE
THE ONE WHO'S FAMOUS,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN I HAVE TO
STOP LOOKING FABULOUS.
RARITY,
I'M SO SORRY I'M --
OH, NO.
SHE'S ALREADY GONE, ISN'T SHE?
SORRY.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I AM SO FRUSTRATED,
I COULD JUST SCREAM.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
Aaaah...
FEEL BETTER?
[ SIGHS ] NO.
CAN I TELL YOU
SOMETHING?
OF COURSE.
YOU PROMISE
NOT TO TELL RARITY?
I SWEAR.
PINKIE PIE SWEAR?
CROSS MY HEART
AND HOPE TO FLY.
STICK A CUPCAKE
IN MY [SCREAMS]
I DON'T LIKE
BEING A MODEL.
NO, I HATE
ALL THIS ATTENTION IS AWFUL,
JUST AWFUL!
AND I'M ONLY DOING IT
BECAUSE RARITY TOLD ME
I MUST, I MUST, I MUST.
[ SIGHS ] I MUST.
OH, REALLY?
WELL...
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE TRUTH, RARITY --
[ SPROING! ]
[ ZIP! ]
W-WHAT WERE YOU
ABOUT TO SAY?
Forever!
NOTHING.
I WAS JUST THINKING --
IF YOU REALLY DON'T LIKE BEING
A MODEL, YOU COULD ALWAYS QUIT.
OH, NO. I COULD NEVER
DO SUCH A THING.
RARITY
WOULD BE DEVASTATED.
BUT RARITY TOLD ME --
[ POP! ]
[ GASPS ]
MMM! JUICY!
[ GROANS ]
OH, IF ONLY ALL THESE PONIES
DIDN'T LIKE ME SO MUCH,
PHOTO FINISH WOULDN'T
WANT ME TO MODEL ANYMORE.
SHE'D FIND
SOMEPONY ELSE WITH...
THE MAGIC.
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
[ DING! ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT! YOU'RE RIGHT!
YOU'RE RIGHT!
[ CROWD GASPS ]
IT'S FLUTTERSHY!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
DON'T YOU SEE?
ON HER OWN, FLUTTERSHY COULD
NEVER DO SOMETHING UNATTRACTIVE.
BUT IF I USE MY MAGIC
TO HELP HER
DO SOMETHING UNATTRACTIVE
AT HER NEXT FASHION SHOW,
NO ONE WILL EVER
WANT HER TO MODEL AGAIN.
AND IF FLUTTERSHY
NO LONGER HAS TO BE A MODEL,
RARITY WILL NO LONGER
HAVE TO BE JEALOUS OF HER.
AND I'LL NO LONGER
HAVE TO KEEP THEIR SECRETS!
IT'S THE PERFECT PLAN!
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYONE ABOUT IT.
PROMISE ME
YOU WON'T TELL ANYONE?!
[ ZIP! ]
SO, YOU DO PROMISE
OR YOU DON'T?
UH, YES!
OBVIOUSLY, THAT'S WHY
I ZIPPED MY MOUTH CLOSED,
THEN LOCKED IT WITH A KEY,
THEN DUG A HOLE,
THEN BURIED THE KEY,
THEN BUILT A HOUSE ON TOP OF THE
HOLE WHERE I BURIED THE KEY,
THEN MOVED INTO THE HOUSE
ON TOP OF THE HOLE!
OBVIOUSLY.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
[ ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING ]
YOU REALLY THINK
IT'LL WORK?
THEY LOVE YOU
FOR BEING YOU,
SO ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS MAKE YOU NOT BE YOU.
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
I GUESS IT'S TIME TO SEE
WHAT ALL THE FUSS IS ABOUT.
[ TINKLING ]
[ RECORD SCRATCHES ]
[ CROWD GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BOING! ]
UHHH...
[ HONK! ]
AAH!
[ CROWD GASPS ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ BARK! BARK! ]
[ CROWD GASPS ]
OH, NO.
[ HEE-HAW! ]
[ CROWD BOOING ]
GET HER OFF THE STAGE!
SHE'S AN EMBARRASSMENT
TO ALL THINGS FASHION!
I, PHOTO FINISH,
HAVE MADE A TERRIBLE MISTAKE!
Rarity:
BRAVO! I SAY, BRAVO!
BRAVO?!
WHO COULD POSSIBLY SAY BRAVO
TO THAT HORRID DISPLAY?
[ RARITY STOMPING ]
SUCH ATTITUDE!
SUCH PIZZAZZ!
SHE'S INVENTED AN ENTIRELY
NEW KIND OF MODELING!
WHO IS SAYING
THESE THINGS?
[ GASPS ] IT'S HER!
THE UNICORN IN THE GORGEOUS CAPE
AND HEADDRESS.
NOW, THAT IS A PONY
WHO CLEARLY KNOWS
A THING OR TWO
ABOUT FASHION.
WELL, IF THAT FABULOUS PONY
LIKES IT, THEN I DO, TOO!
BRAVO!
YES!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
[ SIGHS ]
THIS IS AWFUL.
JUST AWFUL.
SOMEHOW I'VE BECOME
MORE POPULAR THAN EVER.
OH, I'M JUST SO FRUSTRATED,
I COULD JUST KICK SOMETHING!
[ GRUNTS GENTLY ]
IF ONLY RARITY DIDN'T WANT ME
TO BE A MODEL SO BADLY.
[ GROANS ]
BUT RARITY --
[ POP! ]
FLUTTERSHY!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M GREAT.
I'M A SUPER-FAMOUS
FASHION MODEL.
WHY WOULDN'T I
BE GREAT?
BECAUSE YOU HA--
OUT THERE
ON THE RUNWAY,
EVERYONE WAS
TURNING ON YOU, AND --
OH, FLUTTERSHY,
IT'S SO AWFUL.
I WANTED THEM TO.
YOU DID?!
OF COURSE SHE DID!
BECAUSE --
I'M JEALOUS!
I WANTED
ALL THE ATTENTION,
AND INSTEAD,
IT WAS GOING TO YOU.
I EVEN STARTED HOPING THAT
YOU WOULD DO SOMETHING SILLY
SO YOUR MODELING CAREER
WOULD BE OVER.
BUT THEN,
WHEN IT STARTED HAPPENING,
ALL I COULD THINK WAS,
"HOW COULD I
WANT YOU TO FAIL
AT SOMETHING
YOU LOVE SO MUCH?"
BUT FLUTTERSHY
DOESN'T --
[ GRUNTS ]
LOVE?
OH, RARITY,
I HATE BEING A MODEL.
YOU DO?
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
THEN WHY
DID YOU KEEP DOING IT?
I WAS AFRAID IF I QUIT,
YOU'D BE MAD AT ME
FOR NOT WANTING TO
"SHINE ALL OVER EQUESTRIA."
AND I THOUGHT
IF I TOLD YOU
HOW JEALOUS I WAS
OF YOUR SUCCESS,
YOU'D THINK
I WAS A TERRIBLE FRIEND.
NEVER.
ALL THIS TIME.
IF WE JUST TOLD EACH OTHER
THE TRUTH.
I PROMISE NEVER TO KEEP
MY FEELINGS A SECRET AGAIN.
ME TOO.
Both:
CROSS MY HEART AND HOPE TO FLY.
STICK A CUPCAKE IN MY EYE.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
YOU WERE BWILLIANT!
BWILLIANT!
I'VE ALREADY GOT
SIX PHOTO SHOOTS
LINED UP
FOR TOMORROW ALONE.
I'M SORRY, PHOTO FINISH,
BUT I DON'T THINK I'LL BE ABLE
TO MAKE ANY OF THEM.
WHA-A-T?
WE GO!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
VHAT HAS JUST HAPPENED?
[ POP! ]
SPIKE HAS A CRUSH
ON RARITY!
[ ZIP! ]
[ SIGHS ]
AND YOU WERE DOING SO WELL.
NOW, THIS IS A WONDERFUL WAY
TO SPEND AN AFTERNOON.
ISN'T IT, THOUGH?
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
BEING A GOOD FRIEND MEANS
BEING ABLE TO KEEP A SECRET,
BUT YOU SHOULD NEVER BE AFRAID
TO SHARE YOUR TRUE FEELINGS
WITH A GOOD FRIEND.
DID YOU GET ALL THAT,
SPIKE?
NO, I DID NOT.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU TOLD SOMEONE
ABOUT MY SECRET FEELINGS
FOR RARITY!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT WAS WRONG OF ME,
AND I'M VERY SORRY.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
NOW WILL YOU TAKE DOWN
MY LETTER TO PRINCESS CELESTIA?
I WOULD LOVE TO,
BUT I'M A LITTLE BUSY
AT THE MOMENT.
[ SIGHS ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS