WHERE'D I PUT THAT?
OH, I THOUGHT I ALREADY --
[ CLATTER! ]
OH, AND I CAN'T FORGET
I'VE GOT TO --
OHH!
HOW AM I EVER
GONNA GET THIS DONE?
ARE YOU SURE
I CAN'T HELP?
I COULD --
NO!
MAYBE JUST A --
NO, THANKS.
HOW ABOUT --
JUST STAND OVER THERE.
BUT --
WHERE YOU'LL BE
OUT OF THE WAY.
RIBBON, RIBBON --
WHERE'S THE RIBBON?!
I GOT IT!
[ CREAKING ]
WHOA!
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
[ CRASH! CRASH! ]
[ CRASH! CLATTER! ]
[ SHATTER! CRASH! CRASH! ]
UM...
I-I'LL JUST GO
AND STAND OVER THERE,
WHERE I'LL BE...
OUT OF THE WAY.
[ ZIP! ]
[ SIGHS ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
WON'T YOU AT LEAST LET ME
HELP YOU CLEAN UP?
NO. YOU'VE HELPED ME
QUITE ENOUGH.
I'M SORRY, SIS.
I JUST THOUGHT THAT
IF I COULD HELP,
I MIGHT FIND MY SPECIAL GIFT
AND FINALLY EARN MY CUTIE MARK.
I UNDERSTAND.
IT'S JUST THAT...I NEED THIS
TIME TO FILL THIS ORDER
WITHOUT ANY...
COMPLICATIONS.
OKAY, ALL DONE.
NOW BACK TO WORK.
I'VE LOST A LOT OF TIME,
AND I CANNOT HAVE
ANY MORE INTERRUPTIONS.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
OH, WHAT NOW?!
OH, SORRY.
I THOUGHT THE "OPEN" SIGN
MEANT YOU WERE OPEN,
BUT I MUST HAVE BEEN
MISTAKEN.
[ GASPS ]
FLUTTERSHY, FORGIVE ME.
I WAS SO WRAPPED UP
IN MY WORK
THAT I FORGOT YOU WERE BRINGING
OPALESCENCE BACK
FROM HER GROOMING.
NO WORRIES, RARITY.
I'VE LEFT HER THERE
IN THE BASKET.
[ PURRS ]
OH, SHE LOOKS GREAT.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU'RE ABLE TO DO IT.
I CAN'T GET NEAR HER WITHOUT
GETTING A SWIPE FROM HER CLAWS.
[ HISS! SHING! ]
AAH!
DID YOU USE...
THE STARE ON HER?
OH, NO. I WOULDN'T.
I COULDN'T.
I-I DON'T REALLY HAVE ANY
CONTROL OVER WHEN THAT HAPPENS.
I-IT JUST HAPPENS.
NO, I'M JUST GOOD
WITH ANIMALS.
IT'S MY SPECIAL GIFT,
YOU KNOW?
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE A PICTURE
OF OPAL AS A CUTIE MARK
INSTEAD OF
THOSE BUTTERFLIES.
OOH, OOH!
OH, OH, OH, OH!
MAYBE I CAN BE GOOD
WITH ANIMALS, TOO!
[ SHING! ]
OR NOT.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
I'M SORRY I CAN'T INVITE YOU
TO STAY AND CHAT, FLUTTERSHY.
I'VE BITTEN OFF A BIT MORE
THAN I CAN CHEW WITH THIS ORDER.
BUT YOU'RE NOT EATING
ANYTHING.
NO, SWEETIE,
IT'S AN EXPRESSION.
IT MEANS THAT I'VE TAKEN ON
MORE WORK THAN I CAN HANDLE.
I'VE GOT 20 OF THESE
SPECIAL ROBES TO MAKE TONIGHT.
THEY'RE DUE IN TROTTINGHAM
TOMORROW MORNING.
[ TWINKLING ]
[ GASPS ]
SEE? I'VE LINED THEM
IN A SPECIAL GOLD SILK.
IT TOOK SO LONG TO MAKE,
BUT I THINK IT ADDS
JUST THE RIGHT TOUCH, DON'T YOU?
THESE ARE LOVELY,
BUT 20 BY TONIGHT?
HOW WILL YOU
GET IT ALL DONE?
WELL, I, UH...
OH, OH, OH!
MAYBE I COULD...JUST --
JUST STAND OVER HERE
AND WATCH.
I'LL MANAGE.
WELL, MAYBE I SHOULD GET OUT
OF YOUR MANE SO YOU CAN WORK.
HI, FLUTTERSHY!
HI, RARITY!
HELLO, UH, GIRLS.
HEY, SWEETIE BELLE!
SCOOTALOO!
APPLE BLOOM!
YOU READY
FOR TONIGHT?
YEP. CUTIE MARK
PLANNING SESSION IS A GO!
TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT
WE EACH TRY TO FIND
OUR OWN SPECIAL TALENT.
EVEN IF IT TAKES US
ALL NIGHT.
I'M READY.
YOU READY?
VERY READY.
Together: CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS'
SLEEPOVER AT RARITY'S!
YAY!
Sweetie Belle: AND...
LOOK WHAT I MADE US.
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
WHOA!
WOW!
[ LAUGHS ]
THAT'S SO COOL!
WHAT DOES THAT PATCH
ON YOUR CAPE MEAN?
Together:
THE CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS!
YAY!
WE'RE ON A CRUSADE,
A MISSION...
TO FIND
OUR CUTIE MARKS.
YEP, AND LOOK --
I LINED THEM
WITH THIS SPECIAL GOLD SILK.
IT TOOK SO LONG TO MAKE,
BUT I THINK IT ADDS
JUST THE RIGHT TOUCH, DON'T YOU?
OOOH.
AAH!
SWEETIE BELLE,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
THAT WAS THE LAST
OF THE GOLD SILK!
OH, NOW I'LL HAVE TO MAKE MORE!
[ GASPS ]
OH, I HOPE I CAN MAKE MORE.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO WORK
ALL NIGHT, WHICH MEANS --
SORRY, GIRLS.
I'M AFRAID THE CRUSADERS'
SLEEPOVER IS CANCELED.
WHAT?!
I JUST WON'T HAVE ANY TIME
TO WATCH YOU
IF I WANT TO GET THESE ROBES
DELIVERED ON TIME.
BUT --
NO "BUTS" THIS TIME.
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE BELLE.
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT HAS TO BE.
AW!
I, UH -- I SUPPOSE I COULD
TAKE THEM FOR THE NIGHT.
I COULDN'T ASK YOU
TO DO THAT.
OH, IT'S NO PROBLEM
AT ALL.
HAVE YOU MET MY SISTER
AND HER FRIENDS?
A PROBLEM
IS ALL IT WOULD BE.
DID I HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH OPAL?
YOU'VE SEEN HOW WELL
I HANDLE SMALL CREATURES.
I SUPPOSE THAT'S TRUE,
AND I DO HAVE
A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
COME ON.
IT'LL BE FUN.
I ASSURE YOU,
THEY'RE QUITE A HANDFUL.
THESE SWEET
LITTLE ANGELS?
[ TWINKLE! ]
WELL...
ALL RIGHT.
Together:
CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS' SLEEPOVER
AT FLUTTERSHY'S COTTAGE!
YAY!
SO CUTE.
WAIT FOR ME!
OHH.
OH, WON'T THIS BE
EVER SO FUN?
WE CAN HAVE
A NICE LITTLE TEA PARTY
AND BRAID EACH OTHER'S TAILS
AND SIT QUIETLY AND COLOR
AND TELL EACH OTHER
FAIRY TALES AND...
[ BLINK! ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ WHIRL! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
HELLO, FLUTTERSHY.
OH, HELLO, TWILIGHT.
WHERE ARE YOU OFF TO?
I'M HEADING TO THE
EVERFREE FOREST TO ZECORA'S
TO GET SOME OF
MY FAVORITE TEA.
THE -- THE EVERFREE FOREST?
UH, YOU'LL BE CAREFUL,
WON'T YOU?
OF COURSE.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH THE GIRLS?
RARITY HAS A BIG ORDER
TO FILL TONIGHT,
SO I VOLUNTEERED
TO TAKE THE GIRLS
OVER TO MY COTTAGE
FOR A SLEEPOVER.
WOW. SOUNDS LIKE EVERYPONY
HAS THEIR HOOVES FULL TODAY.
TAKING CARE OF THOSE
THREE FILLIES ALL BY YOURSELF --
ARE YOU SURE
YOU CAN HANDLE IT?
WHAT?
THESE SWEET LITTLE ANGELS?
[ TWINKLE! ]
THEY'LL BE NO PROBLEM AT ALL.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ CHIRPING ]
WOW, LOOK AT THIS PLACE!
WHAT'S THAT?!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
NO...PROBLEM AT ALL.
OKAY, GIRLS.
UH, WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
I'M GONNA GET
MY MARK FIRST!
GIRLS...
NUH-UNH!
...SHOULD WE...
I AM!
G-GIRLS,
OKAY, NOW, SETTLE.
I'M STAYING UP
ALL NIGHT!
ME TOO!
ME THREE!
UH, I KNOW
YOU'RE EXCITED,
BUT, GIRLS...
OH. OH, CAREFUL
WITH THE -- OH.
GIRLS.
[ BLOWS ]
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO --
PLAY A GAME?
WE ARE THE CUTIE MARK
CRUSADERS!
AND WE WANT TO CRUSADE
FOR OUR CUTIE MARKS!
UM, AND -- AND WE --
UM, YEAH,
WHAT THEY SAID!
MM, I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT A NICE, QUIET,
LITTLE TEA PARTY?
OR...
WE COULD GO ADVENTURING
IN THE EVERFREE FOREST!
YEAH!
OH, NO.
THE EVERFREE FOREST
IS MUCH TOO DANGEROUS.
IT'S FILLED WITH FAR TOO MANY
STRANGE CREATURES.
BUT YOU COULD GO
WITH US,
AND WE COULD CATCH
THOSE CREATURES.
WE COULD BE, UM,
CREATURE CATCHERS!
YAY!
Together: CUTIE MARK CRUSADER
CREATURE CATCHERS!
RARRR!
I AM A DANGEROUS CREATURE
FROM THE EVERFREE FOREST!
RARRR!
HALT, DANGEROUS CREATURE
OF THE EVERFREE FOREST.
I'M SWEETIE BELLE,
THE CREATURE CATCHER,
AND I'M HERE TO CATCH YOU!
YOU CAN NEVER CATCH ME!
I AM FAR TOO POWERFUL
AND DANGEROUS!
YOU CANNOT RUN FROM ME!
RARRR!
[ LAUGHS ]
UM...OH, MAYBE
THAT'S NOT SUCH A --
NOW, GIRLS, HOW ABOUT WE DO
SOME NICE COLORING?
NO!
COME BACK, DANGEROUS CREATURE,
SO I CAN CATCH YOU!
NEVER!
[ CLATTER! ]
CAREFUL...
...YOU DON'T...
[ CRASH! ]
...BREAK ANYTHING.
SORRY, FLUTTERSHY.
YEAH, SORRY.
I GUESS WE AREN'T
CREATURE CATCHERS.
OH, GIRLS, IT'S OKAY.
I --
I KNOW! WE COULD BE CUTIE MARK
CRUSADER CARPENTERS!
CARPENTERS?
HAMMER.
[ CLATTER! DRILL! ]
UM, THAT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
A TABLE.
WE WERE MAKING A TABLE?
SOMEPONY NEEDS TO PUT THIS THING
OUT OF ITS MISERY.
WE ARE DEFINITELY NOT
CUTIE MARK CARPENTERS.
WHO WANTS A PICTURE OF A HAMMER
ON THEIR FLANK, ANYWAY?
WELL, NOW THAT WE'VE
GOTTEN THAT OUT OF THE WAY,
HOW ABOUT A GAME?
A GAME?
IT'S CALLED "Shh!"
WHAT'S THAT?
WELL, IT'S A GAME ABOUT
WHO CAN BE QUIET THE LONGEST.
SOUND FUN?
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
I'M THE WORLD CHAMP,
YOU KNOW?
I BET YOU CAN'T BEAT ME.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ CREAK! ]
I LOSE!
ME TOO!
ME THREE!
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY.
NOW WHAT CAN WE DO?
OH! HOW ABOUT CUTIE MARK
CRUSADERS COAL MINERS?
YEAH!
NO!
AW!
I MEAN, IT'S TIME FOR BED,
DON'T YOU THINK?
AREN'T YOU EXCITED
TO GET ALL TOASTY AND WARM
IN YOUR SNUGGLY-WUGGLY
LITTLE BEDS?
SNUGGLY-WUGGLY?
BUT WE HAVE
MORE CRUSADING TO DO.
WE'VE GOT PLANS.
AND CAPES!
Fluttershy: UH, OKAY.
UM, MAYBE THE CRUSADING CAN WAIT
UNTIL MORNING
OR WHEN IT'S LIGHT
AND NOT SO...DARK?
HOW ARE WE GONNA FIND
OUR SPECIAL TALENT
IN OUR SLEEP?
[ BLOWS ]
MAYBE YOU'LL HAVE
A LOVELY LITTLE DREAM
ABOUT YOUR SPECIAL TALENT.
BUT WE'RE NOT EVEN TIRED.
HOW ABOUT
I SING YOU A LULLABY?
MM-HMM!
YEAH!
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
* HUSH NOW, QUIET NOW
* IT'S TIME
TO LAY YOUR SLEEPY HEAD *
* HUSH NOW, QUIET NOW
* IT'S TIME TO GO
TO BED *
I KNOW THIS ONE.
OH, HOW WONDERFUL.
WHY DON'T YOU SING IT
WITH ME?
[ COUGHS,
CLEARS THROAT ]
[ DRUM ROLL,
UP-TEMPO SOUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
* HUSH NOW, QUIET NOW
* IT'S TIME TO LAY
YOUR SLEEPY HEAD *
* SAID HUSH NOW, QUIET NOW
* IT'S TIME TO GO TO BED
OKAY, SWEETIE,
THAT WAS --
* DRIFTIN' OFF TO SLEEP
* THE EXCITING DAY BEHIND YOU
* LET THE JOY OF DAYLIGHT
FIND YOU *
THANK YOU, SWEETIE.
I'M --
* HUSH NOW, QUIET NOW
* LAY YOUR SLEEPY HEAD
* SAID HUSH NOW, QUIET NOW
* IT'S TIME TO GO
TO BE-E-E-E-E-E-D *
OW!
[ CHICKENS CLUCKING ]
WHAT IS THAT?
[ GASPS ]
GIRLS!
FLUTTERSHY, YOUR CHICKENS
ARE ON THE LOOSE!
I WONDER
WHAT COULD HAVE CAUSED THAT.
[ CLUCKING CONTINUES ]
DON'T WORRY,
FLUTTERSHY.
THE CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS
WILL HANDLE THIS.
CUTIE MARK CRUSADER
CHICKEN HERDERS!
YEAH!
NO, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A --
UH, COME BACK.
[ LAUGHTER,
INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
PLEASE!
COME ON, GIRLS.
THE CHICKENS ARE FINE.
OH, GIRLS. OH.
[ SHOUTING, CLUCKING CONTINUES ]
GIRLS!
[ SHOUTING STOPS ]
[ CLICKS TONGUE ]
COME ON.
IN YOU GO.
[ WARBLING ]
[ CLUCKS ]
[ WARBLING CONTINUES ]
[ ALL CLUCKING ]
THERE ARE SOME GOOD
CHICKENS.
OKAY. YOU THREE --
ISN'T IT ABOUT TIME
YOU GOT INTO BED?
BUT --
PLEASE?
SO, NO MORE CRUSADING
FOR TONIGHT, ALL RIGHT?
YES,
FLUTTERSHY.
WE PROMISE,
GOOD NIGHT,
FLUTTERSHY.
OKAY, GOOD NIGHT.
Okay, so, what kind of crusading
do we do next?
THERE'S NOT MUCH
WE CAN DO FROM THIS ROOM
UNLESS WE BECOME CUTIE MARK
CRUSADER COTTAGE CLEANERS.
NO, THANKS.
WELL, WE HAVE TO THINK
OF SOMETHING.
WE CAN'T JUST WASTE
THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO FIND OUT
WHAT OUR SPECIAL TALENTS ARE.
HEY, GIRLS!
LOOK!
SOME OF THE CHICKENS
MAY HAVE ESCAPED...
Scootaloo:
INTO THE FOREST.
Together: CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS
CHICKEN RESCUERS ARE GO!
[ SIGHS ]
IT REALLY WASN'T
THAT HARD.
I MEAN,
ALL I NEEDED TO DO
WAS JUST SHOW THEM
WHO'S IN CHARGE.
NOTHING'S GONNA GET PAST
FLUTTERSHY --
GOOD WITH ANIMALS,
GOOD WITH KIDS.
WAIT UP!
[ OWL HOOTS ]
MM, PEACE AND QUIET.
[ GASPS ]
TOO QUIET.
GIRLS?
ELIZABEAK!
SHE'S MISSING!
GIRLS?
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
THEY MUST HAVE GONE LOOKING
FOR MY MISSING CHICKEN,
WHICH MEANS
THEY MUST HAVE GONE INTO...
[ GASPS ]
[ GULPS ]
THE EVERFREE FOREST!
THOSE GIRLS
HAVE REALLY DONE IT THIS TIME.
THEY'VE REALLY BITTEN OFF
MORE THAN THEY CAN CHEW...
OH, JUST LIKE ME.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE OFFERED
TO WATCH THEM.
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
[ HOOTS ]
HERE, CHICK, CHICK,
CHICK, CHICK, CHICK!
[ CLUCKING ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CALLING
FOR THE CHICKEN.
THAT IS NOT HOW YOU CALL
A CHICKEN.
OH, AND YOU KNOW HOW
TO CALL A CHICKEN?
I KNOW
THAT'S NOT THE WAY.
THEN SHOW ME.
I DON'T HAVE TO
SHOW YOU.
YOU'RE JUST CHICKEN.
AM NOT!
OH, WAIT! NOW I KNOW
HOW TO CALL A CHICKEN.
"SCOOTALOO!
SCOOT, SCOOTALOO!"
THAT'S SO FUNNY,
I FORGOT TO LAUGH.
YOU ALSO FORGOT
HOW TO CALL A CHICKEN.
WHY, YOU --
PBHT!
Sweetie Belle:
COME ON, GUYS.
WE'RE NOT GONNA FIND THE CHICKEN
OR OUR CUTIE MARKS
BY ARGUING.
[ WIND RUSHING ]
MAYBE THAT'S
OUR SPECIAL TALENT -- ARGUING.
IS NOT!
IS TOO!
ANYTHING YET?
NO.
DARN.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
HERE, CHICK, CHICK,
CHICK, CHICK!
[ CLUCKING ]
GIRLS?
[ GULPS ]
[ SQUEALS ]
[ GASPS ]
GET AHOLD OF YOURSELF,
FLUTTERSHY.
JUST PUT ONE HOOF
IN FRONT OF THE OTHER.
[ SNAP! ]
AAH!
WHAT WAS THAT?!
AAAH!
TWILIGHT?
IS THAT YOU?
OH, TWILIGHT,
IT IS YOU.
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE HERE.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
THE GIRLS ARE OUT HERE
SOMEWHERE, AND I'M
AFRAID THAT THEY'RE...
[ GASPS ]
W-WHAT'S HAPPENED TO YOU?!
OH!
OH, NO!
IF YOU'VE BEEN TURNED TO STONE,
IT MUST MEAN --
OH!
OH, NO! THE GIRLS!
DON'T MOVE.
I'LL BE BACK FOR YOU.
GIRLS!
IS NOT!
IS TOO!
GIRLS!
OUR SPECIAL TALENT
IS NOT ARGUING.
BESIDES, WHAT WOULD
THE CUTIE MARK
OF SOMEPONY WHOSE TALENT
IS ARGUING EVEN LOOK LIKE?
Fluttershy:
GIRLS? GIRLS?
FLUTTERSHY?!
GIRLS, THANK GOODNESS
I FOUND YOU.
FLUTTERSHY, WHAT --
GIRLS, WE HAVE TO LEAVE
THE FOREST AT ONCE!
BUT WE HAVEN'T FOUND
THE CHICKEN YET.
THERE'S NO TIME
FOR THAT.
THERE'S A COCKATRICE
ON THE LOOSE.
A COCKA-WHAT-NOW?
A COCKATRICE.
IT'S A FRIGHTENING CREATURE
WITH THE HEAD OF A CHICKEN
AND THE BODY OF A SNAKE.
NOW, COME ON.
Scootaloo: THE HEAD OF A CHICKEN
AND THE BODY OF A SNAKE?
[ GASPS ]
THAT DOESN'T SOUND SCARY.
THAT SOUNDS SILLY.
WELL, IF I EVER SAW ONE OF THEM
COCKA-THINGIES FACE-TO-FACE,
I'D LAUGH
AT HOW SILLY IT WAS.
NO! NEVER LOOK ONE
IN THE EYE.
IF YOU LOOK A COCKATRICE
IN THE EYE --
THE CHICKEN!
GIRLS, WAIT!
Together: HERE, CHICK, CHICK,
CHICK, CHICK, CHICK!
[ CLUCKING ]
[ ANIMAL GROWLS ]
Sweetie Belle:
THERE HE IS!
TWO CHICKENS?
I-I THOUGHT
ONLY ONE ESCAPED.
GRAB THEM BOTH!
[ GROWLS ]
[ CROWS ]
[ CLUCKING ]
[ WARBLING ]
[ TINKLING ]
AAAAH!
[ THUD! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
SEE? NOW WE HAVE TO --
AAAH!
GIRLS, PLEASE.
GIRLS. LISTEN TO ME, GIRLS.
I -- PLEASE.
[ GIRLS SCREAMING ]
[ CROWS ]
GIRLS...
BEHIND ME NOW!
[ CROWING ]
[ CROWING CONTINUES ]
YOU!
JUST WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE,
GOING AROUND,
TURNING OTHERS INTO STONE?
[ CROWS ]
[ WARBLING ]
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELF.
I HAVE HALF A MIND
TO FIND YOUR MOTHER
AND TELL YOU WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN UP TO, YOUNG MAN.
[ GROWLS ]
NOW, YOU GO OVER THERE
AND TURN ELIZABEAK
AND MY FRIEND TWILIGHT
BACK TO NORMAL.
[ SQUAWKS ]
AND DON'T EVER LET ME CATCH YOU
DOING THIS AGAIN!
[ TINKLING ]
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
[ CLUCKING ]
ARE YOU GIRLS ALL RIGHT?
I WAS SO WORRIED.
YEAH, FINE.
THANKS TO THAT
STARE OF YOURS.
YOU'RE LIKE THE QUEEN OF STARES.
YOU'RE THE...
STARE MASTER!
WE'RE SORRY WE SNUCK OUT OF
THE HOUSE AND INTO THE FOREST.
YEAH, WE'LL LISTEN TO YOU
FROM NOW ON.
WE PROMISE.
OH, YOU DO, DO YOU?
WELL, YOU'D BETTER,
OR I'LL GIVE YOU...THE STARE.
[ WARBLING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT...
WHAT HAPPENED?
[ CHICKEN CLUCKING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND THAT'S WHEN IT BROUGHT YOU
BACK FROM STONE.
THIS IS GONNA MAKE
QUITE A LETTER TO THE PRINCESS.
I WAS WRONG ABOUT YOU.
YOU CERTAINLY DO KNOW
HOW TO HANDLE THOSE GIRLS.
OH, I WOULDN'T GO
THAT FAR.
HMM? HOW SO?
I ASSUMED THAT I'D BE
JUST AS GOOD WITH KIDS
AS I AM WITH ANIMALS.
BOY, WAS I WRONG.
I REALLY LEARNED
THE HARD WAY
NOT TO BITE OFF
MORE THAN I COULD CHEW.
YOU AND RARITY BOTH.
GOOD MORNING, RARITY.
DID YOU FINISH
ALL THOSE CAPES?
[ SIGHS ]
JUST DELIVERED THEM.
I HAVE TO ADMIT --
IF YOU HADN'T COME ALONG,
I MIGHT NOT HAVE.
THANKS AGAIN.
WON'T YOU STAY
FOR SOME TEA?
I REALLY MUST GET BACK
TO THE SHOP AND CLEAN UP.
GIRLS, GET YOUR THINGS.
TIME TO GO.
GIRLS?
[ LAUGHTER ]
GIRLS, TIME TO --
WHOO-HOO!
YEAH! THAT WAS SO FUN!
GIRLS, YOUR THINGS!
OH, YEAH!
MY TURN! MY TURN!
GIRLS, IT'S TIME TO --
[ SIGHS ]
COME ON!
GIRLS!
SERIOUSLY.
ALLOW ME.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
GIRLS.
[ SILENCE ]
YES, FLUTTERSHY?
YOU CALLED?
GO AND GET
YOUR THINGS.
RARITY'S HERE
TO SEE YOU HOME.
OF COURSE, FLUTTERSHY.
RIGHT AWAY.
H-HOW DID YOU --
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
[ TINK! ]
I GUESS I'M JUST AS GOOD
WITH KIDS AS I AM WITH ANIMALS.
THANKS, FLUTTERSHY!
BYE!
THANK YOU,
STARE MASTER!
BYE-BYE!
UH, UH,
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
I COULD USE YOUR HELP
WITH OPAL.
OF COURSE.
HOW ABOUT LATER TODAY?
[ OPAL MEOWS ]
HOW ABOUT NOW?
[ GROANS ]
[ OPAL YOWLS ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS