"ELEMENTS OF HARMONY.
SEE "MARE IN THE MOON"?
BUT THAT'S JUST
AN OLD PONIES' TALE.
"SHE WILL BRING
ABOUT NIGHTTIME ETERNAL."
IT'S IMPERATIVE THAT
THE PRINCESS IS TOLD RIGHT AWAY.
[ GULPS ]
SEE? I KNEW SHE WOULD WANT
TO TAKE IMMEDIATE ACTION.
"MY DEAR TWILIGHT,
"THERE IS MORE TO A YOUNG PONY'S
LIFE THAN STUDYING.
MAKE SOME FRIENDS."
[ GASPS ]
ALL THE PONIES IN THIS TOWN
ARE CRAZY!
I HOPE THE PRINCESS WAS RIGHT.
SHE'S GONE!
OH, NO.
NIGHTMARE MOON.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
* MY LITTLE PONY
* AH-AH-AH-AH
* I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE *
* MY LITTLE PONY
* UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
THIS MAGIC WITH ME *
* BIG ADVENTURE
* TONS OF FUN
* A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG *
* SHARING KINDNESS
* IT'S AN EASY FEAT
* AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE *
* YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY
* DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? *
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
SEIZE HER!
ONLY SHE KNOWS
WHERE THE PRINCESS IS!
STAND BACK, YOU FOOLS!
[ ZING! ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ PONIES SCREAM ]
[ STRAINS ]
[ SNAP! ]
COME BACK HERE!
[ PANTING ]
NIGHTTIME...FOREVER?
[ HOOFBEATS ]
WHERE'S SHE GOING?
[ MUMBLING ]
WE GOT TO STOP NIGHTMARE!
[ SNORING ]
YOU'VE BEEN UP ALL NIGHT,
SPIKE.
YOU ARE A BABY DRAGON,
AFTER ALL.
[ CRASH! ]
ELEMENTS, ELEMENTS, ELEMENTS.
UGH!
HOW CAN I STOP NIGHTMARE MOON
WITHOUT THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY?
AND JUST WHAT ARE
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY?
AND HOW DID YOU KNOW
ABOUT NIGHTMARE MOON, HUH?
ARE YOU A SPY?
WHOA!
[ SIGHS ]
SIMMER DOWN, SALLY.
SHE AIN'T NO SPY.
BUT SHE SURE KNOWS
WHAT'S GOING ON.
DON'T YOU, TWILIGHT?
I READ ALL ABOUT THE PREDICTION
OF NIGHTMARE MOON.
SOME MYSTERIOUS OBJECTS
CALLED THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY
ARE THE ONLY THINGS
THAT CAN STOP HER.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY ARE,
WHERE TO FIND THEM.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THEY DO.
"THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY:
A REFERENCE GUIDE."
HOW DID YOU FIND THAT?
[ Singsongy voice ]
IT WAS UNDER "E"!
OH.
[ TINKLING ]
"THERE ARE SIX ELEMENTS
OF HARMONY,
"BUT ONLY FIVE ARE KNOWN --
"KINDNESS, LAUGHTER, GENEROSITY,
HONESTY, AND LOYALTY.
"THE SIXTH
IS A COMPLETE MYSTERY.
"IT IS SAID THE LAST-KNOWN
LOCATION OF THE FIVE ELEMENTS
"WAS IN THE ANCIENT CASTLE
OF THE ROYAL PONY SISTERS.
IT IS LOCATED
IN WHAT IS NOW..."
Together:
THE EVERFREE FOREST?!
WHEE! LET'S GO!
NOT SO FAST.
LOOK, I APPRECIATE
THE OFFER,
BUT I'D REALLY RATHER DO THIS
ON MY OWN.
NO CAN DO, SUGAR CUBE.
WE SURE AIN'T LETTING
ANY FRIEND OF OURS
GO INTO THAT CREEPY PLACE
ALONE.
WE'RE STICKING TO YOU
LIKE CARAMEL ON A CANDY APPLE.
MM-HMM.
ESPECIALLY IF THERE'S
CANDY APPLES IN THERE.
WHAT?
THOSE THINGS ARE GOOD.
[ SIGHS ]
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
Fluttershy: SO, NONE OF YOU HAVE
BEEN IN HERE BEFORE?
Rarity: OH.
H-HEAVENS, NO.
JUST LOOK AT IT.
IT'S DREADFUL!
AND IT AIN'T NATURAL.
FOLKS SAY IT DON'T WORK
THE SAME AS EQUESTRIA.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
NO PONY KNOWS.
YOU KNOW WHY?
RAINBOW, QUIT IT.
'CAUSE EVERY PONY
WHO'S EVER COME IN
HAS NEVER COME...OUT!
[ ALL SCREAM ]
FLUTTERSHY, QUICK!
OH, MY GOODNESS.
OH, MY GOODNESS!
AAH!
HOLD ON.
I'M A-COMIN'.
APPLEJACK, WHAT DO I DO?
[ DING! ]
LET GO.
ARE YOU CRAZY?!
NO, I AIN'T.
I PROMISE YOU'LL BE SAFE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
NOW, LISTEN HERE.
WHAT I'M SAYING TO YOU
IS THE HONEST TRUTH.
LET GO, AND YOU'LL BE SAFE.
[ SCREAMS ]
PHEW.
AAH!
SORRY, GIRLS.
I'M NOT USED TO HOLDING ANYTHING
MORE THAN A BUNNY OR TWO.
[ GROWLS ]
Rainbow Dash:
AND ONCE PINKIE AND RARITY
WERE SAFE -- WHOA! --
ME AND FLUTTERSHY
LOOP-THE-LOOPED AROUND
AND -- WHAM! -- CAUGHT YOU
RIGHT IN THE NICK OF TIME.
YES, RAINBOW, I WAS THERE,
AND I'M VERY GRATEFUL.
BUT WE GOT TO -- [ GASPS ]
A MANTICORE!
[ GROWLS ]
WE'VE GOT TO GET PAST HIM.
TAKE THAT, YOU RUFFIAN!
[ ROARS ]
MY HAIR!
[ GROWLS ]
AAH!
WAIT.
[ THUD! ]
YEE-HAW!
GET ALONG, LITTLE DOGGY!
WAIT.
WHOA!
ALL YOURS, PARTNER.
I'M ON IT.
WAIT.
[ GROWLS ]
AAH!
RAINBOW!
[ GROWLS ]
[ SNORTS ]
WAIT!!
[ GROWLS ]
Fluttershy: SHH.
IT'S OKAY.
[ TINK! ]
OH, YOU POOR, POOR
LITTLE BABY.
LITTLE?
NOW, THIS MIGHT HURT
FOR JUST A SECOND.
[ POINK! ]
[ ROARS ]
FLUTTERSHY!
[ PURRS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, YOU'RE JUST A LITTLE OLD
BABY KITTY, AREN'T YOU?
YES, YOU ARE.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE THORN?
I DIDN'T.
SOMETIMES WE ALL JUST NEED TO BE
SHOWN A LITTLE KINDNESS.
[ TINKLING ]
[ SHUDDERS ]
MY EYES
NEED A REST
FROM ALL THIS ICKY MUCK.
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT
LITERALLY.
Pony: THAT ANCIENT RUIN COULD BE
RIGHT IN FRONT OF OUR FACES,
AND WE WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
Pony #2:
I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
Pony #3: MY APOLOGIES.
Pony: ARE YOU THERE?
Pony #2: RIGHT HERE.
Applejack: OH, WAIT.
I THINK
I STEPPED IN SOMETHING.
[ SCREAMS ]
IT'S JUST MUD.
AAH!
[ GROWLING ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
Pinkie Pie: [ LAUGHS ]
HUH?
[ LAUGHING ]
BLEH! OOH!
BL-BL-BL-BL-BL!
[ LAUGHS ]
PINKIE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
RUN!
OH, GIRLS, DON'T YOU SEE?
* WHEN I WAS A LITTLE FILLY
AND THE SUN WAS GOING DOWN *
TELL ME SHE'S NOT.
* THE DARKNESS
AND THE SHADOWS *
* THEY WOULD
ALWAYS MAKE ME FROWN *
SHE IS.
* I'D HIDE UNDER MY PILLOW
* FROM WHAT I THOUGHT I SAW
* BUT GRANNY PIE
SAID THAT WASN'T A WAY *
* TO DEAL WITH FEARS AT ALL
THEN WHAT IS?
* SHE SAID, "PINKIE,
YOU GOT TO STAND UP TALL *
* LEARN TO FACE YOUR FEARS
* YOU'LL SEE
THAT THEY CAN'T HURT YOU *
* JUST LAUGH
TO MAKE THEM DISAPPEAR" *
HA HA HA.
[ BOING! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
* SO GIGGLE AT THE GHOSTIE
* GUFFAW AT THE GROSSLY
* CRACK UP AT THE CREEPY
* WHOOP IT UP WITH THE WEEPY
* CHORTLE AT THE KOOKY
* SNORTLE AT THE SPOOKY
* AND TELL
THAT BIG, DUMB SCARY FACE *
* TO TAKE A HIKE
AND LEAVE YOU ALONE *
* AND IF HE THINKS
HE CAN SCARE YOU *
* THEN HE'S GOT
ANOTHER THING COMING *
* AND THE VERY IDEA
OF SUCH A THING *
* JUST MAKES YOU WANT TO
[ LAUGHS ]
OH.
* LAUGH
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ BOING! BOING! ]
[ LAUGHTER CONTINUES ]
[ WHISTLE! WHISTLE! WHISTLE! ]
HOW ARE
WE GONNA CROSS THIS?
[ CREATURE SOBBING ]
HUH?
[ SOBBING CONTINUES ]
WHAT A WORLD.
WHAT A WORLD!
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS JUST SITTING HERE,
MINDING MY OWN BUSINESS,
WHEN THIS TACKY LITTLE CLOUD
OF PURPLE SMOKE
JUST WHISKED PAST ME
AND TORE HALF OF MY BELOVED
MUSTACHE CLEAN OFF.
AND NOW I LOOK
SIMPLY HORRID!
[ Sobbing ] OH!
OH!
UH!
OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
THAT'S WHAT ALL THE FUSS
IS ABOUT?
WHY, OF COURSE IT IS.
HOW CAN YOU BE
SO INSENSITIVE?
OH, JUST LOOK AT HIM.
SUCH LOVELY,
LUMINESCENT SCALES.
[ SNIFFLES ] I KNOW.
AND YOUR
EXPERTLY COIFFED MANE.
OH, I KNOW, I KNOW!
YOUR FABULOUS MANICURE.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S SO TRUE.
ALL RUINED
WITHOUT YOUR BEAUTIFUL MUSTACHE.
IT'S TRUE!
I'M HIDEOUS!
I SIMPLY CANNOT LET
SUCH A CRIME AGAINST FABULOSITY
GO UNCORRECTED.
[ CRUNCH! PLINK! ]
OW!
WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
[ TWINKLE! ]
RARITY, WHAT ARE YOU --
[ SLASHING ]
OOHHH!
[ THUD! ]
[ TINKLING ]
OH-HO-HO-HO-HO!
MY MUSTACHE!
HOW WONDERFUL!
YOU LOOK SMASHING.
OH, RARITY...
YOUR BEAUTIFUL TAIL.
OH.
IT'S FINE, MY DEAR.
SHORT TAILS ARE IN
THIS SEASON.
BESIDES,
IT WILL GROW BACK.
SO WOULD THE MUSTACHE.
[ GASPS ]
WE CAN CROSS NOW.
LET'S GO.
AAH!
ALLOW ME.
[ BOING! BOING! ]
THERE IT IS!
THE RUIN THAT HOLDS
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY.
WE MADE IT.
TWILIGHT!
WAIT FOR US!
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
WHOA!
WHAT'S WITH YOU
AND FALLING OFF CLIFFS TODAY?
[ SIGHS ]
NOW WHAT?
DUH.
OH, YEAH.
Female voice: [ Echoing ]
RAINBOW.
[ GASPS ] WHO'S THERE?
I AIN'T SCARED OF YOU.
SHOW YOURSELF!
WE'VE BEEN EAGERLY AWAITING
THE ARRIVAL
OF THE BEST FLIER
IN EQUESTRIA.
WHO?
WHY, YOU, OF COURSE.
REALLY?
I MEAN, OH, YEAH, ME.
HEY, UH, YOU WOULDN'T MIND
TELLING THE WONDERBOLTS THAT,
WOULD YOU?
'CAUSE I'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET
INTO THAT GROUP
FOR-LIKE-EVER.
NO, RAINBOW DASH.
WE WANT YOU TO JOIN US,
THE SHADOWBOLTS.
WE'RE THE GREATEST AERIAL TEAM
IN THE EVERFREE FOREST.
AND SOON, WE WILL BE
THE GREATEST IN ALL EQUESTRIA.
BUT FIRST,
WE NEED A CAPTAIN.
[ TING! ]
THE MOST MAGNIFICENT...
YEP.
...SWIFTEST...
YES.
...BRAVEST FLIER
IN ALL THE LAND.
YES.
IT'S ALL TRUE.
WE NEED...
YOU.
WHOO-HOO!
SIGN ME UP.
JUST LET ME TIE THIS BRIDGE
REAL QUICK,
AND THEN WE HAVE
A DEAL.
NO!
IT'S THEM OR US.
Twilight Sparkle: RAINBOW!
WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
OH, NO.
RAINBOW!
DON'T LISTEN TO THEM.
Shadowbolt: WELL?
YOU.
THANK YOU FOR THE OFFER,
I MEAN.
BUT I'M AFRAID
I HAVE TO SAY NO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Pony: YEE-HAW!
Pony #2: YEAH!
WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
GOOD JOB, RAINBOW.
SEE? I'D NEVER LEAVE
MY FRIENDS HANGING.
WHOA!
COME ON,
TWILIGHT.
ISN'T THIS WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR?
Twilight Sparkle:
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY.
WE FOUND THEM.
CAREFUL. CAREFUL.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
UH, THERE'S ONLY FIVE.
WHERE'S
THE SIXTH?
THE BOOK SAID,
"WHEN THE FIVE ARE PRESENT,
A SPARK WILL CAUSE THE SIXTH
ELEMENT TO BE REVEALED."
WHAT IN THE HAY
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
I'M NOT SURE,
BUT I HAVE AN IDEA.
STAND BACK.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
[ TINKLING ]
COME ON, NOW, Y'ALL.
SHE NEEDS TO CONCENTRATE.
AAH!
TWILIGHT!
THE ELEMENTS!
Rarity: WHERE DID SHE GO?
Pony #2: WHAT HAPPENED?
Pony #3:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
TWILIGHT, WHERE ARE YOU?
Rarity: LOOK!
COME ON!
[ COUGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
[ GASPS ]
HM.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ MOANS ]
JUST ONE SPARK.
COME ON, COME ON!
[ ZAP! ]
AAH!
NO! NO!
[ GASPS ]
BUT WHERE'S THE SIXTH ELEMENT?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
YOU LITTLE FOOL!
THINKING
YOU COULD DEFEAT ME.
NOW YOU WILL NEVER SEE
YOUR PRINCESS OR YOUR SUN.
THE NIGHT
WILL LAST FOREVER!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BUZZ! ]
YOU THINK YOU CAN DESTROY
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY
JUST LIKE THAT?
WELL, YOU'RE WRONG,
BECAUSE THE SPIRITS
OF THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY
ARE RIGHT HERE!
WHAT?
APPLEJACK, WHO REASSURED ME
WHEN I WAS IN DOUBT,
REPRESENTS
THE SPIRIT OF HONESTY.
FLUTTERSHY, WHO TAMED THE
MANTICORE WITH HER COMPASSION,
REPRESENTS THE SPIRIT
OF KINDNESS.
PINKIE PIE, WHO BANISHED FEAR BY
GIGGLING IN THE FACE OF DANGER,
REPRESENTS THE SPIRIT
OF LAUGHTER.
RARITY, WHO CALMED A SORROWFUL
SERPENT WITH A MEANINGFUL GIFT,
REPRESENTS THE SPIRIT
OF GENEROSITY.
AND RAINBOW DASH,
WHO COULD NOT ABANDON
HER FRIENDS
FOR HER OWN HEART'S DESIRE,
REPRESENTS THE SPIRIT
OF LOYALTY.
THE SPIRITS
OF THESE FIVE PONIES
GOT US THROUGH EVERY CHALLENGE
YOU THREW AT US.
YOU STILL DON'T HAVE
THE SIXTH ELEMENT.
THE SPARK DIDN'T WORK.
BUT IT DID,
A DIFFERENT KIND OF SPARK.
I FELT IT THE VERY MOMENT
I REALIZED HOW HAPPY I WAS
TO HEAR YOU,
TO SEE YOU,
HOW MUCH I CARED ABOUT YOU.
THE SPARK IGNITED INSIDE ME
WHEN I REALIZED
THAT YOU ALL...
ARE MY FRIENDS.
[ ZAP! ]
YOU SEE, NIGHTMARE MOON,
WHEN THOSE ELEMENTS ARE IGNITED
BY THE -- THE SPARK
THAT RESIDES IN THE HEART
OF US ALL,
IT CREATES THE SIXTH ELEMENT --
THE ELEMENT OF MAGIC.
[ TINKLING ]
NO-O-O-O-O!
NO-O-O-O-O-O!
[ ZAP! ]
[ GROANS ]
MY HEAD.
EVERYPONY OKAY?
Rarity:
OH, THANK GOODNESS!
WHY, RARITY,
IT'S SO LOVELY.
I KNOW.
I'LL NEVER PART WITH IT
AGAIN.
NO, YOUR NECKLACE.
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE
YOUR CUTIE MARK.
WHA-- HUH?
SO DOES YOURS.
[ GASPS ]
LOOK AT MINE!
AW, YEAH!
Applejack:
GEE, TWILIGHT,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST SPOUTING A LOT OF HOOEY.
BUT I RECKON
WE REALLY DO REPRESENT
THE ELEMENTS
OF FRIENDSHIP.
Celestia:
INDEED, YOU DO.
[ TINKLING ]
[ GASPS ]
PRINCESS CELESTIA!
TWILIGHT SPARKLE,
MY FAITHFUL STUDENT.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT.
BUT YOU TOLD ME IT WAS ALL
AN OLD PONY TALE.
I TOLD YOU THAT YOU NEEDED
TO MAKE SOME FRIENDS,
NOTHING MORE.
I SAW THE SIGNS
OF NIGHTMARE MOON'S RETURN,
AND I KNEW IT WAS YOU
WHO HAD THE MAGIC INSIDE
TO DEFEAT HER.
BUT YOU COULD NOT UNLEASH IT
UNTIL YOU LET TRUE FRIENDSHIP
INTO YOUR HEART.
NOW IF ONLY ANOTHER WILL,
AS WELL...
PRINCESS LUNA.
[ GASPS ]
IT HAS BEEN 1,000 YEARS
SINCE I HAVE SEEN YOU
LIKE THIS.
TIME TO PUT OUR DIFFERENCES
BEHIND US.
WE WERE MEANT TO RULE TOGETHER,
LITTLE SISTER.
SISTER?!
WILL YOU ACCEPT
MY FRIENDSHIP?
WHOA!
I'M SO SORRY!
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH,
BIG SISTER.
I'VE MISSED YOU, TOO.
Pinkie Pie:
[ BLOWS NOSE ]
[ SOBBING ]
HEY!
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS CALLS FOR?
A PARTY!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
WHY SO GLUM,
MY FAITHFUL STUDENT?
ARE YOU NOT HAPPY
THAT YOUR QUEST IS COMPLETE
AND YOU CAN RETURN
TO YOUR STUDIES IN CANTERLOT?
THAT'S JUST IT.
JUST WHEN I LEARN HOW WONDERFUL
IT IS TO HAVE FRIENDS,
I HAVE TO LEAVE THEM.
SPIKE, TAKE A NOTE,
PLEASE.
I, PRINCESS CELESTIA,
HEREBY DECREE THAT
THE UNICORN TWILIGHT SPARKLE
SHALL TAKE ON A NEW MISSION
FOR EQUESTRIA.
SHE MUST CONTINUE TO STUDY
THE MAGIC OF FRIENDSHIP.
SHE MUST REPORT TO ME
HER FINDINGS
FROM HER NEW HOME
IN PONYVILLE.
WHOA!
THIS IS GREAT!
OH, THANK YOU,
PRINCESS CELESTIA.
I'LL STUDY HARDER
THAN EVER BEFORE.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
ISN'T THIS EXCITING?
ARE YOU EXCITED?
'CAUSE I'M EXCITED.
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO EXCITED.
WELL, EXCEPT
FOR THE TIME I WENT [GASPS]
BUT, I MEAN, REALLY...
* MY LITTLE PONY
* FRIENDS