♪♪
[birdsong]
Wha! Whoa!
Almost... there.
Agh!
I can't wait!
Twilight's School is supposed
to be amazing inside!
Rarity says there's never
been a school like it.
Ah!
I heard the students get to
do tons of awesome stuff!
Do you see anything yet?
Uh, Yeah!
It looks like... a broom!
And a dustpan...
And some buckets...
That sounds like a closet.
Try another window!
[frightened cries]
Wow!
Who's ready for cupcakes?
[boing boing boing]
[slurp]
They're not for you, silly!
They're for sharing!
First, say something nice.
Like this.
Ocellus, you are
a great listener!
Now you get to
keep one cupcake
and share one with
another creature!
Yona, you're really strong!
[crash]
Whoa!
[thud]
Wow!
All right students, it's time
to meet some new friends!
[excited chatter]
Aaaaah!
[Applejack] Incoming!
[giggling]
That's friendship
in action, y'all.
[chattering]
Wow! And I thought
our school was fun!
Yeah, Miss Cheerilee never
lets us play buckball in class.
I know. I've tried.
Hey!
Why don't we go here instead?
It's still school, right?
Yeah!
[sigh] What could be better
than learning friendship
with your best friends?
Learning friendship with
your best friends and cake!
Chomp!
[laughter]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be. ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me. ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪ ♪
Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[chatter]
Ahem.
Good morning, class!
Today, we're going to
learn about friendship
through the ages.
Spike? Slide one, please.
Back in the days of
Chancellor Puddinghead--
Uh, Spike?
Huh? Sorry,
Twilight.
Still getting used
to my new wings.
They're pretty
great, huh?
Yes, Spike.
As I was saying... huh?
What are you
three doing here?
We wanna go to
your school!
But why?
We want to learn
friendship!
And play Buckball!
I see.
Why don't you
three come with me?
Spike? You're in charge.
Yes!
Hi, Twilight!
Looks like you could use a
guidance counsellor's help!
Hint. Hint.
No thanks, Starlight.
I got this.
Great. Well.
I'll just go dust my office
for the seventieth time.
I'm sorry to have
to tell you this,
but you can't be
my students.
Why not?
Isn't this place
for every creature?
Yes. But we teach
friendship lessons here.
You already know all about
helping ponies in need
and being there
for each other.
Can't you just give
us a chance?
Please?
You need Cheerilee's
classes, not mine.
Hurry up! You don't want late
marks on your permanent record!
O dragon, my dragon!
Spike? What did you do?
Ha ha!
[slam]
[sigh]
Well, I'm not
giving up.
I know we can prove we
belong in this school!
Yeah! Um, how?
By showing Twilight we've
still got lots to learn
about friendship.
And I know just
where to start.
What in tarnation?
Apple Bloom!
You know better than to leave
our good tools out like that.
And aren't you supposed to
be on harvest duty right now?
It's not like the apples
are going anywhere.
What's gotten into you?
Those chores are
your responsibility!
Farm work is family work!
Sorry, Applejack.
Maybe, if I went to
Twilight's School,
I'd learn to be better
at helping the family!
Ah! So that's what
this is all about.
Well, if it's
learning you want,
I'd be happy to give you a
private lesson right now.
Starting with cleanin'
up all this equipment.
[petulant sigh]
Please can I go to
Twilight's school?
[groan]
Please?
I'm going to call
you Repeatie Bell!
We've been through this.
Please let me concentrate!
[frustrated sigh]
How about now?
So there I was, leading the
Wonderbolt formation
into a super-dangerous sundog
spiral, when suddenly
[whooshing sound]
there was a huge storm
cloud in our way!
What happened?
My genius happened!
I changed the
routine on the fly.
And because my crew are such
tight friends, they followed me!
What did you do?
Only the coolest thing ever.
I flew up, did a
super-amazing half twist
into a backflip sonic rainboom.
Hey, I never told that story
to my students before.
Scootaloo.
[nervous laughter]
Never met her.
Aw.
♪♪
They're coming!
Get ready!
Look out!
[yell]
[squeal]
Oof!
Hey! Watch where you are going!
I was watching, watching
you drive like a crazy pony!
Well, maybe if you did not drop
apples all over the street,
I would not have to!
Oh, I've never seen Apple Bloom
and Scootaloo argue like this.
Yeah, they usually go together
like candy canes and stripes.
Whoa!
[oof]
My apples!
This is all your
fault, Scootaloo!
Hey! Sweetie Belle
is the clumsy one.
I'm not talking to either
one of you ever again!
Goodness! They
seem really upset!
It's almost like they
forgot they're friends!
I think it's working.
You are so careless!
Good plan, Apple Bloom!
Careless!
I will show you who is
the one who is careless.
And great acting,
Sweetie Belle.
We're an awesome team!
[Pinke Pie] All right! Yay!
Oops.
You're friends again!
I knew you would be!
Candy cane stripes forever!
[sigh]
Now they'll never let us
into Twilight's school.
OK, we've tried shirkin'
chores, pesterin',
disguises, fightin'...
Hmm. We need to
do something new.
Something unexpected.
[whimpering]
Great idea, Scootaloo!
We haven't tried crying yet!
Yeah! It always
works for Rarity!
I wasn't crying.
I think it's coming
from outside!
[blubbering]
Aw, she looks so sad!
We better go see what's wrong.
Hey, are you ok?
Oh, thank you for asking.
But no.
I'm having real trouble with
[sniffs]
the School of Friendship.
Twilight won't let
you go either, huh?
Oh, no, It's not that.
I'm in her class but
[sob] it's too hard!
[sobbing]
Really?
I just moved here
to go to school,
but everything's so
new and different.
I don't know anypony!
Well, now you do!
I'm Apple Bloom.
This is Sweetie
Belle and Scootaloo.
We're the Cutie
Mark Crusaders!
I'm Cozy Glow.
It's very nice to
meet you.
But I don't know
if I'll stay long.
I'll probably flunk out; I'm
having so much trouble
with my friendship lessons.
[gasp]
We can help with those!
We know all about friendship!
And studying with you
would be almost as good
as being in class!
But why would you help me?
What's in it for you?
That's how
friendship works.
When you give from your heart,
you don't expect anything back.
Well, golly!
If you really mean it,
Mm hm!
I could use some help
with my homework.
I have to do something nice
for each of these ponies.
But I don't know
anything about them.
And it's so hard to talk
to ponies you've never met.
Well, you're in luck.
'Cause we know all
those ponies!
Get ready for a
friendship A plus!
[whoosh]
♪♪
That's Bon Bon.
If you wanna do
something nice for her,
first you gotta figure
out what she needs.
How am I supposed
to do that?
Just pay attention.
Friendship is about
listening to others.
Oh. Ow.
Uh oh. That cactus
keeps pricking her
every step she takes!
If only there was something to
protect her from those spines.
It looks like you need
help carrying your cactus
so here's a safe way
to take it home.
Thank you!
That's so thoughtful!
I did it!
Good job!
But, uh, next time?
Maybe don't give away my helmet.
Oopsie.
♪♪
Green. Purple. Yellow.
And one more purple.
Whew. Sorting all those took
longer than I thought!
You really think Mrs. Cake will
like these new sprinkle shakers?
Mm hm! Now she won't have to use
rainbow sprinkles all the time.
She can just pick
the color she wants!
[door jingles]
Oh, I'm sorry, I
was out to lunch.
Were you fillies
waiting for me long?
No. Um. These
are for you.
Well, what a lovely surprise!
I can't wait to try them out!
Look! I made rainbow sprinkles!
Aren't they wonderful?
But... she... I...
[growl]
At least she likes
her present.
Uh huh.
[crash]
[whistle]
Golly! How'd you know that
would make him so happy?
Friendship means pitching in to
help others' chores go faster.
Especially when their special
somepony's waiting for 'em.
[clanging]
[chatter]
Ugh.
That class was so boring!
Not even Miss Cheerilee
can make the history
of radishes exciting.
I bet they don't have to
learn about that stuff
at Twilight's school.
[crash]
Guess what!
I got an A on my homework!
All right!
Woo hoo!
Nice goin'!
And I never could have
done it without your help.
No problem!
We just wish we
could've done more.
Actually, you can.
Headmare Twilight is
giving us a big test
at the end of the week.
And I could really use
your help studying.
We wanted to go to Twilight's
school more than anything,
but helping you has
been even more fun.
You can count on us!
♪♪
Um, intelligence?
[laughing]
[giggle]
[tittering]
Laughter?
Yes!
Is it control?
♪♪
[whoosh]
Kindness, loyalty, honesty,
generosity, laughter, magic!
Yes!
Woo hoo!
[happy chattering]
How'd the test go?
Were there essay
questions?
Did you remember
what we taught you?
I failed!
[blubbering]
But how could Cozy Glow
fail her friendship test?
Ahem.
I'd like to see you
three in my office.
I know we wanted to
be invited inside.
but it kinda went
different in my head.
I can't believe you'd
do something like this.
Like what?
You are Cozy Glow's
tutors, aren't you?
We've been working
with her for days!
That's what she told me.
So you've been setting
her up to fail?
How?
What?
Huh?
I know you're upset that I
won't let you come to my school.
But to teach Cozy all the
wrong things out of spite,
that's just cruel.
But we taught her
all the right things!
Then how do you explain these
friendship test answers?
What are the six
elements of harmony?
Five turtlenecks
and a cheese grater?
Who is the Princess
of Friendship?
Your mom?
I don't understand.
Me neither.
I never thought you three
would pull such a mean prank.
I'm afraid I'm going
to have to ask you
to stay away from
my school...
and my students.
Oh, no!
[sarcastic] Yay.
Now I'll alphabetize
them in reverse order.
[sigh] Not much need for
a guidance counselor
at a School of Friendship.
Ahem!
Ah!
How much of that
did you hear?
Never mind.
[zap]
Welcome!
Can I get you a comfort pillow?
Security blanket?
Empathy cocoa?
I just need some advice.
Well, I have
plenty of that!
Anecdotes, insight,
midnight confessions...
I'm babbling.
Ahem. Go ahead. I'm listening.
I think I got my
friends in trouble.
They helped me study for my
friendship test and I failed it.
On purpose.
Why would you do that?
Sorry, listening.
The Cutie Mark Crusaders
wanted to go to this school
more than anything.
So I thought if I showed
Headmare Twilight
they're bad at friendship, she'd
let them come here with me!
That's devious!
I mean... I see.
[sip]
I guess I still have a lot
to learn about friendship.
Actually, I think
you're doing all right.
Sure, that was a
really, really bad way
to try to help
your friends.
But what matters
is, you wanted to.
The reason the Cutie Mark
Crusaders don't go to this
school is that they'd make
better teachers than students!
So you do have a
place for them here?
Hmmm.
[chatter]
I bet there's no Wonderful
World of Cleaning lesson
at Twilight's school.
[cough]
We'll never find out now.
[sigh]
I still don't get how
Cozy failed her test
after all that studying!
Or how Twilight could
blame us for it!
Or how gum can be so sticky!
[knocking]
Sorry to interrupt,
Miss Cheerilee,
but can I borrow Apple Bloom,
Sweetie Belle, and Scootaloo?
♪ [sombre military music] ♪
We didn't do anything
wrong, we promise!
I know that. Now.
Which is why I wanted
to talk to you.
Wait. So we're
not in trouble?
Just the opposite.
Cozy Glow, is there
something you'd like to say?
This is all my fault.
I messed up my
test on purpose,
so we could all go
to school together!
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Cozy Glow.
Honesty is one of the
pillars of friendship.
But you already know that.
Which is why I'd like
to give you these.
They're honorary diplomas,
making y'all official
graduates of this here school.
You've more than
earned them.
Without even
having to study!
Yeah!
We are grad-u-ates!
And, if you're interested, I
think Starlight has a place
for you at my school after all.
We can stay?
Really?
Wooo hooo!
We could use some good
friendship tutors on staff.
And I hear you're
the best out there.
Then what're we
waiting for?
Let's get tutoring!
C'mon, Cozy!
And that's why this school needs
you as our guidance counselor.