♪♪
[door opens]
Princess Twilight!
We're glowing!
[giggle] That's what happens
when you're summoned by the
map.
Some pony needs our help?
We're being called by the map?
Did I mention we're glowing?
[laughter]
So where exactly in
Equestria are we needed?
Actually, where you're going
isn't even in Equestria.
Wow. That's almost...
off the table!
But what's way out there?
Mt. Aris.
The home of the Hippogriffs.
And that's where you're headed.
Whooaaaa.
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun! ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness
it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
You really don't need to
come with us, Twilight!
We can take care of this
mission just fine on our own!
Mm-hm!
[Scootaloo] Yeah!
[clatter]
Ugh!
I know that.
But I'm not so
sure the ponies
who care about you
want you going off
so far on your own.
Besides, there's
some school business
I need to take care
of on Mt. Aris.
♪♪
This permission slip
is for Silverstream.
It's very important that her
mother and father sign it,
or else no field trips!
Sounds like somepony
just wants a vacation.
[giggle]
OK, yes, I have been
wanting to visit Mt. Aris
ever since the
Hippogriffs moved back.
But it's purely research.
Silverstream's brother is
going to meet us there,
and take us to their houses.
Wow!
They have more than one house?
I guess so.
The social structure of the
Hippogriffs and Seaponies
is a bit of a mystery.
All aboard!
Last stop, the new
Mt. Aris station!
[excited chatter]
[whistle toots]
[chugging]
I don't know if I'd
like being a Hippogriff.
Part bird, part pony...
I'm happy with just
my pony parts, thanks.
I think Hippogriffs
are pretty neat.
I learned all about
them from Applejack.
The Hippogriffs all once
lived happily on Mt. Aris...
but when the
Storm King invaded,
they used a Magic Pearl
to turn into Sea Ponies
and escaped to the underwater
safety of Seaquestria.
Then, in the Battle
of Canterlot,
when Applejack defeated
the Storm King.
[Twilight] Wait, what? She
told you she defeated him?
By herself?
Maybe she didn't
say that exactly,
but it makes for a
better story.
[chuckle]
[train whistle toots]
[Conductor] Final stop,
Mt. Aris station!
Huh!
[admiring gasp]
♪♪
[squeaking brakes]
[hiss]
All right. So what kind of cutie
mark-related friendship problem
do you think we're
supposed to solve?
I don't know, but hippogriffs
don't have cutie marks,
so it might not have anything
to do with that at all.
Huh. Still the map called us,
so it must be a kind of problem
that only we can solve!
Go crusaders!
But how do we know exactly
who we're supposed to help?
Ahem!
Attention, please!
Anygriff here have a problem?
That's all I got.
Maybe if the map could be
a little more specific
about our mission?
Like maybe an address?
The map doesn't
really work like that.
But I'm sure you, and
whoever needs help,
will find each other.
Excuse me, Miss
Sparkle? Over here!
Sorry I'm late.
I'm Silverstream's brother.
Terramar.
A Hippogriff can have a
Sea Pony for a brother?
How does that work, exactly?
Sssh! It's rude to ask
a question like that!
♪♪
Whoa!
Can I ask now?
It is kind of strange.
See, after the Storm
King was defeated,
the Sea Ponies didn't
have to hide anymore.
So some of them changed
back to Hippogriffs
and went home to Mt. Aris.
But others got used to
living under the water
and stayed in Seaquestria.
And me, well, I kind
of go back and forth.
With this.
It's a tiny piece
of the Magic Pearl.
It was split up
among our kingdoms.
Cool!
Well, I'm pretty eager to
see the Hippogriff village.
You know, to get this form
signed, and research, so...
Hey Terramar, does anygriff you
know up there have a problem
they need help with?
[chuckle] On Mt. Aris?
No, everygriff is
pretty happy up there.
[sigh]
It's a great place to live.
♪♪
[laughing children]
Whoa!
This looks amazing!
Last time I was here,
it was a ghost town!
Yeah! Queen Novo thought
it was important
to return our village
to its former glory.
♪♪
♪ [fanfare] ♪
And now, I
officially open the
"Glad to Be A Hippogriff
Festival!"
[cheering]
[whoosh]
[cheers]
♪♪
[shouts]
[excited shrieks]
Wow! We picked a
good day to show up!
Not really.
We do this every weekend.
Hippogriffs really
like being Hippogriffs.
[cheers]
There's my boy!
Hi, Dad!
Haven't seen you
in days, Son!
Wish you'd come
around more often.
Oh, Dad, these are
Silverstream's friends
from Equestria,
they came up to...
Princess Twilight Sparkle!
[high-pitched shriek]
[shouts]
Attention, Everygriff!
Princess Twilight
Sparkle is here!
She's Silverstream's teacher!
[gasps]
[excited murmurs]
Here to take in the marvel that
is Mt. Aris, Your Highness?
Absolutely!
And to have you sign a
form for Silverstream.
Glad to! But first,
let's show the princess
some real Mt. Aris
hospitality.
To the refreshment tent,
for a stein of salmon juice!
Eh! Research! See you later!
And good luck!
I know you'll find your mission!
Well, your dad's
certainly... outgoing, isn't he?
He's a great guy.
All my relatives are nice.
That's kind of the problem...
Wait, stop!
♪ chiming ♪
What's that
wonderful sound?
Those are the
Harmonizing Heights.
Legend says that...
♪ majestic orchestral theme ♪
[birdsong]
♪♪
[splash]
Woohoo! Yeah! Awesome!
I love this!
Uh... is she OK?
This is absolutely
the best place ever!
You are so lucky!
And you get to
swim in the ocean!
You have two great
places to live!
How do you make up your
mind which one to stay in?
I can't.
That's the problem.
Did you say problem?
You have a problem?
[Sweetie Belle] Yes!
[Sweetie Belle] Whoo hoo!
We discovered our mission!
All right!
We did it!
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Heh heh. Sorry.
You were talking
about your problem?
Right. Like I said, Mt. Aris
is one great place to live.
That's why Silverstream
and my dad
and some of my cousins
came back here.
But seaquestria is another
great place to live.
That's where my mom is.
Oh. I-I didn't know that.
So no matter where I am, I feel
like I'm letting someone down.
No wonder you're having
such a hard time deciding.
And I have to choose soon.
Every other 'griff my age
already knows where they belong.
I'm still not sure.
When in doubt,
chart it out!
Now, we put down everything
great about each place...
and everything not so great.
Compare them, and your
decision is made for you!
Well, it's obvious, isn't it?
Mt. Aris is the best of
all possible worlds.
Pro: It's beautiful!
Con: Too far from Equestria.
I think that pretty
much sums it up.
But, you haven't been
to seaquestria yet.
How can you even compare them?
Terramar's right, Sweetie Belle.
It'd be more fair if we visit
both places before we decide.
Hey, everypony!
this festival is fantastic!
Look what I won at
the ring toss booth!
Ahem! But of course, I'm
really here on business.
Sky Beak's already
signed the form,
now I just need your
mom's signature.
Is she around?
Um, she's a Sea Pony.
In Seaquestria.
That's what Silverstream
meant by "houses."
Mm-hm! If you'd like
to meet my mom,
we're just heading
down there now.
And, how exactly are we
going to visit underwater?
[whoosh]
Wow!
[giggle]
Woooo-hooooo!
Yeah!
Whoa.
This must be just like flying!
Woo-hoo!
Where's your mom's
house, Terramar?
Come on, it's this way!
This is awesome!
[giggling]
♪♪
Mom!
Terramar!
Welcome home, baby!
No excuses, this time
you're staying for dinner!
Scootaloo, Sweetie
Belle, Apple Bloom?
This is my mom, Ocean Flow.
And this is...
[gasp] Princess
Twilight Sparkle!
What an honor!
You know, Silverstream
just raves about you!
Well, she is one of our
most hard-working students.
In fact, I brought this
form for you to sign, so that...
Both my children
are so smart!
Would you like to see
their baby pictures?
Mom!
That sounds adorable,
I'd love to!
And, you know, to find
out about aquatic pony
early development
and uh...
[laughter] Research!
Oh, well maybe your
friends would like a snack
while we're gone?
Some kelp chips?
Fish oil tea?
No thanks, Mom.
I'm gonna go show
them around.
♪♪
Look out!
[giggle]
Can't catch me!
Hmph. Not much sunlight
down here, is there?
[laughter]
♪♪
Boom bada boom bada boom bada
boom bada boom bada
boom bada boom!
No grass to run in and no
hooves to run on it with...
And excuse me, but how do you
keep from getting all pruney?
[sigh]
[giddy laughter]
[thud]
[gurgling] Everything
sounds funny down here!
[gurgle]
OK, I've seen
everything I need to.
So uh, why don't we
find Twilight Sparkle,
finish the chart, and uh,
head back up the mountain?
I have some serious
field-twirling to do.
Where's she going?
I wanna stay and
swim some more!
[sigh]
[squawking]
[shriek]
Princess Twilight,
you're back!
And just in time for the
Screeching Competition!
Why not?
Could be another
trophy in my future!
Be back soon!
All right.
Let's add some positives
to the Seaquestria side...
Uh-huh!
Swimming is like flying,
multi-color fish, and,
did I mention the flying thing?
You forgot the cons.
Dark, wet, sea monsters.
I don't remember
any sea monsters.
Apple Bloom, looks
like it's up to you.
Me? Well, both places have a
lot of good things about them.
I can understand why it's
hard for you to decide.
♪ Your heart is in two places,
You can only live in one ♪
♪ You're torn between the
hilltops and the tide ♪
♪ Thank goodness that the Cutie
Mark Crusaders have begun ♪
♪ To give you hope and
help you to decide ♪
♪♪
♪ These hills, they
call to you ♪
♪ They say
Harmonizing Heights ♪
♪ This is your home ♪
♪ Simple and serene ♪
♪ The sun-dappled leaves ♪
♪ Are a mountain terrace ♪
♪ You can see twenty-three ♪
♪ Different shades of green ♪
♪ To dare to compare ♪
♪ Anywhere to there ♪
♪ Is unfair and
just plain wrong ♪
♪ Colt or mare, or you wear ♪
♪ Feathers, fins, or hair ♪
♪ This is where you belong ♪
Well, on the other hoof, I
can think of a place
that's way more
exciting and cool.
Not to mention more you!
Come on, you know
exactly where I mean!
♪ Seaquestria's the most ♪
♪ You're supposed ♪
♪ To be there ♪
♪ Underneath the sea where ♪
♪ You can feel at home ♪
♪ Swimmin' with your friends ♪
♪ You can spend ♪
♪ All day here ♪
♪ Playing in the bay here ♪
♪ Splashin' in the foam ♪
♪ Sailin' through ♪
♪ The wavy blue ♪
♪ You'll view a slew
of tortoises ♪
♪ Forget the rest ♪
♪ The sea's the best ♪
♪ For all intents and
porpoises ♪
♪ Build your nest ♪
♪ Here on Harmonizing Heights ♪
♪ Live it up here ♪
♪ In Seaquestria ♪
♪ Nothing compares ♪
♪ to Harmonizing Heights ♪
♪ The eagles are regal ♪
♪ But the schools are cooler ♪
♪ Their claws are so awesome ♪
♪ With their sweet maneuvers ♪
♪ Star wishes every night ♪
♪ Starfish by eel light ♪
♪ Better ♪
♪ Wetter ♪
♪ Shinier ♪
♪ Brinier! ♪
♪ Seaquestria ♪
♪ Harmonizing Heights ♪
♪ That's it ♪
♪ This is the end ♪
♪ Don't ever talk to me again ♪
[shattering glass]
♪♪
Terramar! Where are you going?
Ugh! If you all can't even
agree amongst yourselves.
How am I supposed
to make up my mind?
It's hopeless.
♪♪
Hmph!
Sweetie Belle
said to tell you
it's your fault that
Terramar ran off.
Well, you tell Sweetie Belle
that if it weren't for her,
our mission would
have been over by now.
And a success!
[sigh]
Scootaloo says this whole
thing is your fault.
Well, tell her that I'm not the
one who dashed all of Terramar's
hopes and made him
give up on the world.
Both worlds.
[sigh]
Sweetie Belle says it's your
fault that Terramar ra...
Oh, wait, I already told
you that, didn't I?
Uh, what's going on?
Where's Terramar?
Uh. Well, he... kind of left.
He wanted to be by himself.
Which was not my fault.
Mine either!
Well, of course not! Why
would you think that?
Because it was our fault!
All we had to do was help him
choose which world to live in.
And we let him down.
Who ever said that
he had to choose?
Well... he did.
Hmmm...
Maybe Terramar is making it
harder than it has to be.
Yoo-hoo!
Princess!
We're having a seashell
crafting circle, care
to join us?
Actually we're right
in the middle of...
There you are!
The flag folding ceremony
is about to begin!
Thank you, really.
I've had a great time in
both places today, but...
[softly] Wow! This must be how
Terramar feels all the time!
Oh.
Hello, Sky Beak!
Ocean Flow.
You're looking well!
[friendly greetings]
Hm... This gives me an idea.
♪♪
Huh. I thought for sure
he came this way.
[gasp] He did.
And I'm staying here, too.
That way, I don't have to
be on land or in the water.
We're sorry.
We were supposed
to help you, and...
We just ended up
confusing you more.
It's all our fault.
Oh, great.
You're sorry, and
I'm still confused.
I'm staying in my tree.
We might have something
worth coming down for.
♪♪
We thought we'd get
everycreature together
for a picnic on the beach.
And we mean everycreature.
[happy shouts]
[drums]
[splash]
[happy shouts]
[laughter]
Son! There you are!
Your friends told us how
you've been feeling...
and we're sorry if we
ever made you think
you had to choose
between worlds.
That wasn't our
intention, honey.
Your Hippogriff heritage is
something to be proud of,
certainly...
but you're more than
just where you're from,
or who you live with.
We love you because you're you.
No matter where
you choose to be.
You don't have to decide.
You can keep doing
what you've been doing,
going back and forth.
And enjoying both places.
[laughter]
[splash]
Something we forgot to
add that both places have.
Family and friends who love you.
Thanks.
For everything.
Hey, uh... are you glowing?
Yes!
We did it!
Congratulations!
Your first map-mission
is a success.
Guess that means we're
officially done here.
I hope you come visit your
sister in Equestria.
Yeah! Come see us!
You'll love it!
Who knows, you might want
even want to live there!
Yeah, that was a joke.
♪♪