♪♪
Huh?
[whoosh]
Oh!
♪♪
Did I miss the Teacher of
the Month announcement?
You're just in time.
But it's gonna be me.
Yeah, right! I got
this one nailed.
And the Friendship School
teacher of the month is...
Fluttershy!
Ugh. Again?
Come on!
Oh, my. I don't know
how I keep winning.
[click]
Yeah, me neither.
The award is based on
the students' vote.
They must really like you!
Congratulations,
Fluttershy.
[giggle]
Next item of business.
I've been looking
into a new activity
for our friendship classes.
Spike?
Section 147,
paragraph two states
that teamwork is a key
part of friendship.
And section 229, paragraph
nine says outdoor activity
reinforces learning.
Add that together
and what do you get?
Ooh ooh!
OK, lemme see 147,
229 carry the two.
Three hundred and eighty-seven?
Mm-mm. A teamwork field trip!
Leading it is a Teacher
of the Month type-job,
so I thought I'd ask.
I'm yer pony, Twilight.
Sweet Apple Acres has
taught me a thing or two
about workin' together.
Yeah, but being a Wonderbolt's
the definition of teamwork.
Heh heh heh, I'm sure you're
not sayin' fancy flyin'
makes ya a better
choice than me.
Heh heh heh heh, I
wouldn't say better,
just a little
more qualified.
No offense.
Maybe you can lead the
field trip together!
Gah!
Of course!
Who better to model the
importance of working as a team?
Um, Rarity,
Fluttershy, me, Spike.
This flower pot.
Both of you are
teamwork experts.
If the students see the two
of you teaching together,
they'll learn even more.
I know you've been
competitive in the past,
but I'm sure you'd never
let that get in the way of
friendship education!
'A course.
Totally.
[growls]
[laughter]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness
it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
I've never been on
a field trip before.
Yeah, what's the point
of this, exactly?
Getting out of the
classroom, duh.
Yak best at
field tripping!
[thud]
That's what we're doing?
So fun!
[thud]
Heh heh.
Pretty sure the Headmare has
something else in mind.
All right, class.
Today you'll learn how
important working together is
for building a strong
friendship.
Hey y'all!
Ready to get out there
and do some learnin'
the Apple family way?
This is basically gonna
be the best field trip
in the history of ever.
With me in charge, that is.
Heh heh.
With us in charge.
Meanin' mostly me .
Yeah. Good one.
And what teamwork activity do
you two have planned for today?
Canoe-racing.
Shed-building.
No way. We get
to do both?
I bet that's exactly what
your teachers had in mind.
Why don't you start with
shed-building first?
Heh. Don't mind if I do!
Everycreature,
follow the leader!
♪♪
I'll check in later
to see how it's going.
Remember to work together!
[big inhale]
Now take a good deep breath.
What do ya smell?
Ugh. Yak?
[sniffing]
Mm-hm!
Nope. Try again.
Um... apples?
And... Anyone? Anyone? No?
The promise of teamwork!
That there's an apple shed.
And this here is what we're
gonna use to build it!
Nothin' brings friends together
like a little hard work
and honest sweat.
[cackling]
Sweat? Seriously?
That's supposed to be
part of friendship?
Not everypony would
know that, Rainbow Dash.
Just Teacher of the
Month kinda ponies.
Whatever. Let's
just get this done
so we can move on
to my activity!
♪♪
That's it! Measure
twice, and cut once.
Haste makes waste.
Slow and steady.
Emphasis on the slow.
[zoom]
♪♪
[grunts]
Rainbow Dash!
You can't build an
apple shed like that!
Oh, yeah? I just did!
[crash]
Whoa! No way!
[All] Whoa!
Impressive...
if you can call an
apple shed impressive.
Just 'cause it's fast
don't mean it's good.
Oh, sorry!
Can't hear you.
Too busy practicing my
Teacher of the Month pose.
Yeah! Yeah!
Hoo wah!
Don't count your pictures before
they're snapped, Rainbow Dash.
Oh, come on!
These students are
totally gonna vote
for a teacher who
gets things done!
No, they're gonna
vote for a teacher
who gets things done right!
Yeah, this isn't awkward at all.
♪♪
[hammering]
[Applejack] Steady, steady.
Take her nice and slow.
Little to the left.
A hair to the right.
Now a hoofshavin' higher.
Grrrr.
Just bring it down already!
[shouts]
[smash]
Heh heh.
I'll give ya one guess whose
side is still standin.'
Yak side!
[crash]
[sheepish laugh]
[groan]
Um, professors?
I'm a little confused
about teamwork now.
That's because you need
a different teacher.
Follow me!
Last one to the stream
is a rotten apple shed!
[zoom]
[groan]
Who's ready to smash the all-
time Equestria speed record
for river canoeing?
Is that even a thing?
First I've heard of it.
We need to get to the finish
line before this alarm goes off!
That means you gotta move fast!
[whoosh]
Any questions?
Um. Yona have questions.
No time for 'em!
Get in the boat.
♪♪
You really think winnin'
some canoin' record
is gonna get you that
teacher of the month trophy?
I'm pretty sure every creature's
gonna like it a lot better
than pounding nails
and cutting wood.
Yak not like water.
Sometimes, when I'm scared to
try something new, I whistle.
[whistle]
We got you, Yona.
[panicked shout]
Way I see it, Twilight's gonna
give that teachin' trophy
to a teacher, not a racer.
We'll see about that.
[splashing]
Stroke! Stroke! Stroke! Harder!
Put your back into it, newbies!
Stroooke, stroooke,
stroooke, slower!
Focus on your paddle
technique, y'all!
Whoo hoo!
We're really going now!
So, when do we get to
the part when we move?
When everycreature
starts listening to me.
The leader of my
activity, Applejack.
Now stroke!
♪♪
Dig in team!
We can still beat that record!
Stop!
Go!
Which way do we go?
Left!
Right!
Aye-aye, captains!
Wait, what?
Left!
I can see the finish
line from here!
If we go left, we'll
be headin straight
into the Bite-acuda fish!
Who cares about a few fish?
Uh, professors?
You'll care plenty
when they bite ya!
Guys?
[Rainbow Dash] We'll just
go around them.
Rock!
[screams]
[crash]
[splashing]
[gasping and coughing]
♪♪
[giggle]
[weak whistle]
[rip]
I love field trips!
I hope you're happy.
Obviously not, because there
goes our new speed record!
[choking]
Help!
Yak not swim!
♪ adventure music ♪
That's OK.
Your friends can change
into creatures that do!
[Twilight] How's the
canoeing going?
About as good as the
apple shed building.
I totally had things
under control,
until Applejack messed 'em up.
I did not!
Did too!
Did not!
Yeah. It's been
like this all day.
I wouldn't say
all day.
Just, 99% of it.
I can't believe this!
You're not teaching teamwork,
you're competing
with each other.
I thought you were past that!
We are!
Mostly.
We got carried away with
wantin' to be the Teacher
of the Month, is all.
The Teacher of the
Month wouldn't care
about being the
Teacher of the Month!
I know Fluttershy
would be thrilled
to see another pony win.
That's it!
I'm taking over
this field trip.
Hold up, Twilight.
Don't count out Rainbow Dash
for the award just yet.
You should've seen her fire up
those students to build a shed!
No way! You're the one
the students listen to.
Besides, you saved us from
those pony-eating fish.
Long story.
But Applejack should definitely
be teacher of the month.
Hmmm. Maybe you two have
learned something after all.
Does that mean you'll give us
another chance at the Teacher of
...Field Trip?
Well...
C'mon, Twilight.
We get it.
No more arguing.
Right, Applejack?
Right as rain and
twice as fresh!
Fine.
But I'm picking the next
activity you two lead.
A nature walk.
Nopony could possibly
argue over that.
Right?
Right!
See?
We're agreein' already!
♪♪
Well, look at that!
The path splits up ahead.
Left or right?
Here we go again.
Where to, Rainbow Dash?
I was thinking right.
Unless you want to go left.
Because what makes you
happy, makes me happy.
Ah, heck, forget about me.
You want to go right,
we'll go right.
But teamwork means listening to
other ponies, so it's up to you.
Well, aren't you as
sweet as sugar apple pie.
But it's up to you.
Grrrr. Follow me.
Yak know best way.
Hey, where y'all goin'?
♪♪
I think we've gone in the
same circle five times.
Only because 'someponies'
won't make up their minds
about which way to go.
Do you want to keep going
in a circle, Applejack?
Up to you, Rainbow
Dash. I insist.
No no, I insist.
But I insisted first.
Are we still on a field trip?
Cause this just feels
like being lost.
We can still get back
to school before dark
if we cross that ravine
and stop doubling back.
We knew that.
All part of our plan,
right, Applejack?
Yep. All we have to
do is build a bridge
across that giant canyon
and we're home free!
That is if, if you think
a bridge is a good idea.
Only if you want
to build a bridge.
Stop!
Listen, we can just fly
everyone over and be done.
Nope. There's still
plenty of time
to teach y'all a
lesson in teamwork.
Cooperation!
Togetherness!
You are so right!
Only as right as you are!
OK! We'll build the
bridge. What do we use?
Vines!
Branches!
I'm goin' with your idea: vines.
No buts about it.
I'm building
with your idea.
Branches. End of story.
♪♪
[noisy yawn and crickets]
Why use a branch when
you could use a vine!
[grunt]
[snap]
[gasp]
[grunt]
[relieved sigh]
[creaking]
Why didn't I think of
branches to begin with?
They're so...
[crack and thud]
...easy to work with.
[gasps]
These here vines are just
the thing, Rainbow Dash!
Not to disagree, but these
branches are the way to...
[panicked shouts]
Help!
At least now they're
agreeing on something.
I can't get out!
Let me try.
[grunts]
Let me guess.
Bite-acudas?
Mm hm. And they
look mighty hungry.
We gotta get our
professors out of there!
Anycreature have a plan?
Leave 'em hanging?
What?
I'm kidding.
Kinda.
We need to work
fast, and together.
[creaking]
But mainly fast.
[snap]
I hate to admit it, but...
this whole mess is
kinda our fault.
Yeah. No trophy is worth
getting eaten over.
So whaddya say, ya wanna team
up and get ourselves
outta this here pickle barrel?
I thought you'd never ask!
Ahhh!
Don't worry!
I'm just the distraction.
Ocellus?
You nearly scared the
cutie marks off us!
[splash]
[screech]
[snap snap]
[snap]
[yells]
Need a lift?
Yak smash!
[grunts]
Welcome back, Professors!
Now that was a rescue!
And y'all did it together!
[cheering]
No big. Those fish
weren't even a thing.
[growling]
Wha'!
[giggle]
Oops. Sorry.
[zap]
Ha ha! Best. Field trip. Ever!
♪♪
[door opens]
How was the field trip?
What did you all learn?
Yak learn ponies smart!
Yeah! Professors Applejack
and Rainbow Dash
were such good teachers.
It was kinda crazy genius.
They showed us what not
to do so we'd figure
out what we should do.
Really?
It took us a
while to get it.
Especially at the ravine.
It would have been so much
easier to just fly home.
But instead, our professors
built bridges the wrong way
just to show us how
important teamwork is.
Yeah, that was super-dangerous.
Talk about commitment!
We know it's too early to
pick the Teacher of the Month.
But we'd like you to consider
Rainbow Dash and Applejack.
Thank you for telling me!
I'm so glad to hear your
field trip was a success.
I'll make sure to schedule
another one right away!
[cheers]
You were actually just competing
the entire time, weren't you?
To tell ya the truth?
Yeah.
Well, not all the time.
I agreed with you for
the whole nature walk!
Only cause you were anglin' for
that Teacher of the Month award.
[groan]
You were the one
doing the angling.
[arguing continues]
♪♪