♪♪
Who can tell me what these are?
[Various] -Whoa--
-Me likey--
-Shiny!
-Treasure?
Nope!
They're all legendary
magical artifacts!
I read ahead in Equestrian
Cultures and Camaraderie.
Volume seven.
You're right, Ocellus!
This is the Amulet of Aurora,
the Talisman of Mirage,
the Helm of Yksler,
the Crown of Grover,
Knuckerbocker's Shell and
Clover the Clever's Cloak.
And the gems are real!
Not that I tasted them.
Princess Celestia gifted
these to our school,
since they each represent
one of the cultures
our students come from.
And we'll learn all about them
with a Spell-venger hunt!
Is that a pony thing?
It's a magical
scavenger hunt!
Each of you will work
in pairs to try to find
where in the school these
artifacts are hidden.
The team that finds the most
wins a private tour
of the Canterlot archives
with Princess Celestia.
[giggle]
Oooh! Learning and fun?
Does it get any
better than that?
You've been underwater a
long time, haven't you?
Gallus and Silverstream?
Sounds like you're
our first pair.
[gasps]
What? They'll make
a great team!
Um. Why pony glowing?
♪♪
Wait, you all were called on
this friendship quest, too?
It must be a really
important one.
And terribly
far away.
Just getting there
will take days!
Do y'all know
what this means?
There won't be any teachers
left to run the school!
[gasps]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends ♪
♪♪
Should we send
our students home?
I say we take
'em with us!
Road trip!
In the middle of my
friendship quilting class?
I think not!
All of those
unfinished seams.
[shudder]
Problem is, we don't even
know how long we'll be gone!
[Twilight] Don't
worry, everypony.
I already have a
seventy-point plan in place
for this very situation.
You want me to be Headmare?
You're the
perfect choice.
You're a good leader,
and an expert in
friendship!
I trust you to run this
school exactly as I would.
Uh, that's a pretty big
responsibility, Twilight...
Which is why I've prepared
everything you need!
[bell jingles]
[door crashes open]
[crash]
The curriculum, rules
for the Spellvenger hunt,
dining hall menus for
the next six months.
Six months?
You're not really gonna be
gone that long, are you?
And Spike.
Anything that isn't
covered in my files,
he'll be able to
help you with.
Then why not put
him in charge?
No, thanks.
Being a princess for
Twilight was hard enough.
I'm gonna pretend
that made sense.
But if you're sure it's
what you really want...
I promise I won't let you down.
I knew I could count on you.
[door opens and closes]
[rustling]
Gah!
Great.
What could possibly go wrong?
♪♪
Good-bye, Rarity!
And everypony!
Come back soon!
Please.
[honk]
Huh?
I hate goodbyes, don't you?
I just go to pieces!
Discord!
What a...
nice surprise!
This is your first time at
our new school, isn't it?
Oh, was I not invited
to the grand opening?
Friends and Family Day?
Baccalaureate?
I hadn't noticed.
Well, at least you're here now!
Um, why are you here now?
To fill in for
Twilight, of course.
As Headdraconequus.
I seem to recall a whole song
about how this school
is where you make
your own rules.
Now who better at that than me?
Then you also must've heard
Starlight is in charge now.
Really? I thought there
must be some mistake.
Nope, Twilight picked
me for the job.
And she left pretty detailed
instructions for me to follow.
Well, I'm sure that
she wouldn't mind
if I made a few
tiny suggestions.
[snap]
Item one, gravity is optional.
Whoa!
[whoosh]
Item two, the
school's new mascot
is an ambidextrous marmoset.
[quiet mewling]
Item three.
Not gonna happen.
I promised Twilight I'd
handle this her way.
So thanks, but no thanks.
Reeeeeeally?
Well, we'll see if
you change your mind.
[snap]
[splash]
Uh oh.
When we play Ogres
and Oubliettes,
and he puts that many
"E"s in "really,"
things don't usually end well.
Don't worry, Spike.
Discord and I are old
save-Equestria buddies.
He'll be fine.
Now, what's next
on Twilight's list?
Ok, I hid the artifacts
for the Spellvenger hunt
and ordered school
supplies for the week.
All you have to worry
about is teaching class.
Thanks, Spike.
Maybe we will get
through this OK.
[door squeaks open]
♪♪
[bird squawk]
[thunderclap]
[bird squawks]
[typewriter taps]
Come in, come in, you'll
let the twittermites out.
[munch]
Twittermites?
[buzzing]
OW!
Discord! What are you doing?
[gasp]
Nopony was at
your desk.
Imagine what
Twilight would say!
Oh! How could
you, Starlight?
You've broken my trust
and failed me completely!
Oh, don't worry,
I'll cover for you.
By the way, I hope you
like Limburger cheese.
I got a month's supply
for the teacher's lounge.
[snap]
[rolling sound]
Aaah!
[thud]
[sniffing]
[gagging]
We'll take it from
here, Discord.
Go relax, have a
cup of tea, at home.
Ah! Some thanks for all my help.
And after I hired all those
substitute teachers for you.
Actually, that does
sound kinda helpful.
And it was next
on our to do list.
Which teachers did you hire?
[stomp]
They call it making friends
because you have to
Make creatures be
your friends!
Show me what
you got, Yak.
Ahem.
Be my friend.
If you're quiet, I don't buy it!
Be my friend!
I've heard pudding
that's more convincing.
Be... my...
Friend!
That's not how Twilight
teaches friendship.
♪♪
Some field trip!
Where's my iced tea?
[slurp]
[spit]
This is too cold.
[sputter]
Now it's too hot.
Now it's too tea-flavored.
You call yourselves friends?
That is definitely not how
Twilight teaches friendship.
[slurp]
You hired a TREE
as a teacher?
Its schedule was free.
[Spike] Uh, guys?
That's not
just any tree.
Achoo!
It's a
Dragonsneeze tree.
[more sneezing]
[screams]
W-Wait Wait! Calm down,
every creature.
It's gonna be ok!
Achoo!
[crash]
Be my friend!
♪♪
My my my, you do seem like
you're in over your head.
Won't Twilight be
so disappointed
with how you're ruining, I
mean running her school?
♪♪
[panicked shouts]
Discord! This is
all your fault!
Mine? I thought you
were in charge here.
But I'm happy to pitch
in if you need me.
What I need is
for you to leave!
[snap]
Happy now?
Come on, Discord.
You know that's
not what she means.
Fine.
From now on, I
won't try to help.
At all!
[phew]
Thanks, Spike.
Let's just hope
he stays gone.
I wouldn't count on it.
I think Discord's
trying to test you.
But why?
I thought we were friends!
It's kinda what he does.
Even to ponies or
dragons he cares about.
Huh, oh, well, I'm
ready for him.
I told Twilight I'd
run her school right,
and I'm gonna
keep that promise.
No matter what.
♪♪
Good morning, students!
I know there's been a little
bit of adjustment
since the Professors
left for their trip,
but I've brought in
new, new teachers,
and now everything
should run smoothly!
Now it's time for class.
And don't forget, this afternoon
is the Spellvenger hunt!
[chattering]
[door slams open]
[startled gasps]
Yo! Greetings, fellow creatures.
[poof]
Is this seat taken?
[whoosh]
Welcome class!
You may call me the Great and
Powerful Professor Trrrr--
[phone rings]
Shh!
Really, that's so inconsiderate.
[phone rings]
Oh, I'd better take this.
Hello?
Oh, he did not.
And what did you say?
Oh, you did not.
Discord, why are you here?
Why I'm a student of
friendship, of course!
Unless you don't think you're
good enough to teach me.
Of course, I am!
No fruit calls in my class.
[gulp]
Magic is the most important
element of friendship.
So today, I, the Great and
Powerful Trixie, will put on...
a magic show!
[snap]
[squeal]
[whoosh]
[roar]
[screams]
Oh, oh oh, I'm learning
so much, aren't you?
Grr... Discord!
[phone rings]
Hello?
Um, what exactly is a
long-distance plan?
♪♪
Take a lap, team!
Uh, actually, we just finished
Professor Spitfire's workout.
Sounds like somepony
needs a little motivation.
[tweet]
[roar]
[screams]
[growls]
I've never run so
fast in my life.
This is great!
Hey, Coach.
We need a break.
Friendship is about honesty.
So believe me when I say...
We're not stopping!
[tweet]
[gasps]
[roar]
[panicked shouts]
Yona... can't run... faster.
[whimper]
[roar]
[crash]
Discord, that's enough!
Endangering students
crosses the line!
I don't know why you're
trying to ruin this school,
but it stops now.
[zap]
I wouldn't be so sure.
This is your last warning.
Hey, take it easy, Starlight.
Discord's your friend, remember?
Well, he's not acting like it.
She's right, Discord.
What's your problem?
My problem?
How is the fact that Twilight
decided to put an incompetent,
power-hungry unicorn in charge
of her school my problem?
[blast]
[worried groans]
Ha ha hah.. Don't worry.
I just banished him from
school grounds forever.
He's fine.
That probably made
things worse.
Why didn't you just
talk to Discord?
Because he's right
about one thing.
I've been doing a
terrible job as Headmare.
No, you haven't!
Discord is just
being Discord.
Maybe.
But I wonder why me being in
charge bothers him so much.
[school bell rings]
We can figure that out
after the Spellvenger Hunt.
Come on!
♪♪
For this afternoon's
Spellvenger Hunt,
you'll need to use the
artifacts' history
to find where they're
hidden in the castle.
When you spot one, touch
it with a magic shield
to keep track
of your score.
Twilight left a list of your
hunt partners before she left.
I'll pass out the shields.
♪♪
Ready, set... Spellvenger Hunt!
[excited chatter]
C'mon, we can use Twilight's
observatory to watch the teams!
[chattering]
I hope you know
where you're going.
To the Helm of Yksler!
Eh, works for me.
In our book, it says Yksler
was an honorable Yak warrior.
Any enemies that saw him put
down their weapons in peace.
I think his artifact must be in
one of these suits of armor.
I'm guessing that one.
Yes! One down, five to go!
Aw, Ocellus and Smolder
found their first artifact!
Wait. What's that?
[frightened whimper]
I don't think that's part
of the Spellvenger Hunt.
[screams]
[crash]
The school is haunted!
Not cool!
[gasp]
♪♪
We're totally gonna win
this Spellvenger Hunt!
Yeah, I doubt that.
But at least I know where
one of the artifacts is.
Saw Spike hide it yesterday.
The Crown of Grover!
Score!
They say it's magic, and King
Grover used it to become
the first ruler of Griffonstone.
I know, pretty sweet, right?
You paid attention in class!
What! If you
ever tell an-
[slam]
Whoa! 3-D painting!
[hiss]
[screams]
♪♪
[hiss]
[screams]
♪♪
[hiss]
[screams]
♪♪
Ha ha ha!
Yep, that's definitely Discord.
This is not good.
I thought you banished
him from the school!
Only his body.
Apparently, his ghost can
come and go just fine.
Let's go, we have to stop this.
How? No offense, but
I don't think magic
is the answer
against Discord.
This time, I'm not using magic.
Hmm.
What Yona look for?
The shell of Knuckerbocker.
It's like a seashell, but if you
blow into it, you call a dragon!
There's a sweet poem
in our book about it.
"Climb to the heights with
dragon flight."
Like flight of stairs!
Yona take pony word for it.
[squishy sound]
Huh?
♪♪
[grunts]
What's happening?
Yona not know.
But Yona do know Yona not
like Spellvenger Hunt!
[dramatic music]
Hahaha ha.
Ho ho ho ho!
Ah! Boo Boo-boo!
[yells]
♪♪
Everycreature, stop!
But-but-but the
school is haunted!
It's not haunted; it's Discord.
[poof]
Headmare Starlight!
Look at me, look!
I won the Spellvenger Hunt!
Well, done me!
Now what's my prize?
Detention.
Well, that's disappointing.
Discord, you can't keep
messing up the school.
On the contrary, I think
I rather can, and will.
Then I have just one
thing to say to you.
Do go on.
I'm sorry.
What?
[zap]
I had to stop thinking like a
Headmare and start thinking
like a Guidance Counselor
to finally understand.
You felt left out.
I don't know what
you're getting at.
Nopony ever invited
you to the school.
And when you offered to
help, I didn't listen.
I was so worried about doing
things Twilight's way,
I didn't stop to think
about being a good friend.
I'd like to apologize for that.
And offer you the
job of vice-headmare.
-Huh?
-Really?
-What?
-Why?
Totally confused.
I accept!
I mean, I suppose I can find
some time in my busy schedule
to help you out.
But I will need my own office,
expense account, parking space.
You're new to the world
of education, aren't you?
Next time you want something,
just ask for it, all right?
But then we'd miss out on all
these delightful misadventures.
Hey! Watch the wings!
Now, vice-headmare Discord,
if you'll help me get this
Spellvenger Hunt back in order.
[snap]
Everything is re-hidden.
Ah!
[chuckles] Well, with
a few surprises.
[door crashes open]
Discord!
I can't believe you tricked us
into going on a friendship quest
that wasn't real!
Oh, back so soon?
A glamour spell on
our cutie marks?
A fake summons from the map?
Hey, at least we got
to go spelunking
in that really creepy
cave with all those
eyeless worm
creatures chasing us.
Oh, Yona so glad ponies back.
Uh, y'all get the feelin'
we missed something?
Thanks for taking care
of the school, Starlight.
It was a challenge.
But I think
things turned out
just the way you'd
have handled them.
Guess this means you're
not vice-headmare anymore.
Ooh poo!
I just ordered business cards!
♪♪