♪♪
[click]
[frustrated groan]
You said it,
Big Mac!
This is taking forever!
I know it's wrong
to cut corners
when it comes to
gifts from the heart,
but this is
an emergency, right?
Eyup.
Discord?
A little help?
Discord!
[sigh]
[inaudible]
Good idea.
Ahem.
"Captain Wuzz, are you
prepared to enter the world
of Ogres & Oubliettes?"
Huzzah, fellow adventurers!
Shall we storm the ramparts
of Squizard's Castle
to reclaim Calico's Ring of
Imperceptibility?
You did summon me for
a rousing Guys' Night
of Ogres and Oubliettes,
did you not?
Uh. Sort of, but...
Do you think you could
magically hurry-up this pie
real quick first?
You seem to be mixing
up the Lord of Chaos
with a second-rate clown
magician for hire.
Wait!
This needs to go in
the mail today
or it'll never get
to Sugar Belle
in time for Hearts
and Hooves Day.
[sheepish laugh]
Please, can't you see that that
holiday is a commercialized ruse
pushed on you by the
greeting card industry?
Ahem!
[tap tap]
Fine.
You owe me for this.
[snap]
Keep your eye on the pie.
It's magic time!
[poof]
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart! ♪
♪ Faithful and strong! ♪
♪ Sharing kindness
it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete! ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends? ♪
♪♪
[sniff]
This smells... palatable.
Well, pies really are
Sugar Belle's thing.
But I think that makes
this all the more special.
It shows you're interested
in what she cares about.
Eyup.
And, he's planning
a big romantic
Hearts and Hooves dinner.
It was my idea
to bake the
invitation inside.
[poof]
"Happy Hearts and
Hooves Day, Sugar Belle.
Meet me in my barn at
sunset for a surprise."
Pretty clever,
huh?
Eyup.
[giggle]
[moan]
Aw, "Sugar
Belle." See?
Well, you two certainly
have bought into this
romance nonsense hook,
line, and sinker.
For a formerly-friendless
immortal despot,
you're pretty cynical.
I'm a realist.
And love, like all things
warm and fuzzy, isn't real.
Aw, come on. You act
tough, but deep down.
You're a softie.
I mean, you don't have tea with
Fluttershy every weekend
because you like tea.
But I do like tea!
Every tea.
All the teas.
Chamomile, Earl Gray, green,
white, yellow, maté, lemon,
ginger, chai, spearmint,
peppermint, hibiscus,
cinnamon pumpkin spice!
[grunt]
♪♪
Tell you what:
while Big Mac mails
his incredibly
romantic gesture,
I'll show you the splendors
of Hearts and Hooves Day
in Ponyville.
I bet I can prove
you believe in love.
Fine. Call it a
gentleman's wager.
Loser mows my lawn
for eternity.
Is it like a riding
mower, or...?
Tweezers!
[gulp]
♪♪
[whinny]
Hear ye, hear ye!
This special Hearts
and Hooves Day meetin'
of the Cutie Mark Crusaders
is now in session!
First order of business: helpin'
my big brother decorate the barn
for his big date with
Sugar Belle tonight and--
Hello!
It seems like everypony's
got somepony special but us!
When's it going to be our turn?
[knock at door]
Huh?
[squeak]
Who's it from?
Can't tell.
It's all smudged, but it looks
like it's addressed to "Belle".
Hmmm... Sweetie Belle!
Somepony certainly went through
a lot of trouble for me
on Hearts and Hooves Day.
You don't think...? Could
it be...? Hang on a minute.
Mysterious package, smudged
address, no idea who it's from?
I know what this is.
You've got a secret admirer!
[squeals and whoops]
♪♪
[Spike] Ah! Another
Hearts and Hooves Day.
Love is in the air, Discord.
Look at all these happy couples.
How can they be happy if
they aren't playing
Ogres and Oubliettes?
As a great Dragon poet once
wrote to his beloved:
"I love you with
the utmost clarity;
I love you, dear, my
sweet, sweet Rari--"
Are you even listening?
Of course.
"Love is something-something,
and Discord is great."
I don't know.
Can we play O & O now?
Sure, after you admit you
believe in love and--
Sugarbelle!
Big Mac's girlfriend.
What's she doing
in town so early?
Well, Sugar Belle, I'm sure
Big Mac won't be expecting it.
[gasp]
She's planning her own
romantic surprise for Big Mac?
What if she goes to
Sweet Apple Acres
before Big Mac's ready
with his surprise?
We've got to warn him!
[zap]
Whoa! [clang]
Whoa!
Mig Back! Mig Back!
I mean Big Mac!
We just saw Sugar Belle.
She's at Sugarcube Corner,
but I think she's on
her way over here now!
You gotta keep her away from
here until the barn's finished!
Eyup!
I wonder what she
has planned for him.
[chuckle] We don't
have to wonder.
[snap]
Agh!
Will you warn me next
time you do that?
♪♪
Oh, she hasn't seen him yet.
Take note, Discord.
This is what love is all about!
Spike, "Love is about
spying in the bushes."
Make fun of me
all you want,
but look at
Big Mac's face
and tell me you don't
believe in love.
[chuckle]
I hope he'll be
ok without me.
[whimper]
Oh, hey.
We're just...
not spying.
Hush!
I mean, he has been
on his own before,
so he'll be fine, right?
[sigh]
How should I tell
Big Mac tonight?
"You won't need to come visit
me in my village anymore"?
"We need to talk."
Just be honest
with him.
You're right, ok.
"We're finished."
[horrified whinny]
[pounding]
[shattering glass]
[thud]
You're right. She
did surprise him.
Agh!
♪♪
[blubbering]
Ok. Things seem bad;
maybe they're really not.
Maybe "we're finished"
was about the day.
Ponies say that, right?
Like, "Hey, remember yesterday?
That's finished.
Cause it's today."
Maybe not that.
Oooh! I know. Maybe Sugar
Belle has a wacky cousin
who's never been on his own
and she has to leave him
in charge of her shop
while she apprentices
with Mrs. Cake,
who does that, like, two days
a week. No, no, three.
Tha's why she won't need you
to come to her village anymore.
Because she'll already be here!
Nah. I don't even
buy that one.
[pitiful moaning]
[glug glug glug]
She takes pie
baking seriously.
Why'd I even try?
I bet she thought I
was making fun of her.
[high-pitched moans]
Oh, I hate seeing you
like this, Big Mac,
and over a
girl, no less.
I'm calling an emergency Guys'
Night right now to cheer you up.
[honk]
Besides, we can't have
you ruining any more of my
1000-year-old monogrammed
handkerchiefs.
These are silk, you know.
[snap]
♪♪
Class is now in session.
Lesson one: Nothing
can break your heart
if you only love yourself.
You've got to show everypony
that you're too cool
to be bothered with so-called
"love." Observe.
This is how cool guys
lean against things.
When you see a guy leaning
against a thing
looking this cool, you think,
"Wow, that guy doesn't
have a care in Equestria.
Not a guy who leans
on things that cool!"
I don't think leaning
is gonna help.
Am I doing it right?
Whoa!
Oof!
We're not like you, Discord.
We can't put on a front
and pretend not to love.
It's impossible.
Lesson two: Plenty of
ponies in the pasture.
Right, Big Mac?
I know just the gal to make you
forget all about Sugar Belle!
You said her name!
Oy vey.
[snap]
Ok! We finished decoratin'
the barn for Big Mac,
which means we got the rest
of the day to ourselves.
There's a whole town of
possible admirers out there
and only three of us.
But together, we're gonna
get to the bottom of this.
Ready? Break!
Excuse me, Pipsqueak?
Mind answerin' a few questions?
No? Late for something?
Are you Sweetie-Belle's
secret admirer?
Excuse me, I'm doing a research
survey about sending pie
in the mail anonymously.
Would you say you're pro
"that," or anti "that?"
Happy Hearts and Hooves Day.
Did you boys happen to send
any packages to me recently?
It's ok to say no;
I won't be offended.
Please say no, please
say no, please say no.
♪♪
Sir McBiggun, meet Skellinore.
She's a level-18 Bone-Warrior
in Squizard's Mage Army,
but only to pay off
Skeleton Student Loan Debts.
Get to know each
other, why don't you?
Wow! You're really going
all-out to cheer up Big Mac;
I'm impressed.
Yes, yes, I'm amazing.
Anyway, since we're
in the neighborhood,
care for a quick game
of Ogres and Oubliettes?
Like I've been wanting
to play all week?
I take it back.
I'm helping our friend,
first and foremost.
See for yourself.
I think he's showing her
a picture of Sugar Belle.
What?
And now he's crying.
No no no no no no!
No, he's not. Let me see that.
Don't touch it.
I'm looking!
Cut it out, Discord!
Quit it!
[poof]
She used to do this thing
where her nose would
wrinkle when she laughed.
Right there in that hole
where your nose used to be.
I never told her how much I
loved Wrinkle Nose Cutie Face.
And now I never will.
[blubbering]
Agh.
OK. I think we've had enough of
the aloof Master of Chaos'
remedies for a broken heart.
You know what I do when I have
a problem too big to solve?
I hide from it.
When she can't find you, she'll
realize how much she misses you!
Plus, if she can't find you,
she can't break up with you!
Eyup!
♪♪
I don't get it.
We asked every
stallion in Ponyville.
There's got to be
somepony we're missin'.
Somepony obvious.
Somepony right in
front of our noses!
Oh, well.
At least the barn's looking
great for Big Mac's date.
Too bad there won't be a date.
Sugar Belle is so lucky to
have a "non-secret admirer"
like Big Mac.
Well, she certainly doesn't
seem to have appreciated it.
I bet she's gonna take one look
at this barn and say
"What did I ever do
to deserve this?"
Yes, what did she
do to deserve this?
She broke my heart.
Well, not yet.
Technically.
In fact, she can't break your
heart if you break hers first.
Eeeyup.
[Sugar Belle] Thanks for the
tour of Ponyville, Mrs. Cake.
Oh, my pleasure.
I'm off to surprise
Big Mac with the news!
Imagine the look on his
face when I tell him:
"We need to talk."
Oh, dear me, no!
I told you, don't
say it that way
or he'll think you're
breaking up with him!
Break up with him?
Never!
Why, without my
favorite delivery pony,
I couldn't imagine
being happy ever again.
He knows that.
Good. Save your mix-ups
for cake batter;
that's what I always say.
Ha ha ha!
He's a good
listener, that pony.
I promise you: no mix-ups.
[zap]
Ah! Big Mac!
Sugar Belle?
We need to talk.
I know why
you're here.
You do?
But I have something
to tell you first.
Oh, can I go first?
I'm going to be--
Oh. Why don't we tell
each other on three?
One...
It's over.
What's over?
You and me.
It's over.
What?
We're breaking up.
I don't understand.
Why are you breaking
up with me?
And why are you
leaning like that?
I don't know!
Big Mac, please talk to me.
I-- you-- argh!
This is why I
don't like talking!
Words can hurt!
Words hurt!
Goodbye, sugar belle!
[slam]
[sobbing]
♪♪
[door opens]
Big Mac!
Oh, thank goodness.
You gotta help us with this!
Dude, how long have
you been not-hiding?
[zap]
Oh. I should probably
have said something.
Y'all should go.
Did you... did
she... are you...?
Big Mac? What's going on?
Where's Sugar Belle?
Just go.
But we worked so
hard on this chart.
I think we've almost cracked
it, if you could just--
not right now...
But I can't stand having
a secret admirer
who's too scared to
tell me who he is!
Maybe he doesn't like talking.
But that doesn't make any sense!
Maybe he used to
talk too much
and it only ever got
him into trouble!
[sigh] What if you're
right, Discord?
What if love isn't real at all?
[ding]
[zap]
I'm sorry, Sweetie Belle.
I'm just mad and I'm
takin' it out on you.
That's ok.
I bet if felt good to
get it out, though.
Actually, it did.
Tellin' you how
I felt just then.
I gotta go.
Big Mac!
Where are you going?
I gotta talk to Sugar Belle!
Discord, you've got to
use your magic and...
Guess you have
better things to do.
Big Mac's gonna need a miracle.
[sigh]
[splat]
[thud]
Of all the rotten luck.
[crash]
Caught you just in time.
We both know I don't
like to say much,
but I'm going to
say something now.
Even though I'm hurting,
I wouldn't trade this
feeling for anything,
because it'd mean giving up
the good times we had, too.
I only broke up
with you because
you were going to
break up with me.
I respect your decision,
but you should know
you'll always be
in my heart.
I didn't want to
break up with you.
But you said you don't
need me to visit anymore.
You said I'm gonna
be on my own.
I heard you said
"We're finished!"
when I was hiding
in the bushes.
That sounds worse
than it is.
Oh, Big Mac.
I was talking
about my cousin.
I have this wacky cousin
who's never been on his own,
but I have to let him
run my shop on weekends.
Which is why you
won't be delivering
to my village anymore.
Because I'll already be here
apprenticing with Mrs. Cake,
who does that two
days a week.
No, three.
Wait'll I tell Spike.
I'd never break up with you.
I suppose there's a lesson here
somewhere about communication.
Talking instead of assuming,
or eavesdropping is wrong,
wouldn't you say?
Eyyyyyyup.
[giggle]
Wrinkle nose cutie face.
You must have been awful
confused at my breaking up
with you after
you got my pie.
What pie?
You didn't get
the pie I sent?
Mm mm.
Or the invitation?
Uh uh.
Well, in that case...
Allow me to escort you to a
Hearts and Hooves Day surprise!
[giggle]
♪♪
[birdsong]
[sad sigh]
Mind if we join ya?
♪♪
"Happy Hearts and
Hooves Day, Sugar Belle.
Meet me--" Sugar Belle?
You have got to be
pullin' our hooves.
It was all a mix-up?
[laughing]
It's funny; I've been sitting
here feeling sorry for myself
for not having a special pony
on Hearts and Hooves Day,
but remembering all
the fun we had,
I think I have two
special ponies.
My two best friends.
Awww.
[happy sigh]
And so ends another
Hearts and Hooves Day.
Despite a bumpy start...
and middle... and ending.
A lot of bumps today.
Love was in the air.
So was confusion,
apparently.
And a fair number
of assumptions.
But you have to admit,
after seeing everything
Big Mac went through,
love is one hundred
percent real.
[Discord humming to himself]
Seriously?
Discord! Come on.
I can't believe you!
Who do you think broke
Sugar Belle's wagon wheel?
♪ Ta-da. ♪
Happy Hearts and Hooves Day.
You old softie! Ha ha! I
knew you had a heart!
Speaking of how great I am,
are you busy for the
rest of the night?
[snap]
Calico's Ring of
Imperceptibility
isn't going to reclaim
itself, you know.
Ogres and
Oubliettes?
I thought you'd
never ask.
Oh, and just
wondering, no biggie,
but is Skellinore
going to be there?
Spike, she's an imaginary
one-dimensional
paper cut-out skeleton.
Well, nopony's perfect.
♪♪