♪♪
[Twilight] This happened
while we were gone?
[Applejack] Wow! Those are
all the places we went
when we left to
save Equestria!
Ugh! There's that horrid town
where we were almost sold!
The pirates! They were
pretty awesome...
once they decided not
to throw us overboard.
And Mt. Aris! Ooo, Starlight!
Did you know we made seashell
necklaces for all the seaponies?
I...
you...
Really?
What about that unicorn?
The one who attacked
Canterlot?
Tempest. I invited her
to come to Ponyville,
but she wanted to
spread the word
of the Storm
King's defeat...
and share what she
learned about friendship.
Y'all think that's
why the map grew?
Friendship quests
beyond Equestria?
I hope not.
I've had quite enough
life-threatening adventures,
thank you very much.
♪♪
How many friendship quests do
you think we need to go on
before we have to
expand the throne room?
We can't do it all alone.
Sure we can!
We just need to knock this wall
down, get some paint--
No. I mean the world is
filled with so many different
creatures who know nothing
about friendship.
We need help if we're gonna
teach them all about friendship.
Lots of help.
[Rarity] Perhaps. But
where does one go
to learn about
friendship?
Here! They can all go here!
Because we're gonna
open a school!
♪ My little pony,
my little pony ♪
♪ Aaaahhh ♪
♪ My little Pony ♪
♪ I used to wonder what
friendship could be ♪
♪ My Little Pony ♪
♪ Until you all shared
its magic with me ♪
♪ Big adventure! ♪
♪ Tons of fun ♪
♪ A beautiful heart ♪
♪ Faithful and strong ♪
♪ Sharing kindness ♪
♪ it's an easy feat ♪
♪ And magic makes it
all complete ♪
♪ To have my little pony ♪
♪ Do you know you're all
my very best friends ♪
♪♪
[Celestia] I think a
School of Friendship
is a wonderful
idea, Twilight.
I'll help in
any way I can.
♪♪
I just have a few questions:
What time should
school start each day?
It really de--
What's the ideal
length for class?
Do you test regularly?
Oh, well that's--
What about
class projects?
That's a ver--
Assigned seating?
Open seating?
Or is that too
unstructured?
Oh, Twilight! You
were my star pupil.
If anyone knows
how to run a
school, it's you.
There's a big difference
between attending a school
and running one.
It's not like there's a
rulebook to follow.
Actually, there is.
The EEA guidebook
is very specific
about how to
run a school.
The EEA? I've never
heard of that.
Should I have
heard of that?
Of course not, you've never
run a school before!
The Equestria Education
Association is a board
of learned ponies that oversee
every school in Equestria.
Even your school?
But you're... you!
Not even a Princess can
do whatever she likes
when it comes to shaping
young pony minds.
The EEA ensures that whether
it's unicorns studying magic,
pegasi learning weather,
or earth ponies
researching agriculture,
all schools are held to
the same high standard.
They'll need to
approve your plan
before you can
move forward.
OK, Spike.
Looks like we have a
presentation to make!
Pff. After everything
we've been through,
how hard can that be?
♪ ominous music ♪
I'm gonna go with
really hard.
Uh. Hello. My name is--
Princess Twilight
Sparkle.
I am Chancellor Neighsay.
Equestria owes you
a great debt.
But Princess or no, we expect
you to do things by...
The...
Book!
[thud]
♪♪
I think you'll
find my curriculum
meets all your
requirements, Chancellor.
♪♪
And can we trust you to follow
through with this plan?
Or will you leave the
school unattended
to gallop off on your
adventures?
My journey beyond Equestria
showed me first hoof
that the threats out there
are greater than we imagined.
[concerned murmurs]
If we want to keep
our land safe,
and create a
friendlier tomorrow,
we need to teach the magic
of friendship far and wide.
A school for ponies to learn
how to protect themselves.
Uh, more like respecting
differences and communicating
♪♪
The EEA concurs.
Everypony should be prepared
to defend our way of life.
So, if your work is in order,
provisional EEA
approval is granted.
We will need to observe your
school up and running
before it can be
fully accredited.
Then please, join us for
Friends and Family Day.
It'll be a perfect time
to see our progress!
♪ majestic music ♪
♪♪
[Rainbow Dash] It's too much!
Too much!
[Rarity] You think so?
I had hoped dressing the part
would help me feel the part.
Not your dress!
This! Us! Teaching?
They're gonna think
I'm an egghead!
Well, the students are gonna
love my confetti cannon class.
It's gonna be a blast!
Um. Hello there.
I'm your teacher.
I hope you enjoy class.
But if you don't enjoy it,
that's OK, too.
I don't know about all this.
It's going to be fine.
Everything about this
school just feels right.
See? If Twilight
isn't stressed,
you've got nothing
to worry about!
And you're sure you
want us to be teachers?
In classrooms?
The EEA is VERY clear on how
schools should be run.
We have a huge
responsibility,
and I need you all to do
this by the book.
That means no cannons
in class, Pinkie.
Awwwwww! Not even
a teeny cannon?
I know it's not
some big adventure
against the forces
of evil.
But this could be the
most important thing
we've ever done!
I can't run a school
of Friendship
without my best friends.
Can I count on you?
Of course you
can, darling.
Call me Professor
Egghead. I'm in.
[school bell rings]
Ahhhh! First day of school!
So many new ponies!
About that. One thing
I forgot to mention.
It's not just ponies...
[chattering]
That was unexpected!
♪♪
Students certainly
traveled from far and wide
to attend our school!
Princess Celestia helped me
reach out to all the kingdoms.
After all, friendship
is something
that needs to be shared
with every... creature.
[chattering]
Welcome to the School
of Friendship!
I'm your headmare,
Twilight Sparkle!
Please follow Guidance
Counselor Starlight
to sign in and get your
class assignments.
Then we can show you
your living quarters!
Whoa, sorry!
I'm Sandbar.
Are you a student
here, too?
No. I just figured I'd
randomly stand here
and see how many ponies
would walk into me.
[Angry male voice] Gallus!
[cough]
Grandpa Gruff!
What are you
doing here?
Flew all the way
from Griffonstone
to introduce Gallus.
Rainbow Dash, right?
Gilda told me about you.
You're a teacher?
Huh. Thought you'd
be... cooler.
[Gruff male voice] Ponies!
Prince Rutherford!
This Yona Yak.
She come to pony school.
Make it better.
Yak can't wait
to meet ponies
and tell all about
Yakyakistan!
[scream]
[crash]
Why don't I show you around
before you destroy the place?
But dragons are
better than this.
Why am I here?
Because as Dragon Lord,
I'm ordering you to be here!
Hey! Spike! Come meet Smolder.
Great to see you, Ember.
Uh... Which one is Smolder?
♪♪
Ocellus!
What did we
talk about?
[whoosh]
I told you.
Stay in your
own form.
It's the polite
thing to do.
Sorry. She's shy.
What is that?
[whoosh]
No way!
I didn't know ponies
could turn into...
Um... what are you?
A changeling.
Ponies can turn into
changelings?
No. But changelings
can turn into ponies.
Huh. That's confusing.
[whoosh]
I am General Seaspray of Her
Majesty Queen Novo's navy.
I would like to introduce the
queen's niece, Silverstream.
This place is amazing!
I've spent most of my life in
a coral reef under water.
I was a seapony. But now I'm
a hippogriff, long story.
Anyways... Wow!
Is that a yak?
[zoom]
[excited chatter]
Thank you so much for
supporting the grand opening
of our school.
I hope you'll all join us for
Friends and Family Day
to see the amazing progress
your students are making!
[cheers]
Looks like school's
in session!
[singing]
♪ The School of Friendship! ♪
♪ First Day of Class! ♪
♪ Will we fail or
will we pass? ♪
♪ Students come from
far and wide! ♪
♪ Brand new friends
here by our side! ♪
♪♪
♪ Take a breath, look
around, it's amazing ♪
♪ I can't believe
that it's real ♪
♪ Students galore
New ideas to explore ♪
♪ Can't contain the
excitement I feel! ♪
♪♪
♪ Can't mess up
Can't afford a mistake now ♪
♪ Think success!
Keep it firmly in sight ♪
♪ Make sure to do things
by the book! ♪
♪ Make sure to do it
all right! ♪
♪♪
♪ The School of Friendship! ♪
♪ Must get to class! ♪
♪ Will we fail or
will we pass? ♪
♪ Students learning
from the best! ♪
♪ Taking notes to pass
the test! ♪
♪ Wait hold on! Not like that,
just a second ♪
♪ I'm not sure if that
method's approved ♪
♪ Let me take a look ♪
♪ Yup! Right here in the book ♪
♪ Come on!
We just got in the groove! ♪
♪ Can't mess up
Can't afford a mistake now ♪
♪ We are shaping young
minds to ignite! ♪
♪ Do it like it says
in the book now ♪
♪ Make sure you're
doing it right! ♪
♪ There's not an equation
on how to have fun! ♪
♪ The students look bored now
Oh, what have I done! ♪
♪ Can't teach bein' honest
Not sure what to do! ♪
♪ I'm quite certain I'm lost ♪
♪ None of us has a clue ♪
♪ The School of Friendship ♪
♪ Another Class ♪
♪ Wish it were more
of a blast ♪
♪ Thought this school
would be more fun ♪
♪ Can't wait for our
classes to be done ♪
♪ Can't mess up
Can't afford a mistake now ♪
♪ No way to have fun ♪
♪ Oh, what have I done! ♪
♪ Bored with this class ♪
♪ Think success ♪
♪ Keep it firmly in sight ♪
♪ Wish that we could
leave en masse ♪
♪ We don't have a clue ♪
♪ Listen to this one request ♪
♪ Make things fun
we're really stressed ♪
♪ Make sure to do things
by the book now ♪
♪ Can we tell her this
thing is a mess? ♪
[song ends]
[groaning]
Is this what boring is?
Am I bored?
Please.
These ponies are the
heroes of Equestria?
Listen, "these ponies" saved
all of us from The Storm King.
How? By boring him
into surrender?
Our teachers are a little
different than I expected.
Agh! Pony school
waste of time!
Yak school teach how
to braid Yak hair!
Braiding yak hair is best !
Whoa!
Oof!
Is there anything in Yakyakistan
that isn't the best?
Yes! Wait. No.
Yaks best.
No claws, no
wings, no fire.
What is it exactly
you're proud of?
Whoa, cool it.
No need to harsh Yona's
love for her heritage. OK?
Aww.
Are we not being sweet and
friendly enough for you, pony?
That was sarcasm, right?
Because you weren't
being sweet or nice?
Maybe dragons and griffons are
just too tough for friendship.
Yaks tough.
Just not nasty.
Who you calling
nasty, klutz?
[grunts]
OK, break it up!
Break. It. Up!
What is going
on here?
Just a friendly discussion
about the magic of friendship
amongst friends.
Everypony...
I mean... everyone...
go to your next class!
I just can't
believe it.
Fights breaking out
when they're supposed to
be learnin' friendship?
Things definitely aren't
going as "by the book"
as Twilight planned.
That's because we're
terrible teachers!
Face it. This school
isn't gonna work.
[all at once]
Fights breaking out
in the hallways!
I don't look like
that! Do I?
[snoring sound]
I get it.
Things are getting off to a
rougher start than expected.
But that's OK!
Who are you and what have you
done with Twilight Sparkle?
Every school in Equestria
follows these rules.
As long as we do
too, we'll be fine.
Maybe we should...
try something new?
The EEA will be
here this afternoon
for Friends and Family Day.
They need to see a school that
follows their guidelines.
Even if those guidelines
aren't working?
Well, then, we have to try
harder and make sure they do.
[bell rings]
Another morning, another
chance to inspire our students.
Hey! Professor Dash's
class is this way.
Where are you going?
You're not
skipping, are you?
That's exactly
what we're doing.
But Friends and
Family Day--
is after class!
Relax! This is just a
quick... mental health break.
[whispering]
That sounds legit.
We're in.
I guess I'll
tag along too...
make sure you don't
get into trouble.
[laughter]
[Fluttershy] This
way, Angel.
Professor Fluttershy!
We're busted!
[whoosh]
Oh my! What are
you all doing?
Aren't classes
that way?
[ahem]
A generosity field
trip, dahhhling.
I'm taking the students
to the lake...
to look at our
divine reflections.
Oh. That sounds nice.
Have fun!
[whoosh]
[giggling]
I take back everything
I said about you.
That was cool.
Thanks!
Wait... What did you
say about me?
[laughter]
You're sure sticking to the
book is going to work?
My friends can
handle anything.
They'll have these problems
turned around before we know it.
Problems?
[gasp]
Chancellor Neighsay!
You're here!
Yes. And you
seem unprepared.
If there are problems...
Problems? Ha!
Of course not!
We can't wait to
show you around.
[nervous laugh]
And that's why griffons
breathe fire when we get mad.
They do not!
Wait, do they?
No. Really?
Griffons just full of hot air.
[laughter[
And yaks are actually
good at jokes.
How about that?
What are dragons
good at?
Competition.
Who's up for a race?
Rainbow Dash!
Why aren't you in
class teaching?
Because my
students are gone!
Uh, gone... somewhere else!
Doing a loyalty lesson.
And I was just going to
grab, uh... this pencil!
Because they need it.
Wherever they are.
Which I know...
cause I'm the teacher.
I see. Well, Chancellor,
we have other classes.
We can just--
Let's follow
the professor.
I'm quite curious about
this "lesson in loyalty."
[laughter]
[Twilight] Of course,
we want to instill
a sense of loyalty
towards others.
We encourage acts of
generosity and kindness.
[shrieks]
Figured we shouldn't be the
only ones enjoying the view.
Agh! Yaks not best at flying!
An appreciation for
the value of laughter.
Flying is best !
Congratulations, Yona!
You are officially the weirdest
thing I've seen so far!
What do you say, Ocellus?
Can you be weirder
than a flying yak?
[whoosh]
Oh!
...and to always be
honest in any situation.
Honesty is imperative.
Princess, are we
going in circles?
Uh... look at the time!
We'd better head to the lake
for Friends and Family Day!
I'm sure all the students and
faculty will be there!
♪♪
[happy chattering]
Ha ha!
[clink]
What is that?
[panicked shouts]
the school is under attack!
[screaming]
Oh my goodness!
Whoa!
[crash]
[coughing and groaning]
Uh, maybe skipping class
wasn't the best idea?
How dare you!
This act of aggression
against ponies--
I'm so sorry,
Chancellor.
We clearly had some students
get a little carried away.
Those are students?
But, you said you were
opening this school
to protect Equestria!
To defend ponies from
dangerous creatures
who don't have our best
interests at heart.
My school teaches for all
of us to work together
through friendship.
And how do you know
these creatures
won't take what they've learned
here and use it against us?
Friendship isn't
just for ponies.
It should be!
Unicorn think yaks
no need friendship?
Maybe yaks no
need pony school!
Well, then perhaps you
should return to your kind.
"Your kind?"
Smolder? Let's go.
♪♪
Queen Novo will want
to hear of this.
♪♪
Well, this place seemed
lame anyways.
♪♪
It's fine.
We know not everypony
sees us the way you do.
We're used to it.
♪♪
Princess Celestia helped me
reach out to all the kingdoms.
When she hears you closed
the school because...
Because you failed to
meet the EEA's standards?
What?
Irresponsible teachers.
Students skipping class!
Endangering ponies!
Your school is a disaster.
Perhaps if you had higher
standards for who was admitted,
this could have been avoided.
Regardless...
[zapping]
[metallic clanking]
By order of the EEA,
I am shutting
this school down.
Oh!
♪♪