UGH.
IT IS GORGEOUS OUT.
JUST GORGEOUS.
TWI...
LIGHT.
I...HAVE...
LET ME JUST...
[ PANTING ]
"DEAR TWILIGHT,
I AM SURE YOU ARE AS EXCITED AS
I AM ABOUT THE UPCOMING WEDDING
IN CANTERLOT."
WEDDING?
"I WILL BE PRESIDING OVER THE
CEREMONY, BUT WOULD VERY MUCH
LIKE YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS TO
HELP WITH THE PREPARATIONS
FOR THIS WONDERFUL OCCASION.
FLUTTERSHY, I WOULD LIKE YOU AND
YOUR SONGBIRD CHOIR TO PROVIDE
THE MUSIC."
OH, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT AN HONOR.
"PINKIE PIE, I CAN THINK OF
NO ONE MORE QUALIFIED THAN YOU
TO HOST THE RECEPTION."
HIP! HIP! HOORAY!
"APPLEJACK, YOU WILL BE IN
CHARGE OF THE CATERING FOR THE
RECEPTION."
WELL, COLOR ME PLEASED AS
PUNCH.
"RAINBOW DASH, I WOULD VERY
MUCH APPRECIATE IT IF YOU COULD
PERFORM A SONIC RAINBOOM AS THE
BRIDE AND GROOM COMPLETE THEIR
'I DOs.'"
YES!
RARITY, YOU WILL BE
RESPONSIBLE FOR DESIGNING THE
DRESSES FOR THE BRIDE AND HER
BRIDESMAIDS."
PRINCESS CELESTIA WANTS ME TO
[ STAMMERING ]
WEDDING DRESS?
FOR A CANTERLOT WEDDING?
I--
OOH!
"AND AS FOR YOU TWILIGHT,
YOU WILL BE PLAYING THE MOST
IMPORTANT ROLE OF ALL--
MAKING SURE THAT EVERYTHING GOES
AS PLANNED.
SEE YOU ALL VERY SOON.
YOURS, PRINCESS CELESTIA."
BUT...I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHO'S GETTING MARRIED?
OH, WAIT!
UH, I WAS PROBABLY SUPPOSED TO
GIVE YOU THIS ONE FIRST.
"PRINCESS CELESTIA CORDIALLY
INVITES YOU TO THE WEDDING OF
PRINCESS MI AMORE CADENZA AND...
[ GASP ]
MY BROTHER?
[ SOFTLY ] ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
[ UPBEAT ] ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER ♪
♪ WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ I TELL YOU I SHARED ♪
♪ ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART ♪
♪ FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ♪
♪ ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YOU HAVE MY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALL MY VERY ♪
♪ BEST FRIENDS ♪
YOUR BROTHER'S GETTING
MARRIED?
CONGRATULATIONS, TWILIGHT.
THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
YEAH, GREAT NEWS...
THAT I JUST GOT FROM A WEDDING
INVITATION, NOT FROM MY BROTHER
BUT FROM A PIECE OF PAPER.
THANKS A LOT, SHINING ARMOR.
I MEAN, REALLY.
HE COULDN'T TELL ME PERSONALLY?
[ AS HER BROTHER ] HEY,
TWILIGHT, JUST THOUGHT YOU
SHOULD KNOW I'M MAKING A REALLY
BIG DECISION THAT CHANGES
EVERYTHING.
OH, NEVER MIND.
YOU'LL HEAR ABOUT IT WHEN YOU
GET THE INVITATION.
PRINCESS MI AMORE CADENZA.
WHO IN THE HOOF IS THAT?
UM, TWILIGHT, ARE YOU OKAY?
SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT SHINING ARMOR AND
I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN SO CLOSE.
HE'S MY B.B.B.F.F.
BIG BROTHER BEST FRIEND FOREVER.
all: OH!
BEFORE I CAME HERE AND
LEARNED THE IMPORTANCE OF
FRIENDSHIP, SHINING ARMOR WAS
THE ONLY PONY I EVER REALLY
ACCEPTED AS A FRIEND.
[ SOFT ACOUSTIC MUSIC ]
♪ ♪
♪ WHEN I WAS JUST A FILLY ♪
♪ I FOUND IT RATHER SILLY ♪
♪ TO SEE HOW MANY OTHER PONIES ♪
♪ I COULD MEET ♪
♪ I HAD MY BOOKS TO READ ♪
♪ DIDN'T KNOW THAT I WOULD ♪
♪ EVER NEED ♪
♪ OTHER PONIES ♪
♪ TO MAKE MY LIFE COMPLETE ♪
♪ BUT THERE WAS ONE COLT ♪
♪ THAT I CARED FOR ♪
♪ I KNEW HE WOULD BE THERE ♪
♪ FOR ME ♪
♪ MY BIG BROTHER ♪
♪ BEST FRIENDS FOREVER ♪
♪ LIKE TWO PEAS IN A POD ♪
♪ WE DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER ♪
♪ HE TAUGHT ME HOW ♪
♪ TO FLY A KITE ♪
♪ BEST FRIENDS FOREVER ♪
♪ WE NEVER HAD A SINGLE FIGHT ♪
♪ WE DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE SHARED OUR HOPES ♪
♪ WE SHARED OUR DREAMS ♪
♪ I MISS HIM MORE ♪
♪ THAN I REALIZED ♪
♪ IT SEEMS ♪
♪ YOUR BIG BROTHER ♪
♪ BEST FRIENDS FOREVER ♪
♪ LIKE TWO PEAS IN A POD ♪
♪ YOU DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER ♪
♪ AND THOUGH HE'S OH SO ♪
♪ FAR AWAY ♪
♪ I HOPE THAT HE WOULD STAY ♪
♪ MY BIG BROTHER BEST FRIEND ♪
♪ FOREVER ♪
AS ONE OF YOUR P.F.F.s--
PONY FRIENDS FOREVER.
all: OH!
I WANNA TELL YOU THAT I THINK
YOUR BROTHER SOUNDS LIKE A REAL
GOOD GUY.
HE IS PRETTY SPECIAL.
I MEAN, THEY DON'T JUST LET
ANY PONY BE CAPTAIN OF THE ROYAL
GUARD.
SO LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
WE'RE HELPING OUT WITH THE
WEDDING OF NOT ONLY A PRINCESS,
BUT A CAPTAIN OF THE ROYAL
GUARD?
I GUESS WE ARE.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
THAT'S SO RAD!
I CAN'T WAIT TO TRY ON THE
DRESSES!
A SONIC RAINBOOM?
AT A WEDDING?
CAN YOU SAY "BEST WEDDING EVER"?
BEST WEDDING EVER!
SO YOU ALL GET TO HELP WITH A
BIG FANCY WEDDING.
BUT I'M THE ONE WHO GETS TO HOST
THE BACHELOR PARTY.
I HAVE JUST ONE QUESTION.
WHAT'S A BACHELOR PARTY?
[ ALL GIGGLING ]
WHY THE LONG FACE, SUGARCUBE?
I'M JUST THINKING ABOUT
SHINING ARMOR.
EVER SINCE I MOVED TO PONYVILLE,
WE'VE BEEN SEEING EACH OTHER
LESS AND LESS.
AND NOW THAT HE'S STARTING A NEW
FAMILY WITH THIS PRINCESS MI
AMORE CA-WHAT'S-HER-NAME,
WE'LL PROBABLY NEVER SEE EACH
OTHER.
COME ON, NOW.
YOU'RE HIS SISTER.
HE'LL ALWAYS MAKE TIME FOR YOU.
COULDN'T SEEM TO MAKE TIME TO
TELL ME HE WAS GETTING MARRIED.
WE'RE HERE, WE'RE HERE!
WHOA!
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE GUARDS?
I'M SURE THEY'RE JUST TAKING
THE NECESSARY PRECAUTIONS.
ROYAL WEDDINGS DO BRING OUT THE
STRANGEST PONIES.
AHH...
CHOO!
NOW LET'S GET GOING.
WE'VE GOT WORK TO DO.
AND YOU'VE GOT A BIG BROTHER
TO GO CONGRATULATE.
YEAH, CONGRATULATE.
AND THEN GIVE HIM A PIECE OF MY
MIND.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING TO SAY TO
YOU, MISTER.
TWILY!
I'VE MISSED YOU, KID!
HOW WAS THE TRAIN RIDE? I--
HOW DARE YOU NOT TELL ME IN
PERSON THAT YOU WERE GETTING
MARRIED?
I'M YOUR SISTER FOR PONY'S SAKE!
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
PRINCESS CELESTIA HAS REQUESTED
A MAJOR INCREASE IN SECURITY.
DIDN'T YOU SEE ALL THE GUARDS AT
THE TRAIN STATION?
YEAH! THERE'S A BIG WEDDING
COMING UP.
MAYBE YOU HEARD ABOUT IT!
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
WEDDING.
A THREAT HAS BEEN MADE AGAINST
CANTERLOT.
WE DON'T KNOW WHO'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR IT, BUT PRINCESS CELESTIA
ASKED THAT I HELP PROVIDE
ADDITIONAL PROTECTION.
THIS YOU NEED TO SEE.
THE BURDON OF KEEPING CANTERLOT
SAFE AND SECURE RESTS SQUARELY
ON MY SHOULDERS.
STAYING FOCUSED ON THE TASK AT
HAND IS IN MY TOP PRIORITY.
OKAY, OKAY, I GET IT.
YOU'VE GOT A REALLY IMPORTANT
JOB PROTECTING ALL OF CANTERLOT
WITH A FORCE-FIELD ONLY YOU CAN
CONJURE UP.
BUT STILL...HOW COULD YOU NOT
TELL ME ABOUT SOMETHING AS BIG
AS YOUR WEDDING?
AM I NOT THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU
ANY MORE?
HEY, YOU'RE MY LITTLE SISTER.
OF COURSE YOU'RE IMPORTANT TO
ME.
BUT I'D UNDERSTAND IF YOU
DIDN'T WANNA BE MY BEST MARE
NOW.
YOU WANT ME TO BE YOUR BEST
MARE?
WELL, YEAH.
I'D BE HONORED.
BUT I'M STILL PRETTY TICKED
YOU'RE MARRYING SOME PONY I
DON'T EVEN KNOW.
WHEN DID YOU MEET THIS PRINCESS
MI AMORE CADENZA?
TWILY, PRINCESS MI AMORE
CADENZA IS CADENCE.
YOUR OLD FOALSITTER.
CADENCE?
AS IN THE CADENCE?
AS IN THE GREATEST FOALSITTER
IN ALL THE HISTORY OF
FOALSITTERS?
[ CHUCKLING ] YOU TELL ME.
SHE WAS YOUR FOALSITTER.
OH, MY GOSH! OH, MY GOSH!
CADENCE IS ONLY THE MOST AMAZING
PONY EVER!
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL, SHE'S CARING,
SHE'S KIND.
I AM SO LUCKY TO HAVE YOU AS MY
FOALSITTER.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S LUCKY,
TWILIGHT.
HA.
YOU'RE A PRINCESS.
I'M JUST A REGULAR OLD UNICORN.
YOU ARE ANYTHING BUT A
REGULAR OLD UNICORN.
both: SUNSHINE, SUNSHINE.
LADYBUG'S AWAKE.
CLAP YOUR HOOVES AND DO A LITTLE
SHAKE.
I AM GOING FOR A HOOFICURE
AND THAT I THAT!
YOU ARE NOT GOING!
I PAID FOR THREE THIS MONTH.
MY GIRLFRIENDS ARE ALL
GETTING THEIR HOOVES DONE.
[ BOTH ARGUING ]
OH, SWEETIE.
OH.
YOU JUST DID THAT THING.
HOW MANY UNICORNS CAN JUST
SPREAD LOVE WHEREVER THEY GO?
I ONLY KNOW OF ONE.
AND YOU'RE MARRYING HER!
YOU'RE MARRYING CADENCE!
I HOPE I'M NOT INTERRUPTING
ANYTHING IMPORTANT.
CADENCE!
SUNSHINE, SUNSHINE, LADYBUG'S
AWAKE.
CLAP YOUR HOOVES AND DO A LITTLE
SHAKE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CADENCE, IT'S ME TWILIGHT!
UH-HUH.
I'VE GOTTA GET BACK TO MY
STATION.
BUT CADENCE WILL BE CHECKING IN
WITH ALL OF YOU TO SEE HOW
THINGS ARE GOING.
I THINK I SPEAK FOR BOTH OF US
WHEN I SAY WE COULDN'T BE MORE
EXCITED TO HAVE YOU HERE.
RIGHT, DEAR?
ABSOLUTELY.
WELL, WE'LL LET YOU GET TO
IT.
[ FAST BANJO MUSIC ]
CAKE...CHECK.
ICE SCULPTURE...CHECK.
BEST DARN BITE-SIZE APPLE
FRITTER YOU EVER TASTED...
MM.
CHECK!
I DO. DO YOU?
[ GIRL VOICE ] I DO!
[ KISSING SOUNDS ]
[ GIGGLING ]
HIYA, PRINCESS!
PLEASE CALL ME PRINCESS MI
AMORE CADENZA.
HIYA, PRINCESS MI AMORE
CADENZA!
YOU COME TO CHECK OUT WHAT'S
ON THE MENU FOR YOU BIG DAY?
I HAVE.
DELICIOUS.
I LOVE, LOVE, LOVE THEM!
OH, SHUCKS, WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE A FEW TO GO?
I KNOW HOW YOU BRIDES CAN BE.
SO BUSY YOU FORGET TO GET A
LITTLE SOMETHING IN YOUR BELLY.
[ GASP ]
DID YOU SEE WHAT SHE--
OH, YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN HOW SHE
ACTED BACK THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN SHE CHANGED,
BUT SHE CHANGED!
[ IMITATING PRINCESS ] "PLEASE.
CALL ME PRINCESS MI AMORE
CADENZA."
DID I HEAR SOMEONE SAY MY
NAME?
YOUR HIGHNESS!
LET ME JUST START BY SAYING
WHAT AN HONOR IT IS TO PLAY
A ROLE IN SUCH A MOMENTOUS
OCCASION.
UH-HUH.
IS MY DRESS READY?
OH, UH, UH, YES, OF COURSE.
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON IT EVER
SINCE I WAS GIVEN THE
ASSIGNMENT, AND I THINK YOU'LL
BE PLEASED WITH THE RESULTS.
I WAS HOPING FOR SOMETHING
WITH MORE BEADING AND LONGER
TRAIN.
OH! YES! OF COURSE.
AND THOSE SHOULD BE A
DIFFERENT COLOR.
I THINK THEY'RE LOVELY.
ME TOO!
I LOVE THEM.
MAKE THEM A DIFFERENT COLOR.
GEE!
MAYBE HER NAME SHOULD BE
PRINCESS DEMANDYPANTS.
OKAY, LET ME SEE.
WE'VE BEEN OVER THE GAMES.
THE DANCES.
[ POLKA MUSIC ]
I THINK THIS RECEPTION IS GONNA
BE PERFECT, DON'T YOU?
PERFECT.
IF WE WERE CELEBRATING A
SIX-YEAR-OLD'S BIRTHDAY PARTY.
[ GASP ] THANK YOU!
REST, MY SISTER.
AS ALWAYS, I WILL GUARD THE
NIGHT.
BET I CAN GUESS WHAT YOU'RE
ALL THINKING.
CADENCE IS THE ABSOLUTE WORST
BRIDE-TO-BE EVER.
WHO ME?
SPIKE! THAT GOES ON THE CAKE.
[ NERVOUS CHUCKLE ]
TWILIGHT, WHATEVER ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
CADENCE IS AN ABSOLUTE GEM.
RARITY, SHE WAS SO DEMANDING.
WELL, OF COURSE SHE WAS.
WHY SHOULDN'T SHE EXPECT THE
VERY BEST ON HER WEDDING DAY?
APPLEJACK, DID YOU KNOW THAT
AFTER SHE TOLD YOU HOW MUCH SHE
JUST..."LOVE, LOVE, LOVED"
YOUR HORS D'OEUVRES, SHE THREW
THEM IN THE TRASH?
OH, SHE WAS PROBABLY JUST
TRYING TO SPARE MY FEELINGS.
NO, SHE WAS JUST BEING FAKE
AND TOTALLY INSINCERE.
SHE DID RAISE HER VOICE AT
ONE OF MY BIRDS DURING
REHEARSAL.
SEE? RUDE!
BUT HE WAS SINGING REALLY
OFF-KEY.
[ BIRD SQUEALS ]
PINKIE PIE, YOU HAD TO HAVE
NOTICED HOW CADENCE TREATED--
MWAH!
[ KISSING SOUNDS, GIGGLING ]
NEVER MIND.
RAINBOW DASH, YOU'RE WITH ME,
RIGHT?
SORRY, TWI.
BEEN TOO BUSY PREPPING FOR MY
SONIC RAINBOOM TO PAY MUCH
ATTENTION TO THE BRIDE'S BAD
ATTITUDE.
[ GRUNTS ]
THE PRINCESS IS ABOUT TO GET
MARRIED.
I'M SURE ANY NEGATIVE BEHAVIOR
SHE MIGHT BE DISPLAYING IS
SIMPLY THE RESULT OF NERVES.
AND I'M SURE IT'S THE RESULT
OF HER BEING AN AWFUL PONY WHO
DOESN'T DESERVE TO EVEN KNOW
SHINING ARMOR, LET ALONE MARRY
HIM!
THINK MAYBE YOU'RE BEING JUST
A TINY BIT POSSESSIVE OF YOUR
BROTHER?
all: UH-HUH.
I AM NOT BEING POSSESSIVE.
AND I AM NOT TAKING IT OUT ON
CADENCE.
YOU'RE ALL JUST TOO CAUGHT UP
IN YOUR WEDDING PLANNING
TO NOTICE THAT MAYBE THERE
SHOULDN'T EVEN BE A WEDDING!
[ KNOCKING ]
TWILY!
YOU'RE BIG BROTHER'S LOOKING
PRETTY GOOD.
DON'T YOU THINK?
HUH, EVERYTHING OKAY?
WE NEED TO TALK.
I THINK YOU'RE MAKING A BIG--
AHEM.
OH, HI, SWEETIE.
SHE SURE HAS A WAY OF
SNEAKING UP ON PEOPLE.
COULD I SPEAK TO YOU FOR A
MOMENT, DEAR?
BETTER SEE WHAT SHE WANTS.
LOOK, WE NEED TO TALK.
CAN'T DO IT WITH YOUR SISTER
HERE.
LOOK, SHE'S OKAY.
JUST LISTEN TO ME.
I'M LISTENING, I'M LISTENING.
I THOUGHT I MADE IT PERFECTLY
CLEAR I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO WEAR
THAT.
THIS WAS MY FAVORITE UNCLE'S.
AND?
AND I THINK I SHOULD WEAR IT.
ARE YOU DISAGREEING WITH ME?
I GUESS I AM!
AH!
OH, DEAR.
ARE YOU GETTING ANOTHER ONE OF
YOUR HEADACHES?
AGH!
FEELING BETTER?
YEAH. MM-HMM.
SHE ISN'T JUST UNPLEASANT AND
RUDE, SHE'S DOWNRIGHT EVIL!
TWILIGHT!
LET HER GO.
HUH, IT SEEMED LIKE SHE HAD
SOMETHING ELSE SHE WANTED TO
TELL ME.
WHO GOES THERE?
STAY INDOORS, TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
SHINING ARMOR'S IN REAL
TROUBLE, YOU HAVE TO HELP!
[ ALL CHATTERING ]
WHAT ARE YOU--
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
WE'RE GONNA BE PRINCESS MI
AMORE CADENZA'S NEW BRIDESMAIDS.
NEW BRIDESMAIDS?
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER OLD
BRIDESMAIDS?
SHE DIDN'T SAY, BUT SHE DID
TELL US THAT SHE WOULD "LOVE,
LOVE, LOVE IT" IF WE'D FILL IN
FOR THEM.
SEEING AS WE'VE BEEN WORKING
SO HARD AND EVERYTHING.
AND YOU HAD YOUR DOUBTS
ABOUT HER.
TOLD YOU SHE WAS AN ABSOLUTE
JEM.
YOU SURE THIS IS WHAT I
SHOULD WEAR?
DOESN'T SEEM ALL THAT
AERODYNAMIC.
MM, I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
I KNOW! THIS IS AWESOME!
LOOK LIKE I REALLY AM ON MY
OWN.
[ ORGAN PLAYING ]
PERFECT, GIRLS.
NO NEED TO RUSH.
THEN OF COURSE, CADENCE WILL
ENTER.
[ HERE COMES THE BRIDE PLAYS ]
I'LL SAY A FEW WORDS, AND
THEN WE'LL BEGIN WITH THE VOWS.
SHINING ARMOR, YOU'LL GET THE
RING FROM YOUR BEST MARE.
[ LOW VOICE ] DO YOU?
[ HIGH VOICE ] I DO.
HEY, HAS ANY PONY SEEN
TWILIGHT?
I'M HERE!
I'M NOT GONNA STAND NEXT TO HER,
AND NEITHER SHOULD YOU.
I'M SORRY, I--
I DON'T KNOW WHY SHE'S ACTING
LIKE THIS.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST IGNORE
HER.
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME.
OH, GOODNESS.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
I'VE GOT SOMETHING TO SAY.
SHE'S EVIL!
[ ALL REACTING ]
I HEAR THAT.
SHE'S BEEN HORRIBLE TO MY
FRIENDS.
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY DONE SOMETHING
TO HER BRIDESMAIDS.
AND IF THAT WASN'T ENOUGH,
I SAW HER PUT A SPELL ON MY
BROTHER THAT MADE HIS EYES GO
ALL--
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO ME?
[ CRYING ]
BECAUSE YOU'RE EVIL!
EVIL!
AND IF I DON'T STOP YOU, YOU'RE
GONNA RUIN MY BROTHER'S LIFE!
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY MY EYES
WENT ALL--
BECAUSE EVER SINCE I STARTED
HAVING TO PERFORM MY PROTECTION
SPELL, I'VE BEEN GETTING
TERRIBLE MIGRAINES.
CADENCE HASN'T BEEN CASTING
SPELLS ON ME, SHE'S BEEN USING
HER MAGIC TO HEAL ME.
[ GASP ]
AND SHE DECIDED TO REPLACE
HER BRIDESMAIDS BECAUSE SHE
FOUND OUT THE ONLY REASON THEY
WANTED TO BE IN THE WEDDING WAS
SO THEY COULD MEET CANTERLOT
ROYALTY.
AND IF SHE HASN'T BEEN ON HER
BEST BEHAVIOR WITH YOUR FRIENDS,
IT'S BECAUSE WITH ME BEING SO
BUSY SHE'S HAD TO MAKE ALL THE
DECISIONS ABOUT THE WEDDING.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO--
SHE'S COMPLETELY STRESSED OUT
BECAUSE IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT TO
HER THAT OUR BIG DAY BE PERFECT!
SOMETHING THAT OBVIOUSLY WASN'T
IMPORTANT TO YOU.
[ WINCING ]
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME, I HAVE
TO GO AND COMFORT MY BRIDE.
AND YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT BEING
MY BEST MARE.
IN FACT, IF I WERE YOU, I
WOULDN'T SHOW UP TO THE WEDDING
AT ALL.
COME ON, Y'ALL.
LET'S GO CHECK ON THE PRINCESS.
I WA--
YOU HAVE A LOT TO THINK
ABOUT.
MAYBE I WAS BEING
OVERPROTECTIVE.
I COULD'VE GAINED A SISTER.
BUT INSTEAD, I JUST LOST A
BROTHER.
♪ HE WAS MY BIG BROTHER ♪
♪ BEST FRIEND ♪
♪ FOREVER ♪
♪ AND NOW WE'LL NEVER ♪
♪ DO ANYTHING ♪
♪ TOGETHER ♪
I'M SORRY.
YOU WILL BE.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪