[ EXCITED CHATTER ]
&gt;&gt; CAN YOU BELIEVE THE NEW BABY
IS FINALLY HERE?
&gt;&gt; CUP CAKE AND CARROT CAKE MUST
BE SO PROUD.
&gt;&gt; I WONDER IF IT'S A FILLY OR A
COLT.
&gt;&gt; I WANT TO SEE THE NEW BABY
PONY.
I WANT TO SEE!
WHICH ONE IS IT?!
&gt;&gt; MEET OUR SON, POUND CAKE.
&gt;&gt; [ YAWNS ]
&gt;&gt; All: AWW!
&gt;&gt; AND OUR DAUGHTER,
PUMPKIN CAKE.
&gt;&gt; [ YAWNS ]
&gt;&gt; All: HUH?
&gt;&gt; TWO NEW FOALS FOR ME TO PLAY
WITH?
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S TWO -- TWO -- TWO TIMES
THE FUN.
THIS IS THE GREATEST DAY EVER!
WE NEED TO CELEBRATE YOUR
BIRTHDAY, BABIES!
'CAUSE YOU WERE JUST BORN TODAY!
WHOO-HOO!
&gt;&gt; Shh!
THE BABIES ARE TRYING TO SLEEP.
&gt;&gt; BUT I WAS JUST --
&gt;&gt; Shh!
&gt;&gt; BUT --
&gt;&gt; ♪ Happy, happy birthday to
you and you today ♪
&gt;&gt; NOW, HOW IN THUNDERATION IS
ONE OF THEM TWINS A PEGASUS AND
THE OTHER ONE A UNICORN?
&gt;&gt; EASY.
MY GREAT-GREAT-GREAT-GREAT-
GRANDFATHER WAS A UNICORN, AND
CUPCAKE'S GREAT-AUNT, SECOND
COUSIN, TWICE REMOVED WAS A
PEGASUS.
AND THAT MAKES SENSE, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; AW, YEAH.
[ LAUGHS ]
JUST YOU WAIT.
ONCE LITTLE POUND CAKE THERE
GETS HIS WINGS GOING, HE'LL BE
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
&gt;&gt; AND BE CAREFUL AROUND
PUMPKIN CAKE.
&gt;&gt; BABY UNICORNS GET STRANGE
MAGIC SURGES THAT COME AND GO.
&gt;&gt; QUICK!
MAKE A WISH AND BLOW OUT YOUR
CANDLES, WHICH IS EASY 'CAUSE
THERE ARE ZERO CANDLES.
YOU ARE ZERO YEARS OLD, AFTER
ALL.
&gt;&gt; Shh!
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
AND STRONG ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ FOALS GIGGLE ]
&gt;&gt; ♪ HAPPY MONTHAVERSARY TO YOU
AND YOU TODAY ♪
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE ALREADY A
MONTH OLD.
TIME SURE FLIES, DOESN'T IT?
WOW, SEEMS LIKE ONLY YESTERDAY
YOU WERE BORN!
♪ BUT NOW YOU'RE A MONTH OLD
TODAY ♪
HEY!
[ HORNS BLOW ]
[ FOALS GIGGLE, BABBLE ]
ARE YOU READY FOR YOUR
FAVORITEST GAME IN THE WHOLE
WIDE WORLD?
WHERE'S PINKIE PIE?
HERE I AM!
[ DOORS CLOSE ]
WHERE'S PINKIE PIE?
[ DOORS OPEN ]
HERE I AM!
[ FOALS LAUGH ]
[ DOORS CLOSE ]
[ DOORS OPEN ]
HERE I AM!
PBHT!
&gt;&gt; EVERYTHING OKAY IN THERE?
[ Singsong voice ] WHO NEEDS A
DIAPER CHANGE?
&gt;&gt; DON'T WORRY.
[ Singsong voice ] THEY'RE FINE.
[ SNIFFS ]
[ Normal voice ] OH, I MEAN...
&gt;&gt; OH [CHUCKLES] I'VE GOT IT.
[ FOALS GIGGLE ]
[ Singsong voice ] IS ANYPONY
HUNGRY?
&gt;&gt; UH, NO, THANKS.
I JUST HAD A BIG BREAKFAST.
&gt;&gt; [ Normal voice ] I'M ON IT.
[ WHOOSH! ]
&gt;&gt; [ GLUG! GLUG! GLUG! ]
[ WATCH TICKS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GAGS ]
&gt;&gt; OH, OH, YOU'RE MAKING FUNNY
FACES.
I HAVE ONE.
UGH!
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
[ Normal voice ] NO, YOU SEE,
PINKIE, THE BABIES NEED TO BE
BURPED.
[ FOALS BURP ]
&gt;&gt; ALL SET NOW?
EVERYTHING GOOD?
OKAY.
WHO WANTS TO PLAY AGAIN?
[ FOALS LAUGH, BABBLE ]
&gt;&gt; AH, AH, AH, POUND CAKE.
NO POUNDING THINGS.
&gt;&gt; AH, AH, AH, AH.
WE DON'T CHEW ON THINGS,
PUMPKIN CAKE.
&gt;&gt; EXCEPT FOOD.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
FOOD!
GREAT CINNAMON STICKS, I
COMPLETELY FORGOT!
&gt;&gt; NO, YOU JUST FED THEM
BOTTLES, REMEMBER?
&gt;&gt; NOT THE BABIES' FOOD.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
THE FOOD FOR THE ENORMOUSLY BIG
CATERING ORDER WE HAVE TO
DELIVER TODAY!
&gt;&gt; OH, WITH THE NEW TWINS, WE'VE
BEEN SO DISTRACTED.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
QUICK, HONEYBUN, WE NEED TO FIND
A BABYSITTER TO WATCH THE FOALS
WHILE WE TAKE CARE OF THIS.
&gt;&gt; I CAN DO IT!
I WANT TO DO IT.
OH, THE BABIES LOVE PLAYING WITH
ME.
I'LL DO IT!
&gt;&gt; I WONDER WHO WOULD BE
AVAILABLE ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
&gt;&gt; ME! ME! PICK ME!
&gt;&gt; OH, I WOULD LOVE TO
BABYSIT...
BUT I CAN'T TODAY.
SORRY.
I PROMISED ANGEL WE'D GO ON A
PICNIC.
YOU UNDERSTAND, DON'T YOU?
YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME, ARE YOU?
PLEASE DON'T BE MAD AT ME!
&gt;&gt; I'LL DO IT!
PICK ME!
&gt;&gt; I HAVE TO FINISH THIS REPORT
FOR THE PRINCESS, SUMMARIZING
ALL MY OTHER REPORTS TO THE
PRINCESS.
&gt;&gt; I WANT TO BABYSIT.
PICK ME!
&gt;&gt; [ Panting ] BABYSIT? NOW?
WHEN THERE'S A SWARM OF HUNGRY
CATERPILLARS HEADING THIS WAY?
I GOT TO GET ALL THESE APPLES
PICKED BEFORE THEY GET SWARMED
ON.
[ ZOOM! ]
&gt;&gt; OOH! OOH!
I WANT TO DO IT.
&gt;&gt; I GOT TICKETS TO THE
WONDERBOLTS AIR SHOW THIS
AFTERNOON.
GOT TO DASH!
[ WHOOSH! ]
&gt;&gt; ASK ME!
ME, ME, ME, ME, ME, ME, ME, ME,
ME, ME, ME, ME, ME, ME!
&gt;&gt; MOI? BABYSIT?
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I AM FLATTERED THAT YOU WOULD
THINK ABOUT ME, THOUGH.
[ SLOOP! ]
&gt;&gt; UH, UH, PINKIE PIE, HOW WOULD
YOU LIKE TO BABYSIT FOR US?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL HAVE TO CHECK MY SCHEDULE.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; NOW, PINKIE, ARE YOU SURE
YOU REALLY UNDERSTAND THE
RESPONSIBILITY OF WATCHING OVER
TWO BABIES?
&gt;&gt; I CAN BE RESPONSIBLE.
WHY, "RESPONSIBILITY" IS MY
MIDDLE NAME.
PINKIE RESPONSIBILITY PIE.
&gt;&gt; BUT THIS TIME, YOU NEED TO
TAKE CARE OF THEM, NOT JUST PLAY
WITH THEM.
YOU HAVE TO BE RESPONSIBLE.
&gt;&gt; YES.
I KNOW.
I WILL.
I AM.
[ BELL DINGS ]
&gt;&gt; OH, HERE YOU ARE, DEARIE.
ALL OF YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES ARE
ON THIS LIST.
&gt;&gt; WHOA!
THAT'S A LOT OF RESPONSI--
CONSIDER IT DONE.
&gt;&gt; WE'LL FROST IT WHEN WE GET
THERE.
COME ON, SUGAR PLUM, TICK, TICK!
&gt;&gt; TAKE GOOD CARE OF OUR TWO
PRECIOUS LITTLE GINGERSNAPS.
&gt;&gt; NO PROBLEMO,
MR. AND MRS. CAKE.
EVERYTHING IS UNDER CONTROL.
[ BOTH CRYING ]
UH-OH.
[ FOALS CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; OH, DON'T CRY, LITTLE
FRIENDS.
LOOK! LOOK!
[ CRYING STOPS ]
WHERE'S PINKIE PIE?
[ FOALS CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; OH, NO.
I'M RIGHT HERE. SEE?
[ CRYING STOPS ]
[ WARBLE! ]
[ BOTH CRYING ]
UH...THINK, THINK, THINK!
AHA!
HEY, GUYS, WATCH THIS!
[ LIGHT APPLAUSE ]
HEY, YOU'RE A WONDERFUL CROWD
HERE, TONIGHT.
WHERE Y'ALL FROM?
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
YOU KNOW, I USED TO HAVE AN ANT
FARM, BUT I HAD TO GET RID OF IT
BECAUSE I COULDN'T FIND TRACTORS
THAT SMALL.
[ RIMSHOT ]
GET IT?
TRACTORS...THAT...SMALL?
[ BLINK! ]
THE OTHER DAY, I SPILLED SPOT
REMOVER ON MY DOG, AND NOW I
CAN'T FIND HIM!
[ RIMSHOT ]
[ BOTH CRYING ]
PHEW.
TOUGH CROWD.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
FINE!
I WASN'T GONNA PULL OUT THE
SHOWSTOPPER, BUT YOU'RE A LOVELY
AUDIENCE, AND I THINK YOU
DESERVE IT!
♪ FIRST YOU JIGGLE YOUR TAIL ♪
♪ OINK, OINK, OINK! ♪
♪ THEN YOU WRIGGLE YOUR SNOUT ♪
♪ THEN YOU WRIGGLE YOUR RUMP ♪
♪ OINK, OINK, OINK! ♪
♪ THEN SHOUT IT OUT ♪
♪ FIRST YOU JIGGLE YOUR TAIL ♪
♪ OINK, OINK, OINK! ♪
♪ THEN YOU WRIGGLE YOUR SNOUT ♪
♪ THEN YOU WRIGGLE YOUR RUMP ♪
♪ OINK, OINK, OINK! ♪
♪ THEN SHOUT IT OUT ♪
[ BOTH CRYING ]
♪ OINK, OINK, OINK! ♪
♪ THEN YOU WRIGGLE YOUR SNOUT ♪
♪ THEN YOU WRIGGLE YOUR RUMP ♪
♪ OINK, OINK, OINK! ♪
♪ THEN SHOUT IT -- OW!
[ CRYING STOPS ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
THERE. SEE?
NOTHING TO THIS BABYSITTING
BUSINESS.
[ SIGHS ]
SNACK TIME.
THAT'S EASY ENOUGH.
OKIE DOKIE.
EAT UP.
LIKE THIS.
NUM, NUM, NUM!
NUM, NUM, NUM, NUM!
AHH!
NO, PUMPKIN CAKE.
WE EAT FOOD, NOT TABLE CLOTHS.
&gt;&gt; [ CRIES ]
[ SPLAT! ]
&gt;&gt; UH, HEY, GUYS.
LOOK AT ME.
[ CRYING STOPS ]
[ SNEEZES ]
[ BOTH GIGGLING ]
YEAH.
I THINK I CAN SEE WHERE THIS IS
GOING.
[ SNORTS ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ SPROING! ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ CHOMP! ]
TOWELS ARE NOT FOOD,
PUMPKIN CAKE!
[ FOALS GIGGLING ]
DROP IT!
[ High-pitched ] DROP IT!
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ BOTH GIGGLING ]
[ YOINK! ]
[ SPLASH! ]
[ BOTH CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; OOH! LOOK GUYS! BUBBLES!
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
[ CRYING STOPS ]
[ SPLASH! SPLASH! SPLASH! ]
[ POP! ]
[ BOTH CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; UH...UH...DON'T CRY!
LOOK! LOOK!
UH, FLOATY THINGS! OOH! AAH!
[ CRYING STOPS ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ SPLASH! ZOOM! ]
[ SPLASH! ]
[ BOTH CRYING ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ SMACK! SPLAT! ]
[ SQUISH! ]
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
DON'T MAKE ME DO IT, GUYS.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
MIX FLOUR AND WATER, DON'T YOU?
[ BOTH CRYING ]
[ POOF! ]
[ CRYING STOPS ]
[ BOTH GIGGLE ]
[ SNIFFS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
[ Singsong voice ] SMELLS LIKE
SOMEPONY NEEDS ME TO
CHANGEY-WANGEY THEIR
DIAPER-WIPER RIGHT NOW-WOW-WOW.
[ PITTER! PITTER! PATTER! ]
EASY. EASY.
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ THUMP! ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
[ THUMP! ]
[ FOALS GIGGLE ]
NO! STAY THERE! AAH!
[ FOALS GIGGLING ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
JUST ONE MORE SECOND!
[ GIGGLING CONTINUES ]
STAND STILL. I'M ALMOST --
[ HAMMER! HAMMER! ]
[ BOTH GIGGLE ]
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
[ BELL JINGLES ]
OH! THANK GOODNESS THEY'RE HOME!
&gt;&gt; HI.
I FINISHED UP THE WORK I HAD TO
DO, SO I THOUGHT I'D STOP BY AND
SEE IF YOU NEEDED ANY HELP.
[ YANK! ]
WHOA!
[ SLAM! ]
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU! THANK YOU!
THANK YOU FOR COMING!
I CAN'T BEGIN TO TELL YOU WHAT
MY DAY HAS BEEN LIKE.
I MEAN, THESE BABIES JUST WON'T
LISTEN TO REASON, AND DON'T EVEN
GET ME STARTED ON THEIR TASTE IN
STAND-UP COMEDY.
[ RIM SHOT ]
&gt;&gt; IT'S OKAY, PINKIE.
I FIGURED YOU WOULD NEED SOME
HELP.
THAT'S WHY I STOPPED BY.
&gt;&gt; EXCUSE ME?!
&gt;&gt; BABIES TAKE A LOT OF WORK,
AND SOME PONIES ARE JUST NOT CUT
OUT TO HANDLE THE
RESPONSIBILITY.
&gt;&gt; IS THAT SO?!
[ HOOVES SQUEAKING ]
WELL, THANKS FOR STOPPING BY,
TWILIGHT.
SORRY I DON'T HAVE TIME TO
VISIT.
I'M VERY, VERY BUSY WITH MY
RESPONSIBILITIES HERE.
&gt;&gt; I-I'M HAPPY TO HELP.
IT'S NO TROUBLE AT --
[ SLAM! ]
&gt;&gt; WELL, OF ALL THE -- UGH!
SHE THINKS I CAN'T HANDLE THINGS
ON MY OWN!
MAYBE BECAUSE I HAVEN'T HANDLED
THINGS ON MY OWN.
WELL, I CAN HANDLE THINGS ON MY
OWN.
&gt;&gt; [ BABBLING ]
[ MATTRESS SQUEAKING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ FLUMP! FLUMP! FLUMP! ]
&gt;&gt; POUND CAKE!
THIS IS A CRIB.
IT IS ONLY TO BE USED FOR
NAPPING, SLEEPING, AND ON
OCCASION, WITH PERMISSION, AS A
PRETEND, OLD-TIMEY, WESTERN
FORT.
IT IS NOT A TRAMPOLINE, SO STOP
YOUR JUMPING RIGHT NOW, MISTER!
[ GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; AND, YOU, YOUNG FILLY.
WE DO NOT PUT ANYTHING IN OUR
MOUTH THAT WE CANNOT SAFELY AND
PROPERLY DIGEST.
SO STOP SLOBBERING ON THAT TOY
THIS INSTANT!
[ SQUEAK! ]
NOW HAVE ALL HAD A VERY
EXHAUSTING AFTERNOON AND IT'S
TIME FOR ALL GOOD LITTLE FOALS
TO TAKE THEIR NAPS, SO...
FALL ASLEEP!
[ BOTH SNORING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ SMOOCH! SMOOCH! ]
SLEEP TIGHT.
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ CLICK ]
NOW THAT'S WHAT I CALL HANDLING
THINGS.
[ DOOR SQUEAKS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOT GOOD! NOT GOOD! NOT GOOD!
POUND? PUMPKIN? WHERE ARE YOU?!
[ SQUEAK! ]
COME OUT, COME OUT, WHEREVER YOU
ARE!
[ ZIP! ZING! ]
[ ZING! TINK! ]
[ CHICKEN SQUEAKS ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
WHOA!
YOU BE A GOOD LITTLE GIRL NOW,
PUMPKIN-WUMPKIN AND STAY IN YOUR
CRIB FOR YOUR PAL PINKIE-WINKIE!
[ NERVOUS CHUCKLE ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ PONK! ]
[ WHIP! ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
POUND CAKE?
[ CLICKS TONGUE ]
HERE, POUND CAKE!
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
&gt;&gt; [ Echoing ] PINKIE!
[ OMINOUS GIGGLING ]
&gt;&gt; POUND CAKE?
[ SQUEAK! ]
&gt;&gt; [ Echoing ] PINKIE!
[ OMINOUS GIGGLE ]
[ SLOWER, ECHOING SQUEAK ]
[ SLOWER, LOWER-PITCHED SQUEAK ]
&gt;&gt; [ Echoing ] PINKIE.
[ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; [ SQUEALS ]
YOU CAN FLY?!
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING ]
[ BOING! BOING! ]
&gt;&gt; GET DOWN HERE...
[ BOING! ]
...THIS INSTANT...
...YOUNG...
[ BOING! ]
...COLT!
[ THUD! ]
[ PANTING, SIGHS ]
I'M RESPONSIBLE FOR YOU!
[ PIP! POP! PIP! POP! PIP! ]
[ POP! PIP! POP! PIP! POP! ]
[ CREAK! ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING ]
[ CHOMP! ]
[ SLURP! ]
NOM NOM NOM!
&gt;&gt; NO, NO, NO, PUMPKIN!
&gt;&gt; [ SLURP! ]
NOM NOM!
&gt;&gt; NO, NO!
&gt;&gt; [ SLURP! ]
NOM!
&gt;&gt; NO!
HMPH!
I AM THE RESPONSIBLE ONE, AND I
SAID NO.
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! ]
[ CHAIN RATTLES ]
&gt;&gt; [ Giggling ] WHEE!
&gt;&gt; THAT GOES FOR YOU, TOO,
POUND CAKE.
[ SPROING! ]
[ SPROING! SPLAT! ]
[ ZIP! ]
GOTCHA!
I THINK?
WHOA!
[ ZOOM! ]
[ THUMP! THUMP! THUMP! THUMP! ]
[ CLUNK! CLUNK! CLANK! CLANK! ]
[ SPLAT! ] OOH!
[ SPLAT! ] UGH!
[ SPLAT! ]
[ SLURP! ]
MMM! RAZZLEBERRY!
I'M...
NOT...
LETTING...
GO!
I'M...
RE...SPON...SI...BLE!
[ WHAP! WHAP! WHAP! WHAP! ]
[ CREAK! SNAP! SLUMP! ]
[ TINKLING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; OH, NOT YOU, TOO!
[ WHOOSH! SLAM! ]
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! ]
THERE!
NOW WHO'S THE RESPONSIBLE ONE?
[ TINKLING ]
&gt;&gt; YEAH!
[ GIGGLES ]
[ BABBLING, GIGGLING ]
[ R-R-R-R-RIP! ]
[ CREAK! CLANK! ]
&gt;&gt; YAY!
[ SLURP! SLURP! ]
&gt;&gt; [ WARBLE! WARBLE! ]
[ SOBBING LOUDLY ]
[ EXHALES RAGGEDLY ]
[ POOF! ]
[ GIGGLES ]
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT IS FUNNY.
&gt;&gt; [ MUMBLING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SNORING ]
&gt;&gt; "DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
I'VE ALWAYS HAD FUN PLAYING WITH
LITTLE KIDS, AND I THOUGHT
BABYSITTING MEANT JUST MORE
PLAYTIME, RIGHT?
[ Singsong voice ] WRONG!
[ Normal voice ] BEING A
CAREGIVER IS WAY MORE
RESPONSIBILITY THAN JUST BEING A
PLAYMATE.
AND TODAY I LEARNED THAT
SOMETIMES OUR DESIRE FOR
RESPONSIBILITY CAN OUTRUN OUR
ACTUAL ABILITY TO HANDLE IT."
[ BELL JINGLES ]
&gt;&gt; PINKIE PIE, WE'RE BACK.
&gt;&gt; HOW DID EVERYTHING GO?
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ TWINKLING ]
&gt;&gt; ARE WE IN THE RIGHT PLACE?
&gt;&gt; SHH!
[ BOTH SNORING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] PINKIE!
THIS IS JUST...JUST...
&gt;&gt; AMAZING IS WHAT IT IS!
WE HAD NO IDEA HOW RESPONSIBLE
YOU REALLY ARE.
[ BLINK! ]
WOULD YOU BE INTERESTED IN
BECOMING OUR GO-TO BABYSITTER ON
A PERMANENT BASIS?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
MM...UH...LET ME CHECK MY
SCHEDULE.
I SHOULD BE AVAILABLE A WEEK
FROM...
NEVER!
[ FOALS SIGH ]
&gt;&gt; PINKIE!
&gt;&gt; PIE!
&gt;&gt; [ WARBLE! ]
[ SIGHS ]
I HAVE SOME FREE TIME NEXT
TUESDAY.
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪