LUNCHTIME!
WHO'S HUNGRY?
PLENTY FOR EVERYPONY.
[ PONK! ]
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
[ SLAP! THUD! ]
SLOW DOWN, SWEETIE.
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ THUMP! THUMP! THUMP! THUMP! ]
HERE YOU GO, ANGEL BUNNY.
[ SMACK! ]
[ CLUNK! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
[ THUMP! THUMP! THUMP! THUMP! ]
OKAY, MR. PICKY-PANTS.
YOU WIN.
CARROTS, LETTUCE, AND APPLES.
YUM, YUM, YUM!
[ BOWL SHATTERS ]
WHAT?
BUT --
[ THUD! ]
[ POP! ]
WELL, THEN, WHAT WILL YOU EAT?
[ ZIP! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ POINK! ]
I'M NOT SURE I CAN EVEN MAKE
THAT.
WELL, I DON'T WANT YOU TO
STARVE.
OH, ARE YOU SURE I CAN'T TEMPT
YOU WITH A NICE, CRISP PIECE
OF --
[ SLAP! ]
[ SMACK! ]
[ CLANK! ]
[ SIGHS ]
I'LL MAKE YOUR SPECIAL RECIPE.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
HMM. LET'S SEE.
ASPARAGUS.
[ ZIP! ]
EXCUSE ME.
UM, I THINK YOU JUST STEPPED IN
FRONT OF ME.
EXCUSE ME.
I THINK YOU MADE A MISTAKE.
YOU SEE, I WAS ACTUALLY HERE
FIRST AND --
SORRY.
DIDN'T NOTICE YOU THERE.
I KNOW.
[ LAUGHS ]
PARDON ME, SIR.
YES? WHAT?
I THINK YOU JUST CUT IN FRONT
OF ME.
A CUT OF CELERY?
[ SCOFFS ]
THIS IS THE ASPARAGUS STAND.
I SAID, "I THINK YOU JUST CUT
IN FRONT OF ME."
[ LAUGHS ]
NO NEED, DEARY.
I'M ALREADY IN FRONT.
I NOTICED.
I WAS LIKE, UH, WOW.
HEY!
WOULD YOU MIND MOVING BACK?
YOU'RE IN MY PERSONAL SPACE.
BUT --
SERIOUSLY?
DO YOU NEED YOUR ASPARAGUS SO
BADLY?
GET A LIFE!
OH. OKAY. THERE'S NO RUSH.
FLUTTERSHY!
YOU MUSTN'T LET THEM TREAT YOU
THAT WAY.
OH, IT'S -- IT'S REALLY NO
BIG DEAL.
IT'S BIGGER THAN BIG!
IT'S DOUBLE BIG!
YOU ARE A PONY WITH A PROBLEM.
WHAT PROBLEM?
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ WHIRL! ]
OH, GO RIGHT AHEAD, PINKIE PIE.
YOU FIRST.
RIGHT THERE!
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP BEING SUCH
A DOORMAT.
A DOORMAT?
A PUSHOVER, DARLING.
YOU'VE GOT TO STAND UP FOR
YOURSELF.
PROMISE US.
OKAY.
I PROMISE.
OH, GOOD.
[ JINGLE! ]
OH, THAT'S OKAY. I DON'T MIND.
WATCH AND LEARN.
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
MR. SMALL-AND-HANDSOME.
UH, WHO? ME?
WELL, OF COURSE YOU.
NOPONY EVER CALLED YOU HANDSOME
BEFORE?
UH, THAT'D BE A BIG NO.
OH! WELL, THEY SHOULD!
HOW ABOUT FLEXING SOME OF YOUR
MUSCLES FOR ME?
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, MY HEAVENS!
DO YOU THINK A STRONG, HANDSOME
STALLION SUCH AS YOURSELF COULD
GIVE MY FRIEND THE LAST
ASPARAGUS?
[ LAUGHS GOOFILY ]
SEE?
THAT'S NOT SO HARD, IS IT?
UM, I GUESS NOT.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
WHAT ELSE IS ON YOUR LIST?
LET'S SEE.
I ALSO NEED TOMATOES.
[ BAG RUSTLES ]
HERE YOU GO.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
THAT'LL BE TWO BITS.
NOT ONE.
OH, BUT LAST WEEK IT WAS ONLY
ONE BIT.
THAT WAS THEN. THIS IS NOW.
OH, OKAY.
I DON'T WANT TO ARGUE ABOUT IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING?!
MINDING MY OWN BUSINESS.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
TWO BITS FOR TOMATOES IS
OUTRAGEOUS!
ONE BIT IS THE RIGHT PRICE.
I SAY IT'S TWO BITS.
ONE BIT.
TWO BITS.
ONE BIT!
TWO BITS!
TWO BITS.
ONE BIT!
TWO BITS!
I INSIST IT'S TWO BITS OR
ONE BIT!
NOTHING!
I INSIST IT'S TWO BITS OR
ONE BIT AND THAT'S MY FINAL
NOTHING!
OFFER!
ONE BIT AND THAT'S MY FINAL
HAVE IT YOUR WAY.
OFFER!
ONE BIT IT IS.
HAVE IT YOUR WAY.
[ PONK! ]
ONE BIT IT IS.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
[ PONK! ]
SEE?
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
ASSERTING YOURSELF CAN BE FUN!
SEE?
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
ASSERTING YOURSELF CAN BE FUN!
SO, FLUTTERSHY, DO YOU FEEL
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
LIKE GIVING IT A TRY?
SO, FLUTTERSHY, DO YOU FEEL
UM, OKAY.
LIKE GIVING IT A TRY?
[ SQUEAK! ]
UM, OKAY.
I NEED THAT CHERRY.
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
I NEED THAT CHERRY.
BOY, AM I GLAD YOU HAVE ONE
[ ZIP! ]
CHERRY LEFT.
BOY, AM I GLAD YOU HAVE ONE
YOU SEE, I'M MAKING THIS SPECIAL
CHERRY LEFT.
MEAL FOR MY BUNNY, ANGEL.
YOU SEE, I'M MAKING THIS SPECIAL
HE'S A VERY PICKY EATER, AND THE
MEAL FOR MY BUNNY, ANGEL.
RECIPE CALLS FOR A CHERRY ON
HE'S A VERY PICKY EATER, AND THE
TOP.
RECIPE CALLS FOR A CHERRY ON
HERE YOU GO.
TOP.
SO, YOU SAY YOU NEED THIS
HERE YOU GO.
CHERRY VERY BADLY?
SO, YOU SAY YOU NEED THIS
OH, YES.
CHERRY VERY BADLY?
I'M DESPERATE FOR IT.
OH, YES.
THEN IT'LL BE 10 BITS.
I'M DESPERATE FOR IT.
10?!
THEN IT'LL BE 10 BITS.
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
10?!
OH, HEY, MR. HANDSOME.
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
I KNOW YOU WANT TO DO THE RIGHT
OH, HEY, MR. HANDSOME.
THING BECAUSE YOU'RE HANDSOME
I KNOW YOU WANT TO DO THE RIGHT
AND -- AND STRONG, AND BIG,
THING BECAUSE YOU'RE HANDSOME
HANDSOME, STRONG GUYS ARE ALWAYS
AND -- AND STRONG, AND BIG,
NICE TO EVERYPONY, RIGHT?
HANDSOME, STRONG GUYS ARE ALWAYS
[ BLINK! BLINK! ]
NICE TO EVERYPONY, RIGHT?
[ BLINK! ]
[ BLINK! BLINK! ]
10 BITS FOR THE CHERRY.
[ BLINK! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
10 BITS FOR THE CHERRY.
10 BITS FOR ONE CHERRY IS
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
OUTRAGEOUS!
10 BITS FOR ONE CHERRY IS
I INSIST ON PAYING YOU 11 BITS!
OUTRAGEOUS!
11 BITS?
I INSIST ON PAYING YOU 11 BITS!
UM, I MEAN, 9 BITS.
11 BITS?
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
UM, I MEAN, 9 BITS.
OKAY, 12 BITS.
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S MY FINAL OFFER.
OKAY, 12 BITS.
I THINK YOU'RE CONFUSED.
THAT'S MY FINAL OFFER.
IT'S 12 BITS.
I THINK YOU'RE CONFUSED.
TAKE IT OR LEAVE IT.
IT'S 12 BITS.
OKAY. I'LL TAKE IT.
TAKE IT OR LEAVE IT.
DON'T GIVE HIM YOUR MONEY!
OKAY. I'LL TAKE IT.
ONE CHERRY IS NOT WORTH 12 BITS!
DON'T GIVE HIM YOUR MONEY!
BUT I WAS ONLY DOING WHAT YOU
ONE CHERRY IS NOT WORTH 12 BITS!
DID.
BUT I WAS ONLY DOING WHAT YOU
IT WAS A VALIANT EFFORT, BUT
DID.
YOU SHOULD REFUSE TO GIVE HIM
IT WAS A VALIANT EFFORT, BUT
YOUR BUSINESS AND JUST WALK
YOU SHOULD REFUSE TO GIVE HIM
AWAY.
YOUR BUSINESS AND JUST WALK
BUT I CAN'T LET ANGEL STARVE.
AWAY.
HE WON'T EAT IT UNLESS I MAKE IT
BUT I CAN'T LET ANGEL STARVE.
JUST RIGHT.
HE WON'T EAT IT UNLESS I MAKE IT
I NEED THAT CHERRY NO MATTER
JUST RIGHT.
WHAT IT COSTS.
I NEED THAT CHERRY NO MATTER
IN THAT CASE, 20 BITS!
WHAT IT COSTS.
20?!
IN THAT CASE, 20 BITS!
OH, I -- I DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH.
20?!
THEN WHY ARE YOU WASTING MY
OH, I -- I DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH.
TIME?
THEN WHY ARE YOU WASTING MY
I'LL GIVE YOU TWO BITS FOR
TIME?
THAT CHERRY.
I'LL GIVE YOU TWO BITS FOR
SOLD!
THAT CHERRY.
AH, TOUGH BREAK, KID.
SOLD!
NEXT TIME, DON'T BE SUCH A
AH, TOUGH BREAK, KID.
DOORMAT.
NEXT TIME, DON'T BE SUCH A
[ GOAT BLEATS ]
DOORMAT.
TA-DA!
[ GOAT BLEATS ]
HERE YOU GO, ANGEL.
TA-DA!
SORRY THERE'S NO CHERRY ON TOP,
HERE YOU GO, ANGEL.
BUT THE REST OF IT IS EXACTLY
SORRY THERE'S NO CHERRY ON TOP,
WHAT YOU WANTED.
BUT THE REST OF IT IS EXACTLY
[ ZING! ]
WHAT YOU WANTED.
[ ZIP! ]
[ ZING! ]
ANGEL?
[ GROANS ]
LOOK AT ME.
I REALLY AM A DOORMAT.
"THE INCREDIBLE IRON WILL TURNS
DOORMATS INTO DYNAMOS.
ASSERTIVENESS SEMINAR TODAY.
HEDGE MAZE CENTER."
AS CELESTIA AS MY WITNESS, I'M
NEVER GONNA BE A PUSHOVER AGAIN!
OH.
[ STAMMERING ]
EXCUSE ME.
[ SQUEAKS ]
[ SMACK! WHISTLE! ]
[ THUD! ]
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ GOATS BLEAT ]
[ CLICK! SQUEAK! ]
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ GOAT BLEATS ]
[ CHEERS AND STOMPING ]
[ SMOOCH! SMOOCH! ]
WELCOME, FRIENDS.
MY NAME IS IRON WILL, AND TODAY
IS THE FIRST DAY OF YOUR NEW
LIFE.
I WANT TO HEAR YOU STOMP IF
YOU'RE TIRED OF BEING A
PUSHOVER.
[ CHEERS AND STOMPING ]
STOMP IF YOU'RE TIRED OF BEING A
DOORMAT!
[ CHEERS AND STOMPING ]
STOMP IF YOU WANT TO PAY NOTHING
FOR THIS SEMINAR.
[ CHEERS AND STOMPING ]
[ CHEERS AND STOMPING STOP ]
WHAT? NOTHING?
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SNORTS ]
[ LAUGHTER STOPS ]
THAT'S NO JOKE, FRIENDS.
IRON WILL IS SO CONFIDENT THAT
YOU WILL BE 100% SATISFIED WITH
IRON WILL'S ASSERTIVENESS
TECHNIQUES, THAT IF YOU ARE NOT
100% SATISFIED, YOU PAY NOTHING!
BUT I PITY THE FOOL WHO DOUBTS
IRON WILL'S METHODS.
YOU DON'T DOUBT ME, DO YOU?
NO. UNH-UNH. NO, SIR.
AND THAT, MY FRIENDS, IS YOUR
FIRST LESSON.
DON'T BE SHY.
LOOK 'EM IN THE EYE.
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
NOW, TO DEMONSTRATE THAT
IRON WILL'S TECHNIQUES WILL WORK
FOR ANYPONY, I'M GONNA NEED A
VOLUNTEER.
[ SLUMP! ]
[ GOAT BLEATS ]
YOU IN THE BACK ROW!
WHO? ME?
YES, YOU!
IRON WILL WANTS YOU ON STAGE.
[ GULPS ]
UH, WELL --
NOW!
Okay.
[ ZIP! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
WHOA!
HE'S BLOCKING YOUR PATH.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
UM, POLITELY WALK AROUND HIM?
NO.
GINGERLY TIPTOE AROUND HIM?
GO BACK HOME AND TRY AGAIN
NO.
TOMORROW?
GO BACK HOME AND TRY AGAIN
NO!
TOMORROW?
WHEN SOMEPONY TRIES TO BLOCK,
NO!
SHOW THEM THAT YOU ROCK!
WHEN SOMEPONY TRIES TO BLOCK,
[ WHACK! ]
SHOW THEM THAT YOU ROCK!
[ SMACK! ]
[ WHACK! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
[ SMACK! ]
[ THUD! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
OH. SORRY.
[ THUD! ]
DON'T BE SORRY! BE ASSERTIVE!
OH. SORRY.
NEVER APOLOGIZE WHEN YOU CAN
DON'T BE SORRY! BE ASSERTIVE!
CRITICIZE.
NEVER APOLOGIZE WHEN YOU CAN
[ COUGHS ]
CRITICIZE.
WHY DON'T YOU WATCH WHERE YOU'RE
[ COUGHS ]
GOING?!
WHY DON'T YOU WATCH WHERE YOU'RE
NOW YOU TRY.
GOING?!
UH, NEXT TIME, GET OUT OF THE
NOW YOU TRY.
WAY BEFORE I BUMP INTO YOU,
UH, NEXT TIME, GET OUT OF THE
'CAUSE I TOTALLY WON'T BE SORRY
WAY BEFORE I BUMP INTO YOU,
WHEN I DO!
'CAUSE I TOTALLY WON'T BE SORRY
[ CHA-CHING! ]
WHEN I DO!
YOU SEE, MY FRIENDS?
[ CHA-CHING! ]
IF MY TECHNIQUES CAN WORK FOR
YOU SEE, MY FRIENDS?
THIS SHY, LITTLE PONY, THEN THEY
IF MY TECHNIQUES CAN WORK FOR
CAN WORK FOR ANYPONY!
THIS SHY, LITTLE PONY, THEN THEY
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
CAN WORK FOR ANYPONY!
OKAY. I FEEL GOOD.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
I FEEL READY TO ATTACK THE DAY,
OKAY. I FEEL GOOD.
AS IRON WILL SAYS.
I FEEL READY TO ATTACK THE DAY,
[ ANIMALS CHATTERING ]
AS IRON WILL SAYS.
[ HUMMING ]
[ ANIMALS CHATTERING ]
EXCUSE ME, MR. GREENHOOVES.
[ HUMMING ]
BUT I THINK YOU MIGHT BE
EXCUSE ME, MR. GREENHOOVES.
OVER-WATERING MY PETUNIAS...
BUT I THINK YOU MIGHT BE
[ LAUGHS ]
OVER-WATERING MY PETUNIAS...
...AGAIN.
[ LAUGHS ]
LET THE PROFESSIONAL HANDLE
...AGAIN.
IT.
LET THE PROFESSIONAL HANDLE
[ HUMMING ]
IT.
TREAT ME LIKE A PUSHOVER AND
[ HUMMING ]
YOU'LL GET THE ONCE-OVER.
TREAT ME LIKE A PUSHOVER AND
[ CRE-E-E-AK ]
YOU'LL GET THE ONCE-OVER.
HMM?
[ CRE-E-E-AK ]
HMM.
HMM?
[ SPUTTERING, COUGHING ]
HMM.
WELL, PERHAPS THAT IS ENOUGH
[ SPUTTERING, COUGHING ]
WATER.
WELL, PERHAPS THAT IS ENOUGH
THANK YOU.
WATER.
[ LAUGHS ]
THANK YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT WORKED!
[ LAUGHS ]
SHOWPONY BUSINESS IS TOUGH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT WORKED!
GO AHEAD.
SHOWPONY BUSINESS IS TOUGH.
TRY ONE OF YOUR JOKES OUT ON ME.
GO AHEAD.
I LAUGH AT EVERYTHING.
TRY ONE OF YOUR JOKES OUT ON ME.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
I LAUGH AT EVERYTHING.
A DONKEY AND A MULE ARE STUCK ON
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
DESERT ISLAND.
A DONKEY AND A MULE ARE STUCK ON
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
DESERT ISLAND.
EXCUSE ME.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
WOULD YOU MIND MOVING YOUR CARTS
EXCUSE ME.
SO I CAN PASS?
WOULD YOU MIND MOVING YOUR CARTS
YEAH, YEAH. IN A MINUTE.
SO I CAN PASS?
I JUST WANT TO FINISH UP THIS
YEAH, YEAH. IN A MINUTE.
STORY.
I JUST WANT TO FINISH UP THIS
AND SO THE DONKEY SAYS TO THE
STORY.
MULE --
AND SO THE DONKEY SAYS TO THE
AHEM! CAN YOU MOVE?
MULE --
YOU'RE BLOCKING MY PATH.
AHEM! CAN YOU MOVE?
YEAH, YEAH. IN A MINUTE.
YOU'RE BLOCKING MY PATH.
SO THE DONKEY SAYS TO THE
YEAH, YEAH. IN A MINUTE.
MULE --
SO THE DONKEY SAYS TO THE
WHEN SOMEPONY TRIES TO BLOCK,
MULE --
SHOW THEM THAT YOU ROCK.
WHEN SOMEPONY TRIES TO BLOCK,
AND THE MULE SAYS --
SHOW THEM THAT YOU ROCK.
[ SPLAT! ]
AND THE MULE SAYS --
UGH!
[ SPLAT! ]
EASY DOES IT, LADY.
UGH!
WE'RE MOVING, OKAY?
EASY DOES IT, LADY.
GOOD.
WE'RE MOVING, OKAY?
WHO'S NEXT, PLEASE?
GOOD.
AND WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU
WHO'S NEXT, PLEASE?
TODAY?
AND WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
TODAY?
DOING?
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DIDN'T YOU SEE ME?
DOING?
UH, I GUESS. MAYBE.
DIDN'T YOU SEE ME?
MAYBE?
UH, I GUESS. MAYBE.
MAYBEs ARE FOR BABIES!
MAYBE?
[ WHIRL! ]
MAYBEs ARE FOR BABIES!
[ Growling ] NOW GO TO THE BACK
[ WHIRL! ]
OF THE LINE WHERE YOU BELONG!
[ Growling ] NOW GO TO THE BACK
[ ZIP! ]
OF THE LINE WHERE YOU BELONG!
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ZIP! ]
HEY!
[ ALL GASP ]
LOOK AT YOU!
HEY!
[ LAUGHS ]
LOOK AT YOU!
YOUR ATTITUDE IS SO FEISTY.
[ LAUGHS ]
IT'S FABULOUS!
YOUR ATTITUDE IS SO FEISTY.
LOOKS LIKE THAT MONSTER'S
IT'S FABULOUS!
WORKSHOP REALLY PAID OFF.
LOOKS LIKE THAT MONSTER'S
IRON WILL'S NOT A MONSTER.
WORKSHOP REALLY PAID OFF.
HE'S A MINOTAUR AND A TRUE
IRON WILL'S NOT A MONSTER.
INSPIRATION.
HE'S A MINOTAUR AND A TRUE
HIS TECHNIQUES REALLY WORK.
INSPIRATION.
WELL, THEY'VE CERTAINLY MADE
HIS TECHNIQUES REALLY WORK.
A DIFFERENCE IN THE WAY YOU
WELL, THEY'VE CERTAINLY MADE
CARRY YOURSELF.
A DIFFERENCE IN THE WAY YOU
YOU TRULY ARE A WHOLE NEW
CARRY YOURSELF.
FLUTTERSHY.
YOU TRULY ARE A WHOLE NEW
YES, I AM.
FLUTTERSHY.
AND NEW FLUTTERSHY FEELS PRETTY
YES, I AM.
STOKED ABOUT NEW FLUTTERSHY.
AND NEW FLUTTERSHY FEELS PRETTY
WELL, OLD PINKIE PIE FEELS
STOKED ABOUT NEW FLUTTERSHY.
REALLY PROUD OF NEW FLUTTERSHY.
WELL, OLD PINKIE PIE FEELS
PROUD AS PINK PUNCH.
REALLY PROUD OF NEW FLUTTERSHY.
WANT SOME?
PROUD AS PINK PUNCH.
[ SNORTS, LAUGHS ]
WANT SOME?
YOU LAUGH AT ME, I WRATH AT
[ SNORTS, LAUGHS ]
YOU!
YOU LAUGH AT ME, I WRATH AT
[ SPLASH! ]
YOU!
BYE, GIRLS.
[ SPLASH! ]
WHAT A DAY.
BYE, GIRLS.
TAXI!
WHAT A DAY.
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
TAXI!
CUT IN LINE, I'LL TAKE WHAT'S
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
MINE!
CUT IN LINE, I'LL TAKE WHAT'S
HEY!
MINE!
HEY!!
HEY!
[ THUD! ]
HEY!!
NOPONY PUSHES NEW FLUTTERSHY
[ THUD! ]
AROUND!
NOPONY PUSHES NEW FLUTTERSHY
NOPONY!
AROUND!
OLD PINKIE PIE'S NOT SO SURE
NOPONY!
NEW FLUTTERSHY IS SUCH A GOOD
OLD PINKIE PIE'S NOT SO SURE
IDEA AFTER ALL.
NEW FLUTTERSHY IS SUCH A GOOD
OLD RARITY AGREES.
YOU GOT THIS, NEW FLUTTERSHY.
THIS DAY IS YOURS, AND NOPONY IS
GONNA TAKE IT AWAY FROM YOU.
AM I RIGHT?!
RIGHT!
WHAT?!
HE'S DELIVERED THE WRONG MAIL
AGAIN!
OH!
THE NEW FLUTTERSHY DOES NOT
WANT THE WRONG MAIL DELIVERED TO
HER COTTAGE.
OH, DID I MIX THEM UP AGAIN?
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU APOLOGIZE, I PENALIZE!
OHH!
OH!
[ CHOMP! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ ZING! ]
EXCUSE ME.
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO GET TO THE
PONYVILLE TOWER?
SURE. YOU JUST --
[ GASPS ]
OH, THAT'S A SHAME.
[ GROWLS ]
YOU MAKE ME LOSE, I BLOW MY
FUSE!
HEY!
[ CLONG! ]
FLUTTERSHY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
THAT'S NO WAY TO BEHAVE.
DIDN'T YOU SEE WHAT HE DID TO
NEW FLUTTERSHY?
AND HE THOUGHT NEW FLUTTERSHY
WAS A PUSHOVER.
NO, SWEETIE. HE DIDN'T.
WE SAW THE WHOLE THING.
WE THINK THAT YOU'VE TAKEN YOUR
ASSERTIVENESS TRAINING A LITTLE
TOO FAR.
WHAT?!
YOU JUST WANT NEW FLUTTERSHY TO
BE A DOORMAT LIKE
OLD FLUTTERSHY.
BUT OLD FLUTTERSHY IS GONE!
NEW FLUTTERSHY?
OLD FLUTTERSHY?
WHAT HAPPENED TO
NICE FLUTTERSHY?
WE WANT THAT FLUTTERSHY BACK.
NO.
YOU WANT WIMP FLUTTERSHY.
YOU WANT PUSHOVER FLUTTERSHY.
YOU WANT "DO ANYTHING TO HER AND
SHE WON'T COMPLAIN" FLUTTERSHY!
AAH!
TOO MANY FLUTTERSHYS TO KEEP
TRACK OF!
MAKE IT STOP!
THINGS GETTING TOO
COMPLICATED FOR YOUR SIMPLE,
LITTLE BRAIN, PINKIE PIE?
NOW STOP RIGHT THERE!
LET'S NOT LET THINGS DESCEND
INTO PETTY INSULTS.
WHY NOT?
I THOUGHT PETTY WAS WHAT YOU'RE
ALL ABOUT, RARITY, WITH YOUR
PETTY CONCERNS ABOUT FASHION.
[ GASPS ]
HEY! LEAVE HER ALONE!
FASHION IS HER PASSION!
OH, AND WHAT ARE YOU
PASSIONATE ABOUT?
BIRTHDAY CAKE? PARTY HATS?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT THE TWO
MOST FRIVOLOUS PONIES IN
PONYVILLE ARE TRYING TO TELL
NEW FLUTTERSHY HOW TO LIVE HER
LIFE WHEN THEY ARE THROWING
THEIR OWN LIVES AWAY ON
POINTLESS PURSUITS THAT NOPONY
ELSE GIVES A FLYING FEATHER
ABOUT!
[ GASPS ]
LOOKS LIKE NASTY FLUTTERSHY IS
HERE TO STAY.
I CANNOT BELIEVE WHAT THAT
MONSTER, IRON WILL, HAS DONE TO
YOU.
[ BOTH SOBBING ]
IRON WILL IS NOT A MONSTER!
HE'S A MINOTAUR!
[ GROWLS ]
[ SQUEAKS ]
I'M THE MONSTER.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ HOWLING ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
FLUTTERSHY, ARE YOU IN THERE?
IT'S PINKIE PIE AND RARITY.
GO AWAY.
GO AWAY BEFORE NASTY FLUTTERSHY
STRIKES AGAIN.
OH, SWEETIE.
WE ALL SAID THINGS THAT WE
REGRET.
WE DID?
SHH!
PINKIE'S RIGHT.
I'M THE ONLY ONE TO BLAME, BUT
DON'T WORRY.
I'M NEVER COMING OUT OF MY HOUSE
AGAIN.
EVERYPONY WILL BE A LOT SAFER
WITH ME AND MY MEAN MOUTH LOCKED
AWAY.
SWEETIE, PINKIE PIE DOESN'T
BLAME YOU, NOR DO I.
YOU JUST RECEIVED SOME BAD
ADVICE FROM THAT IRON WILL
CHARACTER.
YEAH.
HE'S THE ONE THAT MADE YOU ACT
SUPER-DUPER NASTY.
WHAT I MEAN IS THERE ARE OTHER
WAYS TO ASSERT YOURSELF BESIDES
YELLING AT EVERYPONY.
YES.
YOU CAN STAND UP FOR YOURSELF
WITHOUT BEING UNPLEASANT ABOUT
IT.
I'M NOT SURE I CAN.
I'M TOO FAR GONE.
WHENEVER I TRY TO ASSERT MYSELF,
I BECOME A MONSTER.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
OH, SWEETIE.
YOU'RE NOT A MONSTER.
NO, BUT HE IS.
IRON WILL'S MY NAME.
TRAINING PONIES IS MY GAME.
[ POINK! SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
WHAT A DARLING LITTLE
CATCHPHRASE.
YOUR FRIEND FLUTTERSHY LOVED
IRON WILL'S CATCHPHRASES.
WORD ON THE STREET IS THAT SHE
DOESN'T TAKE NO GUFF FROM
NOPONY, SO IRON WILL IS HERE TO
COLLECT IRON WILL'S FEE.
FLUTTERSHY IS IN NO SHAPE TO
DEAL WITH THAT CREEP.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I'M SURE A BIG, BRAVE, POWERFUL,
AND RICH MONSTER -- I MEAN,
MINOTAUR -- LIKE YOU DOESN'T
NEED THAT MONEY RIGHT AWAY.
YOU CAN AFFORD TO COME BACK
LATER.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
FLUTTERSHY IS OVERDUE AS IT IS.
IRON WILL COLLECTS NOW.
[ THUD! ]
[ GASPS ]
DO SOMETHING!
WE'RE NOT EVEN SURE
FLUTTERSHY IS HOME RIGHT NOW.
SHE MIGHT BE OFF FROLICKING WITH
SOME WOODLAND CREATURES.
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE US SOME TIME
TO TRACK HER DOWN FOR YOU?
IRON WILL DOES HAVE SOME
GROCERY SHOPPING TO DO.
IRON WILL WILL COME BACK THIS
AFTERNOON.
BUT THAT'S ONLY HALF A DAY.
WE NEED ONE FULL DAY AT LEAST.
IRON WILL WILL DELAY FOR HALF
A DAY AND NO LONGER.
A FULL DAY!
HALF DAY!
FULL DAY!
WE NEED HALF A DAY AND NO
MORE!
WELL, YOU'LL GET A FULL DAY
AND NO LESS!
OKIE DOKIE. SEE YOU TOMORROW.
WAIT. WHAT?
[ SNEEZES ]
HUH.
SOUNDS LIKE THE SEARCH WON'T BE
NECESSARY.
IRON WILL COLLECTS NOW.
BUT W-WE HAD AN AGREEMENT.
YOU GOT TO COME BACK TOMORROW.
WHEN SOMEPONY TRIES TO BLOCK,
SHOW THEM THAT YOU ROCK!
AAH!
[ SPITS ]
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
YOUR PAYMENT IS OVERDUE,
FLUTTERSHY.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ SNORTS ]
YOU WERE NOTHING BUT A DOORMAT,
AND IRON WILL TURNED YOU INTO A
LEAN, MEAN, ASSERTIVE MACHINE.
[ WHIP! WHIP! ]
NOW PAY IRON WILL WHAT YOU OWE
IRON WILL.
UM, NO.
[ THUD! ]
[ GOAT BLEATS ]
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
NO.
OOH!
I'D HATE TO BE YOU RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE IRON WILL IS GONNA RAIN
DOWN A WORLD OF HURT UNLESS
IRON WILL GETS MONEY -- PRONTO!
[ SNORTS ]
AS I RECALL, DURING YOUR
WORKSHOP, YOU PROMISED "100%
SATISFACTION GUARANTEED OR YOU
PAY NOTHING."
WELL, I'M NOT SATISFIED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU'RE NOT
SATISFIED?
EVERYPONY HAS ALWAYS BEEN
SATISFIED!
WELL, I GUESS I'M THE FIRST,
THEN.
BUT SINCE I'M NOT SATISFIED, I
REFUSE TO PAY.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
[ WHAP! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ GOATS BLEATING ]
OH.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT JUST A
LITTLE BIT SATISFIED?
UH, BECAUSE MAYBE WE COULD CUT A
DEAL.
I-I MEAN, WE'RE BOTH REASONABLE
CREATURES, AREN'T WE?
I'M SORRY, BUT "NO" MEANS
"NO."
"NO" MEANS "NO," HUH?
NOPONY HAS EVER SAID THAT TO ME
BEFORE.
HUH.
I GOT TO REMEMBER THAT ONE.
THAT'S A GOOD CATCHPHRASE FOR MY
NEXT WORKSHOP.
[ GOAT BLEATS ]
YOU WERE AMAZING, FLUTTERSHY!
YOU TOTALLY STOOD UP TO THAT
MONSTER.
IN FACT, YOU DIDN'T CHANGE AT
ALL.
YOU WERE THE SAME OLD FLUTTERSHY
THAT WE'VE ALWAYS LOVED.
BUT ONE WE'VE MISSED!
DON'T WORRY.
OLD FLUTTERSHY IS BACK FOR GOOD.
I'M SORRY I TOOK THE WHOLE
ASSERTIVENESS THING TOO FAR.
FRIENDS?
Both: FRIENDS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
SOMETIMES IT CAN BE HARD FOR A
SHY PONY LIKE ME TO STAND UP FOR
MYSELF, AND WHEN I FIRST TRIED
IT, I DIDN'T LIKE THE PONY I
BECAME.
BUT I'VE LEARNED THAT STANDING
UP FOR YOURSELF ISN'T THE SAME
AS CHANGING WHO YOU ARE.
NOW I KNOW HOW TO PUT MY HOOF
DOWN WITHOUT BEING UNPLEASANT OR
MEAN.
[ GULP! ]
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪