[ LAUGHS ]
WHOO-HOO!
YEAH!
[ LAUGHS ]
WHOO!
WHO-O-A!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
WHOO! [ LAUGHS ]
[ OWL HOOTS ]
WHO?
OH,
IT'S YOU OWLOWISCIOUS.
COME ON,
TRY AND KEEP UP!
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ IMITATES ENGINE REVVING ]
[ REVVING CONTINUES ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ DOG BARKING ]
[ GASPS ]
WINONA?
I MEAN, WINONA'S HEAD?!
UM, IS THIS WEIRD,
OR IS IT JUST ME?
[ PLOP! ]
ANGEL?!
GUMMY?!
OKAY, THIS IS OFFICIALLY
BEYOND WEIRD NOW
AND MOVED RIGHT ON DOWN
TO FREAKY TOWN.
[ ZIP! ]
[ HISSES ]
[ GASPS ]
AAAAAAH!
WAAH!
[ OPAL SCREECHES ]
[ WINONA BARKING ]
[ OWLOWISCIOUS HOOTS ]
WHEW!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ WINONA BARKING ]
Applejack:
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, SWEETIE.
LET'S GET
THIS THING STARTED.
[ GIGGLING ]
SINCEREST APOLOGIES,
RAINBOW,
IF OUR PETS
WERE BOTHERING YOU.
SAY YOU'RE SORRY, OPAL.
[ OPAL HISSES ]
SHE'S SORRY.
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING
OUT HERE?
WHY, WE ALWAYS ROUND UP
OUR CRITTERS
FOR A REGULAR OLD PONY PET
PLAY DATE IN THIS PARK.
UH, YOU DO?
SAME TIME EVERY WEEK.
I THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW?
SHE DIDN'T KNOW.
WELL, WE HAD
INITIALLY PLANNED ON
INVITING RAINBOW,
OF COURSE,
EXCEPT --
WE WERE TOTALLY GONNA
INVITE YOU, RAINBOW,
THEN TWILIGHT REMEMBERED
THAT YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A PET.
AND RARITY REMEMBERED
THAT YOU REALLY LIKE
TAKING NAPS IN THE AFTERNOON.
SO APPLEJACK FIGURED
YOU WOULDN'T BE MISSING OUT
ON ANYTHING ANYWAY.
AND FLUTTERSHY AND I
NODDED OUR HEADS IN AGREEMENT
LIKE THIS.
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
OH, PLEASE DON'T BE MAD
AT US.
OH, I'M NOT MAD.
YOU ALL ARE RIGHT.
NOT MUCH POINT OF A PONY PET
PLAY DATE FOR ME
IF I'M A PONY
WITHOUT A PET, RIGHT?
EXACTLY.
SO,
IF'N YOU'LL EXCUSE US.
ALL RIGHT,
COME ON, WINONA.
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
[ WINONA BARKING ]
[ OWLOWISCIOUS HOOTING ]
[ TALKING, BARKING,
HOOTING CONTINUES ]
HEY, NOW WAIT A MINUTE.
JUST BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
A PET NOW
DOESN'T MEAN
I NEVER WANT A PET.
[ GASPS ]
OH, REALLY?!
YOU REALLY WANT
A PET?! REALLY?!
'CAUSE I'VE GOT SO MANY
WONDERFUL CHOICES AT MY HOUSE.
OH, AND I KNOW
YOU'LL JUST LOVE THEM,
AND THEY'LL LOVE YOU!
OH! AND YOU'LL BE BEST FRIENDS
FOREVER AND EVER!
[ SIGHS ]
[ GOAT BLEATS, DUCK QUACKING ]
♪ NOW, RAINBOW, MY DEAR
I CANNOT EXPRESS MY DELIGHT ♪
♪ IT'S ABUNDANTLY CLEAR
THAT SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE ♪
♪ IS A PET THAT WILL SUIT YOU
JUST RIGHT ♪
♪ I CAN'T WAIT
TO GET STARTED ♪
♪ BUT FIRST,
LET ME SET A FEW RULES ♪
♪ IT'S OF UTMOST IMPORTANCE
THE PET THAT I GET ♪
♪ IS SOMETHING THAT'S AWESOME
AND COOL ♪
AWESOME, COOL --
GOT IT.
♪ I HAVE SO MANY
WONDERFUL CHOICES ♪
♪ JUST WAIT, YOU WILL SEE ♪
♪ I NEED SOMETHING REAL FAST
LIKE A BULLET ♪
♪ TO KEEP UP WITH ME ♪
[ WHOOSH! ]
♪ SURE
HOW ABOUT A BUNNY? ♪
♪ THEY'RE CUTSIE AND WOOTSIE
AND QUICK AS CAN BE ♪
CUTSIE, WOOTSIE?
HAVE YOU EVEN MET ME?
♪ RAINBOW, HAVE FAITH ♪
♪ YOU SEE,
I WILL BET YOU ♪
♪ SOMEWHERE IN HERE IS A PET
THAT WILL GET YOU ♪
COME ON,
THE SKY'S THE LIMIT.
SKY IS GOOD.
I'D LIKE IT TO FLY.
REALLY? BECAUSE I THINK
THIS WITTLE PUTTY TAT
HAS YOUR NAME
WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.
YES, HE DOES.
[ MEWS ]
AWW, AND LOOK,
HE LIKES YOU!
[ POINK! ]
PASS.
♪ I HAVE SO MANY WONDERFUL
CHOICES FOR YOU TO DECIDE ♪
♪ THERE ARE OTTERS AND SEALS
WITH MASSIVE APPEAL ♪
OTTERS AND SEALS
DO NOT FLY.
MAYBE NOT, BUT I'VE SEEN
THIS PARTICULAR SEAL
CATCH 10 FEET OF AIR
WHEN HE BREACHES THE WATER.
[ SEAL BARKS ]
THAT'S IT.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
♪ WAIT,
THERE MUST BE A PET HERE ♪
♪ THAT WILL FIT THE TICKET ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT A LADYBUG
OR A CUTE CRICKET? ♪
BIGGER AND COOLER.
BIGGER, COOLER, RIGHT.
♪ I'VE GOT JUST THE THING
IN THAT TREE, DASH ♪
♪ MEET YOUR NEW FABULOUS PET
SQUIRRELLY-Y-Y-Y ♪
IT'S JUST A SQUIRREL.
NOT JUST ANY SQUIRREL --
A FLYING SQUIRREL.
YEAH, SO,
LIKE I WAS SAYING...
♪ FLUTTERSHY, PAL ♪
♪ THIS WON'T CUT IT ♪
♪ I NEED A PET TO
KEEP UP WITH ME ♪
♪ SOMETHING AWESOME ♪
♪ SOMETHING FLYING ♪
♪ WITH COOLNESS
THAT DEFIES GRAVITY ♪
I'M SENSING YOU WANT
AN ANIMAL THAT CAN FLY.
YOU THINK?
♪ I HAVE PLENTY OF WONDERFUL
CREATURES WHO SOAR IN THE SKY ♪
♪ LIKE A SWEET HUMMINGBIRD
OR A GIANT MONARCH BUTTERFLY ♪
BETTER, BUT COOLER.
I SEE.
♪ HOW ABOUT AN OWL?
OR A WASP? ♪
♪ OR A TOUCAN? ♪
♪ THERE ARE SO MANY WONDERFUL
CREATURES THE LIKES OF THAT ♪
♪ THERE ARE FALCONS
AND EAGLES ♪
♪ THEY ARE BOTH QUITE REGAL ♪
♪ PERHAPS WHAT YOU NEED IS A
DARK AND MYSTERIOUS BAT ♪
NOW YOU'RE TALKING!
BUT INSTEAD OF JUST
ONE STANDOUT,
NOW THAT'S TOO MANY.
♪ SO MANY CHOICES ♪
♪ AND SUCH RICHES APLENTY ♪
NOT A BAD PROBLEM TO HAVE
IF YOU ASK ME.
♪ THE BAT WOULD BE AWESOME ♪
♪ BUT THE WASP,
I'M DIGGING, TOO ♪
♪ DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING
IN A YELLOW-STRIPED BAT? ♪
NO.
♪ I'VE GOT
A HOT PINK FLAMINGO ♪
♪ JUST DYING TO MEET YOU ♪
♪ WHAT TO DO?
WHAT TO DO? ♪
[ GASPS ]
OF COURSE!
THAT'S IT!
♪ THERE'S REALLY
JUST ONE WAY ♪
♪ TO FIND OUT
WHICH ANIMAL'S BEST ♪
♪ HOLD A CONTEST ♪
♪ OF SPEED ♪
♪ AGILITY AND GUTS ♪
♪ THAT WILL PUT EACH PET TO
THE TE-E-E-E-E-ST ♪
♪ DON'T FORGET STYLE
THAT SHOULD BE CONSIDERED ♪
♪ THEN WE'LL KNOW FOR SURE
WHO'S BEST OF THE LITTER ♪
♪ THE ONE WHO IS AWESOME
IS COOL ♪
♪ JUST LIKE ME! ♪
♪ CAN'T SETTLE FOR LESS
'CAUSE I'M THE BEST ♪
♪ SO A CONTEST, WE WILL SEE ♪
♪ WHO'S THE NUMBER-ONE GREATEST
PERFECTEST PET ♪
♪ IN THE WORLD
FOR ME-E-E-E-E? ♪
♪ MAY THE GAMES
BEGI-I-I-I-I-I-I-N ♪
AND MAY
THE BEST PET WIN!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
Rainbow Dash: SHH!
SO, YOU ALL THINK
YOU'VE GOT WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE MY PET, DO YOU?
WELL,
WE'LL JUST SEE ABOUT THAT.
[ GULPS ]
IF ANY OF YOU
DON'T THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT,
BOW OUT NOW BEFORE YOU HUMILIATE
YOURSELF IN FRONT OF YOUR PEERS.
THIS COMPETITION
ISN'T FOR THE WEAK.
YOU'D BETTER BE PREPARED TO
STEP UP YOUR GAME!
YOU CALL THAT FLAPPING?!
THAT'S BETTER!
THERE'S ONLY ROOM ON TEAM DASH
FOR ONE OF YOU,
AND MY FUTURE PET NEEDS TO BE
ABLE TO TAKE IT TO THE EXTREME.
[ WHOOSH! ]
ANY QUESTIONS?
I GOT ONE.
DOES SHE UNDERSTAND
WHAT A PET REALLY NEEDS?
YEAH, LIKE CARE AND ATTENTION,
LOVE AND AFFECTION.
[ SLURPS ]
UGH!
AND BREATH MINTS!
NOW, YOU JUST PAY ATTENTION
AND TRY YOUR BEST AND --
SERIOUSLY, FLUTTERSHY,
THE TURTLE?!
WHAT DID YOU BRING
THAT THING HERE FOR?
TECHNICALLY,
HE'S A TORTOISE,
AND HE'S ALWAYS DREAMED OF
BEING SOMEPONY'S PET.
HE JUST WANTS
A CHANCE TO COMPETE.
HE WON'T GET IN THE WAY.
YOU WON'T EVEN KNOW HE'S HERE.
NO!
OH, JUST LET HIM TRY.
[ SIGHS ]
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
HE CAN POSSIBLY KEEP UP!
LOOK AT HIM.
IT WON'T HURT TO
LET HIM TRY.
BUT --
JUST LET HIM TRY.
[ CREAK! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SIGHS ]
FINE!
BUT DON'T SAY
I DIDN'T WARN YOU!
THIS ISN'T A GAME,
YOU KNOW!
ALL RIGHT, NOW, THESE GAMES
WILL DETERMINE WHICH ONE OF YOU
HAS THE MOST IMPORTANT QUALITIES
I'M LOOKING FOR IN A PET.
[ WHOOSH! ]
SPEED!
AGILITY!
[ SCREECH! ]
GUTS!
[ WHOOSH! ]
STYLE!
COOLNESS!
AWESOMENESS!
AND RADICALNESS!
AREN'T THOSE
ALL THE SAME THING?
YOU WOULD THINK THAT,
TWILIGHT,
AND THAT'S WHY YOU WOULD
NEVER QUALIFY TO BE MY PET.
[ WHOOSH! ]
Rainbow Dash: SPEED!
ON YOUR MARKS...
[ DUCK QUACKS ]
...GET SET...
[ CREAK! ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
SORT OF SPEEDY.
NOT SPEEDY.
PRETTY SPEEDY.
COULD BE MORE SPEEDY.
[ FALCON SHRIEKS ]
[ SIZZLING ]
[ SCREECH! ]
YEAH, THAT'S SPEED!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
[ SCREECH! ]
THAT'S JUST SAD.
AGILITY!
[ SWOOSH! ]
SORT OF AGILE.
[ BOINK! ]
[ THUD ]
NOT AGILE.
[ SLOOP! POP! ]
PRETTY AGILE.
[ SWOOSH! ]
COULD BE MORE AGILE.
[ SLOOP! ]
WANT TO KNOW
THE OPPOSITE OF AGILITY?
THAT.
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ SMACK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
WHOO-HOO!
YEAH, BABY!
NOW THAT'S
WHAT I CALL AGILITY!
[ HUMMING ]
DON'T LEAVE ME HANGING!
[ ZIP! ]
[ SMACK! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ TINK! ]
I'M GONNA HAVE TO SHAVE A POINT
OFF YOUR SCORE FOR THAT.
[ HUMMING SADLY ]
OKAY, WHICH OF YOU
HAS THE GUTS
TO TRY AND GET OPAL'S
FAVORITE TOY AWAY FROM HER?
[ MOUSE SQUEAKS ]
[ DRUMROLL ]
[ OPAL GROWLS ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ OPAL HISSES ]
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ WARBLE! ]
[ MOUSE SQUEAKS ]
HA!
NOW THAT TAKES GUTS!
[ WARBLE! ]
[ OPAL SCREECHES ]
[ CLAWS PATTERING ]
STYLE!
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
ANY PET OF MINE'S
GOT TO LOOK GOOD
'CAUSE YOU'VE GOT TO
MAKE ME LOOK GOOD.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
COOLNESS!
[ HOOTS ]
SORT OF COOL.
[ QUACKS ]
NOT COOL.
[ SQUEAKS ]
PRETTY COOL.
[ SNORTS ]
COULD BE COOLER.
[ BUZZING ]
NOT WHAT I HAD IN MIND.
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
[ GAGGING ]
EWW!
[ SHRIEKS ]
NOW THAT'S A COOL SOUND!
[ WARBLING ]
SORT OF AWESOME.
[ WHIRRING ]
NOT AWESOME.
[ SCREECHES ]
COULD BE MORE AWESOME.
OH-HO-HO, YEAH!
THAT IS AWESOME!
[ POINK! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
UH,
YOU DID THAT ALREADY.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
ALL YOU CAN DO, HUH?
[ POP! ]
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BUZZING ]
[ GLASSES CHIMING
"MY LITTLE PONY" THEME ]
[ SHRIEKS ]
WHOA!
THAT WAS TRULY AWESOME!
BUT I'M AFRAID THIS IS
THE RADICALNESS COMPETITION,
SO I'M GONNA HAVE TO TAKE
SOME POINTS OFF.
[ BOING! ]
[ TORTOISE GURGLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
LISTEN, TURTLE.
TORTOISE.
WHATEVER!
YOU'VE HAD YOUR FUN,
BUT I THINK YOU AND I
BOTH KNOW WHO MADE THE CUT
AND WHO DIDN'T.
[ GURGLES ]
YOU DIDN'T.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
I MEAN, "A" FOR EFFORT
AND EVERYTHING.
YOU GAVE IT
YOUR BEST SHOT.
MAYBE I'VE GOT
A GOLD-STAR STICKER
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE
YOU CAN HAVE,
BUT, SERIOUSLY, GO HOME.
YOU'RE STARTING TO
CREEP ME OUT.
SO, ANYWAY...
YOU'RE ALL OUTSTANDING
COMPETITORS.
BUT THERE CAN ONLY BE ONE OF YOU
WHO'S NUMBER ONE.
SO THE FINAL TIE-BREAKING
CONTEST IS GOING TO BE...
PAUSE FOR DRAMATIC EFFECT.
A RACE AGAINST...
[ WHOOSH! ]
...ME!
THROUGH GHASTLY GORGE!
DUN-DUN-DU-U-U-N!
[ FALCON SHRIEKS ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
GESUNDHEIT.
[ GRUNTS ]
ACTUALLY,
GHASTLY GORGE ISN'T SCARY.
IT'S FUN.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
I'VE FLOWN THROUGH IT
A MILLION TIMES MYSELF,
SO, UH, OBVIOUSLY, I'LL BE
AT THE FRONT OF THE PACK.
BUT WHICHEVER OF YOU MAKE IT
ACROSS THE FINISH LINE WITH ME
WILL HAVE PROVEN
YOU CAN KEEP UP WITH ME
AND WILL HAVE EARNED THE HONOR
AND GLORY
OF GETTING TO BE MY PET.
READY...
SET, GO!
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ WAGNER'S "RIDE OF THE
VALKYRIES" PLAYING ]
WHOO-HOO!
[ LAUGHS ]
TRY TO KEEP UP!
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ SCREECH! ]
CAN'T CATCH ME!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ WHISTLING CONTINUES ]
[ SQUEAKS ]
[ WHISTLING
"RIDE OF THE VALKYRIES" ]
[ SCREECH! ]
COME ON, SLOWPOKES!
YOU WANT TO WIN, DON'T YOU?
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ THUD ]
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ WARBLING ]
[ SCREECHING ]
OH,
I FORGOT TO TELL YOU --
WATCH OUT
FOR THE QUARRY EELS!
THEY DON'T LIKE IT WHEN YOU GET
TOO CLOSE TO THEIR NESTS!
LIKE THIS!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ FALCON SCREECHES ]
[ EELS GROWL ]
[ POP! ]
[ PLOP! ]
[ SNAP! ]
[ CREAK! ]
EASY-PEASY,
ONE-TWO-THREESY.
RIGHT, GUYS?!
[ CRACK! ]
[ CRACKING ]
AVALANCHE!
HEY!
WHOA!
[ CREAKING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
COME ON!
NO, WAIT, COME BACK!
DON'T LEAVE ME!
I'M THE ONE
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO WIN!
I DON'T WANT TO END UP
STUCK HERE...
...FOREVER!
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
T-T-THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
FOREVER IS WAY TOO LONG TO BE
TRAPPED IN GHASTLY GORGE!
I MEAN, IT'S, LIKE...
FOREVER!
SOMEPONY, ANYPONY, HELP ME!
HELP ME!
[ RATTLING ]
WAHOO!
MY PRAYERS HAVE BEEN ANSWERED!
OH, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, THANK -- YOU?!
OH, NO!
NOW I'M NOT ONLY GONNA BE
STUCK HERE FOREVER,
I'M GONNA BE STUCK HERE FOREVER
WITH THE MOST ANNOYING TURTLE
IN THE WORLD!
[ SCOFFS ]
I'M DOOMED --
DOOMED, I TELL YOU!
[ RUMBLING ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
WHOA! WAY TO GO, FALCON, YEAH!
ALL RIGHT!
WHOO-HOO!
GOOD!
YEAH.
[ ALL MURMURING ]
YEAH, WAY TO GO.
HMM.
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT HERE.
[ TINKLING ]
[ SMACK! ]
WHERE'S RAINBOW DASH?
GREAT GALLOPIN'
GALOSHES!
THERE'S BEEN AN AVALANCHE
IN THERE!
RAINBOW!
[ ALL GASP ]
OH, DEAR!
WAIT, LOOK!
IT'S THE TURTLE!
TORTOISE! TORTOISE!
WHATEVER.
AND HE'S CARRYING SOMETHING
ON HIS BACK.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S RAINBOW DASH!
IT'S HER!
IT'S RAINBOW!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
[ ALL MURMURING ]
MAYBE WE'D BETTER GO
MEET THEM HALFWAY.
[ TINKLING ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
HA! WAY TO GO,
LITTLE GUY!
OH, THANK GOODNESS
YOU'RE NOT HURT, RAINBOW.
JUST MY PRIDE.
I CERTAINLY HOPE ALL OF THIS
DREADFUL DUST WAS WORTH IT!
AH-CHOO!
IT SURE WAS IF'N IT MEANS
RAINBOW GETS TO HAVE
HER OWN LITTLE CRITTER JUST LIKE
THE REST OF US FROM NOW ON.
[ TORTOISE GURGLES ]
UH, THANKS.
WHAT YOU DID...
I OWE YOU ONE.
RAINBOW, YOUR NEW PET IS
OVER HERE WAITING FOR YOU.
[ ALL MURMURING ]
OOH!
WHOA!
[ FALCON SHRIEKS ]
[ GURGLES ]
OH, RIGHT. YEAH.
THAT.
W-WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU GOT
YOUR PERFECT PET, RIGHT?
THE BEST OF THE BEST
LIKE YOU WANTED, REMEMBER?
IT CAN FLY,
AND IT'S NOT A SQUIRREL.
SHOULD WE SING
ABOUT IT AGAIN?
A FALCON SURE
LOOKS GOOD ON YOU, RAINBOW.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
[ TORTOISE SHRIEKS ]
EASY, FELLA.
NOTHIN' TO BE AFRAID OF.
[ SLOOP! ]
A FALCON
SURE DOES LOOK COOL.
HE'S ABSOLUTELY EVERYTHING
I WANTED IN A PET.
[ SIGHS ]
YAY?
BUT I SAID WHOEVER CROSSES
THE FINISH LINE WITH ME
GETS TO BE MY PET.
YOU DID!
YOU DID SAY THAT!
SHE DID SAY THAT!
THAT WAS THE RULE!
AND THE ONLY RACER WHO CROSSED
THE FINISH LINE WITH ME
WAS THE ONE WHO STOPPED
TO SAVE ME WHEN I NEEDED HELP,
THE TORTOISE!
[ FALCON CALLS ]
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE...?
[ TORTOISE GURGLING ]
Applejack:
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
HE EVEN SMILES SLOW.
AWW!
[ LAUGHTER ]
SPIKE, TAKE A LETTER.
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
I USED TO THINK
THAT THE MOST IMPORTANT TRAITS
TO LOOK FOR IN A PET
OR ANY BEST FRIEND
WERE ALL PHYSICAL,
COMPETITIVE ABILITIES.
BUT NOW I CAN SEE
HOW SHORTSIGHTED
AND SHALLOW THAT WAS.
[ GROWLS ]
TODAY, I LEARNED WHAT THE MOST
IMPORTANT QUALITY REALLY IS --
A CERTAIN KIND OF SPIRIT,
A STICK-TO-IT-IVE-NESS.
[ PLOP! ]
A NEVER-GIVE-UP,
CAN-DO ATTITUDE
THAT'S THE MARK
OF A REAL WINNER.
AND THIS TORTOISE HAS IT.
TENACITY.
GESUNDHEIT.
YOU JUST CAN'T STOP
THAT LITTLE GUY.
HE'S LIKE A -- LIKE A...
TANK!
[ PLOP! ]
BUT, RAINBOW, YOU DIDN'T WANT
A PET THAT COULDN'T FLY
BECAUSE IT WOULD KEEP YOU
GROUNDED AND HOLD YOU BACK,
REMEMBER?
HMM.
Applejack: ALL RIGHT, COME ON
OVER HERE, WINONA!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
COME ON, TANK!
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE FOR OUR
VERY FIRST PONY PET PLAY DATE!
[ HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪