[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
HEY, RARITY.
HEY, PINKIE PIE.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
RAINBOW DASH!
ISN'T SHE THE MOST DARING
DEVIL -- I MEAN, THE MOST
DEVILISH DARER -- I MEAN --
SHE'S DAZZLING!
OOH! YEAH!
THAT'S A GOOD WORD.
SHE'S DAZZLING!
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
OH, NO. OH, NO. OH, NO.
AYE-YI-YI-YI-YI!
[ CRASH! ]
All: OOH!
SO MUCH FOR DAZZLING.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
[ Muffled ] IS SHE GONNA BE
OKAY?
[ Muffled ] OH, I'M SO
WORRIED.
IS HER FACE GONNA STAY THAT
WAY?
OH!
HOW IS SHE, DOCTOR?
SHE'S GOING TO BE FINE.
LUCKILY, SHE HAS FRIENDS LIKE
YOU WHO GOT HER OVER HERE IN A
JIFFY.
HOW LONG DO I NEED TO LIE
HERE?
I'VE GOT THINGS I NEED TO DO!
WELL, THAT ALL DEPENDS ON
YOUR RECOVERY.
BUT I'D SAY A FEW DAYS, MINIMUM.
YOU GUYS HAVE GOT TO GET ME
OUT OF HERE!
I'M GONNA CLIMB THE WALLS!
OOH! JUST LIKE A SPIDER!
DID THE CRASH SOMEHOW GIVE HER
SUPERDUPER SPIDER POWERS?
NO.
NOR DID IT GIVE HER AMAZING
HEALING POWERS.
SHE NEEDS TO STAY IN BED FOR A
FEW DAYS.
FEW DAYS?
MIGHT AS WELL BE A FEW MONTHS OR
A FEW YEARS.
IT'S NOT SO BAD,
RAINBOW DASH.
I'LL BET THE CHOW IN HERE IS
HOOF-LICKIN' GOOD!
AND THE HOSPITAL GOWNS!
THEY MATCH THE CURTAINS!
[ TINKLING ]
AND LOOK!
YOU HAVE A ROOMMATE!
[ WHEELS SQUEAKING ]
[ TINKLING ]
WHAT'S THIS?
"DARING DO AND THE QUEST FOR THE
SAPPHIRE STONE."
THIS IS THE FIRST STORY IN
THE SERIES.
I OWN ALL OF THEM.
NO THANKS!
I SO DON'T READ!
I'M A WORLD-CLASS ATHLETE!
READING'S FOR EGGHEADS LIKE YOU,
TWILIGHT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NO OFFENSE, BUT I AM NOT
READING.
IT'S UNDENIABLY, UNQUESTIONABLY
UNCOOL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IS SHE SERIOUS?
WHO DOESN'T LIKE TO READ A
BANG-UP TALE FROM TIME TO TIME?
WHY, A GOOD BOOK IS ALMOST AS
MAGNIFICENT AS SILK PAJAMAS ON A
SUNDAY MORNING.
READING IS FOR EVERYPONY,
RAINBOW DASH.
YEAH! I LOVE READING!
AND MY HEAD ISN'T EVEN CLOSE TO
THE SHAPE OF AN EGG!
IT'S MORE THE SHAPE OF AN APPLE!
OR MAYBE AN ORANGE!
BUT A BIG ORANGE!
MORE LIKE A GRAPEFRUIT, REALLY.
ALL RIGHT, MY LITTLE PONIES.
RAINBOW DASH NEEDS HER REST.
YOU'LL HAVE TO COME BACK
TOMORROW.
I THINK YOU'D LIKE DARING.
SHE'S A LOT LIKE YOU --
ADVENTUROUS, FIERCE, AND
UNDENIABLY, UNQUESTIONABLY
UNSTOPPABLE.
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
[ BALL SQUEAKING ]
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
[ SMACK! ]
[ GLASS CLINKS ]
TO GET TO THE OTHER SIDE!
GET IT?
NEVER MIND.
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
ARGH!
[ SIGHS ]
[ POINK! ]
"AS DARING DO TREKKED THROUGH
[ SIGHS ]
THE TROPICAL JUNGLE, THE WET
"AS DARING DO TREKKED THROUGH
HEAT SAPPED HER ENERGY AND
THE TROPICAL JUNGLE, THE WET
SLOWED HER EVERY STEP.
HEAT SAPPED HER ENERGY AND
IF ONLY SHE COULD ESCAPE THIS
SLOWED HER EVERY STEP.
OPPRESSIVE ATMOSPHERE AND FLY UP
IF ONLY SHE COULD ESCAPE THIS
INTO THE COOL, BLUE SKY, BUT HER
OPPRESSIVE ATMOSPHERE AND FLY UP
CRASH LANDING IN THE JUNGLE HAD
INTO THE COOL, BLUE SKY, BUT HER
INJURED HER WING, AND SHE WAS
CRASH LANDING IN THE JUNGLE HAD
GROUNDED FOR A FEW DAYS."
INJURED HER WING, AND SHE WAS
FEW DAYS.
GROUNDED FOR A FEW DAYS."
IT MIGHT AS WELL BE A FEW MONTHS
FEW DAYS.
OR A FEW YEARS.
IT MIGHT AS WELL BE A FEW MONTHS
I'M RIGHT THERE WITH YOU,
OR A FEW YEARS.
SISTER.
I'M RIGHT THERE WITH YOU,
"THE MOSQUITOES BUZZED LOUDLY.
SISTER.
THE MACAWS CRIED FROM THE HIGH
"THE MOSQUITOES BUZZED LOUDLY.
TREES.
THE MACAWS CRIED FROM THE HIGH
YET ALL OF THESE DISTRACTING
TREES.
NOISES WERE NOT ENOUGH TO COVER
YET ALL OF THESE DISTRACTING
THE SOUND OF THE PREDATORS
NOISES WERE NOT ENOUGH TO COVER
FOLLOWING HER EVERY STEP."
THE SOUND OF THE PREDATORS
[ ROARS ]
FOLLOWING HER EVERY STEP."
[ GROWLING ]
[ ROARS ]
MEOW!
[ GROWLING ]
[ HISSING ]
MEOW!
[ YOWLS ]
[ HISSING ]
[ TIGER ROARING ]
[ YOWLS ]
"SAFELY LANDING ON THE OTHER
[ TIGER ROARING ]
SIDE, DARING FINALLY ALLOWED
"SAFELY LANDING ON THE OTHER
HERSELF A MOMENT TO BREATHE.
SIDE, DARING FINALLY ALLOWED
SHE TURNED AROUND TO FIND
HERSELF A MOMENT TO BREATHE.
HERSELF FACE-TO-FACE WITH THE
SHE TURNED AROUND TO FIND
LONG-LOST TEMPLE THAT SHE HAD
HERSELF FACE-TO-FACE WITH THE
SOUGHT TIRELESSLY FOR OVER 60
LONG-LOST TEMPLE THAT SHE HAD
DAYS AND NIGHTS"!
SOUGHT TIRELESSLY FOR OVER 60
I HATE TO ADMIT IT TO MYSELF AND
DAYS AND NIGHTS"!
WOULD REALLY HATE TO ADMIT IT TO
I HATE TO ADMIT IT TO MYSELF AND
MY FRIENDS, BUT...
WOULD REALLY HATE TO ADMIT IT TO
I LOVE THIS STORY!
MY FRIENDS, BUT...
I-I...
I LOVE THIS STORY!
I LOVE READING!
I-I...
[ POINK! ]
I LOVE READING!
I'M AN EGGHEAD.
"THE SMELL OF DECAY AND
DANGER HIT DARING DO AS SHE
PEERED INTO THE DIMLY LIT
ENTRANCE OF THE ANCIENT TEMPLE."
[ INSECT CHIRPING ]
[ RUMBLE ]
[ TINK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
PHEW!
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CLAMORING ]
[ CLAMORING STOPS ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
Both: HI, RAINBOW DASH!
UH, HEY, GUYS.
WE THOUGHT WE'D COME AND
CHEER YOU UP.
WE BROUGHT YOUR FAVORITE
BOARD GAME.
[ TINKLING ]
WE KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LIKE TO
WIN.
YOU GO FIRST, RAINBOW DASH.
[ NERVOUS CHUCKLE ]
NO, NO. YOU FIRST.
ALL RIGHT.
UH, CLOUD THREE.
AW, SHUCKS!
YOU RAINED ON MY CUMULUS!
[ CHUCKLES ] GO AGAIN.
UM, SKY FIVE?
WHOA!
YOU FOUND MY SEAGULL.
UH, CLOUD TWO?
YOU ZAPPED MY WEATHER PONY!
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU STUNG MY BUMBLEBEE.
AW. MY THUNDERBOLT!
AW. AND THAT'S MY LAST CLOUD.
YOU FOUND IT!
GUESS YOU GUYS WIN! I LOSE!
[ NICKERS ]
BUT, RAINBOW DASH, YOU -- YOU
DIDN'T EVEN GET A TURN.
[ TING! ]
YOU WIN SOME, YOU LOSE SOME.
BUT YOU DON'T LOSE SOME.
I DON'T THINK YOU'VE EVER LOST A
GAME.
[ YAWNS ] THANKS FOR COMING!
BUT YESTERDAY YOU WERE
DESPERATE FOR THINGS TO DO.
DO?
WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT
DARING DO?
I TOLD YOU I'M NOT INTERESTED IN
READING.
[ YAWNS ]
IT'S NAP TIME FOR ME!
[ SNORING ]
GLAD WE COULD CHEER YOU UP?
[ YAWNS ]
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
"DARING DO STOOD AT THE
ENTRANCE TO THE CENTRAL TEMPLE
CHAMBER.
AT LAST, SHE WAS FACE-TO-FACE
WITH THE LEGENDARY SAPPHIRE
STATUE."
HMM.
THERE MUST BE A PATTERN HERE.
WHAT DO ALL THESE ANIMALS HAVE
IN COMMON?
AHA!
THESE ANIMALS ARE ALL PREDATORS,
EXCEPT...
RATS!
PHEW!
[ RUMBLING ]
HELLO, RAINBOW DASH!
[ WHIP! ]
HOW'S OUR PATIENT DOING
TODAY?
WE NEED TO GET SOME FRESH AIR
IN HERE.
YOU'RE LOOKING SWEATIER THAN A
PIG WRANGLER ON A SUMMER'S DAY.
UH, WELL, GUYS, T-THANKS FOR
VISITING, BUT --
OKAY, NOW.
DINNERTIME FOR RAINBOW DASH.
OH. JUST IN TIME.
I AM SO HUNGRY.
OH, WELL, DON'T MIND US,
RAINBOW DASH.
YEAH, JUST GO AHEAD AND EAT
UP.
[ MUNCHING, SLURPING LOUDLY ]
[ GULPS ]
UH, ON SECOND THOUGHT...
UH, WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW,
RAINBOW DASH.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
BLECH! [ SPITS ]
"YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD EVADE ME
AND CAPTURE THE RELIC FOR
YOURSELF, BUT YOU WERE SADLY
MISTAKEN, MISS DO."
AND NOW, YOU SHALL MEET YOUR
DOOM!
[ WHISTLES ]
[ ANIMALS GROWLING ]
MEOW!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
WHOA! WHO IS THIS DUDE?
[ PANTING ]
YOU WON'T GET AWAY WITH THIS,
AHUIZOTL.
BUT I ALREADY HAVE.
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GRUNTS ] NOT AGAIN.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SNAKES HISSING ]
[ SNAKE SCREECHES ]
QUICKSAND.
[ GRUNTING ]
RAINBOW DASH?
[ Singsong voice ] RAINBOW DASH.
UH, O-OH.
UH, GOOD EVENI--
[ Normal voice ] MORNING.
MORNING, D-DOC.
HAVE YOU BEEN UP ALL NIGHT?
UH, OF COURSE NOT.
WELL, I'LL BE QUICK.
CONGRATULATIONS, RAINBOW DASH.
WE'RE CHECKING YOU OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL.
WHAT?! LATER TODAY?
[ TEETH CHATTERING ]
NO.
RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT NOW?!
"RIGHT NOW" RIGHT NOW?
"RIGHT NOW" RIGHT NOW.
BUT I DON'T FEEL BETTER.
NOW, TAKE IT EASY,
RAINBOW DASH.
REMEMBER TO STAY OFF THAT WING
FOR A WEEK.
HOW WILL I EVER FIND OUT WHAT
HAPPENS TO DARING DO?!
IS AHUIZOTL GONNA GET AWAY
WITH THE STATUETTE?
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO DARING?
AHA!
TWILIGHT HAS A COPY OF THE BOOK!
BUT I CAN'T ASK HER AFTER I
CALLED HER AN EGGHEAD AND ALL.
[ THUD! ]
OH!
THIS IS MAKING ME SICK ALL OVER
AGAIN!
[ POINK! ]
OH! OOH!
OH, THE PAIN!
THE PAIN!
RAINBOW DASH, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
A-ANYTHING WRONG?
WELL, UH, MY WING.
IT'S STILL HURTING, DOC.
OH! OUCH! RIGHT THERE.
I WAS TOUCHING YOUR GOOD
WING.
UH, RIGHT.
WELL, I THINK THAT ONE'S HURTING
NOW, TOO.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I THINK I KNOW WHAT THE TROUBLE
IS.
A SEVERE CASE OF LAZYITIS.
B-BUT YOU GOT ME ALL WRONG,
DOC!
I'M NOT BEING LAZY!
YOU'RE FINE, RAINBOW DASH.
GIVE IT SOME TIME, AND YOU'LL BE
RIGHT BACK IN THE SWING OF
THINGS.
GOOD DAY, RAINBOW DASH.
TAKE CARE.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I'LL NEVER GET TO SLEEP WITHOUT
KNOWING WHAT HAPPENS TO
DARING DO!
WHICH MAY NOT BE SUCH A BAD
THING.
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ POINK! ]
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ POINK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ TING! TING! TING! TING! ]
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ TING! TING! TING! TING! ]
[ POING! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ ZIP! ZIP! ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ POING! ]
FEELS LIKE THE HARDER I
[ ZIP! ZIP! ZIP! ZIP! ]
STRUGGLE, THE TIGHTER THE ROPES
FEELS LIKE THE HARDER I
GET.
STRUGGLE, THE TIGHTER THE ROPES
HELP! BURGLAR! BURGLAR!
GET.
SOMEONE'S TRYING TO STEAL MY
HELP! BURGLAR! BURGLAR!
SLIPPERS!
SOMEONE'S TRYING TO STEAL MY
I'M NOT TRYING TO STEAL YOUR
SLIPPERS!
SLIPPERS.
I'M NOT TRYING TO STEAL YOUR
I'M TRYING TO STEAL THIS BOOK!
SLIPPERS.
STOP, THIEF!
I'M TRYING TO STEAL THIS BOOK!
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
STOP, THIEF!
[ CRICK! ]
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ CRICK! ]
[ ALARM BLARING ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ DOG BARKING ]
[ ALARM BLARING ]
HEY! NOPONY INVITED ME!
[ DOG BARKING ]
[ SCREEEEEEECH! ]
HEY! NOPONY INVITED ME!
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
[ SCREEEEEEECH! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
HASN'T ANYPONY HEARD OF BEAUTY
[ GASPS ]
SLEEP?
HASN'T ANYPONY HEARD OF BEAUTY
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
SLEEP?
RAINBOW DASH, WHAT IN THE
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
WORLD IS GOING ON?
RAINBOW DASH, WHAT IN THE
WHY ARE YOU STEALING SLIPPERS?
WORLD IS GOING ON?
[ BARKING ]
WHY ARE YOU STEALING SLIPPERS?
HEY, GET BACK TO THE
[ BARKING ]
HOSPITAL.
HEY, GET BACK TO THE
WHAT'S ALL THE RUCKUS?
HOSPITAL.
HMM, I'D SAY IT'S MORE OF A
WHAT'S ALL THE RUCKUS?
FRACAS THAN A RUCKUS.
HMM, I'D SAY IT'S MORE OF A
WHAT'S GOING ON,
FRACAS THAN A RUCKUS.
RAINBOW DASH?
WHAT'S GOING ON,
[ SIGHS ]
RAINBOW DASH?
I'M AN EGGHEAD.
[ SIGHS ]
PARDON?
I'M AN EGGHEAD.
SEE, I WAS TRYING TO GET BACK
PARDON?
INTO THE HOSPITAL TO FINISH THE
SEE, I WAS TRYING TO GET BACK
LAST CHAPTER OF --
INTO THE HOSPITAL TO FINISH THE
"DARING DO AND THE QUEST FOR
LAST CHAPTER OF --
THE SAPPHIRE STATUE."
"DARING DO AND THE QUEST FOR
YOU GOT ME.
THE SAPPHIRE STATUE."
WOW.
YOU GOT ME.
I KNEW THE BOOK WAS GOOD, BUT I
WOW.
DIDN'T KNOW IT COULD DRIVE A
I KNEW THE BOOK WAS GOOD, BUT I
PONY TO PETTY THEFT.
DIDN'T KNOW IT COULD DRIVE A
"GOOD"? TRY "AWESOMELY
PONY TO PETTY THEFT.
AMAZING"!
"GOOD"? TRY "AWESOMELY
THAT BOOK IS UNDENIABLY,
AMAZING"!
UNQUESTIONABLY UNPUT-DOWNABLE!
THAT BOOK IS UNDENIABLY,
BUT THEN I HAD TO PUT IT DOWN.
UNQUESTIONABLY UNPUT-DOWNABLE!
I WAS SENT HOME BEFORE I COULD
BUT THEN I HAD TO PUT IT DOWN.
FINISH IT.
I WAS SENT HOME BEFORE I COULD
WELL, I'M GLAD THAT'S ALL
FINISH IT.
THIS IS ABOUT.
WELL, I'M GLAD THAT'S ALL
THERE'S NO REASON TO GO
THIS IS ABOUT.
AROUND CAUSING A RUCKUS --
THERE'S NO REASON TO GO
FRACAS!
AROUND CAUSING A RUCKUS --
'CAUSING A FRACAS JUST
FRACAS!
BECAUSE YOU LIKE TO READ.
'CAUSING A FRACAS JUST
LIKE I SAID, I HAVE EVERY
BECAUSE YOU LIKE TO READ.
BOOK IN THE SERIES.
LIKE I SAID, I HAVE EVERY
AND YOU CAN BORROW THEM ALL
BOOK IN THE SERIES.
ANYTIME YOU LIKE.
AND YOU CAN BORROW THEM ALL
THANKS, TWILIGHT.
ANYTIME YOU LIKE.
I'M SORRY I MADE SUCH A BIG DEAL
THANKS, TWILIGHT.
ABOUT ALL THIS.
I'M SORRY I MADE SUCH A BIG DEAL
I THOUGHT READING WAS JUST FOR
ABOUT ALL THIS.
SMART PONIES LIKE YOU.
I THOUGHT READING WAS JUST FOR
RAINBOW DASH, JUST BECAUSE
SMART PONIES LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE ATHLETIC DOESN'T MEAN YOU
RAINBOW DASH, JUST BECAUSE
AREN'T SMART.
YOU'RE ATHLETIC DOESN'T MEAN YOU
YEAH! JUST LOOK AT ME!
AREN'T SMART.
[ SMOOCH! ]
YEAH! JUST LOOK AT ME!
[ TINKLING ]
[ SMOOCH! ]
READING IS SOMETHING
[ TINKLING ]
EVERYPONY CAN ENJOY IF THEY JUST
READING IS SOMETHING
GIVE IT A TRY.
EVERYPONY CAN ENJOY IF THEY JUST
YEAH. I GET IT.
GIVE IT A TRY.
I SHOULDN'T KNOCK SOMETHING
YEAH. I GET IT.
UNTIL I'VE TRIED IT.
I SHOULDN'T KNOCK SOMETHING
THAT'S A GREAT LESSON.
UNTIL I'VE TRIED IT.
AND IT WOULD MAKE A GREAT LETTER
THAT'S A GREAT LESSON.
TO THE PRINCESS.
AND IT WOULD MAKE A GREAT LETTER
[ ZIP! ]
TO THE PRINCESS.
DID YOU GET ALL THAT?
[ ZIP! ]
YEAH?
DID YOU GET ALL THAT?
GREAT!
YEAH?
YOU WRITE THE LETTER!
GREAT!
I GOT TO FINISH THIS BOOK!
YOU WRITE THE LETTER!
[ CRUNCH! ]
I GOT TO FINISH THIS BOOK!
[ ZIP! ]
[ CRUNCH! ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ZIP! ]
AH! [ PANTS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER DUNGEON.
AH! [ PANTS ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER DUNGEON.
WITH DARING DO OUT OF THE WAY,
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
THE WORLD WILL SUFFER MIGHTILY
WITH DARING DO OUT OF THE WAY,
AT MY HANDS.
THE WORLD WILL SUFFER MIGHTILY
I AM VICTORIOUS!
AT MY HANDS.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
I AM VICTORIOUS!
I'LL TAKE THAT.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
WHAT?!
I'LL TAKE THAT.
NOOOOOO!
WHAT?!
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME,
NOOOOOO!
AHUIZOTL.
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME,
CURSE YOU, DARING DO!
AHUIZOTL.
[ SOBBING ]
CURSE YOU, DARING DO!
"AND SO, WITH AHUIZOTL
[ SOBBING ]
DEFEATED AND THE SAPPHIRE STATUE
"AND SO, WITH AHUIZOTL
SECURED, THE WORLD WAS SAFE AND
DEFEATED AND THE SAPPHIRE STATUE
SOUND ONCE AGAIN, THANKS TO
SECURED, THE WORLD WAS SAFE AND
DARING DO."
SOUND ONCE AGAIN, THANKS TO
[ SIGHS ]
DARING DO."
"DARING DO AND THE GRIFFIN'S
[ SIGHS ]
GOBLET."
"DARING DO AND THE GRIFFIN'S
AWESOME!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪