CALLING ALL PEGASUS PONIES!
MEETING TONIGHT!
[ ZIP! ]
MANDATORY MEETING FOR ALL
PONYVILLE PEGASI.
LIBRARY, TONIGHT!
BE COOL OR BE A MULE.
[ ZIP! ]
NO OFFENSE.
NONE TAKEN.
[ ZIP! ]
ALL RIGHT. GO ON IN.
NONE TAKEN.
FIND A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT. GO ON IN.
[ GROANS ]
FIND A SEAT.
YOU, TOO, FLUTTERSHY.
[ GROANS ]
[ BLINK! ]
YOU, TOO, FLUTTERSHY.
[ POP! ]
[ BLINK! ]
COME ON! LET'S GO!
[ POP! ]
[ CREEEEEAK! ]
COME ON! LET'S GO!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
[ CREEEEEAK! ]
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ '50s-P.S.A.-STYLE MUSIC
PLAYS ]
EVERY LIVING THING DEPENDS ON
THE LIFE-GIVING NOURISHMENT OF
RAINWATER.
AND IT IS UP TO CLOUDSDALE TO
PROVIDE RAIN-FILLED CLOUDS TO
EVERY CORNER OF EQUESTRIA!
"BUT HOW," ONEPONY MIGHT ASK,
"DOES CLOUDSDALE GATHER ALL
THIS EXTRA WATER?"
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
TORNADO POWER!
THAT'S RIGHT, PEGASI-DRIVEN
A TEAM OF PEGASI COMBINE THEIR
TORNADO POWER!
WINGPOWER TO CREATE A JUMBO
A TEAM OF PEGASI COMBINE THEIR
TORNADO, POWERFUL ENOUGH TO
WINGPOWER TO CREATE A JUMBO
PULL WATER OUT OF THE LOCAL
TORNADO, POWERFUL ENOUGH TO
RESERVOIR AND FUNNEL IT ALL THE
PULL WATER OUT OF THE LOCAL
WAY UP TO CLOUDSDALE.
RESERVOIR AND FUNNEL IT ALL THE
REMEMBER, PEGASI, YOUR JUMBO
WAY UP TO CLOUDSDALE.
TORNADO MUST REACH A MINIMUM OF
REMEMBER, PEGASI, YOUR JUMBO
800 WINGPOWER TO LIFT THAT
TORNADO MUST REACH A MINIMUM OF
WATER UP TO CLOUDSDALE!
800 WINGPOWER TO LIFT THAT
SO, THE NEXT TIME YOU'RE
WATER UP TO CLOUDSDALE!
WONDERING, "WHERE DOES ALL THAT
SO, THE NEXT TIME YOU'RE
EXTRA RAINWATER COME FROM,"
WONDERING, "WHERE DOES ALL THAT
JUST REMEM --
EXTRA RAINWATER COME FROM,"
[ FILM WARBLES ]
HEY, SPIKE!
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
UH, INTERMISSION?
SO, HERE'S THE SCOOP.
CLOUDSDALE HAS CHOSEN OUR OWN
HIGHLAND RESERVOIR AS THE SOURCE
OF THE RAINWATER THEY NEED FOR
ALL OF EQUESTRIA.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
IT MEANS IT'S UP TO PONYVILLE'S
PEGASI TO BRING THAT WATER UP TO
CLOUDSDALE.
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
NOT ONLY THAT, BUT SPITFIRE,
CAPTAIN OF THE WONDERBOLTS WILL
BE HERE TO OVERSEE THE WATER
TRANSFER AND RECORD OUR TOP
TORNADO WIND SPEED.
NOW, LAST YEAR, FILLYDELPHIA
BROKE THE WIND-SPEED RECORD WITH
A TOP SPEED OF 910 WINGPOWER.
BUT I THINK WE CAN DO BETTER.
I THINK WE CAN GET A TOP SPEED
OVER 1,000!
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
IF EACH AND EVERY PONY TRAINS
AND TRAINS HARD TO GET THEIR
WINGPOWER NUMBERS UP.
[ COUGHS ]
THAT COUGHING BETTER BE FROM
A POPCORN KERNEL, THUNDER LANE!
NOPONY'S GETTING SICK ON MY
WATCH!
SO, ARE WE GONNA TRAIN HARD?
All: YEAH!
ARE WE GONNA BE STRONG?
ARE WE GONNA BE FAST?
All: YEAH!
RECORD SMASHING FAST?!
YEAH!
WHO'S WITH ME?!
[ ALL CHEER ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
FLUTTERSHY.
STRETCH THOSE GLUTES, FLITTER!
NICE FLEXIBILITY, CLOUD CHASER.
A LITTLE TOO MUCH FLEXIBILITY,
BLOSSOMFORTH.
UH, SOMEPONY GIVE BLOSSOMFORTH A
HOOF.
LET'S SEE SOME FASTER TROTTING,
THUNDER LANE!
GOOD PACE, SILVER SPEED!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
KEEP IT UP!
WE'RE GONNA NEED ALL THE
WINGPOWER WE CAN GET TO BREAK
THAT RECORD!
YEAH!
[ SNORTS ]
GOOD WORK, EVERYPONY!
[ SIGHS ]
EVERYPONY EXCEPT FLUTTERSHY.
FLUTTERSHY!
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE!
YOU'RE AVOIDING TORNADO DUTY,
AND I WANT TO KNOW WHY!
FLUTTERSHY, OPEN --!
[ Weakly ] AH-CHOO.
HI, RAINBOW DASH.
[ COUGHS WEAKLY ]
FLUTTERSHY, WHAT HAPPENED TO
YOU?
OH, I [SNIFFLES]
I THINK I HAVE [COUGHS WEAKLY]
THE PONY POX.
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY, REALLY WANTED TO COME
TO TRAINING DAY TOD-- [ SIGHS ]
BUT THIS PONY POX HAS REALLY
KNOCKED ME FOR A LOOP.
AH-CHOO.
[ COUGHS WEAKLY ]
OH, YOU POOR THING.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S ONLY ONE CURE
FOR PONY POX.
I KNOW.
PLENTY OF BED -- AAH!
COLD WATER!
THOSE PONY POX ARE CLEARING
RIGHT UP!
[ GASPS ]
YOU KNOW, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I'M -- I'M STARTING TO
FEEL...BETTER.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
I'LL JUST GET OUT OF THESE ROBES
AND -- OWW!
OH! MY WING!
OH, OW.
IT'S HURT.
I GUESS I CAN'T FLY AFTER --
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
AA-AA-AA-AAH!
MESSED UP WING, HUH?!
STOP HORSING AROUND, FLUTTERSHY.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF TRAINING TO
DO.
COME ON NOW.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WELL, YOU SEE...
UH, WELL...
OH, RAINBOW DASH!
I JUST CAN'T DO IT!
I CAN'T FLY!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
JUST LAST WEEK, YOU WENT INTO
THAT WICKED NOSE DIVE TO SAVE
THAT FALLING BABY BIRD RIGHT
BEFORE IT HIT THE GROUND.
BUT THAT WAS DIFFERENT!
THAT WAS AN EMERGENCY.
THIS WHOLE TORNADO THING, IT'S
MORE LIKE A PERFORMANCE.
AND YOU KNOW HOW I HATE
PERFORMING IN FRONT OF OTHERS.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER FLIGHT CAMP?
I COULDN'T GALLOP HARD OR FLY
FAST, NOT WITH EVERYPONY LOOKING
AT ME.
IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
YOU'RE RIGHT, RAINBOW DASH.
IT WASN'T BAD.
IT WAS HORRIBLE!
[ GASPS ]
[ TREMBLING ]
AAH-AH-AH!
[ GASPS ]
[ ZOOM! ]
ALL THE OTHER FOALS USED TO
TEASE ME A LOT.
All: FLUTTERSHY! FLUTTERSHY!
FLUTTERSHY CAN'T HARDLY FLY!
[ Echoing ] FLUTTERSHY!
[ GASPS ]
I JUST CAN'T RISK THAT SORT OF
HUMILIATION AGAIN.
SUCK IT UP, FLUTTERSHY!
THIS IS NO TIME FOR --!
I MEAN, CONFIDENCE OR NO
CONFIDENCE, I'M GONNA NEED EVERY
PEGASUS TO BREAK THE RECORD,
INCLUDING YOU.
I NEED EVERY OUNCE OF WINGPOWER
I CAN GET.
OH, UH, I DON'T THINK SO,
RAINBOW DASH.
[ SIGHS ]
THANKS ANYWAY.
WAIT.
I'LL DO IT.
YOU WILL?
I WILL.
YOU'RE GAME?
I'M GAME.
ALL RIGHT!
WHAT EXACTLY DOES THIS
MACHINE DO?
THIS IS AN ANEMOMETER.
IT MEASURES YOUR ACCELERATIVE
VELOCITY AND TRANSLATES IT INTO
WINGPOWER, THUS GAUGING YOUR
CUMULATIVE H2O
ANTI-GRAVITATIONAL POTENTIAL.
ANY OTHER QUESTIONS?
YEAH.
WHAT EXACTLY DOES THIS MACHINE
DO?
IT TELLS YOU HOW FAST YOU'RE
FLYING AND HOW STRONG YOUR WINGS
ARE.
OH, OH, OKAY.
All: OHH.
YEAH, I SEE.
YEAH, RIGHT, YEAH.
[ COUGHS ]
[ TINKLE! ]
IS THAT YOU AGAIN,
THUNDER LANE?
PLEASE, WE NEED TO HAVE A
GERM-FREE ENVIRONMENT.
IT WASN'T ME.
IT WAS BLOSSOMFORTH!
DON'T WORRY, TWILIGHT.
THUNDER LANE'S JUST COOKING UP
AN EXCUSE TO SPEND TORNADO DAY
IN BED.
WHY DON'T YOU GET OVER HERE AND
BE OUR FIRST TEST FLIER,
THUNDER LANE?
[ COUGHS ]
[ ZOOM! ]
WE HAVE 9.3 WINGPOWER.
[ CHEERING ]
WOW, THAT'S FAST.
YEAH!
NOT BAD. NOT BAD.
[ CRACK! CRACK! ]
[ CRACK! CRACK! CRACK! ]
[ ZING! ZIP! ]
[ CRACK! CRACK! ]
16.5 WINGPOWER!
[ ZING! ZIP! ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
16.5 WINGPOWER!
NOW LISTEN UP!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
IF EACH OF YOU CAN GET YOUR
NOW LISTEN UP!
NUMBERS UP TO AT LEAST 10.0
IF EACH OF YOU CAN GET YOUR
WINGPOWER BY THE END OF THE
NUMBERS UP TO AT LEAST 10.0
WEEK, WE'LL NO DOUBT SET A NEW
WINGPOWER BY THE END OF THE
TORNADO SPEED RECORD.
WEEK, WE'LL NO DOUBT SET A NEW
WE'LL BE NUMBER ONE!
TORNADO SPEED RECORD.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
WE'LL BE NUMBER ONE!
[ ZIP! ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
[ SMACK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
IMPRESSIVE.
FLUTTERSHY, YOUR TURN.
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
FLUTTERSHY! FLUTTERSHY!
FLUTTERSHY CAN'T HARDLY FLY!
TELL HER.
NO, YOU TELL HER.
NO, YOU.
UM, GREAT JOB, FLUTTERSHY.
YOU MEASURED, UH, UH, 0.5.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
0.5?
ISN'T THAT, LIKE, LESS THAN 1?
[ BONK! ]
OW!
FLUTTERSHY! FLUTTERSHY!
FLUTTERSHY CAN'T HARDLY FLY!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
FLUTTERSHY! FLUTTERSHY!
[ CRYING ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
FLUTTERSHY, WAIT!
[ CRYING ]
SO, SOME PUNKS POKED A LITTLE
FLUTTERSHY, WAIT!
FUN AT YOU WHEN YOU GOT STAGE
SO, SOME PUNKS POKED A LITTLE
FRIGHT.
FUN AT YOU WHEN YOU GOT STAGE
BIG DEAL!
FRIGHT.
YOU AREN'T GONNA GO QUIT JUST
BIG DEAL!
BECAUSE OF THAT ARE YOU?
YOU AREN'T GONNA GO QUIT JUST
[ Voice breaking ] YES!
BECAUSE OF THAT ARE YOU?
[ SOBBING ]
[ Voice breaking ] YES!
BUT I NEED YOU!
[ SOBBING ]
I'M SORRY, RAINBOW DASH.
BUT I NEED YOU!
I JUST DON'T HAVE THE COURAGE
I'M SORRY, RAINBOW DASH.
RIGHT NOW.
I JUST DON'T HAVE THE COURAGE
[ SNIFFLING ]
RIGHT NOW.
[ WHIMPERS, SOBS ]
[ SNIFFLING ]
[ POINK! ]
[ WHIMPERS, SOBS ]
[ POINK! POINK! ]
[ POINK! ]
[ CHATTERS ]
[ POINK! POINK! ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ CHATTERS ]
OH, THANK YOU, BUT I'M AFRAID A
[ SNIFFLES ]
COUPLE OF LITTLE ACORNS WON'T
OH, THANK YOU, BUT I'M AFRAID A
SOLVE MY BIG FLYING PROBLEM.
COUPLE OF LITTLE ACORNS WON'T
[ QUACK! QUACK! ]
SOLVE MY BIG FLYING PROBLEM.
I TRIED, BUT -- OH, YOU
[ QUACK! QUACK! ]
SHOULD HAVE SEEN THOSE PONIES
I TRIED, BUT -- OH, YOU
LAUGHING AT ME!
SHOULD HAVE SEEN THOSE PONIES
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
LAUGHING AT ME!
I KNOW IT'S IMPORTANT TO HAVE
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
CONFIDENCE IN MYSELF.
I KNOW IT'S IMPORTANT TO HAVE
[ CHATTERS ]
CONFIDENCE IN MYSELF.
YES, YES.
[ CHATTERS ]
I DO REMEMBER.
YES, YES.
THE RIVER WAS SWELLING.
I DO REMEMBER.
[ CHATTERS ]
THE RIVER WAS SWELLING.
AND YOU WERE SCARED.
[ CHATTERS ]
YES, I DID TELL YOU TO NEVER
GIVE UP AND TO BELIEVE IN
YOURSELF.
YOU'RE RIGHT, MY FRIENDS!
I SHOULDN'T GIVE UP.
I WILL GET MY CONFIDENCE UP AND
SHOW EVERYPONY THAT I AM A GOOD
FLIER!
A GREAT FLIER!
[ ANIMALS CHEERING ]
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ SPLASH! ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ ZIP! ]
THAT'S WONDERFUL, FLITTER,
MUCH BETTER THAN YESTERDAY.
THIS IS CRAZY AWESOME!
WE'RE GONNA SMASH THAT RECORD!
[ CHATTERS ]
WHAT DID HE SAY?
DO I LOOK LIKE I SPEAK
SQUIRREL?
WHAT'S THAT?
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MUSIC DISTORTS ]
2.3? 2.3?
THAT HAS TO BE SOME KIND OF
MISTAKE!
I WORKED SO HARD!
FLUTTERSHY, THAT'S A HUGE
IMPROVEMENT!
YOU DID AWESOME, FLUTTERSHY.
NO, I DIDN'T.
I THOUGHT I'D GOTTEN OVER MY
NERVES, BUT THE STILL GOT THE
BEST OF ME.
THERE'S NO WAY I'LL FLY WITH
10.0 WINGPOWER TOMORROW.
SO YOU WON'T FLY WITH 10.0
WINGPOWER.
EVERY BIT COUNTS!
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL IF
EVERYPONY ELSE WAS FLYING WITH
10.0 WINGPOWER, AND YOU WERE
FLYING WITH 2.5?
ACTUALLY, IT WAS ONLY 2.3,
AND -- OW!
[ BONK! RATTLE! ]
[ ZIP! ]
WELL, UH, I'D FEEL, UM...
EXACTLY!
HUMILIATED!
I'M SORRY, RAINBOW DASH.
I JUST CAN'T DO IT.
IT'S OKAY, RAINBOW DASH.
YOU'VE STILL GOT PLENTY OF
WINGPOWER FOR YOUR TORNADO.
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO LIFT TONS OF
WATER UP TO CLOUDSDALE!
[ TINKLE! ]
[ SIGHS ]
IF ONLY THERE WAS A WAY TO LIFT
FLUTTERSHY OUT OF THE DUMPS.
[ MARCH-STYLE MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
ARE WE READY TO DO THIS?
All: YEAH!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
LOOK!
LAZY, THUNDER LANE!
WHERE IS HE?
HE'S BEEN TRYING TO GET OUT OF
TORNADO DUTY THE WHOLE TIME WITH
HIS FAKE COUGHING AND ALL.
RUMBLE, WHERE'S YOUR LAZY
BROTHER?
HE'S GOT THE FEATHER FLU.
HE'S DOWN IN PONYVILLE HOSPITAL.
BUT HE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE.
[ BLINK! ]
LET'S SEE.
WITH THOSE EIGHT SICK PEGASI OUT
WITH THE FEATHER FLU --
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
DON'T TELL ME WE WON'T BE
ABLE TO BREAK THE WIND-SPEED
RECORD!
NO.
WHEW.
YOU MIGHT NOT HAVE ENOUGH
WINGPOWER TO CREATE A TORNADO
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO LIFT THE
WATER TO CLOUDSDALE!
WELL, SHOULD WE PACK UP?
NO, OF COURSE NOT!
FORGET THE RECORD!
CLOUDSDALE STILL NEEDS WATER.
OKAY, EVERYPONY.
LET'S GIVE IT ALL WE'VE GOT!
ON THE SOUND OF THE HORN, WE
TAKE OFF!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ HORN SOUNDS ]
YOU THINK THEY'RE GONNA MAKE IT
TO 800 WINGPOWER?
I SURE HOPE SO.
150 WINGPOWER.
250 WINGPOWER.
500 WINGPOWER!
750 WINGPOWER!
TWILIGHT!
FLUTTERSHY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
I FIGURED IF I COULDN'T HELP
RAINBOW DASH WITH THE TORNADO,
THE LEAST I COULD DO WAS OFFER
MORAL SUPPORT!
SHE COULD SURE USE IT,
CONSIDERING THAT EIGHT PEGASI
ARE SICK WITH THE FEATHER FLU!
OH, NO!
THAT'S TERRIBLE NEWS!
OH!
AAH! AAH!
AAH!
All: AAH!
AAH! OOH!
[ CREAK! BLINK! ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ Muffled ] I'M FINE!
YOU WERE SO CLOSE TO THE 800
WINGPOWER MINIMUM.
I'M SORRY RAINBOW DASH.
[ CREAK! POP! ]
BLBLBLB.
WE'VE GOT TO TRY AGAIN!
[ TINKLE! ]
BUT YOU'VE PUSHED YOUR CREW
TO THEIR LIMIT ALREADY!
AAH!
IF YOU BREAK APART AGAIN,
SOMEPONY COULD GET HURT.
YOU SHOULD QUIT.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
NO!
ONE MORE TIME!
I GOT TO KNOW WE GAVE IT OUR
ALL!
IF I'M GOING DOWN, I'M GOING
DOWN FLYING!
[ ZIP! ]
COME ON, PONIES!
LET'S MAKE THIS HAPPEN!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
YEAH!
[ HORN SOUNDS ]
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
100 WINGPOWER!
200!
500!
STAY IN POSITION!
FLAP THOSE WINGS!
FASTER!
700!
750 WINGPOWER!
[ SMACK! ]
OHH!
THEY FELL APART RIGHT AFTER
THIS!
OH, I'M TOO NERVOUS TO LOOK!
COME ON!
JUST A LITTLE HARDER!
I CAN SEE THE WATER TRYING TO
FUNNEL THROUGH!
795!
THEY ARE SO CLOSE!
FLUTTERSHY, THEY NEED YOU UP
THERE!
I WON'T MAKE A DIFFERENCE!
YOU CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE!
MY MEASLY 2.3 WINGPOWER IS
STILL TOO LITTLE!
IT'S STICKING AT 795.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY GOT ANY
MORE IN 'EM!
DO IT FOR EQUESTRIA!
DO IT FOR RAINBOW DASH!
DO IT FOR YOURSELF!
[ BLINK! ]
[ GULPS ]
[ QUACK! ]
AAH! AAH! OH!
WHOA!
IT'S MOVING!
SHE'S DOING IT!
798!
SHE'S SURPASSED HER BEST
WINGPOWER NUMBER!
FLUTTERSHY! FLUTTERSHY!
FLUTTERSHY CAN'T HARDLY FLY!
[ LAUGHS ]
NO!
[ ZIP! ZOOM! ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
I THINK IT WAS FLUTTERSHY.
[ METER BEEPING ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
SHE DID IT! SHE DID IT!
THEY ALL DID IT!
[ HORN SOUNDS ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
GREAT JOB!
YOU DID IT!
[ SOFT THUD ]
WHOA, GIRL!
TAKE IT EASY!
WHA-- WHAT?
DID WE DO IT?
YEAH! WE DID IT!
YOU DID IT!
[ BOTH GRUNT, LAUGH ]
GREAT JOB, FLUTTERSHY!
THAT WAS AWESOME!
YEAH, WE COULDN'T HAVE DONE
IT WITHOUT YOU.
NICE JOB, RAINBOW DASH.
YOU MAY NOT HAVE SET A NEW
RECORD, BUT YOU SHOWED A LOT OF
GUTS.
THANKS!
BUT IF YOU WANT TO TALK GUTS,
THEN YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE IT TO MY
NUMBER-ONE FLIER, FLUTTERSHY!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR FLUTTERSHY!
All: FLUTTERSHY! FLUTTERSHY!
FLUTTERSHY CAN REALLY FLY!
[ CHEERING ]
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA.
SOMETIMES, YOU CAN FEEL LIKE
WHAT YOU HAVE TO OFFER'S TOO
LITTLE TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE, BUT
TODAY, I LEARNED THAT
EVERYPONY'S CONTRIBUTION IS
IMPORTANT, NO MATTER HOW SMALL.
IF YOU JUST KEEP YOUR HEAD HIGH,
DO YOUR BEST, AND BELIEVE IN
YOURSELF, ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪