[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ CREAK! SNAP! ]
[ WHIP! ]
[ CLINK! ]
LET'S DO THIS.
[ SPROING! ]
BL-BL-BL-BL-BL-BL-BL!
[ CREAK! ]
AHHHHHH.
HAPPY -- SAD.
OPEN, SHUT, OPEN, SHUT, OPEN,
SHUT, OPEN, SHUT.
YEP, YEP, YEP, YEP, YEP, YEP,
YEP, YEP!
NOPE, NOPE, NOPE, NOPE, NOPE,
NOPE, NOPE, NOPE!
WHOO! WHOO!
WHOO! WHOO! WHOO-WHOO-WHOO!
PBHT!
[ PANTING ]
[ POINK! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! ]
[ BONK! HONK! ZING! ]
[ BABBLES, LAUGHS ]
[ WHIP! ]
NAILED IT!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
MORNING, DAISY JO.
HERE TO PICK UP SOME COOKIES TO
GO WITH YOUR MILK?
OH, YEAH, PINKIE, DONTCHA
KNOW?
WELL, MRS. CAKE JUST MADE A
FRESH BATCH OF YOUR FAVORITE
OATMEAL.
MOO! SOUNDS DELIGHTFUL!
OH, ROSE, YOUR CALLA LILIES
LOOK EVEN BETTER THAN LAST YEAR.
I BET YOU'LL TAKE FIRST PRIZE IN
THE FLOWER SHOW AGAIN.
THANKS, PINKIE.
WOULD YOU LIKE ONE?
ABSOLUTELY.
[ CHOMP! ]
[ SPROING! WHIP! ]
LOOKIN' FIT AS A FIDDLE,
MR. WADDLE, AND YOU'RE WEARING
MY FAVORITE TIE!
AW, SHUCKS, MISS PINKIE, YOU
FLATTERER, YOU.
WELL, HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
CHEERILEE.
THANK YOU, PINKIE.
HAPPY DAY AFTER YOUR
BIRTHDAY, ZECORA.
WHAT A LOVELY "HI,"
MISS PINKIE PIE.
AND, MISS MATILDA, HAPPY
BIRTHDAY TO YOU...
IN 132 DAYS!
PINKIE PIE, HOW DO YOU
REMEMBER EVERYTHING ABOUT
EVERYPONY?
'CAUSE EVERYPONY'S MY FRIEND,
AND I LOVE TO SEE MY FRIENDS
SMILE!
♪ MY NAME IS PINKIE PIE ♪
HELLO!
♪ AND I AM HERE TO SAY ♪
HOW YOU DOIN'?
♪ I'M GONNA MAKE YOU SMILE, AND
I WILL BRIGHTEN UP YOUR DA-A-Y ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER NOW ♪
WHAT'S UP?
♪ IF YOU ARE SAD OR BLUE ♪
HOWDY!
♪ 'CAUSE CHEERING UP MY FRIENDS
IS JUST WHAT PINKIE'S HERE TO
DO ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LOVE TO MAKE YOU
SMILE, SMILE, SMILE ♪
♪ YES, I DO ♪
♪ IT FILLS MY HEART WITH
SUNSHINE ALL THE WHILE ♪
♪ YES, IT DOES ♪
♪ 'CAUSE ALL I REALLY NEED'S
A SMILE, SMILE, SMILE ♪
♪ FROM THESE HAPPY FRIENDS OF
MINE ♪
♪ I LIKE TO SEE YOU GRIN ♪
AWESOME!
♪ I LOVE TO SEE YOU BEAM ♪
ROCK ON!
♪ THE CORNERS OF YOUR MOUTH
TURNED UP IS ALWAYS PINKIE'S
DREAM ♪
HOOF-BUMP!
♪ BUT IF YOU'RE KIND OF WORRIED
AND YOUR FACE IS MADE OF
FROWNS ♪
♪ I'LL WORK REAL HARD AND DO MY
BEST TO TURN THAT SAD FROWN
UPSIDE DOWN ♪
♪ BECAUSE I LOVE TO MAKE YOU
GRIN, GRIN, GRIN ♪
♪ YES, I DO ♪
♪ BUST IT OUT FROM EAR TO EAR ♪
♪ LET IT BEGIN ♪
♪ JUST GIVE ME A JOYFUL GRIN,
GRIN, GRIN ♪
♪ AND YOU FILL ME WITH GOOD
CHEER ♪
♪ IT'S TRUE, SOME DAYS ARE
DARK AND LONELY ♪
♪ AND MAYBE YOU FEEL SAD, BUT
PINKIE WILL BE THERE TO SHOW YOU
THAT IT ISN'T THAT BAD ♪
♪ THERE'S ONE THING THAT MAKES
ME HAPPY AND MAKES MY WHOLE LIFE
WORTHWHILE ♪
♪ AND THAT'S WHEN I TALK TO MY
FRIENDS AND GET THEM TO SMILE ♪
♪ I REALLY AM SO HAPPY ♪
♪ YOUR SMILE FILLS ME WITH
GLEE ♪
♪ I GIVE A SMILE, I GET A
SMILE ♪
♪ AND THAT'S SO SPECIAL TO ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LOVE TO SEE YOU
BEAM, BEAM, BEAM ♪
♪ YES, I DO ♪
♪ TELL ME, WHAT MORE CAN I SAY
TO MAKE YOU SEE ♪
♪ THAT I DO? ♪
♪ IT MAKES ME HAPPY WHEN YOU
BEAM, BEAM, BEAM ♪
♪ YES, IT ALWAYS MAKES MY DAY ♪
♪ COME ON, EVERYPONY, SMILE,
SMILE, SMILE ♪
♪ FILL MY HEART UP WITH
SUNSHINE, SUNSHINE ♪
♪ ALL I REALLY NEED'S A SMILE,
SMILE, SMILE ♪
♪ FROM THESE HAPPY FRIENDS OF
MINE ♪
♪ COME ON, EVERYPONY, SMILE,
SMILE, SMILE ♪
♪ FILL MY HEART UP WITH
SUNSHINE, SUNSHINE ♪
♪ ALL I REALLY NEED'S A SMILE,
SMILE, SMILE ♪
♪ FROM THESE HAPPY FRIENDS OF
MINE ♪
♪ YES, A PERFECT GIFT FOR ME IS
A SMILE AS WIDE AS A MILE ♪
♪ TO MAKE ME HAPPY AS CAN BE ♪
♪ SMILE, SMILE, SMILE, SMILE ♪
♪ SMILE ♪
♪ COME ON AND ♪
♪ COME ON AND SMILE ♪
♪ SMILE ♪
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU BEFORE.
♪ COME ON AND SMILE ♪
KID, YOU'RE SMARTER THAN YOU
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU BEFORE.
LOOK.
KID, YOU'RE SMARTER THAN YOU
THANKS! I'M PINKIE PIE.
LOOK.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
THANKS! I'M PINKIE PIE.
"PROPERTY OF C.D.D."
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
I'M GUESSING THAT LAST "D" IS
"PROPERTY OF C.D.D."
FOR "DONKEY."
I'M GUESSING THAT LAST "D" IS
QUICK AS A WHIP, KID.
FOR "DONKEY."
NOW, HOW ABOUT THAT "C"?
QUICK AS A WHIP, KID.
HMM.
NOW, HOW ABOUT THAT "C"?
CALVIN?
HMM.
CALHOUN?
CALVIN?
CALEB?
CALHOUN?
CARL?
CALEB?
CARMINE?
CARL?
CARLO?
CARMINE?
CHARLIE?
CARLO?
CHESTER?
CHARLIE?
CHICO?
CHESTER?
CLAUDIO?
CHICO?
CLETUS?
CLAUDIO?
CLIFFORD?
CLETUS?
CONROY?
CLIFFORD?
CORNELIUS?
CONROY?
CORTEZ?
CORNELIUS?
CRANKY -- IT'S CRANKY, ALL
CORTEZ?
RIGHT?!
CRANKY -- IT'S CRANKY, ALL
AND YOUR MIDDLE NAME?
RIGHT?!
[ Mumbling ] DOODLE.
AND YOUR MIDDLE NAME?
I'M SORRY?
[ Mumbling ] DOODLE.
ONE MORE TIME.
[ GROANS ]
DOODLE.
[ GASPS ] SO YOU'RE A
CRANKY DOODLE DONKEY?
♪ YOU'RE A CRANKY DOODLE DONKEY
GUY ♪
♪ YOU'RE A CRANKY DOODLE
DONKEY ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER MET YOU, BUT YOU'RE
MY NEW FRIEND, AND I'M YOUR BEST
FRIEND, PINKIE PIE ♪
COME ON, NOW, DOODLE!
GIVE A SMILE!
[ DROOP! ]
NOPONY CALLS ME DOODLE!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
MEET SOMEPONY NEW -- CHECK.
INTRODUCE MYSELF -- CHECK.
SING RANDOM SONG OUT OF
NOWHERE -- CHECK.
BECOME INSTANT BEST FRIENDS --
[ BUZZER ]
UNCHECK.
I DON'T GET IT.
HOW CAN SOMEPONY NOT BECOME
INSTANT BEST FRIENDS WITH ME?
WAS IT SOMETHING I SAID?
WAS IT SOMETHING I SANG?
THIS IS NO TIME FOR THE BLAME
GAME, PINKIE!
THERE'S SOMEPONY NEW IN TOWN,
AND YOU NEED TO WIN HIM OVER.
"TRY EVERYTHING YOU CAN TO MAKE
CRANKY SMILE AND BE YOUR
FRIEND --"
CHECK!
[ WHIP! ]
ALL RIGHT, PINKIE, IF YOU'RE
GONNA WIN CRANKY'S FRIENDSHIP,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BRING YOUR
"A" GAME.
LET'S DO THIS.
[ ZIP! ]
[ SPROING! SPROING! ]
HOWDY DOODIE, CRANKY DOODLE!
[ SPROING! SPROING! SPROING! ]
SO, UH, ARE YOU MOVING TO
PONYVILLE, CRANKY?
WHAT GAVE YOU THE HINT THERE,
KID -- THE CART FULL OF STUFF,
MAYBE?
WELL, I'D BE HAPPY TO SHOW
YOU AROUND.
IT'S THE LEAST A NEW FRIEND CAN
DO.
[ CREAK! ]
LISTEN, KID, I TRAVELED
AROUND EQUESTRIA MY ENTIRE LIFE.
I'VE MADE MANY FRIENDS.
I DON'T NEED ANY MORE.
GOSH, I COULD NEVER HAVE TOO
MANY FRIENDS.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU GO AND
MAKE SOME MORE?
BUT I DON'T NEED TO GO WHEN I
CAN STAY AND MAKE FRIENDS...
[ WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! ]
...WITH YOU.
[ DROOP! ]
[ BRAYS ]
LOOK, KID --
OH, CRANKY, YOU CAN CALL ME
"PINKIE."
ALL OF MY FRIENDS DO.
[ TINK! TINK! TINK! ]
LOOK, KID, I CAME TO
PONYVILLE FOR SOME PEACE AND
QUIET AND PRIVACY, TO BE ALONE
WITH MY MEMORIES.
ALL I WANT IS TO GET TO MY NEW
HOME AND UNPACK MY STUFF.
[ CLANK! ]
WHOO!
WHAT DOES THIS BAUBLE DO?
[ CLINK! CLINK! CLINK! ]
DON'T TOUCH THAT!
OH, WHAT'S THIS?
[ WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! ]
PLEASE DON'T!
OH, LOOK AT THESE.
[ CHIMES RINGING ]
HEE HEE HEE!
HEY, HEY!
KEEP YOUR HOOVES OFF MY WAGON!
OKAY, CRANKY.
[ POINK! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ ZIP! ]
I PROMISE NOT TO TOUCH YOUR
WAGON, 'CAUSE I GOT ONE OF MY
OWN!
I USE IT TO WELCOME FOLKS.
WHO'D HAVE GUESSED?
MAYBE WE CAN BE WAGON
BUDDIES.
WELL, YOU'VE GOT TO AT LEAST LET
ME GIVE YOU THE SPECIAL WELCOME
THAT COMES WITH IT.
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ SIGHS ]
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
[ CREAK! WHOOSH! ]
[ HONK! ]
[ FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ WELCOME, WELCOME, WELCOME ♪
♪ A FINE WELCOME TO YOU ♪
♪ I SAY HOW DO YOU DO? ♪
♪ WELCOME, WELCOME, WELCOME ♪
♪ I SAY HIP, HIP, HURRAY! ♪
♪ WELCOME, WELCOME, WELCOME TO
PONYVILLE TODAY ♪
WAIT FOR IT!
[ DING! ]
[ HORN BLOWS ]
[ WHIP! ]
NO!
[ SPLAT! ]
OH, SILLY ME, I MUST HAVE PUT
THE CONFETTI IN THE OVEN AND THE
CAKE IN THE CONFETTI
CANNONS...AGAIN!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SPLAT! ]
MMM! BUT STILL DELICIOUS!
TRY SOME, CRANKY.
IT'S SURE TO MAKE YOU SMILE.
WHERE IS IT? WHERE IS IT?!
WHERE'S WHAT?
[ TWANG! ]
[ SCREAMS ]
SPIDER -- BIG, HAIRY SPIDER!
[ SMACK! SMACK! SMACK! ]
STOP, STOP, STOP!
[ WHOOSH! ]
OH, WAS THAT YOUR WIG?
[ GROWLS ]
I CAN FIX THIS, I CAN FIX
THIS!
[ PITTER! PITTER! PITTER! ]
HEY, EVERYBODY, DOES ANYBODY
HAVE A TOUPEE?!
All: HUH?
TOU-- TOUPEE?
HUH?
OH.
THIS DONKEY IS REALLY, REALLY
BALD!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ BRAYS ]
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?!
THIS IS SERIOUS BUSINESS,
EVERYPONY!
CRANKY NEEDS A NEW WIG TO COVER
HIS HAIRLESS HEAD!
I HAVE HAD ENOUGH!
[ CRUNCH! ]
[ GASPS ]
YOU'RE LOSING HIM, PINKY.
WAIT, CRANKY, PLEASE, LET ME
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
NO!
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE?
LADIES, THIS IS A SPA EMERGENCY.
CRANKY NEEDS HELP STAT.
[ WHIP! ]
[ BELLS RINGING ]
[ GROANS ]
HI, CRANKY!
I HAVE A GIFT FOR YOU.
THE SPA TREATMENT WAS GIFT
ENOUGH.
IT'S NOT GOING TO EXPLODE OR
ANYTHING, PROMISE.
JUST OPEN IT.
[ POINK! ]
IT'S A NEW TOUPEE.
I HAD MY FRIEND RARITY MAKE IT.
SHE CALLS IT "THE DREAMBOAT
SPECIAL."
[ CREAK! ]
[ WHIP! ]
THIS IS WONDERFUL.
THANKS, KID.
HE'S STARTING TO WARM UP, BUT
STILL NO SMILE.
HMM...
HEY, WHAT YOU DOING THERE, OLD
BUDDY, OLD PAL?!
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
LOOKS LIKE A YARD SALE.
I'LL GIVE YOU TWO BITS FOR THIS!
[ WOBBLE! WOBBLE! WOBBLE! ]
I'M NOT SELLING, KID.
I'M UNPACKING.
[ CREAK! ]
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SO?
I THOUGHT I HAD.
THIS IS SO PRETTY.
WHERE'D YOU GET IT?
MANEHATTAN.
NOW PUT IT DOWN, GENTLY.
REALLY?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING THERE?
TRYING TO FIND A FRIEND.
OOH! I'M ALWAYS TRYING TO
FIND FRIENDS, AND TODAY I FOUND
YOU.
SEE HOW GOOD I AM AT IT?
THIS WAS A SPECIAL FRIEND.
LIKE ME?
[ TINK! TINK! TINK! ]
NO, YOU'RE EXTRA-SPECIAL,
KID.
[ POINK! ]
YES! I'M IN.
[ WHOOSH! ]
WOW! WHERE IN EQUESTRIA DID YOU
GET THIS, CRANKY?
FILLYDELPHIA.
IT'S AWFULLY PRETTY.
YEAH, SHE WAS.
HUH?
I MEAN, IT WAS -- I MEAN, IT
IS -- YES, IT'S PRETTY!
NOW PUT IT DOWN!
I WONDER WHERE CRANKY GOT
THIS.
HUH? WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT?
HEY, CRANKY, CAN I ASK YOU
ABOUT --
[ BLAM! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
OH, NO!
WHAT DID YOU SA-A-A-A-AY?!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
[ WHIP! ]
THERE!
UH, ALL BETTER?
NO, NOT ALL BETTER!
ALL SOGGY!
I'M SORRY, CRANKY.
OH, YOU'RE SORRY.
WELL, THEN, EVERYTHING IS FINE!
IT IS?
NO, IT ISN'T!
LISTEN TO ME, KID!
I WILL NEVER BE YOUR FRIEND!
[ HONK! ]
NEVER OR NEVER, EVER?
NEVER, EVER, EVER, EVER,
EVER!
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
[ CREAK! ]
THAT'S FOUR EVERS.
THAT'S LIKE...FOREVER.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
CRANKY SAID HE WOULD NEVER,
FOREVER BE MY FRIEND.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
I KNOW THIS IS HARD FOR YOU,
PINKIE, SEEING THAT YOUR FRIENDS
WITH EVERYPONY, BUT YOU JUST
HAVE TO ACCEPT THAT CRANKY IS
GONNA BE AN EXCEPTION.
HE JUST DOESN'T WANT TO BE
BOTHERED.
YEAH. HE DOESN'T WANT TO BE
BOTHERED BY YOUR OVER-THE-TOP,
SUPER-HYPER ANTICS.
RAINBOW!
NO, NO.
IT'S OKAY, TWILIGHT.
I GET WHAT YOU'RE SAYING -- WHAT
YOU'RE BOTH SAYING.
AND I GUESS I CAN LEAVE CRANKY
ALONE...
RIGHT AFTER HE ACCEPTS MY
APOLOGY.
[ THUD! ]
[ SPROING! SPROING! SPROING! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
CRANKY!
NO, NO!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
WAIT!
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU DON'T WANT
ME AS A FRIEND!
NO, I DON'T!
SO I JUST WANTED TO SAY I'M
SORRY!
FINE! YOU SAID IT!
BUT DO YOU ACCEPT MY APOLOGY?
NO!
CRANKY, PLEASE ACCEPT MY
APOLOGY, PLEASE!
NO!
BUT I'M REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY...
[ GASPS ]
...REALLY, REALLY...
[ ZOOM! ]
[ SIGHS ]
AAH!
...REALLY, REALLY, REALLY...
[ WHIP! ]
[ RUMBLE! ]
AAH!
...REALLY, REALLY, REALLY...
[ WHIP! ]
...REALLY, REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY, REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY, REALLY, REALLY
[Echoing] SORRY!
[ HAMMER POUNDING ]
[ CLUNK! ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ KNOCKING AT DOOR ]
CRANKY, PLEASE, PLEASE ACCEPT
MY APOLOGY.
[ CLANK! ]
[ CREAK! POP! ]
I'D DO ANYTHING TO MAKE IT UP TO
YOU.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN
DO.
YOU RUINED MY BOOK!
YOU DESTROYED ALL I HAVE TO
REMEMBER HER BY!
"HER"? HER WHO?
THE SPECIAL FRIEND?
GO AWAY, PINKIE!
[ TWANG! WHOOSH! ]
[ BRAYS ]
[ KNOCK AT DOOR ]
CRANKY, IT'S ME AGAIN.
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE MY FRIEND OR ACCEPT MY
APOLOGY.
BEFORE I LEAVE YOU ALONE
FOREVER, I HAVE SOMETHING TO AT
LEAST TRY TO MAKE UP FOR RUINING
YOUR BOOK.
NO, I DON'T WANT IT, KID.
ANYTHING YOU WOULD GIVE ME IS
SURE TO LEAD TO SOME SORT OF
DISASTER.
GOODNESS, YOU REALLY ARE
CRANKY.
[ RATTLE! RATTLE! CREAK! ]
[ WHIP! ]
IT CAN'T BE.
IS IT REALLY YOU?
IT CAN...AND IT IS.
MATILDA! BUT HOW?
PINKIE.
[ DING! DING! DING! ]
BUT I NEVER TOLD YOU ABOUT
HER.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO!
I PUT TWO AND TWO AND TWO
TOGETHER, AND IT ADDED UP TO
MATILDA.
WHAT?
WELL, WHEN YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT YOUR SOUVENIRS, YOU SAID
SOMETHING ABOUT TRYING TO FIND A
SPECIAL FRIEND.
[ BRAYS ]
AND, YOU KNOW, I WASN'T JUST
BORN YESTERDAY.
NUH-UH! MY BIRTHDAY ISN'T FOR
ANOTHER 75 DAYS.
HUH?
AND THEN, IN YOUR SCRAPBOOK,
THERE WAS A FLOWER, AN OLD
TICKET, AND A MENU FROM THE
GRAND GALLOPING GALA, AND I KNEW
I'D RECOGNIZED ALL THESE THINGS.
BUT HOW COULD YOU HAVE EVER
SEEN THEM BEFORE?
BECAUSE I ALSO HAVE THEM IN
MY SCRAPBOOK.
AND I'D SEEN THEM IN
MATILDA'S BOOK!
OH, MATILDA, THE NIGHT WE MET
AT THE GALA WAS THE MOST MAGICAL
NIGHT OF MY LIFE.
I COULDN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU
AGAIN.
BUT WHEN I CAME TO YOUR ROOM THE
NEXT DAY, YOU WERE GONE.
DIDN'T YOU GET MY
NO! I NEVER GOT IT.
AND EVER SINCE THAT DAY, I'VE
GONE FROM TOWN TO TOWN TO TOWN,
SEARCHING ALL OVER EQUESTRIA FOR
YOU, UNTIL FINALLY I GAVE UP.
I CAME TO PONYVILLE TO RETIRE
FROM MY SEARCH.
I WAS LIVING IN PONYVILLE THE
WHOLE TIME.
I ALWAYS HOPED THAT SOMEDAY YOU
WOULD COME AND FIND ME...DOODLE.
[ POINK! ]
UH, MATILDA, NOPONY CALLS HIM
DOODLE.
NOPONY BUT MATILDA.
MM.
OH.
[ TING! ]
OH, DOODLE, I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE
YOU.
[ SMOOCHES ]
[ BRAYS ]
[ CREAK! ]
SO, DOES THIS MEAN THAT YOU
ACCEPT MY APOLOGY?
YES, PINKIE, I ACCEPT YOUR
APOLOGY, AND I AM HONORED TO
CALL YOU MY FRIEND.
[ WARBLE! ]
[ ZOOM! WHISTLE! ]
WHOO-HOO!
THIS IS JUST FANTASTIC!
NOW WE'LL HANG OUT TOGETHER AND
CHAT AND SING SONGS AND [GASPS]
PARTY!
OOH, I CAN THROW YOU GUYS A BIG
IT'LL GET CALLED THE "WELCOME TO
PARTY!
PONYVILLE/I FOUND MY LOST
IT'LL GET CALLED THE "WELCOME TO
LOVE/I'M BFF WITH PINKIE PIE
PONYVILLE/I FOUND MY LOST
PARTY"!
LOVE/I'M BFF WITH PINKIE PIE
[ TINK! PLOP! ]
PARTY"!
OR MAYBE SOMETHING LESS
[ TINK! PLOP! ]
OVER-THE-TOP AND NOT SO
OR MAYBE SOMETHING LESS
SUPER-HYPER.
OVER-THE-TOP AND NOT SO
PINKIE, WE'RE ETERNALLY
SUPER-HYPER.
GRATEFUL TO YOU, BUT MATILDA AND
PINKIE, WE'RE ETERNALLY
I JUST WANT TO SPEND SOME TIME
GRATEFUL TO YOU, BUT MATILDA AND
TOGETHER IN PEACE AND QUIET.
I JUST WANT TO SPEND SOME TIME
OH. UM, BUT WE'RE STILL
TOGETHER IN PEACE AND QUIET.
FRIENDS?
OH. UM, BUT WE'RE STILL
PINKIE, YOU WENT WAY, WAY,
FRIENDS?
WAY OUT OF YOUR WAY TO MAKE ME
PINKIE, YOU WENT WAY, WAY,
HAPPY.
WAY OUT OF YOUR WAY TO MAKE ME
OF COURSE WE'RE FRIENDS.
HAPPY.
GREAT!
OF COURSE WE'RE FRIENDS.
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA, THERE
GREAT!
ARE MANY DIFFERENT KINDS OF
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA, THERE
FRIENDS AND MANY WAYS TO EXPRESS
ARE MANY DIFFERENT KINDS OF
FRIENDSHIP.
FRIENDS AND MANY WAYS TO EXPRESS
SOME FRIENDS LIKE TO RUN AND
FRIENDSHIP.
LAUGH AND PLAY TOGETHER, BUT
SOME FRIENDS LIKE TO RUN AND
OTHERS JUST LIKE TO BE LEFT
LAUGH AND PLAY TOGETHER, BUT
ALONE, AND THAT'S FINE, TOO.
OTHERS JUST LIKE TO BE LEFT
BUT THE BEST THING ABOUT
ALONE, AND THAT'S FINE, TOO.
FRIENDSHIP IS BEING ABLE TO MAKE
BUT THE BEST THING ABOUT
YOUR FRIENDS SMILE."
FRIENDSHIP IS BEING ABLE TO MAKE
♪ HE HAD A CRANKY DOODLE
YOUR FRIENDS SMILE."
SWEETHEART ♪
♪ HE HAD A CRANKY DOODLE
♪ SHE'S HIS CRANKY DOODLE JOY ♪
SWEETHEART ♪
♪ I AM THE CRANKY DOODLE BOY ♪
♪ SHE'S HIS CRANKY DOODLE JOY ♪
♪ YES, I AM THE CRANKY DOODLE
♪ I AM THE CRANKY DOODLE BOY ♪
BOY ♪
♪ YES, I AM THE CRANKY DOODLE
Both: PINKIE!
BOY ♪
WHOOPS! PRIVACY.
Both: PINKIE!
SORRY!
[ "YANKEE DOODLE DANDY" PLAYS ]