[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]
[ PONIES CHEERING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
CAN YOU BELIEVE
FEATHERWEIGHT GOT
HIS CUTIE MARK?
FEATHERWEIGHT -- BEFORE US!
[ CHEERING ]
GREAT CUTIE MARK,
FEATHERWEIGHT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
LOOKING GOOD!
[ BOTH SIGH ]
I GIVE UP.
I'VE GOT IT!
[ SPROING! ]
THE ANSWER TO ALL OUR PROBLEMS!
THE "FOAL FREE PRESS"?
HOW'S THE SCHOOL PAPER GONNA GET
US OUR CUTIE MARKS?
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
MOVE YOUR CABOOSE!
UH-OH.
THAT'S GRANNY SMITH.
GOTTA RUN!
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING TO
THIS NEWSPAPER IDEA.
I GUESS IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
[ TINKLE! ]
[ SLUMP! ]
[ TING! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ BUBBLING ]
APPLE BLOOM, YOUR NEWSPAPER
IDEA WAS NOTHING BUT A BIG BUST.
WE TRIED EVERYTHING FROM
PAPER-MACHE TO MAKING BIRDS'
NESTS AND NOTHING WORKED.
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
WHAT I MEANT WAS WE SHOULD
WRITE FOR THE PAPER.
WE CAN GET OUR CUTIE MARKS AS
JOURNALISTS!
[ BOTH SIGH ]
[ THUD! ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART ♪
♪ FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
OKAY, CLASS, SEE YOU TOMORROW!
OH, FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO WANT TO
JOIN THE NEWSPAPER STAFF,
STAY HERE BECAUSE WE'RE
MEETING RIGHT NOW!
CUTIE MARKS IN JOURNALISM.
SUCH A GOOD IDEA!
WELCOME, EVERYPONY!
NOW, AS YOU KNOW, OUR EDITOR IN
CHIEF GRADUATED LAST YEAR.
OH! OH! OH!
OH-WO-WO-WO-WO!
YES?
WHAT'S AN EDITOR IN CHIEF?
GOOD QUESTION, SWEETIE BELLE.
I LIKE THOSE REPORTER'S
INSTINCTS.
THE "FOAL FREE PRESS" IS A
STUDENT-RUN PAPER.
I'M ONLY INVOLVED AS AN ADVISOR,
SO THE EDITOR IN CHIEF IS THE
PONY IN CHARGE, FROM CHOOSING
THE STORIES TO MAKING SURE IT
GETS TO PRESS ON TIME.
NOW, AS I SAID, WE HAVE A NEW
EDITOR THIS YEAR.
All: DIAMOND TIARA?!
HMM!
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE NOW TO
DISCUSS EVERYPONY'S ASSIGNMENTS.
HAVE FUN!
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
ALL RIGHT! LISTEN UP!
[ THUD! ]
THE "FOAL FREE PRESS" IS A JOKE.
All: HUH?
NO PONY AT THIS SCHOOL TAKES
IT SERIOUSLY.
WELL, I, THE EDITOR IN CHIEF IN
CHARGE, AM GONNA DELIVER US TO
NEWFOUND GLORY!
YAY!
FIRST THINGS FIRST -- WHERE'S
THE STAFF PHOTOGRAPHER?
[ POINK! ]
GET OUT THERE AND DOCUMENT
EVERYTHING!
[ RATTLE! ]
I'LL DECIDE WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
THE REST OF YOU, I WANT
HARD-HITTING NEWS AND
INTERESTING THINK PIECES.
NO MORE NAMBY-PAMBY STORIES LIKE
LAST YEAR'S EDITOR.
BUT NAMBY PAMBY WAS A GREAT
EDITOR.
WELL, THERE'S A NEW REGIME
NOW, AND I WANT JUICY STORIES --
THE JUICIER THE BETTER!
NOW GET OUT THERE AND REPORT!
[ THUD! ]
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE, GIRLS.
MAYBE WE CAN TRY PACKING BOXES
AGAIN.
BUT THIS COULD BE OUR LAST
CHANCE TO EARN OUR CUTIE MARKS.
IF WE REALLY ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
JOURNALISTS, ISN'T IT WORTH A
LITTLE GRIEF?
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE CAN TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF
DIAMOND TIARA FOR A LIFETIME OF
CUTIE MARKS.
COME ON!
LET'S GO GET THOSE MARKS!
MY FIRST STORY'S GONNA BE AN
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW.
[ POINK! POINK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHIFFLE! ]
[ TINKLE! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ SLINK! ]
I SAW A BRAND-NEW NEST OF
BABY BIRDS THE OTHER DAY.
I BET OUR READERS WOULD EAT UP A
SWEET STORY LIKE THAT!
[ SPLAT! ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
GRANNY SMITH HAS ALL SORTS OF
GREAT STORIES.
I RECKON I'LL DO A PIECE ON THE
HISTORY OF PONYVILLE.
[ CLATTER! ]
[ SLINK! ]
[ TYPEWRITERS CLACKING ]
I HOPE YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING
BECAUSE EVERYTHING SO FAR IS
UNUSABLE.
[ WHIP! ]
"BABY BIRDS BORN"?
"RARITY'S HOT, NEW HAT"?
"PONYVILLE: THE EARLY YEARS"?!
UGH!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU CALL THIS,
BUT IT SURE ISN'T NEWS!
WE JUST THOUGHT...
GET SOMETHING ELSE ON MY DESK
BY THE END OF THE DAY!
AND IT BETTER BE JUICY!
[ THUD! ]
[ TWEET! ]
[ WHIP! WHIP! ]
NOW WHAT?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I HAD TO DO
TO GET THAT STORY?
OH, YOU DON'T EVEN WANT TO
KNOW WHAT I HAD TO SIT THROUGH.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
[ ZIP! ]
OH, GET IT OFF ME, SNAILS!
EH, YOU GET IT OFF ME, SNIPS.
AAH! STOP IT!
YOU ARE MAKING IT WORSE!
[ BLINK! ]
[ CREAK! ]
YAH!
[ SQUISH! ]
AH, GREAT.
I'LL GET IT.
[ GROANS ]
AAH!
GET IT OFF!
GET IT OFF!!
[ GIGGLES ]
HEY, FEATHERWEIGHT, COME HERE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
TAKE A FEW PICTURES OF THIS.
THEN MEET ME DURING LUNCH.
[ ZIP! ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
GIRLS, I HAVE OUR STORY!
"SNIPS AND SNAILS AND BUBBLEGUM
VEILS" -- AND THAT'S WHEN THE
BIGGEST JOKESTER IN SCHOOL
REALLY STUCK HIS HOOF IN IT,
LITERALLY!
THE "FOAL FREE PRESS" IS
USUALLY JUST BORING NEWS AND
STUFF.
SO FUNNY!
OUR MOTHERS ALWAYS TOLD US
WE'D END UP IN THE PAPER SOME
DAY.
YEAH. HEY, LOOK!
WE FINALLY GOT THE GUM OUT!
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOUR COLUMN IS A SENSATION!
I DON'T WANT YOU DOING NEWS
ANYMORE.
I WANT MORE COLUMNS LIKE THIS --
COLUMNS ABOUT PONIES AND THEIR
PRIVATE LIVES, THE THINGS THEY
DO WHEN THEY THINK THEY'RE
ALONE...
YOU THREE OUR MY NEW GOSSIP
COLUMNISTS!
[ TWINKLE! ]
AND I LOVE THE WAY YOU SIGNED
IT.
"GABBY GUMS" -- THAT WAS A
STROKE OF GENIUS!
WE COULDN'T FIT ALL OF OUR
NAMES, SO WE DECIDED TO CREATE
ONE FOR ALL THREE OF US.
WELL, I WANT MORE GABBY GUMS!
NICE WORK, GIRLS.
BUT WE SURE SEEM TO HAVE A
GIFT FOR GOSSIP.
IF WE CAN WRITE A FEW MORE OF
THESE GABBY GUMS COLUMNS, WE'LL
EARN OUR CUTIE MARKS FOR SURE!
All: WHOO-HOO!
[ SMACK! ]
SCOOTALOO, DO YOU HAVE
ANYTHING?
NO.
APPLE BLOOM?
[ SIGHS ] SORRY.
LET'S FACE IT.
NOTHING VERY JUICY HAPPENS
AT THIS SCHOOL.
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
[ SNAP! ]
WE'RE DOOMED.
♪♪
[ TINKLE! ]
[ THUD! ]
OOH!
SWEETIE BELLE -- WAS SHE RAISED
IN A BARN OR SOMETHING?
[ GASPS ]
[ DING! ]
OOH, YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T BE
SNOOPING, RARITY.
OH, BUT IT'S SO MUCH FUN,
RARITY.
HELLO.
WHAT'S THIS?
[ CHUCKLES ]
GUM ON THEIR BUM!
[ LAUGHS ]
TOO RICH!
CAN YOU PLEASE KEEP IT DOWN
WITH ALL THE LAUGHTER!
I'M TRYING TO --
[ POINK! ]
HEY!
EH!
I-I WAS JUST --
ARE YOU SNOOPING THROUGH MY
SADDLEBAG?
[ WHIP! ]
[ SPROING! ]
HOW DARE YOU?!
OH, BUT THIS GABBY GUMS
COLUMN IS SO FUNNY!
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU ACTUALLY LIKE THE SCHOOL
PAPER?
IT'S SO MUCH JUICIER THAN
ANYTHING IN THE BORING OLD
"PONYVILLE EXPRESS."
[ GASPS ]
COULD I BORROW THIS TO SHOW MY
FRIENDS?
YOUR FRIENDS WOULD WANT
TO READ THE "FOAL FREE PRESS"?
OH, THEY JUST LOVE
GABBY GUMS!
[ PLINK! ]
WHO IS SHE, ANYWAY?
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF HER BEFORE.
IS SHE A NEW...
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
WE GAVE UP TOO QUICKLY,
GIRLS.
FORGET TRYING TO SQUEEZE STORIES
OUT OF THIS SCHOOL.
WE NEED TO EXPAND!
WE COULD FIND ALL KINDS OF
GREAT GOSSIP OUT THERE IN
PONYVILLE!
WE'LL NEED TO TELL
FEATHERWEIGHT TO START WORKING
OVERTIME.
SWEETIE BELLE, YOU'RE A
GENIUS!
[ PONIES SOBBING ]
"POUND AND PUMPKIN CAKE: TRIP
TO THE STORE ENDS IN TEARS."
GABBY GUMS COMES THROUGH AGAIN!
[ PANTING ]
THE PONYVILLE NEWSSTAND WANTS TO
CARRY THE "FOAL FREE PRESS"!
PONIES KEEP COMING BY AND ASKING
FOR IT.
SEND THEM 20 COPIES.
AND IF THEY RUN OUT OF THOSE,
WE'LL SEND THEM 20 MORE!
YOU THREE ARE DOING A GREAT JOB
FOR THIS PAPER.
KEEP THOSE COLUMNS COMING!
THIS IS GREAT!
[ SMACK! ]
[ DING! ]
[ SQUIRT! ]
[ THUD! ]
[ SIGHS ]
THIS IS THE LIFE, ISN'T IT,
GIRLS?
THE BEST HOOFICURE I'VE EVER
HAD.
[ Shaking ] YOU SAID IT. UH.
[ SIGHS ]
I DON'T KNOW IF I'VE EVER BEEN
SO RELAXED.
YOU GUYS!
AAH!
[ BLOOP! ]
THE NEW GABBY GUMS JUST CAME
OUT!
"THE GREAT AND POWERFUL TRIXIE'S
SECRETS REVEALED"!
WE ALREADY READ THAT ONE,
RAINBOW DASH.
COME ON, RELAX.
HAVE A HOOFICURE.
IT FEELS AMAZING.
[ GULP! ]
DID YOU FORGET WHO YOU'RE
TALKING TO?
THE DAY I GET A HOOFICURE IS THE
DAY I TURN IN MY DAREDEVIL
LICENSE.
BESIDES, I HAVEN'T READ THIS
GABBY GUMS, YET.
WELL, DO IT QUIETLY, WILL
YA?
[ SIGHS ]
SOME OF US ARE TRYING TO UNWIND.
I LIKE GABBY GUMS, TOO, BUT
DON'T YOU THINK SHE CAN BE A
LITTLE MEAN?
SHE'S NOT MEAN, TWILIGHT.
SHE'S A HOOT!
"CELESTIA JUST LIKE US"?
GABBY GUMS DOESN'T VALUE
ANYPONY'S PRIVACY.
OH, LIGHTEN UP, TWILIGHT.
IT'S NOTHING BUT HARMLESS
GOSSIP.
YEAH, TWILIGHT.
I MEAN, LISTEN TO THIS ONE!
[ SPLASH! ]
"MAYOR NOT NATURALLY GREAT" --
THE MAYOR IN A MANE-DYEING
SCANDAL?
WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO READ THAT?
I JUST CAN'T HELP FEELING
SORRY FOR THE PONIES FEATURED IN
HER COLUMNS.
IT'S GOT TO BE A LITTLE
EMBARRASSING.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
DO YOU KNOW HOW AWESOME IT IS TO
GET YOUR NAME IN THE PAPER?
RAINBOW, WHY DON'T YOU JOIN
ME IN ONE OF THESE DELICIOUS
HOOFICURES?
IT'S THAT GOOD, HUH?
WELL, MAYBE JUST ONE LITTLE
HOOF.
[ RATTLE! ]
AAH!
FORGET IT.
I DON'T LIKE PONIES TOUCHING MY
HOOVES.
[ ZIP! ]
MAN, I'D LOVE IT IF GABBY GUMS
DID A STORY ON ME.
SHE DID ONE ON ME.
[ ZIP! ]
All: WHAT?!
WAAH!
"EXCLUSIVE: LOCAL DRAGON
TELLS ALL"!
SPIKE OPENS UP ABOUT
CANTERLOT, NAPS, AND HIS
FAVORITE JAMS.
IT'S OUR BEST COLUMN YET!
MORE LIKE YOUR WORST COLUMN
YET!
GABBY GUMS DIDN'T BECOME THE
BIGGEST THING IN PONYVILLE WITH
NAMBY-PAMBY STORIES LIKE THIS!
[ SIGHS ]
YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
THIS COLUMN IS A LITTLE SOFTER
THAN OUR USUAL GOSSIP.
WERE YOU GUYS FEELING GUILTY
ABOUT ALL THE GOSSIP, TOO?
LIKE, MAYBE WE COULD BE HURTING
OTHER PONIES' FEELINGS?
YEAH.
I DIDN'T WANT TO SAY ANYTHING
BECAUSE EVERYPONY LOVES
GABBY GUMS SO MUCH, BUT I WAS
SORT OF HOPING WE COULD START
WRITING MORE STORIES LIKE THIS
ONE.
ME TOO.
IF WE'RE GONNA GET OUR
CUTIE MARKS, WE'VE GOT TO GIVE
THE PONIES WHAT THEY WANT.
All: AW.
[ SMACK! ]
"APPLEJACK ASLEEP ON THE JOB."
CAN Y'ALL BELIEVE THIS?
AND THIS ONE -- "BIG MACINTOSH:
WHAT'S HE HIDING?"
WHO THE HAY DOES THIS GABBY GUMS
THINKS SHE IS?
LISTEN TO THIS ONE --
"TWILIGHT SPARKLE: I WAS A
CANTERLOT SNOB."
"A WELL-PLACED SCALY SOURCE
CLOSE TO THE PRISSY PONY SAYS,
'TWILIGHT SPARKLE THINKS
PONYVILLE IS NOTHING BUT MUDDY
ROADS AND LOW-CLASS RUDES.'"
SPIKE.
[ BURP! ]
HOW COULD YOU SAY SUCH A THING?
WELL, I-I DIDN'T!
GABBY GUMS MADE THAT UP!
I NEVER SAID ANYTHING LIKE THAT!
EVERYPONY, PLEASE.
SHE'S JUST A HARMLESS SCHOOL
PONY ENGAGED IN A LITTLE IDOL
GOSSIP.
YOU'RE REALLY MAKING TOO BIG A
DEAL OUT OF THIS.
BUT IT'S ALL LIES.
GABBY GUMS PRINTS WHATEVER SHE
WANTS.
SHE DOESN'T CARE WHOSE
REPUTATION SHE DESTROYS.
"FLUTTERSHY HAS TAIL
EXTENSIONS."
[ SLUMP! ]
"PINKIE PIE IS AN OUT-OF-CONTROL
PARTY ANIMAL."
WHAT?!
IT'S TRUE!
I DO HAVE A PROBLEM!
[ CRYING ]
OH, LOOK.
ACCORDING TO THIS ONE, THE CAKES
ARE BREAKING UP.
WE ARE?!
[ CRASH! ]
WELL, MY LIFE IS OFFICIALLY
OVER.
GABBY GUMS HAS MADE IT TO
CLOUDSDALE.
"RAINBOW DASH: SPEED DEMON OR
SUPER SOFTY?"
I GRABBED AS MANY COPIES AS I
COULD, BUT IT WAS TOO LATE!
I'M A LAUGHINGSTOCK!
SEE, RARITY.
YOUR SO-CALLED HARMLESS GOSSIP
CAN BE VERY HURTFUL.
HONESTLY, YOU PONIES HAVE NO
SENSE OF HUMOR.
SO SHE TWEAKS A FEW PONIES
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
MAYBE THEY DESER--
[ GASPS ]
I'LL DESTROY HER!!
"THE DRAMA QUEEN DIARIES" --
SHE'S REPRINTED MY DIARY!
HOW COULD GABBY GUMS POSSIBLY
GET ACCESS TO MY PRIVATE DIARY?!
WE'VE GOT TO PUT A STOP TO
THIS ONCE AND FOR ALL.
SWEETIE BELLE'S ON THE NEWSPAPER
STAFF.
MAYBE SHE KNOWS WHO GABBY GUMS
IS.
[ GASPS ]
MY SISTER WOULD NEVER ASSOCIATE
WITH SOMEONE AS BEASTLY AS
GABBY GUMS!
I RESENT YOU EVEN SUGGESTING
SUCH A THING, TWILIGHT!
WHY, SHE'S THE MOST INNOCENT,
MOST LOVELY...
MOST EVIL PONY IN EQUESTRIA!
HOW COULD MY OWN SISTER STEAL MY
PRIVATE DIARY?
HOW COULD MY OWN SISTER BE...
GABBY GUMS?
[ THUD! ]
ET TU, GABBY GUMS?
[ GASPS ] YOU KNOW?
HOW'D YOU FIND OUT?
LOOK IN THE PAGES OF YOUR
BETRAYAL!
OH, YEAH.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME?
YOU STOLE MY SECRET DIARY AND
PUBLISHED IT FOR ALL THE WORLD
TO READ.
GOSSIP CAN BE A VERY HURTFUL
THING.
IT IS AN INVASION OF PRIVACY,
JUST LIKE WHEN I SNOOPED THROUGH
YOUR SADDLEBAG.
YOU DIDN'T LIKE THAT MUCH,
DID YOU?
NO.
WHAT IS IMPORTANT IS THAT YOU
UNDERSTAND HOW YOUR COLUMN MAKES
THE PONIES THAT YOU'RE WRITING
ABOUT FEEL.
I DO UNDERSTAND, AND WE'VE
ALL BEEN FEELING GUILTY.
BUT WE JUST WANT OUR CUTIE MARKS
SO BADLY.
DO YOU REALLY THINK THAT
WRITING NASTY THINGS AND MAKING
EVERYPONY FEEL HORRIBLE IS YOUR
DESTINY?
WELL, WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT
WAY...
NO!
I WON'T LET YOU QUIT!
BUT THE GOSSIP WE'VE BEEN
PRINTING IS HURTING EVERYPONY'S
FEELINGS!
FEELINGS?!
I DON'T CARE ABOUT FEELINGS!
GABBY GUMS IS MY BREAD AND
BUTTER, AND I'M NOT GONNA LET
YOU GOODY-TWO-HORSESHOES TAKE
THAT AWAY FROM ME!
WE'RE SORRY, DIAMOND TIARA,
BUT WE'VE MADE OUR DECISION.
YEAH, YOU CAN'T FORCE US TO
KEEP GOSSIPING.
WHEN YOU SEE THESE...
YOU MAY NOT WANT TO QUIT AFTER
ALL.
[ WHIRL! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
I TOLD FEATHERWEIGHT TO DOCUMENT
EVERYTHING.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT HE DID.
[ GASPS ] GIVE ME THOSE!
SORRY, GIRLS -- PROPERTY OF
THE "FOAL FREE PRESS."
AND IF GABBY GUMS REALLY DOES GO
INTO RETIREMENT, I'LL NEED
SOMETHING TO FILL THAT EMPTY
COLUMN SPACE.
NOW, GET OUT THERE AND BRING ME
MORE GABBY GUMS!
WE'LL FIND A WAY OUT OF THIS,
GIRLS.
MAYBE RAINBOW DASH WILL HAVE
A STORY FOR US.
SHE'S ALWAYS GOOD FOR SOME
GOSSIP.
RAINBOW DASH!
HEY, RAINBOW DASH!
WELL, IF IT ISN'T GABBY GUMS.
YOU HEARD, TOO, HUH?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
EVERYPONY IN TOWN KNOWS IT'S YOU
THREE.
DON'T SUPPOSE YOU'LL LET US
WRITE A COLUMN ON YOU, HUH?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CRYING ]
OH, HI, ANGEL.
IS FLUTTERSHY HOME?
[ THUD! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
HEY, WHAT GIVES?
AHA!
TWILIGHT THOUGHT YOU MIGHT TRY
TO SHOW YOUR FACES AROUND HERE,
SO SHE PUT UP A FORCE FIELD.
OH, COME ON, APPLEJACK.
YOU'RE NOT MAD AT US, TOO,
ARE YOU?
YUP.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GONNA
TALK TO US?
NOPE.
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF
YOURSELF, HUMILIATING YOUR
SISTER AND ME LIKE THAT.
WE DON'T WANT TO TALK TO ANY OF
Y'ALL RIGHT NOW, SO TAKE YOUR
LITTLE GOSSIP COLUMN AND YOUR
EMBARRASSING PHOTOGRAPHS AND
JUST GO AWAY!
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
[ SHUTTERS SLAM ]
WE'VE RUINED ALL OF OUR
FRIENDSHIPS, AND WE STILL DON'T
HAVE OUR CUTIE MARKS.
THIS IS THE WORST DAY EVER.
OH, YEAH?
WAIT TILL TOMORROW -- OUR MOST
EMBARRASSING MOMENTS ARE ABOUT
TO BE PUBLISHED FOR EVERYPONY TO
LAUGH AT.
SO WHAT DO WE DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT WE'RE NOT LEAVING THIS
CLUBHOUSE UNTIL WE THINK OF
SOMETHING.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
THAT'S IT!
GABBY GUMS IS OUT OF TIME.
RUN THESE INSTEAD!
I WANT THIS PAPER ON EVERY
STREET CORNER IN PONYVILLE!
YES, MA'AM.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
STOP THE PRESSES!
UH...THEY HAVEN'T STARTED
YET.
WE HAVE A GABBY GUMS COLUMN!
HMM.
YOU'RE LUCKY I'M NICE.
[ WHIP! ]
THIS BETTER NOT HAPPEN AGAIN, OR
ELSE.
[ DING! ]
[ SIGHS ]
WELL DONE, DIAMOND TIARA.
YOU'VE AVERTED YET ANOTHER
CRISIS WITH YOUR AMAZING
DIPLOMATIC SKILLS.
[ GASPS ]
"AN OPEN LETTER TO PONYVILLE BY
GABBY GUMS"?!
WHAT IS THIS?!
OOH, THEY'RE NOT GONNA GET AWAY
WITH THIS!
I'LL PUBLISH THOSE PHOTOS
TOMORROW!
THEY MESSED WITH THE WRONG PONY.
"TO THE CITIZENS OF
PONYVILLE -- FOR SOME TIME NOW,
YOU'VE BEEN READING THIS COLUMN
TO GET THE LATEST DIRT AND THE
HOTTEST BUZZ, BUT THIS WILL BE
MY FINAL PIECE.
WE WANT TO APOLOGIZE FOR THE
PAIN AND EMBARRASSMENT
WE'VE CAUSED."
"YOU SEE, I'M ACTUALLY THREE
LITTLE FILLIES -- SWEETIE BELLE,
APPLE BLOOM, AND SCOOTALOO."
[ ZIP! ]
"AS THE POPULARITY OF OUR
COLUMN GREW, WE GOT SWEPT UP IN
THE HYPE.
WE KNEW THAT WHAT WE WERE DOING
DIDN'T FEEL QUITE RIGHT, BUT WE
IGNORED THE GUILT BECAUSE
EVERYPONY SEEMED TO WANT TO READ
WHAT WE WERE WRITING."
"FROM NOW ON, WE PROMISE TO
RESPECT EVERYPONY ELSE'S PRIVACY
AND WE WON'T ENGAGE IN HURTFUL
GOSSIP ANYMORE."
"ALL WE CAN DO IS ASK FOR
YOUR FORGIVENESS, PONYVILLE.
SIGNING OFF FOR THE VERY LAST
TIME -- XOXO, GABBY GUMS."
WELL, STAFF, I GUESS I GAVE A
LITTLE TOO MUCH AUTHORITY TO A
FIRST-TIME EDITOR.
I'M SORRY, DIAMOND TIARA.
I HAVE TO STRIP YOU OF YOUR
TITLE.
[ THUD! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AND FOR THE NEXT EDITOR OF
THE "FOAL FREE PRESS"...
PBHT!
HERE'S YOUR NEW EDITOR IN
CHIEF...
FEATHERWEIGHT!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
[ CLACK! ]
[ SCOFFS ] HIM?!
BUT WHAT ABOUT ME?
HERE YOU GO!
I'VE BEEN PROMOTED TO STAFF
PHOTOGRAPHER.
[ WARBLE! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪