I WANT TO START
OUR FIELD TRIP HERE,
IN THE WORLD-FAMOUS
CANTERLOT SCULPTURE GARDEN.
THAT ONE OVER THERE
REPRESENTS FRIENDSHIP.
[ BONK! BONK! BONK! ]
[ TWEET! TWEET! TWEET! ]
ALL RIGHT,
MY LITTLE PONIES.
THIS ONE REPRESENTS
VICTORY.
HOW COOL WOULD IT BE TO HAVE
THAT FOR A CUTIE MARK?
COOL!
IF YOU WERE ACTUALLY
VICTORYFUL AT SOMETHIN'.
THAT'S NOT A WORD!
WHAT ARE YOU,
A DICTIONARY?
GIRLS! NOW, THIS IS
A REALLY INTERESTING STATUE.
WHAT DO YOU NOTICE
ABOUT IT?
IT'S GOT
AN EVIL CLAW!
AND A LION PAW!
AND A SNAKE TAIL!
THIS CREATURE IS CALLED
A DRACONAQUIS.
HE IS THE HEAD OF A PONY
AND A BODY MADE UP
OF ALL SORTS OF THINGS.
WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
THAT REPRESENTS?
CONFUSION!
EVIL!
CHAOS!
IT'S NOT CHAOS,
YOU DODO.
DON'T CALL ME THINGS
I DON'T KNOW THE MEANING OF.
AND IT IS TOO CHAOS.
IS NOT!
YOU'RE BOTH WRONG.
[ GRUNTING, SHOUTING ]
CHAOS!
CHAOS ISN'T ANY --
IT'S NOT RIGHT!
ACTUALLY, IN A WAY,
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
THIS STATUE REPRESENTS
DISCORD,
WHICH MEANS A LACK OF HARMONY
BETWEEN PONIES.
IN FACT, YOU THREE HAVE
DEMONSTRATED DISCORD SO WELL
THAT YOU'RE EACH GOING TO WRITE
ME AN ESSAY EXPLAINING IT.
[ GIGGLING ]
NOW LET'S GO. AND I DON'T WANT
ANY MORE FIGHTING.
It's confusion!
Evil!
Chaos!
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ ZIP! ]
COME BACK HERE, YOU!
GOTCHA!
EW! WHAT IS THIS?
[ SLURP! ]
[ SMACKS LIPS ]
COTTON CANDY?
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ DRIP! ]
WAIT A SECOND!
IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO RAIN
UNTIL TOMORROW.
YOU CAN'T JUST --
YOU DID.
HEY! I DIDN'T
TELL YOU TO GO ANYWHERE.
RAINBOW DASH,
WHAT'S GOING WITH THIS RAIN --
I MEAN,
CHOCOLATE MILK --
CHOCOLATE-MILK-RAIN.
THERE'S CRAZY WEATHER
ALL OVER EQUESTRIA.
CLOUDSDALE'S GETTING SOAKED BY
A MAJOR COLA STORM RIGHT NOW.
BUT DON'T WORRY --
I'M LEAVING YOU TILL
I GET CONTROL OF PONYVILLE.
[ POP! POP! POP! POP! ]
Pinkie Pie: WHY WOULD YOU
WANT TO STOP THIS?
[ SLURP! ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
I HEARD ABOUT YOUR TROUBLES,
APPLEJACK,
AND I CAME TO SEE
IF THERE'S
ANYTHING I CAN DO --
WITHOUT GETTING WET.
OR DIRTY.
OR OUT FROM UNDER MY UMBRELLA.
[ TING! TING! ]
[ CHOMP! ]
Applejack:
FLUTTERSHY, DO SOMETHING!
NOW, ANGEL,
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T --
NO! IT'S NOT POSSIBLE!
[ GASPS ]
I MUST BE SEEING THINGS!
DON'T WORRY, EVERYONE.
I'VE LEARNED A NEW SPELL
THAT'LL FIX EVERYTHING.
[ TINKLING ]
MY FAILSAFE SPELL...
FAILED!
WHAT DO WE DO?
UH, GIVE UP?
SPIKE, TWILIGHT WILL
COME UP WITH SOMETHING.
HMM.
TIME FOR PLAN "B."
RAINBOW, CAN YOU
CORRAL ALL THOSE CLOUDS
IN ONE CORNER OF THE SKY?
[ ZIP! ]
APPLEJACK, I NEED YOU TO BRING
THOSE HIGH-STRUNG STORM CLOUDS
DOWN TO EARTH.
[ WHIRL! ]
[ SQUISH! ]
[ GULP! ]
HEY! WHAT HAPPENED?
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ WHISPERING ]
OH, DEAR.
I HOPE THAT
NONE OF THE ANIMALS SEE THESE
DELICIOUS CHOCOLATE-FILLED
COTTON CANDY CLOUDS.
I'D HATE
TO HAVE TO SHARE THEM.
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
AH! YOU AND ME BOTH, SISTER.
[ WHOOSH! ]
HEY!
[ SLURPING ]
HEY, WHEN Y'ALL
ARE DONE THAT,
FEEL FREE TO HAVE
SOME POPCORN FOR DESSERT.
YOU SEE, SPIKE?
YOU SHOULD NEVER GIVE UP.
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN'T
OVERCOME IF ALL WORK TOGETHER.
[ BELCH! ]
[ GASPS ]
COME ON, GIRLS.
PRINCESS CELESTIA WANTS TO SEE
US ALL IN CANTERLOT IMMEDIATELY.
PRINCESS CELESTIA,
WE CAME AS FAST AS WE COULD.
THANK YOU, TWILIGHT.
THANK YOU ALL.
IS THIS ABOUT THE WEATHER
AND THE ANIMALS' WEIRD BEHAVIOR?
WHAT'S HAPPENING OUT THERE?
WHY ISN'T MY MAGIC WORKING?
IS THERE --
FOLLOW ME.
I'VE CALLED YOU HERE FOR
A MATTER OF GREAT IMPORTANCE.
IT SEEMS
AN OLD FOE OF MINE,
SOMEONE I THOUGHT I HAD DEFEATED
LONG AGO, HAS RETURNED.
HIS NAME IS DISCORD.
[ SQUEALS ]
DISCORD IS THE MISCHIEVOUS
SPIRIT OF DISHARMONY.
BEFORE MY SISTER AND I
STOOD UP TO HIM,
HE RULED EQUESTRIA IN AN ETERNAL
STATE OF UNREST AND UNHAPPINESS.
LUNA AND I SAW
HOW MISERABLE LIFE WAS
FOR EARTHPONIES, PEGASI,
AND UNICORNS ALIKE.
SO AFTER DISCOVERING
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY,
WE COMBINED OUR POWERS
AND ROSE UP AGAINST HIM,
TURNING HIM TO STONE.
ALL RIGHT, PRINCESS!
I THOUGHT
THE SPELL WE CAST
WOULD KEEP HIM CONTAINED
FOREVER,
BUT SINCE LUNA AND I
ARE NO LONGER
CONNECTED TO THE ELEMENTS,
THE SPELL
HAS BEEN BROKEN.
NO LONGER CONNECTED?
THIS IS CANTERLOT TOWER,
WHERE THE ELEMENTS
ARE KEPT INSIDE,
SINCE ALL OF YOU
RECOVERED THEM.
I NEED YOU TO WIELD THE ELEMENTS
OF HARMONY ONCE AGAIN
AND STOP DISCORD
BEFORE HE THRUSTS ALL OF
EQUESTRIA INTO ETERNAL CHAOS.
BUT WHY US?
WHY DON'T YOU --
HEY, LOOK!
WE'RE FAMOUS!
YOU SIX SHOWED THE FULL
POTENTIAL OF THE ELEMENTS
BY HARNESSING THE MAGIC OF YOUR
FRIENDSHIP TO BEAT A MIGHTY FOE.
ALTHOUGH LUNA AND I
ONCE WIELDED THE ELEMENTS,
IT IS YOU
WHO NOW CONTROL THEIR POWER,
AND IT IS YOU
WHO MUST DEFEAT DISCORD.
PRINCESS CELESTIA,
YOU CAN COUNT ON --
HOLD ON A SECOND!
ETERNAL CHAOS COMES WITH
CHOCOLATE RAIN, YOU GUYS --
CHOCOLATE RAIN!
DON'T LISTEN TO HER,
PRINCESS.
WE'D BE HONORED TO USE
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY AGAIN.
[ TINKLING ]
[ CREAKING ]
OOOOH!
YOU CAN KEEP THE ELEMENTS.
I'LL TAKE THAT CASE!
HAVE NO FEAR, PONIES.
I HAVE TOTAL CONFIDENCE
THAT YOU WILL BE ABLE TO DEFEAT
DISCORD WITH THESE.
[ ALL GASP ]
OH, WELL.
IF ANYONE NEEDS ME,
I'LL BE OUTSIDE
IN THE CHOCOLATE PUDDLES
WITH A GIANT SWIZZLE STRAW.
THE ELEMENTS --
THEY'RE GONE!
THAT CHAMBER IS PROTECTED
BY A POWERFUL SPELL
THAT ONLY I CAN BREAK.
THIS DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
[ MANIACAL LAUGHTER ]
Discord:
[ Echoing ] MAKE SENSE?
OH, WHAT FUN IS THERE
IN MAKING SENSE?
DISCORD...
SHOW YOURSELF!
[ LAUGHS ]
DID YOU MISS ME, CELESTIA?
I MISSED YOU.
IT'S QUITE LONELY
BEING ENCASED IN STONE,
BUT YOU WOULDN'T KNOW THAT,
WOULD YOU,
BECAUSE I DON'T
TURN PONIES INTO STONE.
[ CLINK! CLINK! CLINK! ]
ENOUGH.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
WITH THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY?
WELL, I JUST BORROWED THEM
FOR A TEENSY LITTLE WHILE.
[ SNAPS FINGERS ]
YOU'LL NEVER GET AWAY
WITH THIS, DISCORD.
OH, I'D FORGOTTEN HOW GRIM
YOU CAN BE, CELESTIA.
IT'S REALLY QUITE BORING.
HEY! NOPONY
INSULTS THE PRINCESS!
UGH!
[ RATTLE! ]
OH, YOU MUST BE RAINBOW DASH,
FAMED FOR HER LOYALTY --
THE ELEMENT OF HARMONY
YOU REPRESENT.
THAT'S RIGHT!
I'LL ALWAYS BE LOYAL
TO THE PRINCESS.
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE WASTING OUR TIME
TALKING TO A TACKY WINDOW.
THE BEAUTIFUL RARITY,
REPRESENTING THE ELEMENT OF
GENEROSITY, IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN.
SO YOU KNOW WHO WE ARE.
BIG DEAL.
OH, I KNOW MUCH MORE THAN THAT,
HONEST APPLEJACK.
YOU SEEM TO KNOW
OUR STRENGTHS, TOO.
YES, TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
AND YOURS IS THE MOST POWERFUL
AND ELUSIVE ELEMENT -- MAGIC.
FLUTTERSHY'S IS KINDNESS,
AND PINKIE PIE'S IS A PERSONAL
FAVORITE OF MINE -- LAUGHTER.
[ GIGGLING ]
PINKIE!
[ LAUGHS ]
HE'S STANDING ON YOUR HEAD!
STOP STALLING, DISCORD.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
WITH THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY?
OH, SO BORING,
CELESTIA, REALLY.
FINE, I'LL TELL YOU,
BUT I'LL ONLY TELL YOU MY WAY.
TO RETRIEVE
YOUR MISSING ELEMENTS,
JUST MAKE SENSE
OF THIS CHANGE OF EVENTS.
TWISTS AND TURNS
ARE MY MASTER PLAN,
THEN FIND THE ELEMENTS
BACK WHERE YOU BEGAN.
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
CAN WE GO HOME NOW?
WHAT DO YOU RECKON
HE MEANT,
"TWISTS AND TURNS" AND
ENDING BACK WHERE WE STARTED?
"TWISTS AND TURNS."
"TWISTS AND TURNS"!
THAT'S IT!
I BET DISCORD HID THE ELEMENTS
IN THE PALACE LABYRINTH.
GOOD LUCK,
MY LITTLE PONIES.
THE FATE OF EQUESTRIA
IS IN YOUR HOOVES.
THANKS, PRINCESS.
WE WON'T LET YOU DOWN.
[ DISCORD LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
[ ALL GASP ]
DO...WE...
HAVE TO GO IN THERE?
NOPE! DOPEY DISCORD
FORGOT ABOUT THESE BABIES.
I'LL JUST
DO A QUICK FLY-OVER,
AND WE'LL HAVE THE ELEMENTS
IN NO TIME.
[ ZING! ]
AAH!
[ THUD! ]
MY WINGS!
AAH!
YOUR HORN!
MY HORN!
AAAH!
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
YOU SHOULD SEE
THE LOOKS ON YOUR FACES.
PRICELESS! [ LAUGHS ]
GIVE US
OUR WINGS AND HORNS BACK!
YOU'LL GET THEM BACK
IN GOOD TIME.
I SIMPLY TOOK THEM
TO ENSURE THERE'S NO CHEATING.
YOU SEE, THIS
IS THE FIRST RULE OF OUR GAME --
NO FLYING AND NO MAGIC.
THE FIRST RULE?
THE SECOND RULE IS,
EVERYPONY HAS TO PLAY,
OR THE GAME IS OVER AND I WIN.
GOOD LUCK, EVERYPONY!
[ LAUGHS ]
NEVER FEAR, GIRLS.
WE HAVE EACH OTHER.
YEAH.
LIKE TWILIGHT SAID,
THERE'S NOTHING
WE CAN'T OVERCOME
IF WE ALL STICK TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS.
LET'S DO THIS.
TOGETHER! TOGETHER!
[ ALL SCREAM ]
STAY CALM, GIRLS!
EVERYPONY,
HEAD TO THE MIDDLE
AS FAST AS YOU CAN,
AND WE'LL REGROUP THERE.
MOVING OUT!
SEE YOU
IN THE CENTER.
YEE-HAW!
SEE YOU GUYS THERE!
[ ZIP! ]
[ PANTING ]
WHAT'S THAT? WHO'S THERE?
GIRLS!!
WHAT IN TARNATION?
WHERE AM I?
[ PONK! ]
[ MANIACAL LAUGHTER ]
WHO ARE Y'ALL?
THE KEEPERS
OF THE GROVE OF TRUTH.
YOU MAY ASK US...
ONE QUESTION...
PAST, FUTURE, OR PRESENT.
BUT BE WARNED...
THAT THE TRUTH...
MAY NOT ALWAYS
BE PLEASANT.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I DON'T TRUST THIS PLACE
WORTH A HILL OF BEANS,
BUT I GOT A REAL BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS FELLA DISCORD.
WHAT'S GONNA COME
OF THIS HERE MISSION WE'RE ON?
FOR THE ANSWER
YOU SEEK...
GO AHEAD,
TAKE A PEEK.
I HOPE
I NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN!
ME TOO!
FINE!
IT'S SETTLED, THEN!
NO!
OUR FRIENDSHIP? OVER?
[ LAUGHS ]
IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
IT JUST CAN'T!
THAT JUST
CAN'T BE THE TRUTH.
WELL,
ALL THE TRUTH DOES...
IS MAKE YOUR HEART PAY.
Discord: SOMETIMES A LIE
IS EASIER TO TAKE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
APPLEJACK,
THANK GOODNESS!
I THOUGHT I HEARD VOICES
OVER HERE.
WHO WERE YOU TALKING TO?
I WAS TALKING TO,
UH, NOPONY.
NOPONY WHATSOEVER.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
COME ON.
UH, WE BEST BE GOING.
DID APPLEJACK JUST...
COME ON, TWILIGHT.
APPLEJACK WOULDN'T LIE.
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ WHISTLING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GIGGLES ] THIS IS THE GREATEST
BALLOON GARDEN I'VE EVER SEEN!
IT'S THE FIRST BALLOON GARDEN
I'VE EVER SEEN, BUT STILL!
WHA?!
[ SPLAT! ]
[ MOCKING LAUGHTER ]
HEY! WHAT GIVES?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
PINKIE PIE?
I THOUGHT YOU APPRECIATED
A GOOD LAUGH.
IT'S DIFFERENT.
THEY'RE LAUGHING AT ME.
IT'S HARD BEING DIFFERENT.
YOUR FRIENDS LAUGH AT YOU
ALL THE TIME.
MY FRIENDS LAUGH WITH ME,
NOT AT ME.
OH, REALLY?
[ MOCKING LAUGHTER ]
NO! STOP IT!
[ LAUGHTER CONTINUES ]
♪ HA-HA HA-HA-HA!
HA-HA HA-HA-HA! ♪
STOP LAUGHING AT ME!
OH, POOR PINKIE PIE.
AND HERE I THOUGHT
LAUGHTER MADE YOU HAPPY.
HAPPY?
I DON'T THINK SO.
[ POP! POP! POP! POP! POP! ]
PINKIE PIE!
ARE WE GLAD TO SEE YOU!
OH, YOU ARE, HUH?
WHY? NEED A GOOD LAUGH?!
PINKIE?
WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
HAS HER SO UPSET?
IT'S NOT LIKE HER.
I DIDN'T NOTICE ANYTHING
STRANGE ABOUT PINKIE.
WEIRD.
BETTER PICK UP THE PACE
BEFORE THE STRESS OF THIS
GETS THE BETTER OF ALL OF US.
Rarity: I WAS EXPECTING
AN AUDIENCE WITH THE PRINCESS,
NOT OUTDOOR SPORTS.
[ SMACK! ]
[ SQUEALS ] OH, MY...
[ DISCORD LAUGHS ]
WELCOME TO YOUR LUCKY DAY,
RARITY.
YOU FOUND THE ONE THING
IN EQUESTRIA
THAT COULD RIVAL MY FACE
FOR SHEER BEAUTY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU LIKE?
YES.
I LIKE VERY MUCH!
[ RATTLE! RATTLE! ]
NO! NO!
I SHAN'T SUCCUMB
TO SUCH FABULOUSNESS.
MUST...
GET TO THE CENTER...
TO MEET...
THE OTHERS!
[ ZIP! ]
MINE!
[ CRUMBLING ]
WELL, RARITY.
IT TOOK FOREVER,
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
WHO KNEW
THREE LITTLE GEMSTONES
WOULD TURN OUT TO BE THIS
HANDSOME HUNK OF A DIAMOND.
NOW TO GET YOU HOME.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CRUMBLES ]
RARITY!
ARE WE GLAD TO SEE --
WHY ARE YOU CARRYING
A HUMONGOUS BOULDER?
[ THUD! ]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
BOULDER?
THIS BIG, BEAUTIFUL,
BEDAZZLING ROCK IS A DIAMOND!
AND IT'S ALL MINE.
KEEP YOUR ENVIOUS
LITTLE EYES OFF IT!
I FOUND IT, AND IT'S MINE,
FAIR AND SQUARE!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ BOING! ]
OKAY, I CAN DO THIS.
I CAN -- AAAH!
WAIT A MINUTE!
BUTTERFLIES?
WAIT!
DON'T LEAVE ME HERE!
FLUTTERSHY, LOOKS LIKE
YOU'VE BEEN LEFT BEHIND
BY YOUR SO-CALLED
FRIENDS, HUH?
OH, NO.
I'M CERTAIN THEY'RE
DOING THEIR BEST TO FIND ME.
WELL, IT MUST BE
SO UPSETTING
TO KNOW HOW WEAK AND HELPLESS
THEY THINK YOU ARE.
NOT AT ALL.
I AM WEAK AND HELPLESS, AND I
APPRECIATE THEIR UNDERSTANDING.
YES, WELL,
I'M SURE IT BURNS YOU UP,
I MEAN, THAT THEY'RE ALWAYS
POINTING OUT YOUR FLAWS, RIGHT?
NOT REALLY.
IN FACT,
I THINK I'M AWFULLY LUCKY
TO HAVE FRIENDS WHO WANT ME
TO BE THE BEST I CAN BE.
OH, FOR GOODNESS' SAKE!
YOU'VE BEEN KIND
FOR FAR TOO LONG, MY DEAR.
TIME TO BE CRUEL!
ARRIVEDERCI!
FLUTTERSHY! I'M SO GLAD
TO SEE A FRIENDLY FACE.
THIS AWFUL LABYRINTH
IS GETTING TO EVERYPONY.
[ GROWLS ]
PBHT!
OH, BOO-HOO-HOO!
WHY DON'T YOU
WAVE YOUR MAGIC LITTLE HORN
AND MAKE EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT.
UH...
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T.
YOU DON'T HAVE ONE.
[ SLAP! ]
WHAT IS HAPPENING
TO MY FRIENDS?
[ LAUGHS ]
AND WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT?!
CHOCOLATE MILK?
[ GRUNTS ]
A LITTLE HELP HERE?
THANKS, TWILIGHT.
YOU'RE WELCOME --
BUT DON'T GET ANY IDEAS
ABOUT MY GEM.
I KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ]
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
I'VE GOT YOU NOW,
ELEMENT.
OH, I CAN SEE WHY YOU LIKE
THESE CLOUDS SO MUCH --
VERY PLUSH.
GET OFF THERE AND PUT 'EM UP!
COME ON! LET'S GO!
HEY, I'M HERE
TO DELIVER A MESSAGE.
I GOT A MESSAGE
FOR YOU, TOO!
LISTEN CLOSELY.
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
A WEIGHTY CHOICE
IS YOURS TO MAKE --
THE RIGHT SELECTION
OR A BIG MISTAKE.
IF THE WRONG CHOICE
YOU CHOOSE TO PURSUE,
THE FOUNDATIONS OF HOME
WILL CRUMBLE WITHOUT YOU.
[ SNAPS FINGERS ]
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
Rainbow Dash:
CLOUDSDALE...CRUMBLE...
WITHOUT ME.
NO!
THAT BOX
CONTAINS YOUR WINGS.
YOU CAN TAKE THEM
AND LEAVE THE GAME,
OR YOU CAN CARRY ON,
AIMLESSLY WANDERING THIS MAZE.
YOUR CHOICE.
Twilight Sparkle:
[ GRUNTS ]
MUST...FIND...
RAINBOW DASH.
AS A TEAM...
WE'RE UNSTOPPABLE.
RAINBOW DASH
WON'T LET US DOWN.
WELL, LOOKY THERE.
RAINBOW DASH IS FLYING AWAY.
SHE'S ABANDONING US.
NOW, I KNOW
THAT'S A LIE.
[ GASPS ]
HOW CAN IT BE?
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ CRUMBLING ]
Discord:
WELL, WELL, WELL.
SOMEPONY BROKE
THE "NO WINGS, NO MAGIC" RULE.
[ SNAPS FINGERS ]
GAME'S OVER,
MY LITTLE PONIES.
YOU DIDN'T FIND
YOUR PRECIOUS ELEMENTS.
LOOKS LIKE WE MIGHT BE DUE
FOR A BIG OL' STORM OF CHAOS.
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪