[ HOOVES CLOPPING ]
WHOO!
WHOA!
[ HOOVES CLOPPING ]
[ CREAK! ]
WHOO-HOO!
APPLEJACK, YOU'RE SURE TO KNOCK
EVERYPONY'S HEAD OFF AT THE
EQUESTRIA RODEO COMPETITION.
AW, SHUCKS, APPLE BLOOM.
I SURE HOPE SO.
HOPE SO? I KNOW SO!
AFTER ALL, YOU'RE THE 10-TIME
RODEO CHAMPION OF PONYVILLE.
WHY, YOU'VE GOT MORE BLUE
RIBBONS THAN ANY PONY IN
PONYVILLE -- EVER!
AND I CAN'T WAIT FOR MY BIG SIS
TO WIN EVERY BLUE RIBBON IN
EQUESTRIA AND BRING HOME THE
TITLE OF "EQUESTRIA RODEO
CHAMPION"!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
HUH?
NOW, CAREFUL, DERPY.
I DON'T WANT TO DO ANY MORE
DAMAGE THAN YOU'VE ALREADY DONE.
[ CREAK, CRASH! ]
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT WENT
WRONG!
[ ZAP! ]
YEAH. IT'S A MYSTERY.
NICE WORK, RAINBOW DASH!
[ CREAK! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ CRASH! ]
YOU OKAY, RAINBOW DASH?
ANYTHING I CAN DO TO HELP?
[ CLATTER ]
NO! NOTHING!
IN THE NAME OF CELESTIA, JUST
SIT THERE AND DO NOTHING.
[ CREAKING ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ CRASH! ]
MY BAD!
All: APPLEJACK! APPLEJACK!
APPLEJACK! APPLEJACK!
EVERYPONY, CAN I GET YOUR
ATTENTION?
ATTENTION, PLEASE!
YES, WE ARE ALL HERE TO SEND
APPLEJACK TO COMPETE IN THIS
YEAR'S EQUESTRIA RODEO
COMPETITION IN CANTERLOT.
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
AND I WANT TO THANK APPLEJACK IN
ADVANCE FOR GENEROUSLY OFFERING
UP HER PRIZE MONEY TO FIX TOWN
HALL.
[ CLATTER ]
YEAH, APPLEJACK! WHOO-HOO!
[ THUD ]
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
SPEECH! SPEECH!
AW, SHUCKS.
I'M NOT MUCH FOR SPEECHES.
ALL RIGHT, THEN. NO SPEECH.
BUT...THIS HERE IS THE NICEST
SEND-OFF ANYPONY COULD ASK FOR.
Y'ALL HAVE BEEN CHEERING ME ON
IN EVERY RODEO SINCE I WAS A
LITTLE, LITTLE PONY.
SO, IT SEEMS ONLY FITTING TO USE
MY WINNINGS TO FIX UP TOWN HALL.
I PROMISE TO MAKE PONYVILLE
PROUD!
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
[ BELL DINGS ]
I WANT YOU TO SHOW ALL THEM
HIGHFALUTIN RODEO PONIES WHAT A
REAL RODEO PONY'S LIKE.
YOU BETCHA, GRANNY SMITH.
AND BRING BACK ALL THAT
MONEY!
YOU BETCHA, MAYOR.
AND HAVE FUN!
AND DON'T BE NERVOUS!
OR, IF YOU ARE, USE THAT NERVOUS
ENERGY TO DO EVEN BETTER THAN
YOU ALREADY WOULD!
AND EAT PEANUTS AND POPCORN AND
TAFFY.
TAFFY GIVES YOU LOTS OF NERVOUS
ENERGY.
[ MUNCHING ]
JUST DO YOUR BEST, APPLEJACK.
I'LL DO BETTER THAN MY BEST.
THE TRAIN TO CANTERLOT IS
ABOUT TO LEAVE!
ALL ABOARD THAT'S COMING ABOARD!
GUESS THAT MEANS ME.
SEE YOU IN A WEEK!
WITH LOTS OF NEW BLUE
RIBBONS!
AND LOTS OF MONEY!
DARN TOOTIN'!
[ ENGINE CHUGS ]
SEE Y'ALL IN A WEEK -- WITH A
BIG BAG FULL OF BLUE RIBBONS!
All: BYE, APPLEJACK!
AND DRINK SARSAPARILLA!
WHAT? IT GIVES YOU EXTRA SASS.
OH, I HOPE APPLEJACK IS
SURPRISED BY THE SURPRISE PARTY.
WELL, THAT IS THE POINT.
I KNOW, BUT I HOPE SHE ISN'T
SO SURPRISED, SHE'S STARTLED,
BECAUSE, WHILE BEING SURPRISED
CAN BE NICE, BEING STARTLED CAN
BE VERY STARTLING.
SURPRISE!
[ GASPS ]
[ THUD ]
OH, PINKIE, YOU STARTLED ME.
SORRY!
I WAS JUST PRACTICING MY
SURPRISE FOR WHEN WE SURPRISE
APPLEJACK WITH THIS SUPER-COOL
PARTY FOR BECOMING RODEO
CHAMPION OF EQUESTRIA!
SURPRISE!
[ THUD ]
QUIET, PINKIE.
I THINK APPLEJACK'S COMING.
[ ZIP! ]
DON'T WORRY, TWILIGHT -- GOT
MY LIPS ALL LIMBERED UP.
PBHT!
[ GRINDS TEETH, SMOOCHES ]
[ CREAK, CREAK ]
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ CREAK ]
All: SURPRISE!
SURPRISE!
AW, SHOOT.
WOW!
THIS IS THE BEST SURPRISE EVER!
HOW DID YOU KNOW IT WAS MY
BIRTHDAY?
[ TINKLING ]
[ SLAM! ]
WHO'S IT FROM, TWILIGHT?
WHAT'S IT SAY?
IT'S FROM APPLEJACK.
"FAMILY AND FRIENDS, NOT COMING
BACK TO PONYVILLE.
DON'T WORRY -- WILL SEND MONEY
SOON."
THAT'S ALL THERE IS.
[ ALL GASP ]
APPLEJACK'S...NOT COMING
BACK?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, APPLEJACK'S
NOT COMING BACK?
SHE LOVES PONYVILLE!
AND SHE LOVES SWEET APPLE
ACRES.
AND SHE LOVES HER FAMILY!
[ GASPS ]
SOMETHING JUST DREADFUL MUST
HAVE HAPPENED TO APPLEJACK TO
MAKE HER NOT RETURN.
MAYBE SHE'S HURT OR SAD OR
SCARED.
SO WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S GO FIND HER!
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL SEARCH ALL OF EQUESTRIA IF
WE HAVE TO.
WE'LL BRING HER BACK.
Y'ALL ARE THE BEST.
THANK YOU, GIRLS.
OUR LITTLE BUSHEL JUST LOST ONE
APPLE.
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ ENGINE CHUGS ]
[ BRAKES SQUEAL ]
[ AIR HISSES ]
[ FIZZLE! ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ THUD ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ EAGLE CRIES ]
[ CLATTER ]
I HOPE THIS LEAD DOESN'T TURN
OUT TO BE A DEAD END.
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME
EMPTY-HOOFED AFTER PROMISING
WE'D FIND HER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'LL BREAK
IT TO THE APPLE FAMILY.
IT TO PONYVILLE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I'LL MAKE IT
TO THE NEXT STOP!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
THIS IS DODGE JUNCTION,
GIRLS.
APPLEJACK IS SUPPOSED TO HAVE
COME HERE AFTER THE RODEO ENDED.
[ AIR HISSES ]
[ THUD ]
LET'S FAN OUT AND TRY TO FIND
HER.
[ WHOOSH! ]
PICKLES!
HURRY! HURRY! HURRY! HURRY!
HURRY IT UP IN THERE!
[ SLAM! ]
SOME PONIES -- SHEESH.
[ ZIP! SLAM! ]
APPLEJACK!
I FOUND HER! I FOUND HER!
I FOUND HER!
OH, APPLEJACK, THANK HEAVENS.
WE'RE SO GLAD YOU'RE SAFE.
I FOUND HER! I FOUND HER!
[ BLINK! ]
[ SLAM! ]
BE RIGHT BACK.
H--HEY, EVERYPONY.
W--WHAT'S UP?
WHY DIDN'T YOU COME BACK TO
PONYVILLE?
YES, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
ARE YOU OKAY?
DO YOU HAVE ANY SNACKS?
TELL US WHAT HAPPENED,
APPLEJACK.
APPLEJACK, ARE THESE SOME OF
YOUR PONYVILLE FRIENDS?
YES, MA'AM.
AND YOU ARE?
WHY, I'M CHERRY JUBILEE, BOSS
OF CHERRY HILL RANCH.
HASN'T APPLEJACK TOLD YOU?
I SAW HER COMPETE AT THE
EQUESTRIA RODEO -- NEVER SAW
ANYPONY WIN SO MANY RIBBONS IN
ALL MY LIFE.
AW, SHUCKS, MS. JUBILEE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO INTO ALL
THAT.
AW, SHE'S SO MODEST.
ANYWAY, I CAN ALWAYS USE A PONY
WITH QUICK HOOVES AND A STRONG
BACK.
SO, WHEN I HEARD APPLEJACK WAS
LOOKING FOR A CHANGE OF SCENERY,
I SNAPPED HER UP, QUICK AS I
COULD, AND BROUGHT HER TO DODGE
JUNCTION.
WELL, I'LL LET YOU CATCH UP WITH
YOUR FRIENDS.
SEE YOU BACK AT THE RANCH.
"CHANGE OF SCENERY"?!
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, GUYS.
I THOUGHT CHERRIES WOULD BE A
NICE CHANGE FROM APPLES, SO I
TOOK THE JOB AND CAME HERE.
THAT'S IT -- END OF STORY.
THAT'S IT?
WELL, THAT'S A TERRIBLE STORY.
SORRY, BUT THAT'S ALL THERE
IS TO TELL.
THANKS FOR CHECKING ON ME, BUT
Y'ALL CAN GO HOME NOW.
TELL MY FAMILY "HI" AND THAT I'M
DOING A-OKAY.
EXCUSE ME, A.J., BUT WE
DIDN'T TRAVEL ALL OVER
EQUESTRIA, SEARCHING FOR YOU, TO
COME HOME WITHOUT YOU!
WELL, I DIDN'T ASK YOU TO
COME LOOKING FOR ME!
THERE IS NOTHING TO TELL, AND I
AM NOT GOING BACK TO PONYVILLE.
I DON'T CARE WHAT SHE SAYS.
APPLEJACK'S NOT TELLING US
SOMETHING.
TWILIGHT'S RIGHT.
WE GOT TO GET HER TO SPILL THE
BEANS.
WHAT? SHE HAD BEANS? UGH!
I TOLD HER I WAS SNACKY!
YOU READY TO PUT YOUR BACK
INTO IT, APPLEJACK?
SURE AM, MS. JUBILEE.
TERRIFIC! COME ON IN, GIRLS.
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING HERE?
WE'RE YOUR CHERRY SORTERS.
SHALL WE GET STARTED?
FINE.
RED CHERRIES GO IN ONE BIN,
AND YELLOW CHERRIES GO IN THE
OTHER -- SIMPLE AS CHERRY PIE.
JUST ONE TEENSY THING TO
REMEMBER -- HAVE FUN!
WHAT ARE YOU FIVE UP TO?
WELL, UH, YOU MADE WORKING ON
A CHERRY ORCHARD SOUND SO
DELIGHTFUL.
UH-HUH.
WELL, JUST REMEMBER, NO TALKING
ABOUT PONYVILLE.
FINE.
WHY DON'T YOU QUIT TALKING AND
GET WALKING?
[ SQUEAKING ]
SO, A.J., HOW WAS CANTERLOT?
NOT TALKING ABOUT PONYVILLE.
TALKING ABOUT CANTERLOT --
TOTALLY DIFFERENT TOWN.
CANTERLOT WAS FINE.
WAS THE RODEO FUN?
YES.
DID YOU MEET SOME NICE PONIES
THERE?
SOME.
REALLY?
DID YOU SEE WILD WOOL HICKOK?
WHAT ABOUT CALAMITY MANE?
YES. I SAW THEM BOTH.
[ SQUEAKING CONTINUES ]
AND HOW DID YOU MEET
MS. JUBILEE?
UM, WELL, MS. JUBILEE HAD A
CHERRY STAND AT THE RODEO --
REAL GOOD TREATS.
[ GALLOPING INTENSIFIES ]
UM, EXCUSE ME?
CHERRYWINKS, CHERRY
CHEESECAKE, CHERRY TARTS -- WE
STRUCK UP A CONVERSATION, BEING
ORCHARD FOLK AND ALL.
SO YOU TOLD HER ABOUT SWEET
APPLE ACRES?
YES.
DID YOU TELL HER WHY YOU
WEREN'T GOING BACK?
NO, 'CAUSE IT WAS NONE OF HER
BUSINESS!
OH, CAN YOU PLEASE SLOW DOWN?
IS IT BECAUSE I MADE IT RAIN
ON YOU THAT ONE TIME?
NO!
HELP!
[ SQUEAKING INTENSIFIES ]
IS IT BECAUSE YOU WERE
INSULTED WHEN I GAVE YOU THAT
BOOK ON ORGANIZED ORCHARDS?
NO!
[ GALLOPING INTENSIFIES ]
IS IT BECAUSE YOU WERE
INSULTED WHEN I INSULTED YOUR
HAIR?
NO! NO! NO!
I'M NOT TELLING YOU WHY, SO
JUST --
STOP!
[ SCREECH ]
[ SPLAT ]
[ ALL GASP ]
WELL, GIRLS, WE SEEM TO BE
STRIKING OUT.
THAT'S 'CAUSE WE'RE PLAYING
TOO NICE.
YES, DESPERATE TIMES DO CALL
FOR DESPERATE MEASURES.
IT'S TIME TO CALL IN THE BIG
GUNS.
[ SLURPING ]
[ THUD ]
HEY, APPLEJACK!
NEED SOME HELP?
YOU PROMISE NOT TO ASK ME ANY
QUESTIONS?
I PROMISE.
[ THUD ]
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF
CHERRYCHANGA?
OOH. SORRY. THAT WAS A QUESTION.
THAT KIND OF QUESTION IS
FINE, PINKIE.
NO, I NEVER HAD A CHERRYCHANGA.
WELL, NO WONDER, BECAUSE I
MADE IT UP MYSELF.
A CHERRYCHANGA IS MASHED UP
CHERRIES IN A TORTILLA THAT'S
DEEP-FRIED!
CHERRYCHANGA -- GREAT NAME, HUH?
OH, BUT MAYBE I SHOULD CALL IT A
CHIMICHERRY.
OOH, THAT'S GOOD, TOO!
WHICH DO YOU THINK SOUNDS
BETTER -- - CHERRYCHANGA OR
CHIMICHERRY?
OR WHAT IF I COMBINE THEM --
CHIMICHERRYCHANGA?
WHAT SOUNDS THE FUNNIEST?
I LIKE FUNNY WORDS!
ONE OF MY FAVORITE FUNNY WORDS
IS "KUMQUAT"!
I DIDN'T MAKE THAT ONE UP.
I WOULD WORK IN A KUMQUAT
ORCHARD JUST SO I COULD SAY
"KUMQUAT" ALL DAY.
KUMQUAT! KUMQUAT! KUMQUAT!
AND PICKLE BARREL -- ISN'T THAT
JUST THE FUNNEST THING TO SAY?
PICKLE BARREL! PICKLE BARREL!
PICKLE BARREL!
SAY IT WITH ME -- PICKLE BARREL,
KUMQUAT.
PICKLE BARREL, KUMQUAT.
CHIMICHERRYCHANGA!
NO! MAKE IT STOP.
MAKE IT STOP!
THE ONLY WAY TO MAKE IT STOP
IS FOR YOU TO SPILL THE BEANS.
NEVER!
SPEAKING OF BEANS, DID YOU
EVER REALIZE HOW MANY WORDS
RHYME WITH "BEANS"?
LEAN. MEAN. SPLEEN. UNCLEAN.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT!
I'LL TELL EVERYPONY WHAT'S GOING
ON.
JUST, PLEASE, STOP TALKING!
BUT CAN IT WAIT TILL TOMORROW AT
BREAKFAST?
I'M PLUMB TUCKERED OUT.
TOMORROW, HUH? I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU PINKIE PROMISE?
[ SIGHS ]
I WILL TELL YOU THE WHOLE TRUTH
AT BREAKFAST -- PINKIE PROMISE.
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
I'M GLAD WE'RE FINALLY GONNA
GET SOME ANSWERS FROM APPLEJACK.
YEAH. MAYBE.
DON'T WORRY, RAINBOW.
SHE'S GOT TO FESS UP AFTER
MAKING A PINKIE PROMISE.
[ CREAK ]
GOOD MORNING, APPLEJACK!
YOU READY FOR BREAK--
[ GASPS ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
NO PONY BREAKS A PINKIE
PROMISE!!
[ ZIP! ]
APPLEJACK! YOU PINKIE PROMISED!
AAH!
APPLEJACK, COME BACK HERE!
GIDDY-UP, FELLAS.
I GOT TO GET THE HECK OUT OF
DODGE.
[ ALL WHINNY ]
SHE'S GONNA GET AWAY!
OH, NO, SHE WON'T.
LOOK, GIRLS!
FOLLOW THAT STAGECOACH!
OH, WE HAVE YOU NOW!
[ SCREECH ]
[ SNIFFS ]
WHOA! WHAT THE...
PULL OVER!
HEY! CUT THAT OUT!
WHOA!
I'LL PAY YOU DOUBLE TO OUTRUN
THEM.
WE'LL PAY YOU TRIPLE TO SLOW
DOWN.
I'LL PAY YOU QUADRUPLE TO
LEAVE THEM IN THE DUST!
[ WHINNIES ]
[ ALL COUGHING ]
THAT WAS RUDE!
GET THEM! GET THEM!
COME ON, FLUTTERSHY!
OH!
YAH! COME ON, Y'ALL! GO! GO!
APPLEJACK, YOU BROKE YOUR
PINKIE PROMISE!
APOLOGIZE!
PINKIE, I DID NOT BREAK MY
PROMISE.
WHAT?
IF Y'ALL RECKON BACK, I TOLD
YOU THAT I WOULD TELL YOU
EVERYTHING AT BREAKFAST.
BUT I DIDN'T COME FOR BREAKFAST.
I COULDN'T COME TO THAT
BREAKFAST -- NOT IF IT MEANT
TELLING Y'ALL WHAT HAPPENED.
WELL, I -- I --
I'M SORRY, PINKIE, BUT I
CAN'T TELL Y'ALL THE TRUTH.
I JUST CAN'T!
WELL, I HEARD A "SORRY" IN
THERE, SO THAT'LL HAVE TO DO,
FOR NOW.
I'LL GET A REAL APOLOGY LATER.
RARITY, CATCH ME!
WHAT? PINKIE!
[ SCREAMS ]
RAINBOW, GO BACK!
NO TIME!
THEY KNEW WHAT THEY WERE GETTING
INTO.
[ TING! ]
[ COUGHS ]
[ BELL DINGING ]
[ ENGINE CHUGS ]
YES! HYAH!
[ WHINNIES ]
[ CLACKING ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ SCREECH ]
YEEHAW!
All: LADY, YOU'RE TROUBLE.
HA! TRY AND CATCH ME NOW!
OH, NUTS.
[ PANTING ]
NOT SO FAST!
[ ZOOM! ]
FINE. NOW YOU KNOW.
KNOW WHAT?
WELL, JUST LOOK!
I AM.
YOU WON AN AMAZING NUMBER OF
RIBBONS, JUST LIKE MS. JUBILEE
SAID.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
THERE'S EVERY COLOR OF RIBBON
DOWN THERE -- EVERY COLOR
BUT...BLUE.
I CAME IN FOURTH, THIRD, EVEN
SECOND, BUT I DIDN'T WIN ONE
FIRST PRIZE.
AND I CERTAINLY DIDN'T WIN ANY
PRIZE MONEY.
BUT THE TELEGRAM SAID YOU
WERE GONNA SEND MONEY.
THAT'S WHY I CAME HERE.
I WANTED TO EARN SOME MONEY.
AFTER THAT BIG OLD SEND-OFF
PONYVILLE GAVE ME, I JUST DIDN'T
HAVE THE NERVE TO COME HOME
EMPTY-HOOVED.
I COULDN'T COME HOME A FAILURE.
APPLEJACK, YOU'RE NOT A
FAILURE.
AND WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS.
WE DON'T CARE IF YOU CAME IN
50th PLACE.
YOU'RE STILL NUMBER ONE IN OUR
BOOKS.
SO...YOU'RE NOT UPSET OR
DISAPPOINTED?
All: UNH-UNH.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE MAYOR?
I DON'T THINK I CAN FACE HER AND
TELL HER I DIDN'T GET THAT MONEY
TO FIX THE BROKEN ROOF.
APPLEJACK, WE CAN ALWAYS FIND
A WAY TO FIX THAT HOLE IN THE
ROOF.
BUT IF YOU DON'T COME BACK,
WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO FIX THE
HOLE IN OUR HEARTS.
[ SNIFFLES ]
DARN IT!
NOW YOU GOT ME ACTING ALL SAPPY.
[ Thinking ] DEAR PRINCESS
CELESTIA, IT'S A TAD EASIER TO
BE PROUD WHEN YOU'VE COME IN
FIRST THAN IT IS WHEN YOU FINISH
FURTHER BACK.
BUT THERE'S NO REASON TO HIDE
WHEN YOU DON'T DO AS WELL AS
YOU'D HOPED.
YOU CAN'T RUN AWAY FROM YOUR
PROBLEMS -- BETTER TO RUN TO
YOUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
[ SQUEAKING ]
I MEAN, WHICH DO YOU THINK,
RARITY -- CHIMICHERRY OR
CHERRYCHANGA?
CHIMICHERRY? CHERRYCHANGA?
WHEN I GET BACK, YOU'RE GONNA
GET IT, RAINBOW DASH!
CHIMICHERRY? CHERRYCHANGA?
CHIMICHERRY, OR CHERRYCHANGA?
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪