Twilight Sparkle:
QUILL.
CHECK.
[ TINKLING ]
PARCHMENT.
CHECK.
EXTRA INK.
EXTRA EXTRA INK.
CHECK.
IS THAT EVERYTHING
ON THE CHECKLIST?
YEP.
GREAT.
NOW THAT WE'VE COMPLETED
THE CHECKLIST
OF THINGS WE NEED
TO CREATE A CHECKLIST,
WE CAN MAKE MY CHECKLIST
OF THE THINGS I HAVE TO GET DONE
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
READY?
READY.
ITEM ONE --
CREATE CHECKLIST
OF THE THINGS
I HAVE TO ACCOMPLISH
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
[ SIGHS ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
Twilight Sparkle:
HOW ARE WE DOING, SPIKE?
LET'S SEE.
WE'VE ALREADY DROPPED OFF
YOUR CAPE AT THE CLEANER'S,
RETURNED THE BLACKBOARD
YOU BORROWED FROM CHEERILEE,
ORDERED NEW PARCHMENT AND QUILLS
FROM THE STATIONERY SHOP.
HMM. SEEMS LIKE WE JUST PLACED
AN ORDER FOR THOSE
A FEW DAYS AGO.
CAN'T IMAGINE WHY
WE GO THROUGH SO MANY OF THEM.
SOUNDS LIKE WE'RE AHEAD
OF SCHEDULE.
WHAT'S NEXT?
CUPCAKES!
OOH.
UH, I ONLY ORDERED 12.
OH, I KNOW, DEAR,
BUT I HAD AN EXTRA,
SO I THOUGHT I'D MAKE IT
A BAKER'S DOZEN.
OH.
UNH!
[ TINKLING ]
THAT WAS VERY THOUGHTFUL
OF YOU.
IT'S JUST SOME OF THE ICING
FROM THE EXTRA CUPCAKE
IS GETTING ALL OVER
THE ONE NEXT TO IT.
SEE?
OH. SURE.
IT'S JUST THAT I'M PLANNING ON
SHARING THESE AT A PICNIC LATER,
AND I DON'T WANT ANYPONY
TO FEEL LIKE SOMEPONY ELSE
IS GETTING MORE ICING.
OH, NO.
O-OF COURSE NOT.
[ TINKLING ]
NOT TO WORRY.
I'LL JUST MOVE
SOME OF THIS ONE TO --
HMM.
I THINK I MAY HAVE
SCOOPED TOO MUCH.
OOPS.
NOW THOSE TWO HAVE MORE.
LET'S JUST
TRY THIS AGAIN.
[ SWISH! SWISH! ]
HMM.
NO, THAT WON'T DO.
COULD WE JUST -- HMM.
[ SPLAT! ]
PUT SOME HERE, THEN --
NO, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
OKAY,
WE'RE ON THIS ONE.
UH, WAIT.
I'LL JUST --
OOH, A LITTLE BIT HERE.
HERE.
AND...PERFECT!
HMM. OH, YES.
MUCH BETTER.
OKAY. TIME TO TACKLE
THE NEXT ITEM ON OUR -- OOPS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
ADD "GIVE A BABY DRAGON A BATH"
TO OUR LIST.
[ WHIR! ]
[ GULP! ]
VERY EFFICIENT.
AND A LITTLE BIT GROSS.
WELL.
LOOKS LIKE
THAT'S EVERYTHING.
ALMOST EVERYTHING.
"TRIPLE-CHECK CHECKLIST TO MAKE
SURE WE DIDN'T MISS ANYTHING
WHEN WE DOUBLE-CHECK
THE CHECKLIST."
UH, CHECK.
OHH!
I'VE BEEN HOLDING THAT QUILL
SO LONG, I'VE GOT A CLAW CRAMP.
GOOD THING WE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO REPORT
TO PRINCESS CELESTIA
THIS WEEK.
[ SPLAT! ]
I DON'T THINK
I COULD WRITE ANOTHER WORD.
WE HAVEN'T SENT A LETTER
TO PRINCESS CELESTIA THIS WEEK?
WHY? IS THAT BAD?
BAD? BAD?!
OF COURSE IT'S BAD!
I'M SUPPOSED TO SEND
PRINCESS CELESTIA
A LETTER EVERY WEEK,
TELLING HER ABOUT A LESSON
I'VE LEARNED ABOUT FRIENDSHIP!
NOT EVERY OTHER WEEK.
NOT EVERY 10 DAYS.
EVERY. SINGLE. WEEK.
HUH?
[ TINKLING ]
WHERE'S MY CALENDAR?
WHERE IT ALWAYS IS?
[ TINKLING ]
[ BONK! ]
WHEN DID WE SEND
THE LAST ONE?
LAST TUESDAY?
AND TODAY IS...
TUESDAY?
AAH!
NO! NO! NO! NO!
NO! NO! NO! NO! NO!
[ TICKING ]
IF I DON'T SEND HER
A LETTER BY SUNDOWN,
I'LL BE [GASPS] TARDY!
WHAT'S THAT, NOW?
TARDY, SPIKE.
LATE! I'LL BE LATE!
OH, HOW COULD I HAVE
LET THIS HAPPEN?
I'M USUALLY
SO ORGANIZED.
I'VE NEVER BEEN LATE
WITH AN ASSIGNMENT.
OH, PLEASE!
YOU'RE THE MOST STUDIOUS
STUDENT EVER.
I'M SURE THE PRINCESS
WILL FORGIVE YOU
IF YOU MISS
ONE LITTLE DEADLINE.
I'M AFRAID TO TAKE
THAT CHANCE, SPIKE.
THIS IS THE RULER OF ALL OF
EQUESTRIA WE'RE TALKING ABOUT --
THE PONY WHO HOLDS MY FATE
IN HER HOOVES.
WHAT IF SHE DOESN'T
FORGIVE ME?
YEAH.
I DON'T THINK SHE'LL --
WHAT IF INSTEAD,
SHE STARTS THINKING
I'M NOT TAKING MY STUDIES
ON FRIENDSHIP SERIOUSLY?
WHY WOULD SHE --
WHAT IF SHE MAKES ME
COME BACK TO CANTERLOT
AND PUTS ME BACK IN SCHOOL
AND MAKES ME PROVE
I'VE BEEN TAKING THEM SERIOUSLY
BY GIVING ME A TEST?!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT IF I DON'T PASS?
BUT WHY
WOULDN'T YOU PASS --
SHE'S MY TEACHER.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT TEACHERS DO
TO STUDENTS WHO DON'T PASS?
THEY SEND THEM
BACK A GRADE!
BUT SHE WON'T
JUST SEND ME BACK A GRADE.
SHE'LL SEND ME BACK
TO [GASPS] MAGIC KINDERGARTEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ BLIND FLUTTERS ]
[ TEETH CHATTERING ]
TWILIGHT.
TWILIGHT!
HUH?
THAT IS THE MOST RIDICULOUS
THING I'VE EVER HEARD.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE SENT BACK
TO MAGIC KINDERGARTEN.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE NO REASON TO WORRY.
BECAUSE I AM GOING TO SOLVE
A FRIEND'S PROBLEM
AND GET THAT LETTER
TO PRINCESS CELESTIA
BEFORE SUNDOWN.
UGH.
SO...
GOT ANY PROBLEMS, TROUBLES,
CONUNDRUMS,
OR ANY OTHER SORT OF ISSUES,
MAJOR OR MINOR,
THAT I, AS A GOOD FRIEND,
COULD HELP YOU SOLVE?
HUH...
HMM...
UHH...
UH...
I GOT NOTHING.
[ SIGHS ]
THEN IT LOOKS I'M GONNA HAVE TO
FIND SOMEPONY WHO DOES.
OH, THIS WON'T END WELL.
[ TICKING ]
YOU'VE GOT THIS, TWILIGHT.
YOU STILL HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
TO GET THAT LETTER
TO PRINCESS CELESTIA.
HAS TO BE SOMEPONY AROUND HERE
WHO NEEDS THE HELP
OF A GOOD FRIEND.
[ PONY WAILING ]
RARITY!
[ RARITY SCREAMING ]
DON'T WORRY, RARITY.
I'M HERE.
[ Crying ] WHY ME?
WHY? WHY? WHY?
OF ALL THE WORST THINGS
THAT COULD HAPPEN,
THIS IS
THE WORST POSSIBLE THING!
WHAT'S HAPPENED?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'VE LOST MY DIAMOND-ENCRUSTED
PURPLE RIBBON!
I HAVE SEARCHED HIGH,
AND I HAVE SEARCHED LOW.
LOW AND HIGH!
HIGH AND LOW.
BUT I CAN'T FIND IT
ANYWHERE!
[ TINKLING ]
[ Crying ] ANYWHERE!
HOW CAN I POSSIBLY FINISH
MY LATEST CREATION
IF I CAN'T FIND IT?
NEVER FEAR, RARITY.
AS YOUR FRIEND,
I'LL DO MY BEST TO HELP YOU F--
OH, THERE IT IS.
ISN'T IT ALWAYS
JUST THE LAST PLACE YOU LOOK?
SO, YOU JUST LOST
YOUR RIBBON?
MM-HMM.
BUT NOW YOU'VE FOUND IT.
YEAH-HUH.
AND NOTHING ELSE
IS BOTHERING YOU?
NOTHING THAT I AS A GOOD FRIEND
COULD HELP YOU WITH?
HMM.
THERE IS ONE THING.
YES?
I THINK I LEFT MY MEASURING TAPE
UNDER THE FABRIC OVER THERE.
COULD YOU GET THAT
FOR ME?
[ SIGHS ]
[ TINKLING ]
MEASURING TAPE.
SURE.
TWILIGHT, IS THERE
SOMETHING BOTHER--
TWILIGHT?
[ TICKING ]
NO NEED TO PANIC.
RARITY IS JUST ONE PONY.
I'M SURE ONE OF MY OTHER FRIENDS
WILL NEED ME.
HYAH!
HYAH! HYAH!
[ CRASH! ]
WHAT IN THE WORLD?
RAINBOW MUST BE ANGRY
WITH APPLEJACK.
SHE MUST HATE HER GUTS.
OH, WONDERFUL!
RAINBOW DASH, STOP!
[ SCREECH! ]
[ TINKLING ]
LISTEN, RAINBOW,
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET
WITH APPLEJACK, BUT DON'T WORRY.
WHATEVER IT IS
THAT HAS COME BETWEEN YOU TWO,
I'M SURE THAT I,
AS A GOOD FRIEND,
CAN HELP YOU RESOLVE
YOUR PROBLEMS.
[ THUD! ]
UH, WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OH, RAINBOW DASH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HIDE
YOUR FEELINGS FROM ME.
I CAN TELL YOU TWO
MUST HAVE HAD A TERRIBLE FIGHT.
[ TINKLING ]
NOW, WHAT DON'T YOU TELL ME
ALL ABOUT YOUR ISSUES
WITH APPLEJACK?
I DON'T HAVE ANY ISSUES
WITH APPLEJACK.
YOU DON'T?
THEN WHY ARE YOU
DESTROYING HER PROPERTY?
BECAUSE SHE ASKED ME TO.
RIGHT, APPLEJACK?
YES, MA'AM.
I WANTED TO PUT UP A NEW BARN,
BUT THIS ONE'S
GOT TO COME DOWN FIRST.
[ LAUGHS ]
NOW GET BACK TO IT, R.D.
YOU GOT IT, BOSS.
I'D TAKE COVER
IF I WERE YOU.
AAH!
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ TICKING ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I WASTED ALL THAT TIME.
I SHOULD HAVE
JUST COME HERE FIRST.
FLUTTERSHY ALWAYS HAS SOME FEAR
SHE'S TRYING TO GET OVER.
AS A GOOD FRIEND,
I'LL BE ABLE TO HELP HER.
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ ROARING ]
HYAH!
[ ROARS ]
FLUTTERSHY?
AAH!
[ ROARS ]
HYAH!
[ RATTLE! RATTLE! ]
HOW CAN THIS BE HAPPENING?
OF ALL THE DAYS SHE HAD TO STOP
BEING SUCH A SCAREDY-PONY,
SHE HAD TO PICK TODAY!
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
YOU REALLY SHOULD HAVE
COME TO ME SOONER.
YOU WERE CARRYING SO MUCH
TENSION IN THAT SHOULDER.
[ GROWLS ]
IT'S FINE.
IT'LL ALL BE FINE.
THE DAY ISN'T OVER YET.
BUT IT WILL BE OVER SOON!
[ TICKING ]
UGH!
IT'LL BE ALL OVER --
MY TIME IN PONYVILLE,
MY ADVANCED STUDIES!
NO, NO.
YOU'RE A GOOD STUDENT.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
OH, BUT WHAT IF I CAN'T?
YOU CAN! YOU JUST HAVE TO
KEEP IT TOGETHER.
KEEP IT TOGETHER!
ARE YOU TALKING
TO YOURSELF?
TWILIGHT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ POOF! ]
SNAP OUT OF IT!
[ RATTLE! RATTLE! ]
HUH?
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ LAUGHTER ]
Spike: TWILIGHT,
I'M REALLY WORRIED.
I MEAN, THIS LETTER THING
IS REALLY GETTING TO YOU.
HERE.
YOU'VE BEEN SO ANXIOUS
ALL DAY
THAT YOU COMPLETELY FORGOT
ABOUT THE PICNIC.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST RELAX
AND GO HANG OUT WITH --
THE PICNIC!
[ TINKLING ]
I SHOULD GO SEE MY FRIENDS.
GLAD YOU'VE COME
TO YOUR SENSES.
[ SPROING! SPROING! ]
PLEASE TELL ME
I DID NOT FORGET THE PLATES.
[ GASPS ] I DID.
I TOTALLY FORGOT THEM.
OF ALL THE WORST THINGS
THAT COULD HAPPEN,
THIS IS THE WORST
POSSIBLE THING!
[ TINKLING ]
[ Crying ] WHY? WHY? WHY?
WHAT?
YOU DIDN'T EXPECT ME TO LAY
ON THE GRASS, DID YOU?
YOU ALL RIGHT, HON?
NO!
I AM NOT ALL RIGHT.
WHAT?
OH, NO.
WHAT CAN WE DO?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S JUST TERRIBLE.
YES?
SIMPLY AWFUL.
YES? YES?
IT'S THE MOST HORRIFIC TROUBLE
I'VE EVER BEEN IN,
AND I REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY NEED YOUR HELP.
YES? YES?
MY LETTER TO PRINCESS CELESTIA
IS ALMOST OVERDUE,
AND I HAVEN'T LEARNED ANYTHING
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
[ ALL SIGH ]
OH, THANK GOODNESS.
I THOUGHT SOMETHING
REALLY AWFUL HAD HAPPENED.
AAH!
SOMETHING AWFUL
HAS HAPPENED!
IF I DON'T TURN IN THE LETTER
ON TIME, I'LL BE TARDY!
TARDY!
[ GIGGLING ]
NO OFFENSE, SUGAR CUBE,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEPONY'S
GETTING THEMSELVES
ALL WORKED UP OVER NOTHING.
THIS IS NOT NOTHING.
THIS IS EVERYTHING.
I NEED YOU GUYS
TO HELP ME FIND SOMEPONY
WITH A PROBLEM
I CAN FIX BEFORE SUNDOWN.
MY WHOLE LIFE DEPENDS ON IT!
[ Laughing ] OH, TWILIGHT,
YOU'RE SUCH A CRACK-UP.
[ LAUGHS ]
COME ON, NOW. HAVE A SEAT AND
STOP SWEATING THE SMALL STUFF.
OHH!
UGGGH!
WOW. I'VE NEVER SEEN TWILIGHT
SO UPSET BEFORE.
OHH, WHAT A DRAMA QUEEN.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
RELATIVELY SPEAKING.
[ TICKING ]
CLOCK IS TICKING, TWILIGHT.
CLOCK IS TICKING.
KEEP IT TOGETHER.
IF I CAN'T FIND
A FRIENDSHIP PROBLEM,
[ TINKLING ]
I'LL MAKE A FRIENDSHIP PROBLEM.
[ CHIRPING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ ALL GIGGLING ]
[ TINKLING ]
HI, GIRLS.
OH, HI, TWILIGHT.
HOW'S IT GO--
GR-R-EAT. JUST GREAT.
YOU THREE LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE DOING GREAT, TOO.
LOOKS LIKE THREE GOOD FRIENDS
WHO OBVIOUSLY DON'T NEED
THE HELP OF ANOTHER GOOD FRIEND.
[ TINKLING ]
THIS IS SMARTY-PANTS.
SHE WAS MINE
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE,
AND NOW I WANT TO GIVE HER
TO YOU!
UH, SHE'S GREAT.
YEAH. GREAT.
I REALLY LIKE
HER...MANE.
SHE EVEN COMES
WITH HER OWN
FOR WHEN YOU WANT TO PRETEND
SHE'S DOING HER HOMEWORK!
THAT'S, UM, GREAT.
YEAH. GREAT.
UH...
I REALLY LIKE
HER...MANE?
I JUST HOPE THE FACT
THAT THERE ARE THREE OF YOU
AND ONLY ONE OF HER
DOESN'T BECOME A PROBLEM.
I'D HATE TO CAUSE A RIFT
BETWEEN SUCH GOOD FRIENDS.
[ CUCKOO! CUCKOO! ]
SO, WHO WANTS TO PLAY
WITH HER FIRST?
UH, YOU SHOULD PLAY WITH HER
FIRST, SWEETIE BELLE.
YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE YOU LIKE
HER MANE SO MUCH.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I THINK SCOOTALOO SHOULD
GET TO PLAY WITH HER FIRST.
I'D LOVE TO, BUT, UM,
YOU TAKE HER, APPLE BLOOM.
APPLEJACK SAYS
IT'S IMPORTANT TO SHARE.
[ Thinking ]
I GOT TO THINK OF SOMETHING.
THINK, THINK, THINK, THINK,
TWILIGHT, THINK!
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S IT!
OOH, YOU'RE GOING TO
LIKE SMARTY-PANTS,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE HER
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
[ TINKLING ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ GASPS ] I WANT IT.
I NEED IT.
I REALLY LIKE HER MANE!
I WANT HER FIRST!
NO, I --
THE WANT-IT-NEED-IT SPELL.
WORKS EVERY TIME.
OKAY, OKAY,
LET'S BREAK IT UP.
I THINK WE CAN ALL SEE
THAT THERE IS AN IMPORTANT
LESSON TO BE LEARNED HERE
ABOUT -- UNH!
HEY! GIVE IT BACK!
COME ON, GIRLS.
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS
HERE, RIGHT?
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU OUGHT TO SHARE?
COME ON!
NO WAY!
GIVE IT BACK!
UGH!
IT'S MINE!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
BIG MACINTOSH.
THANK GOODNESS!
YOU GOT TO HELP ME GET THAT DOLL
AWAY FROM THOSE GIRLS.
YUP.
GIVE IT BACK!
IT'S MINE!
I NEED HER!
OH, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
NOW, IF YOU COULD
JUST GIVE HER TO ME.
NOPE.
OH, NO!
Scootaloo:
GIVE HER BACK!
I LOVE HER SO MUCH!
DON'T TOUCH IT!
WHAT'S ALL
THE COMMOTION ABOUT?
THEY'RE FIGHTING
OVER THAT DOLL.
THAT INCREDIBLE,
AMAZING DOLL.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
CAN'T...GET...A CLEAR SHOT.
[ GRUNTING ]
GIMME!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
NOPE.
OH, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ HOOFBEATS,
INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
Y'ALL HEAR THAT?
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
WHAT IN THE NAME OF ALL THINGS
ORCHARD APPLES IS GOING ON HERE?
DON'T LOOK AT IT!
DON'T LOOK AT WHAT?
MY SMARTY-PANTS DOLL.
I ENCHANTED HER, AND NOW
EVERYPONY IS FIGHTING OVER HER.
WHY WOULD YOU ENCHANT
YOUR DOLL?
WELL, I HAD TO DO
SOMETHING!
I HAD NOTHING TO REPORT
TO PRINCESS CELESTIA.
I THOUGHT IF I COULDN'T FIND
A PROBLEM, I'D MAKE A PROBLEM.
THE DAY
IS ALMOST OVER!
NOT ALMOST.
Princess Celestia:
TWILIGHT SPARKLE!
[ TINKLING ]
WHOA, NELLIE.
[ TINK! TINK! TINK! ]
[ SQUEAKS ]
[ WHINNIES ]
MEET ME IN THE LIBRARY.
GOODBYE, GIRLS.
IF YOU CARE TO VISIT,
I'LL BE
IN MAGIC KINDERGARTEN...
BACK IN CANTERLOT.
MAGIC KINDERGARTEN?
CANTERLOT?
WE'RE NEVER GONNA SEE
TWILIGHT AGAIN!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO,
Y'ALL?
OF ALL THE WORST THINGS
THAT COULD HAPPEN,
THIS IS THE WORST
POSSIBLE THING!
WHAT?
I REALLY MEAN IT
THIS TIME.
Twilight Sparkle: BUT -- BUT I'M
SUPPOSED TO SEND YOU A LETTER
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP
EVERY WEEK.
I MISSED THE DEADLINE.
I'M A BAD STUDENT.
I'M TARDY.
YOU ARE A WONDERFUL STUDENT,
TWILIGHT.
I DON'T HAVE TO GET A LETTER
EVERY WEEK TO KNOW THAT.
REALLY?
WAIT!
YOU CAN'T PUNISH HER!
IT WASN'T HER FAULT.
I'M LISTENING.
PLEASE, YOUR HIGHNESS.
WE ALL SAW
THAT TWILIGHT WAS UPSET.
BUT WE THOUGHT THAT THE THING
THAT SHE WAS WORRYING ABOUT
WASN'T WORTH
WORRYING ABOUT.
SO, WHEN SHE RAN OFF,
ALL WORKED UP,
NOT A SINGLE ONE OF US
TRIED TO STOP HER.
AS TWILIGHT'S
GOOD FRIENDS,
WE SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
HER FEELINGS SERIOUSLY
AND BEEN THERE FOR HER.
Fluttershy: PLEASE DON'T
TAKE HER AWAY FROM US
JUST BECAUSE WE WERE
TOO INSENSITIVE TO HELP HER.
LOOKS LIKE YOU ALL LEARNED
A PRETTY VALUABLE LESSON TODAY.
MM-HMM. MM-HMM.
VERY WELL.
I'LL FORGET TWILIGHT'S
PUNISHMENT
ON ONE CONDITION.
Fluttershy: ANYTHING.
FROM THIS DAY FORTH, I WOULD
LIKE YOU ALL TO REPORT TO ME
YOUR FINDINGS ON THE MAGIC
OF FRIENDSHIP
WHEN -- AND ONLY WHEN --
YOU HAPPEN TO DISCOVER THEM.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
PRINCESS CELESTIA, WAIT.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
I WAS IN TROUBLE?
YOUR FRIEND SPIKE
MADE ME AWARE
THAT YOU WERE LETTING YOUR FEARS
GET THE BEST OF YOU.
I COMMEND HIM FOR TAKING
YOUR FEELINGS SERIOUSLY.
NOW, IF YOU WILL ALL EXCUSE ME,
I MUST RETURN TO CANTERLOT.
I'M EXPECTING SOME MAIL.
Y'ALL HEARD THE PRINCESS.
SPIKE, TAKE A LETTER.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
WE'RE WRITING TO YOU
BECAUSE TODAY WE ALL LEARNED
A LITTLE SOMETHING
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
WE LEARNED THAT YOU SHOULD TAKE
YOUR FRIEND'S WORRIES SERIOUSLY.
EVEN IF YOU DON'T THINK THAT
SHE HAS ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
AND THAT YOU SHOULDN'T LET YOUR
WORRIES TURN A SMALL PROBLEM...
INTO AN ENORMOUSLY HUGE,
"ENTIRE TOWN IN TOTAL CHAOS,"
"PRINCESS HAS TO COME
AND SAVE THE DAY" PROBLEM.
SIGNED,
YOUR LOYAL SUBJECTS.
P.S. OBVIOUSLY, SPIKE DID NOT
HAVE TO LEARN A LESSON
BECAUSE HE IS THE BEST,
MOST AWESOME FRIEND
A PONY COULD ASK FOR.
UNLIKE EVERYPONY ELSE,
HE TOOK THINGS SERIOUSLY AND...
[ CHUCKLES ]
UH, YEAH.
I'LL JUST...
[ LAUGHTER ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪