[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]
HMM.
I JUST DON'T FEEL LIKE IT'S
QUITE FINISHED.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
IF IT'S FOR MISS CHEERILEE, IT
NEEDS TO BE PERFECT.
HEARTS AND HOOVES DAY ONLY COMES
ONCE A YEAR, AFTER ALL.
I SAY WE ADD A LITTLE MORE
RIBBON.
MM-HMM.
YEAH.
AND JUST A TINY BIT MORE
LACE.
A FEW MORE HOOFPRINTS.
[ SQUISH! SQUISH! SQUISH! ]
GLITTER!
IT COULD DEFINITELY USE JUST A
LITTLE MORE GLITTER.
NOW, THAT'LL SHOW
MISS CHEERILEE HOW MUCH WE CARE
ABOUT HER.
JUST HAVE TO GET IT TO THE
HEARTS AND HOOVES PARTY AT
SCHOOL.
I THINK WE'RE GONNA NEED A
BIGGER ENVELOPE.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
I LIKE THE RED ONE.
IT'S LOVELY, AND SO...
BIG!
WE JUST WANTED TO LET YOU
KNOW THAT WE THINK YOU'RE THE
BEST TEACHER IN THE WHOLE, WIDE
WORLD, AND WE THINK YOU'RE
SUPER AND THAT WE LOVE YOU SO,
SO MUCH, AND WE WANT YOU TO HAVE
THE BEST HEARTS AND HOOVES
DAY...
All: EVER!
THANK YOU SO MUCH, GIRLS.
I LOVE IT. I REALLY DO.
I'M SURE IT'S NOTHING,
COMPARED TO THE GIFTS YOU'VE
GOTTEN FROM YOUR VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY!
OH, I DON'T HAVE A VERY
SPECIAL SOMEPONY AT THE MOMENT.
REALLY?!
HOW COULD SOMEPONY AS AMAZING AS
YOU NOT HAVE A VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY ON HEARTS AND HOOVES
DAY?
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
SWEETIE BELLE.
I HAVE LOTS OF GOOD FRIENDS AND
WONDERFUL STUDENTS WHO CARE
ABOUT ME VERY MUCH.
I'M GONNA HAVE AN ABSOLUTELY
TERRIFIC HEARTS AND HOOVES DAY.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYPONY!
WHO'S READY TO PLAY PIN THE
HEART ON THE PONY?
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
I WANT TO GO FIRST!
ME, ME, ME!
IF ANYPONY DESERVES A VERY
SPECIAL SOMEPONY, IT'S HER.
[ GASPS ]
UH, YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M MORE THAN ALL RIGHT.
I'VE JUST COME UP WITH THE BEST
IDEA EVER!
WE'RE GONNA FIND MISS CHEERILEE
A VERY SPECIAL SOMEPONY!
THAT IS THE BEST IDEA EVER!
I TOLD YOU!
SO, WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
HEARTS AND HOOVES DAY IS ALMOST
OVER!
LET'S GET OUT THERE AND FIND
SOMEPONY SPECIAL FOR CHEERILEE
ALREADY!
YEAH!
LET'S DO IT!
[ WHACK! ]
NOW, IT CAN'T BE JUST
ANYPONY.
MISS CHEERILEE IS ONE OF THE
BEST MARES IN PONYVILLE.
SHE DESERVES TO HAVE ONE OF THE
BEST STALLIONS AS HER VERY
SPECIAL SOMEPONY.
[ MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ CHEERILEE IS SWEET AND KIND ♪
♪ SHE'S THE BEST TEACHER WE
COULD HOPE FOR ♪
♪ THE PERFECT STALLION, YOU AND
I MUST FIND ♪
♪ WANT TO REALLY MAKE HER HEART
SOAR ♪
♪ BUT THIS ONE'S TOO YOUNG ♪
♪ THIS ONE'S TOO OLD ♪
♪ HE CLEARLY HAS A TERRIBLE
COLD ♪
[ SNEEZES ]
♪ THIS GUY'S TOO SILLY ♪
♪ HE'S WAY TOO UPTIGHT ♪
I SAY!
♪ WELL, NOTHING'S WRONG WITH
THIS ONE ♪
♪ HE SEEMS ALL RIGHT ♪
HIS GIRLFRIEND SURE THINKS
SO.
♪ HOW 'BOUT THIS ONE? ♪
♪ HE LOOKS TOO FLASHY ♪
♪ HE MIGHT DO ♪
Both: ♪ IF HE WEREN'T SO
SPLASHY ♪
♪ TOO SHORT ♪
♪ TOO TALL ♪
♪ TOO CLEAN ♪
♪ TOO SMELLY ♪
♪ HE'S STRANGELY OBSESSED
WITH TUBS OF JELLY ♪
[ ALL SIGH ]
♪ I DON'T THINK THAT WE'RE
MISTAKEN ♪
♪ IT SEEMS ALL THE GOOD ONES ARE
TAKEN ♪
♪ I REALLY FEEL THAT AT THIS
RATE ♪
♪ WE'LL NEVER FIND THE PERFECT
DATE ♪
All: ♪ DON'T WANT TO QUIT AND
GIVE UP HOPE ♪
DOING ANYTHING SPECIAL FOR
HEARTS AND HOOVES DAY?
♪ OH, PLEASE, OH, PLEASE, OH,
PLEASE SAY... ♪
NOPE.
[ GASPS ]
♪ WE DID IT, GIRLS ♪
♪ WE FOUND THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL SEND OUR TEACHER'S
HEART AFLUTTER ♪
WAIT A MINUTE.
LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
ARE YOU TALKING 'BOUT MY
BROTHER?
SWEETIE BELLE IS RIGHT.
BIG MACINTOSH IS THE PERFECT
MATCH FOR MISS CHEERILEE.
HE'S REALLY NICE.
SUPER-HARDWORKING.
HMM. BUT HE'S ALSO PRETTY SHY.
HE'S NEVER GONNA ASK
MISS CHEERILEE TO BE HIS VERY
SPECIAL SOMEPONY.
MAYBE HE DOESN'T HAVE TO.
HUH?
IF WE CAN GET BIG MAC AND
MISS CHEERILEE IN A REALLY
ROMANTIC SETTING, I BET SHE'LL
ASK HIM!
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN TO ME.
SO, WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S GET OUT THERE AND CREATE
THE PERFECT DAY!
All: YAY!
FLOWERS.
DON'T FORGET THE FLOWERS.
OOPS. I'M ON IT!
THEY'RE COMING.
THIS IS GONNA BE PERFECT.
MISS CHEERILEE IS GONNA HAVE THE
BEST HEARTS AND HOOVES DAY EVER!
WITH HER NEW VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY!
[ ALL GIGGLE ]
HI, GIRLS.
All: HI, MISS CHEERILEE.
SO, YOU THREE SAID YOU NEEDED
HELP IDENTIFYING A TREE YOU
FOUND HERE NEAR THE GAZEBO?
[ ZIP! ]
[ BLINK! ]
THAT'S AN APPLE TREE.
IS IT?
[ ALL GIGGLE ]
OH. SORRY, BIG BROTHER.
WE WENT AND FIXED UP THE GAZEBO
ALL ON OUR OWN.
SEE?
AS LONG AS YOU'RE HERE, WHY
NOT HAVE A BITE TO EAT FROM THIS
ROMANTIC-LOOKING PICNIC?
OH, GOSH.
SEEMS LIKE THERE'S ONLY ROOM FOR
TWO.
I GUESS WE'LL JUST BE GOIN',
THEN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ ZING! ]
[ ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
YOU REALLY THINK THIS WILL
WORK?
OF COURSE IT WILL WORK.
THEY'RE PERFECT FOR EACH OTHER.
BEAUTIFUL DAY WE'RE HAVING.
YEP.
ANY BIG PLANS FOR TONIGHT?
NOPE.
OH, COME ON, MISS CHEERILEE.
ASK HIM TO BE YOUR VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY.
[ GASPS ]
OH, MY GOSH! LOOK!
BIG MAC...
YEP.
YOU HAVE SOMETHING STUCK IN
YOUR TEETH.
[ RECORD SCRATCHES ]
OH, COME ON!
WELL, THIS HAS BEEN...
[ MUSIC RESUMES, DISTORTED ]
...STRANGE.
YEP.
I NEED TO GET GOING, BUT IT'S
ALWAYS GREAT RUNNING INTO A
GOOD FRIEND.
YEP.
DO YOU THINK IT JUST WASN'T
ROMANTIC ENOUGH?
MAYBE IT WAS TOO ROMANTIC.
[ SIGHS ]
EITHER WAY, WE FAILED.
OHH.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING ELSE
WE CAN --
OHH!
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE YOU THERE.
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
OH, IT'S OKAY, TWILIGHT.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I'VE JUST BEEN READING THE
MOST FASCINATING BOOK ABOUT
HEARTS AND HOOVES DAY.
DID YOU KNOW THAT THIS HOLIDAY
GOT ITS START BECAUSE OF A LOVE
POTION?
DID YOU SAY A LOVE POTION?
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT EVEN HAS THE RECIPE.
I...DON'T SUPPOSE WE COULD
BORROW THAT BOOK FOR A LITTLE
WHILE, DO YOU?
OF COURSE YOU CAN.
I HAVE ANOTHER BOOK HERE THAT I
THINK YOU'LL --
[ GIGGLING ]
TAKE A TUFT OF CLOUD...
[ CHOMP! ]
...A BRIGHT RAINBOW'S GLOW.
[ WHIRRING ]
STIR WITH A PEGASUS FEATHER.
[ YOINK! ]
HEY!
FAST, NOT SLOW.
SERVE IT TO PONIES WHO AREN'T IN
THE KNOW.
[ BUBBLE! BUBBLE! ]
I FEEL KIND OF BAD, TRICKING MY
BROTHER AND MISS CHEERILEE THIS
WAY.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WE ALL AGREE THESE TWO ARE
PERFECT FOR ONE ANOTHER.
YEAH.
THEY JUST NEED A LITTLE NUDGE.
AND WHAT COULD MAKE THEM
HAPPIER THAN BEING TOGETHER,
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
OH! OH! HERE THEY COME!
HI, MISS CHEERILEE!
HELLO AGAIN, GIRLS.
HELLO, BIG MAC.
WOULD YOU THREE LIKE TO TELL US
WHY IT WAS SO VERY IMPORTANT
THAT WE MEET YOU HERE?
PUNCH!
EXCUSE ME?
PUNCH. WE MADE PUNCH.
WE WERE GONNA SET UP A STAND AND
TRY TO SELL IT, BUT [CHUCKLES]
WE NEEDED SOMEPONY TO TASTE-TEST
IT FIRST.
YEP!
WE THOUGHT YOU TWO WOULD BE
PERFECT TOGETHER.
TO TEST IT.
TOGETHER.
SO, UH, WE'LL JUST LEAVE YOU TWO
ALONE.
[ ZIP! ]
TOGETHER. TO TEST IT.
[ GIGGLING ]
I'M VERY SORRY ABOUT THIS.
I MENTIONED TO THE GIRLS THAT I
DON'T HAVE A VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY, AND I BELIEVE THEY'RE
PUTTING US IN THESE AWKWARD
SITUATIONS BECAUSE THEY'VE
DECIDED IT SHOULD BE YOU.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
I SUPPOSE WE SHOULD JUST HUMOR
THEM FOR A MOMENT.
THIS PUNCH DOES LOOK DELICIOUS.
YEP.
I THINK THEY'RE GONNA DRINK
IT.
TO GOOD FRIENDS.
THEY'RE DRINKING IT.
THEY'RE DRINKING IT!
[ BOTH HICCUP ]
[ BUBBLE! ]
THEY'RE LOOKING INTO EACH
OTHER'S EYES.
[ ALL GIGGLE ]
All: THEY'RE ABOUT TO BE IN
FOR A BIG SURPRISE.
BIG MAC...
YEP.
WILL YOU BE MY VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY?
YEP.
YES!
All: ♪ HE'S HER SPECIAL
SOMEPONY ♪
♪ SHE'S HIS SPECIAL SOMEPONY ♪
HE'S MY SPECIAL SOMEPONY.
Y-Y-Y-YEP.
All: AWW!
HE'S MY SCHMOOPY-DOOPY,
SWEETIE-WEETIE PONY PIE.
YOU'RE MY SCHMOOPY-DOOPY,
DID HE JUST SAY...
SWEETIE-WEETIE PONY PIE.
YOU'RE MY CUTIE-PATOOTIE,
DID HE JUST SAY...
LOVEY-DOVEY HONEY BUNNY.
YOU'RE MY CUTIE-PATOOTIE,
YOU'RE MY HEARTY-SMARTY,
LOVEY-DOVEY HONEY BUNNY.
SMOOCHY-WOOCHIE BABY WABY.
YOU'RE MY HEARTY-SMARTY,
BIG MAC! HEY!
SMOOCHY-WOOCHIE BABY WABY.
HELLO?!
BIG MAC! HEY!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HELLO?!
MISS CHEERILEE, ARE YOU ALL
WHAT'S GOING ON?
RIGHT?
MISS CHEERILEE, ARE YOU ALL
I HAVE A SPECIAL SOMEPONY --
RIGHT?
A KISSY-WISSY, SNUGGY-WUGGY,
I HAVE A SPECIAL SOMEPONY --
SUGAR BEAR.
A KISSY-WISSY, SNUGGY-WUGGY,
[ SQUEAK! ]
SUGAR BEAR.
I THINK WE MAY HAVE GIVEN
[ SQUEAK! ]
THEM TOO BIG OF A NUDGE.
I THINK WE MAY HAVE GIVEN
YOU'RE MY CUDDLY-WUDDLY...
THEM TOO BIG OF A NUDGE.
BLAH!
YOU'RE MY CUDDLY-WUDDLY...
...PUMPKIN PIE.
BLAH!
YOU THINK?
WHAT HAVE WE DONE?!
MY BROTHER'S ACTING LIKE A
GRADE-A GOOFBALL!
MAYBE WE ADDED TOO MUCH
RAINBOW.
OR MAYBE NOT ENOUGH CLOUD.
OR MAYBE...
UH-OH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "UH-OH"?
WE MIGHT NOT HAVE GIVEN
BIG MAC AND MISS CHEERILEE A
LOVE POTION.
WE MAY HAVE GIVEN THEM A LOVE
POISON!
Both: WHAT?!
APPARENTLY, SOME PRINCE A
LONG TIME AGO WHIPPED UP THIS
RECIPE AND GAVE IT TO THIS
PRINCESS HE LIKED.
HE MEANT IT TO BE A LOVE POTION,
BUT THINGS DIDN'T TURN OUT SO
WELL.
HOW "NOT SO WELL" DID THINGS
TURN OUT?
WELL, THERE'S SOMETHING HERE
ABOUT A DRAGON, A KINGDOM
FALLING, CHAOS REIGNING.
OKAY.
APPARENTLY, IT WAS ALL BECAUSE
THE PRINCE AND PRINCESS WERE SO
LOST IN EACH OTHER'S EYES THAT
THEY COULDN'T PERFORM THEIR
ROYAL DUTIES.
GREAT!
WE'VE NOT ONLY TURNED BIG MAC
AND MISS CHEERILEE INTO A COUPLE
OF NONSENSE-SPOUTING
NINCOMPOOPS, WE MAY HAVE PUT ALL
OF PONYVILLE IN JEOPARDY!
[ THUD! ]
COME ON, APPLE BLOOM.
MISS CHEERILEE AND BIG MAC DON'T
HAVE ANY ROYAL DUTIES.
BUT THEY STILL GOT
RESPONSIBILITIES.
IF WE DON'T FIX THIS -- OH,
NO -- MISS CHEERILEE WON'T BE
ABLE TO TEACH.
BIG MAC WON'T BE ABLE TO HARVEST
ANY APPLES.
AND, BEFORE YOU KNOW IT...
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
...PONYVILLE WILL BE OVERRUN
WITH UNEDUCATED LITTLE PONIES
STARVED FOR APPLES.
OH, IT'LL BE CHAOS.
IT'LL BE CHAOS!
[ WHIFFLE! ]
THERE'S AN ANTIDOTE.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SO?
DIDN'T YOU SEE ME GETTING ALL
PANICKED BACK THERE?
IF WE CAN KEEP MISS CHEERILEE
AND BIG MAC FROM LOOKING INTO
EACH OTHER'S EYES FOR ONE FULL
HOUR, THE LOVE CURSE WILL BE
BROKEN.
ONLY AN HOUR?
PUH!
WE CAN PULL THAT OFF IN A
SECOND.
YOU TAKE THE FIRST SIP,
SNOOGLE-WOOGLES.
NO, YOU TAKE IT,
SHNOODLEBUNNY.
NO, YOU, SHNOOKY-LIPS.
NO, YOU, POOKIE-PIE.
I'M ALL FOR ROMANCE, BUT THIS
HAS BEEN GOING ON FOR HOURS.
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO THESE TWO?
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
WHO KNOWS?
WELL, THESE LOVEBIRDS WILL
PROBABLY BE PLANNING A WEDDING
SOON.
WE CAN ALWAYS USE THE CATERING
BUSINESS.
A WEDDING! THAT'S IT!
MISS CHEERILEE AND BIG MAC
SHOULD GET MARRIED!
HOW IS GETTIN' HITCHED GONNA
KEEP THEM APART?
THEY AREN'T REALLY GONNA GET
MARRIED.
THEY'RE JUST GONNA GET READY TO
GET MARRIED.
NO, YOU, BISCUIT-WISCUIT
BEAR.
NOPE, YOU,
HUGGIE-WUGGIE-SNUGGIE BUNNY.
HI, MISS CHEERILEE.
HOW ARE YOU?
I HAVE A VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY.
YEAH. WE NOTICED.
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
GOSH!
YOU TWO ARE SO IN LOVE, THE NEXT
THING YOU KNOW, YOU'LL BE
GETTING MARRIED.
[ SMACK! ]
Both: MARRIED?!
THAT'S RIGHT -- MARRIED.
Both: MARRIED.
[ GURGLES ]
YUCK!
[ SQUEAK! ]
'COURSE, IF YOU'RE GONNA GET
MARRIED, YOU WANT TO PICK OUT A
REALLY NICE DIAMOND FOR YOUR...
YUCK!
...SHMOOPY-DOOPY POOKIE PIE.
DIAMOND!
SHMOOPY!
DON'T YOU THINK YOU SHOULD
START LOOKING FOR YOUR WEDDING
DRESS?
YOU'LL WANT TO LOOK YOUR BEST
FOR YOUR...
HONEY-BUNNY SNUGGLE BABY.
OH! YOU'RE RIGHT!
NOW WE JUST NEED TO KEEP THEM
APART.
I'LL KEEP MISS CHEERILEE
OCCUPIED.
YOU TWO DO THE SAME WITH
BIG MAC.
NO PROBLEM!
[ BELL TOLLS ]
MEET YOU BACK AT THE
CLUBHOUSE IN AN HOUR, WHEN THIS
WHOLE MESS IS OVER.
THIS ONE LOOKS NICE.
BETTER TRY IT ON, THOUGH.
[ BELL TOLLS ]
10 MINUTES DOWN.
50 MINUTES TO GO.
[ RATTLE! RATTLE! RATTLE! ]
NO.
NOT THAT ONE, EITHER.
TOO SHINY.
NO.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING LESS SHINY.
[ GROANS ]
MISS CHEERILEE DESERVES THE
BEST.
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
HOW MUCH TIME IS LEFT?
I'M RUNNING OUT OF WAYS TO MAKE
DIAMONDS SOUND BAD.
WE STILL HAVE 25 MINUTES.
OHH!
[ POINK! ]
WHERE'S MY BROTHER?
HE MADE HIS PURCHASE AND
DEPARTED OUT THE BACK.
SAID SOMETHING ABOUT NEEDING TO
SEE HIS...SHNOOPY-SHMOO.
UGH!
OKAY.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO SLOW THEM
DOWN.
YOU GO ON TO CAROUSEL BOUTIQUE
AND WARN SWEETIE BELLE.
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ SPLAT! SPLAT! SPLAT! SPLAT! ]
[ SCRAPE! ]
[ ZOOM! ZIP! ]
[ TWANG! ]
MOO!
OH!
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
[ GASPS ]
[ PANTING ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHERE'S APPLE BLOOM?
WHERE'S BIG MAC?
[ Breathlessly ] ON...HIS...
WAY.
GOT TO...KEEP HIM...
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
...OUT OF...BOUTIQUE!
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ TWANG! ]
HUH?!
[ CREAK! ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ RUMBLE! ]
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
[ POINK! ]
MOVE AWAY!
HE'LL GET TO HER!
HE'S SO STRONG!
[ CREAK! SNAP! ]
LET HIM GO!
SHNOOPY-DOO!
WHOA!
[ POING! ]
[ SIGHS ]
I SURE AM GLAD YOU FOUND THOSE
SHOVELS.
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
OH!
ONE MORE MINUTE, AND THE SPELL
WILL BE BROKEN!
SHNOOPY-DOOOO!
SWEETUMS?!
[ CRUNCH! CRUNCH! CRASH! ]
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
[ CRACK! CRACK! ]
[ CRASH! ]
SHNOOPY-DOOOO!
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
[ STRIKE! ]
[ Slo-mo ] N-O-O-O!
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
OH! PLEASE BE NORMAL!
PLEASE BE NORMAL!
AM I WEARING A WEDDING VEIL?
YEP.
ARE YOU SITTING ON A FEATHER
BED IN A HOLE IN THE GROUND?
YEP.
GIRLS!
CAN YOU EXPLAIN WHY I LOOK LIKE
I'M GETTING MARRIED AT THE
BOTTOM OF A PIT?
WE MAY HAVE GIVEN YOU THE
TEENY, TINIEST BIT OF LOVE
POTION THAT MAY HAVE TURNED OUT
TO ACTUALLY BE A LOVE POISON,
AND YOU MAY HAVE GONE JUST A
TEENY, TINIEST BIT NUTTY.
BUT WE ONLY DID IT BECAUSE WE
THOUGHT YOU AND BIG MAC WOULD BE
REALLY HAPPY IF YOU COULD BE
EACH OTHER'S VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONIES ON
HEARTS AND HOOVES DAY.
OUR HEARTS AND HOOVES WERE IN
THE RIGHT PLACE.
WE APPRECIATE THAT YOU CARE
ABOUT US AND WANT US TO BE
HAPPY, BUT...
BUT NO MATTER HOW GOOD OUR
INTENTIONS MIGHT HAVE BEEN, WE
SHOULD HAVE NEVER MEDDLED IN
YOUR RELATIONSHIP.
NO PONY CAN FORCE TWO PONIES
TO BE TOGETHER.
IT'S UP TO EVERY PONY TO
CHOOSE THAT VERY SPECIAL
SOMEPONY FOR THEMSELVES.
All: WE'RE SORRY.
AND YOU CAN THINK ABOUT HOW
SORRY YOU ARE WHILE YOU'RE DOING
ALL OF BIG MAC'S CHORES AT
SWEET APPLE ACRES.
DOES THAT SEEM LIKE A FAIR
PUNISHMENT TO YOU?
YEP.
[ ALL SIGH, GROAN ]
HEY, THERE, MISS CHEERILEE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
SINCE YOU THREE ARE DOING ALL
OF HIS CHORES, BIG MAC AND I
THOUGHT WE'D HAVE A PICNIC AT
THE GAZEBO.
READY, SUGAR BEAR?
YEP, PUMPKIN PIE.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ TINK! ]
All: N-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪