TODAY'S THE DAY,
CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS!
I CAN JUST FEEL IT.
TODAY'S THE DAY
WE ARE ALL GONNA GET
OUR CUTIE MARKS IN...
BOWLING!
WHOO-HOO!
[ Muffled ] WHOO!
PLEH!
I MEAN, YAY!!
WHY, AFTER TODAY,
WE WON'T EVEN BE THE CUTIE MARK
CRUSADERS ANYMORE.
WE'LL BE THE...
THE THREE STRIKES!
THAT MAKES US SOUND LIKE
WE STRUCK OUT.
HMM.
HOW ABOUT THE PIN TWINS?
BUT THERE ARE THREE
OF US.
OKAY, THEN.
UM, THE BOWLING DOLLS!
THE BOWLING DOLLS.
THAT'S IT.
PERFECT.
ALL RIGHTY, THEN.
LET'S BOWL THEM OVER.
[ BOWLING PINS RATTLE ]
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
[ ZIP! ]
PEH!
[ PONIES CHEERING ]
COOL!
A BOWLING CUTIE MARK!
I DID IT! I DID IT!
BLANK?
[ PONIES CHEERING ]
BUT...BUT...
BUT WHAT ABOUT MY BALL?
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
THAT BOWLING SURE WAS FUN,
EVEN IF ALL I GOT
WAS GUTTER BALLS.
YEAH. AT LEAST YOU'RE ABLE TO
KEEP YOUR BALL IN YOUR LANE.
I DON'T THINK MR. KINGPIN
IS EVER GONNA LET ME
PLAY AGAIN.
[ SCREECH! ]
HEY, MAYBE I COULD GET
MY CUTIE MARK IN DEMOLITION!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
AW, COME ON, APPLE BLOOM.
I KNOW JUST WHAT YOU NEED
TO PUT THE BLOOM BACK
ON YOUR APPLE.
A TREAT FROM SUGARCUBE CORNER
WILL CHEER YOU UP.
NO, IT WON'T.
[ TOOT! ]
[ BOING! ]
A PARTY WILL CHEER YOU UP!
[ TOOT!! ]
NO, IT WON'T.
[ THUD! ]
A LOVELY NEW CHAPEAU
WILL CHEER YOU UP.
NO, IT WON'T.
COME ON, APPLE BLOOM!
IT'S JUST A CUTIE MARK.
OR LACK OF A CUTIE MARK!
Shh!
THAT'S NOT HELPING!
APPLE BLOOM,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
APPLE BLOOM, COME BACK!
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER, REVS ]
WHOA!
OOH! UH! OOH! OH! UGH!
OHH!
WELL, WHO IS IT
THAT WE HAVE HERE?
WHY, IT'S APPLE BLOOM,
MY DEAR.
OH!
WHAT HAS HAPPENED TO YOU,
YOUTH?
AH, YOU'VE GONE
AND CHIPPED YOUR TOOTH.
COME WITH ME.
I HAVE JUST THE TRICK THAT
WILL FIX YOU UP QUITE QUICK.
Apple Bloom: [ Lisping ]
I'VE TRIED EVERYTHING, ZECORA,
AND STILL NO CUTIE MARK.
I'M GONNA BE AS OLD
AS GRANNY SMITH
AND STILL HAVE A BLANK FLANK.
YOUR FRUSTRATION
IS WELL UNDERSTOOD,
BUT ONE MUST BE PATIENT
FOR ALL THINGS GOOD.
UGH! I'VE HEARD THAT
FROM EVERY PONY I KNOW
AND NOW FROM EVERY ZEBRA
I KNOW.
I'M JUST TOO IMPATIENT
TO BE PATIENT.
I JUST WANT MY CUTIE MARK
AND I WANT IT NOW!
[ BOOM! ]
[ ZIP! ]
FOR YOUR CUTIE MARK,
YOU WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
WE MUST FIX THAT TOOTH
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
NOW, DRINK DOWN
EVERY LITTLE DROP,
AND THIS MIXTURE WILL MEND
THAT CHIP ON TOP.
[ GULP! GULP! ]
[ DING! ]
[ Normal voice ]
OH, MY STAR APPLES.
YOU DID IT, ZECORA!
GOLLY.
YOU HAVE TONICS THAT HEAL
ALL SORTS OF AILMENTS --
"BAD BONES, BAD BACK,
BAD BREATH."
YES, LITTLE ONE.
IT IS TRUE.
I HAVE MANY A HEALING BREW.
AND NOT ONLY STUFF
THAT FIXES THE BAD,
BUT STUFF
THAT BRINGS THE GOOD.
"GOOD HEALTH, GOOD HAIR,"
GOOD HEAVENS!
HMM.
I BET YOU CAN MIX UP A BREW
TO FIX ANYTHING.
THERE ARE MANY MIXTURES
IN THIS ROOM,
BUT NONE FOR WHAT YOU WANT,
DEAR APPLE BLOOM.
A MAGIC POTION DOES NOT HOLD
THE KEY FOR A CUTIE MARK.
TIME IS THE ONLY REMEDY.
FINE.
[ RATTLE ]
WHATCHA GOT GOING ON THERE?
I AM BREWING UP
ANOTHER MIX
FOR A ROOSTER
AND HIS CHICKS.
IT SEEMS THE ROOSTER
HAS LOST HIS CROW,
MAKING MORNINGS VERY SLOW.
HEY! I'VE SEEN THAT FLOWER
BLOOMING IN PONYVILLE.
WHAT IS IT?
IT IS ONE WE CALL
HEART'S DESIRE.
A DASH WILL IGNITE
THE ROOSTER'S FIRE.
WITH HEART'S DESIRE,
HIS TALENT COMES INTO VIEW,
AND HE'LL GIVE A MIGHTY
COCK-A-DOODLE-DOO!
ZOWIE!
HEART'S DESIRE, HUH?
AY, ME.
BUT WHAT IS THIS?
I'VE RUN OUT OF AMETHYST.
I MUST GO GET
THIS PURPLE FLOWER
FOR MY BREW TO HAVE
FULL POWER.
YEAH, YOU GO. YOU GO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M SO HUNGRY.
YEAH, I CAN'T WAIT --
Both: UHH!
APPLE BLOOM!
YOU GOT YOUR CUTIE MARK!
[ DING! ]
UM, APPLE BLOOM,
WHAT IS IT?
YEAH?
IS IT AN "O"?
IS YOUR TALENT SPELLING?
OR IS IT A RING?
ARE YOU A JEWELRY-MAKER?
OR IS IT A POWDERED DOUGHNUT?
'CAUSE THAT SOUNDS DELICIOUS!
NO. IT'S A LOOPTY-HOOP!
[ GASPS ]
A WHAT, NOW?
A LOOPTY-HOOP.
AT LEAST THAT'S
WHAT I ALWAYS CALLED IT.
APPLEJACK MADE IT FOR ME
FROM AN OLD RAIN BARREL
WHEN I WAS LITTLER.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT
LOOPTY-HOOPING WOULD END UP
BEING MY SPECIAL TALENT?
WOW, APPLE BLOOM!
THAT'S AMAZING!
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S YOUR TALENT?
SPINNING A HOOP
AROUND YOUR WAIST?
PUH-LEASE.
OH, YOU AIN'T SEEN NOTHING YET.
[ PONIES CHEERING ]
APPLE BLOOM, YOU'RE
A SUPER-DUPER LOOPTY-HOOPER!
THANKS, AMBER PONY.
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]
ALL RIGHT, MY LITTLE PONIES.
TIME FOR CLASS.
OH, WOW.
WOW.
APPLE BLOOM?
YES, MISS CHEERILEE?
I WANT YOU TO TAKE YOUR
LOOPTY-HOOP INTO THE YARD...
AND GIVE US ALL A LESSON ON YOUR
AMAZING LOOPTY-HOOPING!
All: YAY!
OH. OH!
WHOA! UGH!
DON'T WORRY, GALS.
KEEP AT IT, AND YOU MIGHT GET
TO BE HALF AS GOOD AS ME!
GRRR!
[ BOING! BOING! ]
GREAT JOB, GIRLS!
YOU'RE TOO KIND,
APPLE BLOOM.
YEAH, WE STINK.
NAH. YOU JUST NEED
A LITTLE PRACTICE.
SOON YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO HOOP AND BOP!
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
AND HOP.
[ Muffled ] HOOP AND SKIP.
AND HOOP AND FLIP!
[ PONIES CHEERING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
SHOW US SOME MORE, APPLE BLOOM.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
JUST A FEW MORE TRICKS.
BUT BE WARNED.
THESE ARE ADVANCED MOVES,
NOT FOR BEGINNERS.
GOT THAT, DIAMOND TIARA?
[ ZIP! ]
GRRR!
I CALL THIS ONE THE HOOPLA!
[ WHIR! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
HUH?
[ THUD! ]
OOH!
ANOTHER CUTIE MARK?
HA!
I GUESS THAT LAST TRICK
WAS A LOT OF HOOPLA.
THOSE CUTE MARKS ARE FAKE!
[ ALL GASP ]
WHAT?
NO, THEY'RE NOT!
MISS CHEERILEE,
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF A PONY
WITH TWO CUTIE MARKS?
Miss Cheerilee:
I MUST SAY THAT I NEVER HAVE,
BUT MAYBE APPLE BLOOM
HAS TWO SPECIAL TALENTS.
OH, YEAH?
THEN LET'S SEE YOU DO THAT.
SPIN PLATES.
YEAH!
[ ALL GASP ]
TWO CUTIE MARKS?
TWO TALENTS?
AW, YEAH!
OUR FRIEND IS THE MOST
SPECIAL PONY EVER!
ALL RIGHT, EVERYPONY.
YOU READY FOR A REAL SHOW?
[ CHEERING ]
[ SNORING ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ BOING! ]
[ PONIES CHEERING ]
[ WHISTLES ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ PONIES CHEERING ]
YEEHA, LITTLE SIS!
CONGRATULATIONS ON GETTING NOT
JUST ONE, BUT TWO CUTIE MARKS!
OH, WE'RE MIGHTY PROUD OF YOU.
RIGHT, BIG MACINTOSH?
YE-E-P.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
HAVE YOU, BIG MAC?
NO.
RIGHT AWAY YOU WERE
A-HOOPING AND A-HOPPING
AND KICKING AND SPINNING!
REMINDED ME OF WHEN I WAS
A SPRY YOUNG FILLY.
[ SPROING! ]
UGH! CHARLIE HORSE!
CHARLIE HORSE!
[ BOING! ]
OOH!
THAT'S BETTER.
WHY, APPLE BLOOM.
I THINK YOU'RE READY TO HIT
THE RODEO CIRCUIT RIGHT NOW.
ACTUALLY, I'M READY
TO HIT THE HAY RIGHT NOW.
I'M PLUM TUCKERED.
I'LL SEE Y'ALL IN THE MORNING.
NIGHT.
OH, MY. LITTLE APPLE BLOOM
HAS FINALLY BLOSSOMED.
HASN'T SHE, BIG MAC?
YE-E-P.
[ HOOFBEATS TAPPING ]
UGH. UGH.
OHH!
WHAT IN TARNATION IS THAT?
[ TAPPING CONTINUES ]
APPLE BLOOM,
WHAT IS ALL THAT AWFUL...
...TAPPING?
[ GASPS ]
THREE CUTIE MARKS?
HELP ME!
COME HERE, YOU!
OW! OW! OW.
WHOA!
I'M SORRY, APPLEJACK!
I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO MAKE IT STOP!
WELL, I KNOW SOMEPONY
WHO MIGHT.
THREE CUTIE MARKS.
THREE TALENTS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE IT.
I WAS JUST READING SOMETHING
ABOUT UNUSUAL EQUINE ILLNESSES.
WHAT WAS IT?
Spike: "PERPLEXING
PONY PLAGUES," PERHAPS?
YES, SPIKE.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
YES, WELL, I DO
HAVE SOME TALENTS.
"HAY FEVER, THE TROTS."
[ GASPS ]
"CUTIE POX"!
All: CUTIE POX?!
"CUTIE POX.
THIS PUZZLING PONY PLAGUE
"AFFLICTED A POPULATION
OF PONIES
BACK IN
THE PALEO-PONY PERIOD."
SAY THAT 10 TIMES FAST.
[ THUD! ]
"RANDOM CUTIE MARKS APPEARED
ALL OVER THE PONIES' BODIES,
"CAUSING THEM TO PERFORM
ALL THE TALENTS
THAT CAME WITH THEM."
JUST LIKE ME!
YES, BUT WHAT'S THE CURE?
WHAT'S THE CURE?!
IT SAYS HERE
THERE'S NO KNOWN CURE.
All: NO KNOWN CURE?!
THE CAUSE OF THE BREAKOUT
WAS NEVER DISCOVERED,
AND THE CUTIE POX DISAPPEARED
AS MYSTERIOUSLY AS THEY ARRIVED.
OH, NO!
[ TWINKLE! ]
SACRE BLEU!
[ SPEAKING FRENCH ]
[ GASPS ]
QU'EST-CE QUE C'EST?
[ SPEAKING FRENCH ]
MY SISTER'S
SPEAKING IN FANCY!
SHE NEEDS HELP.
I KNOW SHE NEEDS HELP.
WE CAN'T JUST WAIT
FOR THIS TO GO AWAY.
WE GOT TO FIND SOME PONY
TO MIX UP A CURE -- AND FAST!
Apple Bloom: TOUTE DE SUITE!
NOT SOME PONY, SOME ZEBRA!
ZECORA!
HURRY! HURRY!
[ SPEAKING FRENCH ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ ROAR! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
SHE'S CURSED.
HEXED!
ENCHANTED!
NO, SHE'S NOT.
[ SIGHS ]
OH.
SHE JUST HAS SOME WEIRD,
MYSTERIOUS DISEASE
WITH NO KNOWN CURE
CALLED CUTIE POX.
All: CUTIE POX?!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ BIRD SCREECHES ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
I THOUGHT I HAD REMOVED
THEIR FEAR
THE LAST TIME
THAT I VISITED HERE.
BUT DOORS ARE BARRED
AND SHUTTERS SHUT.
GUESS I SHOULD HAVE STAYED
INSIDE MY HUT.
ZECORA!
APPLE BLOOM HAS CUTIE POX!
WE WERE JUST ON OUR WAY
TO SEE IF YOU HAD A CURE.
BUT MAGICALLY YOU'RE HERE.
WAS YOUR ZEBRA SENSE
A-TINGLING?
MY ZEBRA SENSE
DID NOT BRING ME 'ROUND.
IT WAS A SPECIAL FLOWER
THAT I NEEDED FOUND.
I THOUGHT I'D PICKED ENOUGH
TO FIX
ALL THE POTIONS I HAD TO MIX,
BUT AFTER MY VISIT
FROM APPLE BLOOM,
SOME HAD MYSTERIOUSLY
LEFT MY ROOM.
APPLE BLOOM,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DID THIS FLOWER
JUST WALK AWAY?
[ TWINKLE! ]
I, UM...
[ ZIP! ]
A CUTIE POX CURE
I HAVE FORSOOTH.
FOR HEALING POWER IS
IN THE SEEDS OF TRUTH.
W-WELL, THEN, GIVE THEM
TO HER. QUICK!
THESE SEEDS MUST BE PLANTED
IN THE GROUND.
WITH THE TRUTH, THEY'LL GROW,
AND THE CURE IS FOUND.
COME AGAIN?
THE SEEDS OF TRUTH
DO HOLD THE CURE,
BUT ONE MUST SPEAK WORDS
TRUE AND PURE.
HUH. WELL, THEN,
LET'S GET TO IT!
ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE PLANTED.
NOW, SOMEPONY TELL THE TRUTH!
[ TWINKLE! ]
WHOA!
NO, NO, NO!
WHO-O-A!
SOMEPONY! ANYPONY!
Apple Bloom: WHOA! WHOO!
YESTERDAY I TOLD MRS. CAKE
THAT I ATE TWO CORN CAKES,
BUT I REALLY ATE THREE.
OKAY, SIX!
I ATE SIX CORN CAKES!
[ SOBS ]
MAKE IT STOP!
OH, MAKE IT STOP!
Apple Bloom: UHH!
OH, I CAN'T STAND IT ANYMORE!
IT'S ME! I ADMIT IT!
I DIDN'T EARN MY CUTIE MARK!
THEY'RE ALL FAKE!
I FIGURED THE HEART'S DESIRE
WOULD HELP ME GET
WHAT I WANTED MOST.
SO WHEN ZECORA LEFT HER HUT,
I MIXED UP A SPECIAL POTION
AND PUT THE REST
OF THE HEART'S DESIRE IN IT.
[ TINKLING ]
All: WHOA!
[ GULP! ]
[ GULPS, SIGHS ]
[ THUD! ]
APPLE BLOOM!
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M GREAT.
AND I'VE NEVER BEEN HAPPIER
TO BE A BLANK FLANK.
BUT I'M AWFUL SORRY I LIED,
ESPECIALLY TO YOU GALS.
I WAS SO DESPERATE
FOR MY CUTIE MARK,
I JUST GOT CARRIED AWAY.
AND I'M REALLY SORRY I SNUCK
THOSE FLOWERS FROM YOU, ZECORA.
WHY, I WOULDN'T BLAME YOU
IF YOU NEVER WANTED ME
TO COME BY AGAIN.
NOW, APPLE BLOOM.
DO NOT BE SILLY.
YOU ARE ALWAYS WELCOME,
MY LITTLE FILLY.
WITH EACH MISTAKE,
YOU LEARN SOMETHING NEW,
GROWING UP
INTO A BETTER YOU.
APPLE BLOOM, WOULD YOU MIND
WRITING TO PRINCESS CELESTIA
AND TELLING HER
WHAT YOU LEARNED?
I'D BE HAPPY TO, TWILIGHT.
SPIKE?
READY.
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
"WAITING FOR WHAT YOUR HEART
DESIRES CAN BE REALLY HARD.
"SO YOU MAY TRY TO TAKE
A SHORTCUT.
"WELL, THIS DISHONESTY
NEVER WORKS
"BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T EARN
WHAT YOUR HEART DESIRES.
"THE ONLY CURE IS BEING HONEST
WITH YOURSELF AND OTHERS,
AND THAT'S SOMETHING
EVERY HEART DESIRES."
[ FOOSH! ]
I SURE AM PROUD
OF YOU, SIS.
SEEMS LIKE
YOU FINALLY LEARNED
THE IMPORTANCE OF PATIENCE.
YEP. ALL GOOD THINGS
COME TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
WELL, I'VE WAITED
LONG ENOUGH.
[ POING! ]
ACTUALLY,
THAT WAS WAY TOO LONG.
WHAT?!
SO WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO TODAY
TO EARN OUR CUTIE MARKS?
WELL, I WAS THINKING.
FOR A PONY WHO'S NEVER MIXED UP
A POTION BEFORE,
YOU SURE STIRRED UP
SOMETHING FIERCE.
YEAH. SO WHAT IF YOUR TALENT
IS POTION-MAKING?
[ Chuckling ]
OH, MY GOSH! TOTALLY!
LET'S GO TALK
TO ZECORA...NOW!
YEAH!
WHOO-HOO!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪