[ TOOT! TOOT! TOOT! ]
WE'RE GETTING CLOSER.
I CAN HARDLY WAIT!
I'M SO EXCITED,
I FEEL LIKE SHOUTING.
WHOO-HOO!
WHOO-WEE!
CANTERLOT, HERE WE COME!
OH, I DO HOPE
I LOOK FESTIVE ENOUGH.
THERE IT IS -- CANTERLOT!
All: OOH!
Twilight Sparkle: OH,
ISN'T CANTERLOT WONDERFUL
THIS TIME OF YEAR?
YEAH. I WISH IT WAS HEARTH'S
WARMING EVE EVERY DAY.
THERE'S SO MUCH TO LOOK AT!
I FEEL LIKE MY DARN EYES ARE
GONNA POP RIGHT OUT OF MY HEAD.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
LET'S PLAY "I SPY WITH
MY LITTLE EYE" AS WE WALK.
I'LL GO FIRST.
I SPY
AN 8-FOOT CANDY CANE.
I SPY A SNOW PONY!
I SPY SOMEPONY EATING
A GINGERBREAD HOUSE.
[ CHOMP! ]
AND IT'S ME!
MMM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
Twilight Sparkle:
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
PRINCESS CELESTIA CHOSE US
TO PUT ON THE MOST IMPORTANT
PLAY OF THE SEASON.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT AN HONOR
THIS IS FOR ALL OF US?
OH, I WISH SHE HADN'T HONORED ME
QUITE SO MUCH.
I CAN'T GO ON STAGE!
I DON'T WANT EVERY PONY
LOOKING AT ME!
FLUTTERSHY, DARLING, THERE'S
NOTHING TO FEEL NERVOUS ABOUT.
NO?
OF COURSE NOT!
ALL ACROSS EQUESTRIA, PONIES
ARE PREPARING THEIR OWN PAGEANT
FOR HEARTH'S WARMING EVE
IN THEIR OWN TOWNS.
IT'S TRADITION.
SO, YOU'RE SAYING THEY'LL BE
TOO BUSY TO COME TO OUR PLAY?
WELL, NO.
WE'RE IN
THE CANTERLOT PAGEANT --
THE BIGGEST, MOST IMPORTANT
PRODUCTION IN ALL EQUESTRIA.
A LOT OF PONIES
WILL COME TO WATCH US.
A LOT?
HUNDREDS.
HUNDREDS?
[ GASPS ]
MAYBE EVEN THOUSANDS!
[ ZIP! ]
[ WIND GUSTS ]
OH! MY HAIR!
APPLEJACK, BE A DEAR AND SHUT
THOSE WINDOWS, WILL YOU?
RAINBOW DASH!
THANK YOU!
IT'S A RE-ENACTMENT OF
THE FOUNDING OF EQUESTRIA.
IT'S NOT
THE RAINBOW DASH SHOW.
WELL, IT SHOULD BE
I'M THE STAR.
FLUTTERSHY, YOU'VE GOT
TO COME OUT OF THERE.
CURTAIN IN TWO MINUTES.
TWILIGHT,
LET ME HANDLE THIS.
MY HAIR!
PINKIE!!
THE HEARTH'S WARMING EVE
PAGEANT
IS ABOUT HARMONY
AND FRIENDSHIP.
Together: SHUT THE WINDOW!
MM.
ONCE UPON A TIME, LONG BEFORE
THE PEACEFUL RULE OF CELESTIA
AND BEFORE PONIES DISCOVERED
OUR BEAUTIFUL LAND OF EQUESTRIA,
PONIES DID NOT KNOW HARMONY.
IT WAS A STRANGE
AND DARK TIME --
A TIME WHEN PONIES
WERE TORN APART BY HATRED.
[ ALL GASP ]
I KNOW.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
DURING THIS FRIGHTFUL AGE,
EACH OF THE THREE TRIBES --
THE PEGASI, THE UNICORNS,
AND THE EARTH PONIES --
CARED NOT FOR WHAT BEFELL
THE OTHER TRIBES,
BUT ONLY FOR THEIR OWN WELFARE.
IN THOSE TROUBLED TIMES, AS NOW,
THE PEGASI WERE THE STEWARDS
OF THE WEATHER.
BUT THEY DEMANDED SOMETHING
IN RETURN --
FOOD THAT COULD ONLY BE GROWN
BY THE EARTH PONIES.
THE UNICORNS
DEMANDED THE SAME...
...IN RETURN FOR MAGICALLY
BRINGING FORTH DAY AND NIGHT.
AND SO, MISTRUST BETWEEN
THE TRIBES FESTERED
UNTIL ONE FATEFUL DAY,
IT CAME TO A BOIL.
AND WHAT PROMPTED THE PONIES
TO CLASH?
'TWAS A MYSTERIOUS BLIZZARD
THAT OVERTOOK THE LAND
AND TOPPLED THE TRIBES'
PRECARIOUS PEACE.
THE NORMALLY INDUSTRIOUS
EARTH PONIES
WERE UNABLE TO FARM THEIR LAND.
[ WIND GUSTING ]
EARTH PONIES WERE FREEZING.
THE HOME OF THE PEGASI
FARED NO BETTER.
THE PEGASI WERE HUNGRY.
[ GULP! ]
AND THE UNICORNS
WERE FREEZING AND HUNGRY.
EVEN THE UNICORNS' MAGIC WAS
POWERLESS AGAINST THE STORM.
EACH TRIBE BLAMED THE OTHERS
FOR THEIR SUFFERING,
AND THE ANGRIER EVERYPONY GREW,
THE WORSE THE BLIZZARD BECAME.
AND SO, IT WAS DECIDED THAT
A GRAND SUMMIT WOULD BE HELD
TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO COPE WITH THE BLIZZARD.
EACH TRIBE SENT THEIR LEADERS.
[ HORNS SOUND ]
DAUGHTER OF THE UNICORN KING,
PRINCESS PLATINUM.
[ HORNS SOUND ]
RULER OF THE PEGASI,
COMMANDER HURRICANE.
AND LASTLY, LEADER OF THE EARTH
PONIES, CHANCELLOR PUDDING HEAD.
PERHAPS THE THREE TRIBES COULD
FINALLY SETTLE THEIR DIFFERENCES
AND AGREE ON A WAY TO GET
THROUGH THIS DISASTER.
[ ALL SHOUTING AT ONCE ]
ALL I WANT TO KNOW
IS WHY THE EARTH PONIES
ARE HOGGING ALL THE FOOD.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
US? WE'RE NOT HOGGING
ALL THE FOOD.
YOU ARE!
OH, WAIT. YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S US.
WELL, IT'S ONLY 'CAUSE
YOU MEAN OLD PEGASUSESES
ARE MAKING IT SNOW
LIKE CRAZY!
FOR THE HUNDREDTH TIME,
IT'S NOT US!
WE'RE NOT MAKING IT SNOW.
IT MUST BE THE UNICORNS.
THEY'RE DOING IT
WITH THEIR FREAKY MAGIC!
[ GASPS ]
HOW DARE YOU?
UNLIKE YOU PEGASI RUFFIANS,
WE UNICORNS WOULD NEVER STOOP
TO SUCH A THING.
HMPH!
All: HMPH!
WELL, IF YOU NON-EARTHS
AREN'T GONNA STOP USING YOUR
WEIRDO POWERS TO FREEZE US ALL,
THEN I'M JUST
PLUMB OUT OF IDEAS.
WHAT A SHOCKER --
AN EARTH PONY WITH NO IDEAS.
COMMANDER HURRICANE, PLEASE
CEASE WITH THE INSULTS!
YOU'RE NOT THE BOSS OF ME,
YOUR ROYAL SNOOTINESS!
I BEG YOUR PARDON!
I AM A PRINCESS!
I WON'T BE SPOKEN
TO THAT WAY.
WELL, I'M LEAVING FIRST.
NO, I'M FIRST!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
Spike:
AND THE BLIZZARD RAGED ON.
SO THE SUMMIT OF THE TRIBES
DID NOT TURN OUT
AS WELL AS HOPED,
AND THE THREE LEADERS RETURNED
HOME TO LICK THEIR WOUNDS
AND, BASICALLY, COMPLAIN.
ATTENTION!
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
WELL? AREN'T YOU CURIOUS
ABOUT HOW IT WENT?
OOH, COMMANDER HURRICANE,
SIR.
HOW DID IT GO, SIR?
HORRIBLY!
THOSE OTHER TRIBE LEADERS
ARE SO DISRESPECTFUL.
DON'T THEY REALIZE THAT WE
ARE A MIGHTY TRIBE OF WARRIORS
AND SHOULD NOT BE CROSSED?
WE HAVE GOT TO BREAK RIGHT
THROUGH THOSE WEAK FOALS.
[ SPLAT! ]
[ SHIVERING ]
CLOVER THE CLEVER,
I NEED YOU!
YES, YOUR MAJESTY?
DID THE OTHER PONY TRIBES
SEE REASON, AS I PREDICTED?
THOSE OTHER TRIBES
ARE IMPOSSIBLE!
I, FOR ONE,
CAN NO LONGER BEAR
TO BE ANYWHERE NEAR
THOSE LOWLY CREATURES.
THE UNICORNS
ARE NOBLE AND MAJESTIC.
WE WILL NO LONGER CONSORT
WITH THE LIKES OF THEM.
[ SPLASH! ]
WOULDN'T IT HAVE BEEN EASIER
TO USE THE DOOR, CHANCELLOR?
MAYBE FOR YOU, SMART COOKIE,
BUT I AM A CHANCELLOR.
I WAS ELECTED
BECAUSE I KNOW HOW
TO THINK OUTSIDE THE BOX,
WHICH MEANS I CAN ALSO THINK
INSIDE THE CHIMNEY.
CAN YOU THINK
INSIDE A CHIMNEY?
UH...
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
UGH.
OH, MY GOSH.
HOLD ON TO YOUR HOOVES!
I AM JUST ABOUT
TO BE BRILLIANT!
THAT'D BE A FIRST.
I HAVE DECIDED
THAT THE EARTH PONIES
ARE GONNA GO IT ALONE!
OH, SO YOU MEAN THE OTHER
TRIBES DIDN'T COME AROUND?
SHOOT.
I REALLY THOUGHT WE'D GET
THROUGH TO THEM IF WE --
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THEM.
WE'RE THE ONES
WITH ALL THE FOOD, RIGHT?
ACTUALLY, WE'RE ALL OUT.
FINE. THEN WE'LL HAVE TO GO
SOMEWHERE NEW
WHERE WE CAN GROW
SOME NEW FOOD,
AND WITH ME AS OUR FEARLESS
LEADER, WHAT COULD GO WRONG?
WHERE SHOULD I START?
[ POP! ]
THE POINT IS...
All: ...WE MUST FIND A NEW LAND.
COME ON, PRIVATE PANSY.
LET'S GET A MOVE ON.
HUP ONE, HUP TWO.
[ LIGHTNING CRASHES ]
AAH!
GET AHOLD OF YOURSELF,
PRIVATE!
WE CANNOT LET ANYTHING
DISTRACT US
FROM THE MISSION AT HAND --
TO FIND, AND, IF NECESSARY,
TO CONQUER A NEW LAND.
CONQUER, SIR?
NEVER KNOW WHERE ENEMIES
MIGHT BE LURKING.
I DON'T SEE ANY ENEMIES,
COMMANDER.
JUST SNOW.
AHA!
WHAT'S THAT?
[ SHRIEKS ]
OKAY.
THIS IS GETTING OLD.
THIS IS SIMPLY
TAKING FOREVER.
MY HOOVES ARE KILLING ME.
HOW LONG
HAVE WE BEEN WALKING FOR?
ABOUT FIVE MINUTES,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
[ SIGHS ]
I NEVER IMAGINED FINDING
A NEW LAND WOULD BE SO HARD.
BUT IT'LL ALL BE WORTH IT,
DON'T YOU AGREE?
I ACTUALLY THINK
THAT THE THREE TRIBES
COULD'VE TRIED HARDER.
STOP!
WHAT'S WRONG?
THAT IS WHAT'S WRONG.
YOUR HIGHNESS,
IT'S JUST A STREAM.
WE CAN CROSS IT EASILY.
I REFUSE
TO GET MY GOWN WET.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF ARRIVING AT MY NEW LAND
LOOKING LIKE A BEDRAGGLED
EARTH PONY,
OR WORSE YET,
A ROUGH-AND-TUMBLE PEGASUS.
I, FOR ONE,
HAVE NO INTENTION
OF STOOPING DOWN
TO THEIR LEVEL.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
I HAVE NO TROUBLE
WATCHING YOU STOOP DOWN.
UGH.
AND DO WATCH THE GOWN,
DARLING.
IT'S WORTH MORE THAN ALL
OF THE BOOKS IN YOUR LIBRARY.
YES, YES.
THIS IS DEFINITELY
THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
IT FEELS LIKE
WE'RE GOING IN CIRCLES.
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
ARE YOU SUGGESTING THAT
I'M READING THE MAP WRONG?
ABSOLUTELY NOT,
YOUR CHANCELLORNESS.
IT'S JUST THAT THERE ARE HOLES
IN THE MAP, AND --
OF COURSE!
HOW ELSE COULD I SEE
WHERE I WAS GOING?
YEAH. UH...
OR TALK?
I NEED TO BE ABLE TO TALK.
I MEAN,
HOW WOULD WE SURVIVE
IF I JUST SUDDENLY
SHUT UP?
HEAVEN FORBID THAT SHOULD
HAPPEN, YOUR CHANCELLORSHIP.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT'S JUST THAT THE MAP
IS ALSO UPSIDE DOWN.
I GOT A NEWS FLASH
FOR YOU, COOKIE.
THE EARTH IS ROUND.
THERE IS NO UP OR DOWN.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S SUCH A RELIEF TO ME
THAT YOU'RE IN CHARGE
OF THIS MAP.
RELIEF?
YOU DON'T NEED RELIEF.
IF ANYPONY NEEDS RELIEF
AROUND HERE, IT'S ME!
I'M A CHANCELLOR!
I'M A BIG SHOT.
YOU'RE JUST MY,
UH...MY...
SECRETARY.
WHATEVER.
YOU TAKE THE MAP
WHILE I ENJOY SOME RELIEF.
[ ZIP! ]
YES,
CHANCELLOR PUDDING HEAD.
AND SO, EACH LEADER ENCOUNTERED
OBSTACLES ALONG THE WAY,
BUT EVENTUALLY, THEY ALL ARRIVED
IN A NEW AND WONDROUS LAND.
NO PONY HAD EVER SEEN
PARADISE BEFORE.
THIS IS THE NEW LAND
WE'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR!
WHAT A VIEW!
I CAN SEE MY FUTURE HOUSE
FROM HERE.
I PROCLAIM THIS NEW LAND
TO BE...
PEGASOPOLIS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH JEWELS.
THIS RUBY IS DAZZLING.
THIS WHOLE LAND IS DAZZLING!
I'M DOUBLE DAZZLED!
[ SQUEALS ]
IN THE NAME OF THE UNICORNS, I
HEREBY DUB THIS LAND UNICORNIA.
THE AIR! THE TREES!
[ PLOP! ]
THE DIRT.
THIS DIRT IS THE DIRTIEST DIRT
IN THE WHOLE DIRT WORLD!
AND FERTILE, TOO --
PERFECT FOR GROWING FOOD.
IN THE NAME
OF THE EARTH PONIES,
I THINK I'M GONNA CALL THIS
NEW PLACE, UH, DIRTVILLE!
HOW ABOUT EARTH?
EARTH!
CONGRATULATIONS TO ME
FOR THINKING OF IT.
All: WE FOUND OUR NEW HOME!
I PLANTED MY FLAG FIRST!
DID NOT!
DID TO!
I PLANTED MINE
EARLIER THAN FIRST.
ALL OF YOU RIFFRAFF
ARE TRESPASSING IN UNICORNIA.
THE NAME IS PEGASOPOLIS.
EARTH!
PEGASOPOLIS!
UNICORNIA!
I SAY
WE FIGHT FOR THE LAND.
MAY THE BEST PONY WIN.
THAT'S BARBARIC.
CLOVER THE CLEVER, THROW
THAT BRUTE INTO THE DUNGEON!
WHAT DUNGEON?
LOOK, PERHAPS
IF WE ALL CALM DOWN...
I AGREE.
LET'S ALL CALM DOWN.
I VOTE FOR CALM.
I'LL HAVE YOU COURT-MARTIALED
FOR INSUBORDINATION, PRIVATE!
WE SETTLE THIS
ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
[ SPLAT! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ RATTLE! ]
WHO DARES THROW
A SNOWBALL AT ROYALTY?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHERE'D ALL THIS SNOW
COME FROM, ANYWAY?
OH, NO.
NOT AGAIN!
[ WENDIGOS NEIGHING ]
AND SO, THE PARADISE THE PONIES
HAD FOUND WAS SOON LOST,
BURIED BENEATH A THICK BLANKET
OF SNOW AND HARD FEELINGS.
INSTEAD OF BEAUTIFUL,
IT WAS BLIZZARDY.
INSTEAD OF WONDERFUL,
IT WAS WINTRY.
INSTEAD OF SPECTACULAR,
IT WAS SNOW-TACULAR.
INSTEAD OF --
WE GET IT! MOVE ON!
[ ZIP! ]
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY,
CLEARS THROAT ]
EVERYPONY WAS FORCED
TO SEEK SHELTER.
THEY SEARCHED HIGH AND LOW,
BUT THE ONLY SHELTER FOR MILES
WAS A COLD AND DESOLATE CAVE.
AND, OF COURSE, THE THREE TRIBES
HAD TO SHARE IT,
AND NO PONY WAS TOO HAPPY
ABOUT THAT.
PLEASE,
COMMANDER HOT HEAD.
IT'S COMMANDER HURRICANE.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
PLEASE, COMMANDER,
COULD YOU JUST STAND BACK
AND GIVE ME MY ROYAL SPACE?
YOU MEAN LIKE THIS,
YOUR HIGHNESS?
INDEED NOT.
YOU SEE
THIS INVISIBLE LINE?
PRIVATE, OUTLINE OUR TERRITORY
FOR EVERYPONY TO SEE.
YOU SEE THIS REAL,
NON-INVISIBLE LINE?
NO UNICORNS OR EARTH PONIES
ARE ALLOWED TO CROSS IT.
THIS IS THE SOVEREIGN TERRITORY
OF PEGASOPOLIS.
CLOVER THE CLEVER!
SMART COOKIE!
I KNOW, I KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON'T GO AROUND THE ROCK!
GO OVER IT!
I'M NOT GIVING UP AN INCH
OF TERRITORY TO THE ENEMY.
THAT ROCK IS CLEARLY
ON THE UNICORNIA SIDE
OF THE CAVE,
AND IT BELONGS TO US.
WHO KNOWS?
THERE COULD BE JEWELS INSIDE.
[ GRUNTS ]
I CLAIM THIS ROCK
FOR PEGASOPOLIS!
UNHAND THAT ROCK
THIS INSTANT,
YOU SCOUNDREL!
OH, LOOK.
YOU FOUND MY ROCK.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR IT
EVERYWHERE.
[ ZIP! ]
HEY!
YOU INVADED OUR TERRITORY!
[ Singsong voice ] FINDERS,
KEEPERS, LOSERS, WEEPERS!
THAT'S THE LAST STRAW!
GIVE ME MY ROCK!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
LOOK, EVERYBODY, THE ENTRANCE!
GREAT.
NOW THERE'S NO WAY OUT!
WE'RE TRAPPED!
YOU TWO DESERVE
THIS HORRIBLE FATE!
YOU'VE DONE NOTHING BUT ARGUE
AND FIGHT WITH EACH OTHER!
YOU'VE BEEN FIGHTING, TOO,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
YEAH. WORSE.
I HAVEN'T BEEN FIGHTING
NEARLY AS MUCH AS YOU.
HOW RIDICULOUS!
A UNICORN NEVER STOOPS
TO FIGHTING.
THAT'S JUST 'CAUSE YOU WIMPY
UNICORNS KNOW YOU'D NEVER WIN.
EARTH PONIES ARE NUMSKULLS!
PEGASI ARE BRUTES!
UNICORNS ARE SNOBS!
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ALL SIGH ]
[ HORSE GROWLING ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
AH!
[ WENDIGOS NEIGHING ]
WHAT IS THAT THING?
THEY MUST BE WENDIGOS.
WENDIGOS?
MY MENTOR,
STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED,
TAUGHT ME ABOUT THEM.
THEY'RE WINTER SPIRITS THAT
FEED OFF FIGHTING AND HATRED.
THE MORE HATE THE SPIRIT FEELS,
THE COLDER THINGS BECOME.
THEN THIS IS OUR FAULT --
WE THREE TRIBES.
WE BROUGHT THIS BLIZZARD
TO OUR HOME
BY FIGHTING AND NOT TRUSTING
EACH OTHER.
NOW IT'S DESTROYING
THIS LAND, TOO.
AND NOW OUR BODIES WILL BECOME
AS COLD AS OUR HEARTS,
ALL BECAUSE WE WERE FOOLISH
ENOUGH TO HATE.
WELL, I DON'T HATE YOU.
I ACTUALLY HATE
COMMANDER HURRICANE
A LOT MORE
THAN I HATE YOU GUYS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ NEIGHS ]
ACTUALLY,
I DON'T REALLY HATE HER.
I JUST REALLY, REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY, REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY DISLIKE HER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GALLOPING ]
WELL, I DON'T HATE
YOU GUYS, EITHER.
NOR DO I.
[ NEIGHING ]
NO MATTER WHAT OUR DIFFERENCES,
WE'RE ALL PONIES.
[ NEIGHING INTENSIFIES ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
I DIDN'T KNOW UNICORNS
COULD DO THAT.
I DIDN'T, EITHER.
NOTHING LIKE THIS
HAS EVER HAPPENED BEFORE,
BUT I KNOW IT COULDN'T
HAVE BEEN JUST ME.
IT CAME FROM ALL THREE OF US,
JOINED TOGETHER IN FRIENDSHIP.
Spike: ALL THROUGH THE NIGHT,
THE THREE PONIES KEPT THE FIRE
OF FRIENDSHIP ALIVE
BY TELLING STORIES
TO ONE ANOTHER
AND BY SINGING SONGS, WHICH, OF
COURSE, BECAME THE WINTER CAROLS
THAT WE ALL STILL SING TODAY.
EVENTUALLY, THE WARMTH OF THE
FIRE AND SINGING AND LAUGHING
REACH THE LEADERS,
AND THEIR BODIES BEGAN TO THAW.
AND IT EVEN BEGAN
TO MELT THEIR HEARTS.
[ ICE CRACKING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
THE THREE LEADERS AGREED
TO SHARE THE BEAUTIFUL LAND
AND LIVE IN HARMONY FOREVER
AFTERWARDS,
AND TOGETHER, THEY NAMED
THEIR NEW LAND...
All: ...EQUESTRIA.
[ AUDIENCE CHEERING ]
♪ THE FIRE OF FRIENDSHIP
LIVES IN OUR HEARTS ♪
♪ AS LONG AS IT BURNS,
WE CANNOT DRIFT APART ♪
♪ THOUGH QUARRELS ARISE,
THEIR NUMBERS ARE FEW ♪
♪ LAUGHTER AND SINGING
WILL SEE US THROUGH ♪
♪ WILL SEE US THROUGH ♪
♪ WE ARE A CIRCLE
OF PONY FRIENDS ♪
♪ A CIRCLE OF FRIENDS
WE'LL BE TO THE VERY END ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WE SHOULD BE SO HONORED THAT
PRINCESS CELESTIA CHOSE US.
SHE MUST REALLY THINK
WE EXEMPLIFY
WHAT GOOD FRIENDS ARE.
[ WIND GUSTS ]
Rarity: APPLEJACK, I THOUGHT
YOU CLOSED ALL THE WINDOWS.
DON'T BLAME ME.
RAINBOW DASH SHOULD'VE FLOWN UP
THERE AND SHUT IT.
AFTER ALL, SHE'S GOT WINGS.
WHY DO I ALWAYS HAVE TO DO
ALL THE HIGH-UP CHORES?
WHY CAN'T TWILIGHT USE
HER MAGIC FOR A CHANGE?
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
[ WIND GUSTS ]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GOT IT.
[ WINDOWS CLOSE ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪