&gt;&gt; [ YAWNS ]
I MADE IT FOR YOU, RARITY.
WHY, YES.
IT IS AN ICE-CREAM HOUSE.
CHOCOLATE-FUDGE SHINGLES...
ROCKY-ROAD GARAGE.
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ POINK! ]
HUH?
TWILIGHT!
&gt;&gt; OH. HI, SPIKE.
&gt;&gt; IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
WHY ARE YOU PACING LIKE THIS?
&gt;&gt; FRANKLY, I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU
CAN SLEEP AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
&gt;&gt; 3:00 A.M.?
&gt;&gt; IT'S AWFUL.
IT'S HORRIBLE.
IT'S TRAGIC!
&gt;&gt; EH, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; HERE.
NOW DO YOU SEE WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; WE FORGOT TO CELEBRATE
ARBOR DAY?
&gt;&gt; NO, THE PROBLEM IS, I JUST
FINISHED PLANNING MY SCHEDULE
FOR THE MONTH, BUT I FORGOT TO
LEAVE TIME TO PLAN FOR NEXT
MONTH.
[ ZING! ]
[ ZIP! ]
DON'T YOU SEE?
THERE'S NO TIME IN MY SCHEDULE
TO PUT TOGETHER ANOTHER
SCHEDULE.
I COULD MOVE MY MEETING WITH THE
PONYVILLE HAY BOARD TO THE
FOLLOWING TUESDAY, BUT THEN I
HAVE TO RESCHEDULE MY LUNCH WITH
PINKIE PIE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT A NIGHTMARE
SHE IS WITH SCHEDULING.
THIS IS AN ABSOLUTE DISASTER.
MY WHOLE YEAR COULD BE THROWN
OFF!
&gt;&gt; AND I WOKE UP FROM AN
ICE-CREAM DREAM FOR THIS.
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
&gt;&gt; ♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
&gt;&gt; ♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
AND STRONG ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
&gt;&gt; OH, MY GOSH!
I THINK I DID IT!
IF I CAN FIND A WAY TO READ "THE
"ART OF INVISIBILITY SPELLS"
AND THORNHOOF'S
"BRIEF HISTORY OF CANTERLOT" AT
THE SAME TIME...
...THAT COULD LEAVE ME A
HALF-HOUR SCHEDULING WINDOW.
HUH?
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
AAH!
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT, YOU'VE GOT TO
LISTEN TO ME!
&gt;&gt; WHO ARE YOU?
I MEAN, YOU'RE ME, BUT I'M ME,
TOO.
HOW CAN THERE BE TWO MEs?
IT'S NOT SCIENTIFICALLY
POSSIBLE.
YOU ARE NOT SCIENTIFICALLY
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT, PLEASE.
POSSIBLE.
I HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT MESSAGE
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT, PLEASE.
FOR YOU FROM THE FUTURE.
I HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT MESSAGE
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE FROM THE FUTURE?!
FOR YOU FROM THE FUTURE.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S RIGHT. NOW LISTEN.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE FROM THE FUTURE?!
&gt;&gt; WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S RIGHT. NOW LISTEN.
THE FUTURE MUST BE AWFUL.
&gt;&gt; WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
&gt;&gt; PLEASE.
THE FUTURE MUST BE AWFUL.
I DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE.
&gt;&gt; IS THERE SOME SORT OF EPIC
I DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
PONY WAR IN THE DISTANT FUTURE
&gt;&gt; IS THERE SOME SORT OF EPIC
OR SOMETHING?
PONY WAR IN THE DISTANT FUTURE
&gt;&gt; ACTUALLY, I'M FROM NEXT
OR SOMETHING?
TUESDAY MORNING, BUT THAT'S NOT
&gt;&gt; ACTUALLY, I'M FROM NEXT
IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW.
TUESDAY MORNING, BUT THAT'S NOT
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T BELIEVE TIME TRAVEL
IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW.
IS REALLY POSSIBLE.
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T BELIEVE TIME TRAVEL
HOW DID YOU -- I MEAN, I --
IS REALLY POSSIBLE.
FIGURE IT OUT?
HOW DID YOU -- I MEAN, I --
&gt;&gt; THE TIME SPELLS ARE IN THE
FIGURE IT OUT?
CANTERLOT ARCHIVES, BUT THAT'S
&gt;&gt; THE TIME SPELLS ARE IN THE
NOT --
CANTERLOT ARCHIVES, BUT THAT'S
&gt;&gt; REALLY?! WHERE?
NOT --
I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?! WHERE?
&gt;&gt; THEY'RE IN THE
I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM.
STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED WING.
&gt;&gt; THEY'RE IN THE
NOW, YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME.
STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED WING.
&gt;&gt; IS TIME TRAVEL FUN OR DOES IT
NOW, YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME.
HURT?
&gt;&gt; IS TIME TRAVEL FUN OR DOES IT
I HAVE SO MANY QUESTIONS --
HURT?
[ MUFFLED SPEAKING ]
I HAVE SO MANY QUESTIONS --
&gt;&gt; I HAVE SOMETHING EXTREMELY
[ MUFFLED SPEAKING ]
IMPORTANT TO TELL YOU ABOUT THE
&gt;&gt; I HAVE SOMETHING EXTREMELY
FUTURE, AND I ONLY HAVE A FEW
IMPORTANT TO TELL YOU ABOUT THE
SECONDS, SO YOU'VE GOT TO
FUTURE, AND I ONLY HAVE A FEW
LISTEN.
SECONDS, SO YOU'VE GOT TO
WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T --
LISTEN.
[ ZAP! ]
WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T --
&gt;&gt; FUTURE TWILIGHT?
[ ZAP! ]
OH, NO!
&gt;&gt; FUTURE TWILIGHT?
WHAT WAS SHE TRYING TO WARN ME
OH, NO!
ABOUT?
WHAT WAS SHE TRYING TO WARN ME
HER CLOTHES, HER MANE, THAT
ABOUT?
SCAR!
HER CLOTHES, HER MANE, THAT
OH! WHAT A MESS SHE IS!
SCAR!
I MEAN, I AM...
OH! WHAT A MESS SHE IS!
OR I WILL BE.
I MEAN, I AM...
[ GASPS ]
OR I WILL BE.
SHE MUST WANT ME TO PREVENT
[ GASPS ]
WHATEVER HORRIBLE THING HAPPENS
SHE MUST WANT ME TO PREVENT
IN THE FUTURE.
WHATEVER HORRIBLE THING HAPPENS
[ GASPS ]
IN THE FUTURE.
&gt;&gt; COME ON, FLUTTERSHY.
[ GASPS ]
THE PARTY CAN'T START TILL THE
&gt;&gt; COME ON, FLUTTERSHY.
PARTY SUPPLIES GET THERE!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
[ Weakly ] HAPPY TO HELP, BUT...
CAN I CARRY...THE BALLOONS NEXT
TIME?
[ WHOOSH! ]
WHOA!
[ ZING! ]
&gt;&gt; LISTEN, EVERYPONY, I'VE GOT
SOMETHING REALLY IMPORTANT TO
SAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ POINK! ]
[ WHIP! ]
THIS IS NO LAUGHING MATTER.
WE HAVE A CRISIS ON OUR HOOVES!
[ ALL GASP ]
I'VE JUST BEEN VISITED BY MYSELF
FROM THE FUTURE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THIS ISN'T A JOKE!
MY FUTURE SELF TRIED TO WARN ME
ABOUT A HORRIBLE DISASTER THAT'S
GONNA OCCUR SOMETIME BEFORE NEXT
TUESDAY MORNING!
&gt;&gt; WHAT KIND OF DISASTER?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW.
I GOT SUCKED BACK INTO THE
FUTURE BEFORE I COULD EXPLAIN.
&gt;&gt; RUN FOR YOUR LI-I-I-I-I-VES!
&gt;&gt; WHAT EVER SHOULD WE DO,
TWILIGHT?
HOW DO WE STOP A DISASTER IF WE
DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS?
&gt;&gt; WE'LL JUST HAVE TO WORK
TOGETHER TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
SAFE.
RAINBOW DASH...
[ WHOOSH! ]
...YOU AND THE OTHER PEGASI
SPREAD OUT OVER EQUESTRIA AND
LOOK FOR ANY KIND OF PROBLEM
THAT COULD LEAD TO A DISASTER.
AND I MEAN ANYTHING.
&gt;&gt; YOU GOT IT!
[ WHOOSH! ]
&gt;&gt; EVERYPONY ELSE --
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
ANYPONY ELSE WANT TO PANIC WITH
ME?
NO?
AAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; EVERYPONY ELSE, TIME TO
DISASTER-PROOF EQUESTRIA.
[ POOF! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
&gt;&gt; YEP.
[ SPLASH ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ SPROING! ]
[ WARBLE! ]
&gt;&gt; DONE AND DONE AND DONE.
APPLEJACK, WHAT ABOUT THE
EVERFREE FOREST?
&gt;&gt; THE PERIMETER'S CLEAR.
&gt;&gt; GREAT.
&gt;&gt; AND MY TEAM GAVE THE "ALL
CLEAR" FROM FILLYDELPHIA TO
LAS PEGASUS.
&gt;&gt; EXCELLENT.
WELL, WE'VE DONE EVERYTHING ON
THE LIST, BUT STILL...
FUTURE TWILIGHT LOOKED LIKE
SHE'D BEEN THROUGH A HORRIBLE
ORDEAL.
I JUST HAVE THIS NAGGING FEELING
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING BIGGER THAN LOOSE
BOLTS OR LEAKY PIPES.
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
[ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; OKAY, EVERYPONY, FOLLOW MY
LEAD.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT IS THAT THING?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S CERBERUS.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE GUARDING THE
GATES OF TARTARUS.
BUT IF HE'S HERE, THEN ALL THE
ANCIENT EVIL CREATURES THAT HAVE
BEEN IMPRISONED THERE CAN ESCAPE
AND DESTROY EQUESTRIA.
&gt;&gt; DESTROY EQUESTRIA?!
&gt;&gt; YEAH! ISN'T IT GREAT?
HEY, CERBERUS!
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU COULD USE SOME
OBEDIENCE TRAINING.
MAGIC OBEDIENCE TRAINING.
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; WHO'S THE CUTE, LITTLE
THREE-HEADED DOG?
&gt;&gt; WOW.
I KNEW YOU WERE GOOD WITH
ANIMALS, BUT THIS IS AMAZING!
&gt;&gt; AWW, HE'S JUST A BIG, FURRY
GUY WHO GOT OUT OF HIS YARD.
THAT'S ALL. RIGHT, CERBERUS?
WHO'S A GOOD BOY?
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAH!
AAA-AAA-AAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; YES, TWILIGHT?
&gt;&gt; DO YOU HAVE A BALL I CAN
BORROW?
[ ZIP! ]
&gt;&gt; I HAVE BALLS STASHED ALL OVER
PONYVILLE -- IN CASE OF BALL
EMERGENCY.
&gt;&gt; [ Singsong voice ] HEY,
CERBERUS!
[ WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! ]
LOOK WHAT I HAVE!
&gt;&gt; [ PANTING ]
&gt;&gt; I'LL BE BACK AS SOON AS I'VE
RETURNED HIM TO THE GATES OF
TARTARUS.
ONCE HE'S BACK AT HOME, THERE'LL
BE NO DISASTER.
&gt;&gt; [ PANTING ]
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
&gt;&gt; [ YAWNS ]
[ BONES CRACK ]
I WISH TWILIGHT WOULD GO ON
EPIC ADVENTURES MORE OFTEN.
BEST NIGHT'S SLEEP I'VE HAD IN
WEEKS.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
HEY, TWILIGHT.
HOW'D IT GO WITH CERBERUS?
&gt;&gt; GREAT!
I GOT HIM BACK BEFORE ANY OF THE
EVIL CREATURES COULD ESCAPE.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
[ BELCHES ]
&gt;&gt; UNH!
OH, NO.
[ ZING! ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
IT'S JUST A "LOST DOG" FLIER.
I GUESS THE PRINCESS HASN'T
HEARD WE FOUND CERBERUS YET.
&gt;&gt; IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S THIS.
&gt;&gt; A PAPER CUT?
COME ON, TWILIGHT.
YOU REALLY NEED TO TOUGHEN UP.
JUST CLEAN IT OUT, AND YOU'LL BE
FINE.
&gt;&gt; THE CUT'S IN THE EXACT SAME
SPOT AS THE SCAR ON
FUTURE TWILIGHT'S CHEEK.
WE HAVEN'T CHANGED THE FUTURE AT
ALL.
THE DISASTER IS STILL COMING!
&gt;&gt; IF THE DISASTER WASN'T CAUSED
BY CERBERUS GETTING LOOSE, THEN
WHAT COULD IT POSSIBLY BE?
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
I DON'T KNOW, BUT MAYBE YOU
OUGHT TO GIVE THE PACING A REST.
YOU'VE WORN A GROOVE INTO THE
FLOOR.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR ANOTHER
ONE OF YOUR LECTURES, SPIKE.
THIS IS SERIOUS!
&gt;&gt; MY LECTURES?
&gt;&gt; I DID EVERYTHING I COULD
THINK OF TO CHANGE THE FUTURE,
BUT IT DIDN'T WORK.
SO MAYBE IT'S NOT WHAT I DO.
MAYBE IT'S WHAT I DON'T DO.
[ TINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; IF I STAND RIGHT HERE AND
DON'T MOVE A MUSCLE UNTIL NEXT
TUESDAY, I CAN'T POSSIBLY DO
WHATEVER IT IS THAT
FUTURE TWILIGHT WANTED TO WARN
ME NOT TO DO.
[ SPROING! ]
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
SO, NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA MOVE A MUSCLE,
HUH?
THEN MAYBE YOU WON'T MIND IF
I...
[ ZIP! ]
...EAT AN ENTIRE TUB OF
ICE CREAM!
[ SLUNK! ]
[ SLINK! ]
MMM!
[ MOANS ]
[ Muffled ] SO GOOD!
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
[ Muffled ] SPIKE, STOP.
THINK OF THE STOMACHACHE.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
STOMACHACHE, HUH?
THAT'S FUTURE SPIKE'S PROBLEM.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
&gt;&gt; HEY, TWILIGHT, ANOTHER
PEGASUS JUST GOT BACK FROM
BALTIMARE WITH AN "ALL CLEAR,"
AND --
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
AREN'T YOU GONNA STOP HIM?
&gt;&gt; SHE SURE ISN'T.
IN FACT, SHE'S NOT GONNA MOVE
TILL NEXT TUESDAY.
SHE THINKS IT'LL PREVENT THE
DISASTER FROM HAPPENING.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
OH, THIS IS TOO RICH.
[ GASPS ]
HEY, TWILIGHT, THERE'S A MOUSE
RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
&gt;&gt; WAIT. WAIT, WAIT.
LET ME TRY.
[ SCIFFLE! SCIFFLE! SCIFFLE! ]
[ SCIFFLE! ]
[ SCIFFLE! SCIFFLE! ]
[ TINKLE! ]
WHUA-AAH-AAAAH!
UNGH!
[ FOOSH! ]
&gt;&gt; OH, NO!
&gt;&gt; [ Sternly ] WHAT HAPPENED?
&gt;&gt; I'M SO SORRY!
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
IT WAS A TOTAL ACCIDENT.
&gt;&gt; SHOW ME.
&gt;&gt; UH...
I'M NOT SO SURE THAT'S A --
&gt;&gt; SHOW ME!
OH, NO.
THIS IS THE SAME MANECUT AS
FUTURE TWILIGHT.
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW, IT REALLY DOESN'T
LOOK TOO BAD.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T CARE HOW IT LOOKS.
IT'S JUST ANOTHER SIGN THAT THE
FUTURE HASN'T CHANGED.
NOT DOING ANYTHING DIDN'T WORK,
EITHER.
OH, I WISH THERE WAS A WAY TO
KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN SO I
CAN STOP IT.
&gt;&gt; YOU WANT TO SEE THE FUTURE?
I MIGHT KNOW SOMEPONY WHO CAN
HELP.
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S THIS?
&gt;&gt; IT'S MADAME PINKIE'S PLACE.
&gt;&gt; MADAME PINKIE?
&gt;&gt; [ Spooky voice ] COME...
ENTER THE CHAMBER OF
MADAME PINKIE PIE.
FOR THE ANSWERS YOU SEEK, LET US
CONSULT THE MYSTICAL ORB OF
FATE'S DESTINY.
[ Normal voice ] DO YOU LIKE MY
MYSTICAL ORB OF FATE'S DESTINY?
I JUST GOT IT.
COOL, HUH?
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
UH...BEST ONE I'VE SEEN.
&gt;&gt; [ Spooky voice ] LOOK DEEP
INTO THE CRYSTAL BALL, FOR SOON,
IT WILL REVEAL ALL!
AH, YES.
I SEE SOMETHING.
IT IS A VISION OF THE FUTURE.
I SEE...YOU, TWILIGHT.
YOU WILL GET A REALLY COOL
BIRTHDAY PRESENT NEXT YEAR.
&gt;&gt; YES, AND...?!
&gt;&gt; [ Normal voice ] THAT'S IT.
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU SURE?
&gt;&gt; YEP. COOL BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
&gt;&gt; PINKIE, I NEED YOUR PINKIE
SENSE TO TELL ME WHAT THE
IMPENDING DISASTER IS THAT
FUTURE TWILIGHT WAS TRYING TO
WARN ME ABOUT!
&gt;&gt; OH, MY FORTUNE-TELLING HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH MY
PINKIE SENSE, SILLY.
IT'S ONLY GOOD FOR VAGUE AND
IMMEDIATE EVENTS.
[ RATTLE! ]
[ WHISTLE! BAP! ]
LIKE THAT. SEE?
WHERE DID THAT EVEN COME FROM?
♪ LA LA-LA LA-LA LA-LA,
LA-LA LA-LA ♪
GOSH, I HAVEN'T SEEN TWILIGHT
SINCE THE FLOWERPOT INCIDENT.
HOPE SHE STILL ISN'T MAD.
UHHH...
&gt;&gt; OFF BY .02 FROM YESTERDAY.
[ ZIP! ]
CARRY THE 15...
NEGATIVE AZIMUTH AND THE 14th
MOON.
&gt;&gt; HI, PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT'S REALLY SERIOUS
ABOUT FINDING OUT ABOUT THAT
COOL BIRTHDAY PRESENT, ISN'T
SHE?
&gt;&gt; WHO CARES?
AS LONG AS I CAN KEEP EATING ICE
CREAM.
SORRY, FUTURE SPIKE.
[ MOANS ]
MMM!
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; AH, PINKIE.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
CAN YOU HELP ME RECALIBRATE THE
APERTURES ON THE
9 1/4 CATADIOPTRIC TELESCOPES?
&gt;&gt; SURE!
&gt;&gt; SO, I WAS THINKING -- AFTER I
CAME TO SEE MADAME PINKIE AND
THE FLOWERPOT LANDED ON MY
HEAD -- SEE THE BANDAGE?
JUST LIKE THE BANDAGE FROM THE
FUTURE.
&gt;&gt; NICE!
&gt;&gt; I HAD AN EPIPHANY AFTER THAT
FLOWERPOT.
DOING THINGS DIDN'T WORK.
NOT DOING THINGS DIDN'T WORK.
AND I COULDN'T PREDICT THE
FUTURE, EITHER.
SO I ONLY HAD ONE OTHER CHOICE.
[ ZIP! ]
MONITOR EVERYTHING!
&gt;&gt; MAKES SENSE TO ME.
&gt;&gt; THAT WAY, NO MATTER WHAT
HAPPENS IN THE FUTURE, I'LL BE
READY.
I THOUGHT I SAW SOMETHING LAST
NIGHT IN THE HORSEHEAD NEBULA.
BUT AFTER STARING AT IT FOR
THREE STRAIGHT HOURS, I REALIZED
I WAS WRONG.
&gt;&gt; THREE HOURS?
WELL, WHEN DID YOU SLEEP?
&gt;&gt; OH, I DIDN'T SLEEP.
I HAVEN'T SLEPT SINCE
FUTURE TWILIGHT WAS HERE.
THERE ARE ONLY THREE DAYS LEFT
UNTIL NEXT TUESDAY.
I CAN SLEEP ALL I WANT AFTER
THAT!
&gt;&gt; YOU'VE BEEN AWAKE TOO LONG,
TWILIGHT.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, TUESDAY'S NOT THREE
DAYS FROM NOW.
TUESDAY'S TOMORROW.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ TINKLE! ]
PINKIE, DID YOU FINISH
RECALIBRATING THE APERTURES ON
THE 9 1/4-INCH CATADIOPTRIC
TELESCOPES?
&gt;&gt; I HAVE NO IDEA.
[ FOOSH! ]
&gt;&gt; AAH! MY EYE!
&gt;&gt; DON'T WORRY, TWILIGHT.
I HAVE EYE PATCHES STASHED ALL
OVER PONYVILLE -- IN CASE OF
EYE-PATCH EMERGENCY.
THERE!
NOW YOU LOOK LIKE A PIRATE --
A SLEEPY PIRATE WITH A REALLY
WEIRD MANECUT.
&gt;&gt; THE EYE PATCH...
[ GASPS ]
ANOTHER SIGN!
[ WHOOSH! ]
NEARLY ALL THE SIGNS HAVE COME
TRUE!
I HAVEN'T DONE A THING TO
PREVENT THE CATASTROPHE!
IF TUESDAY'S TOMORROW AND THE
DISASTER HAPPENS BY TUESDAY
MORNING, THEN THERE'S ONLY ONE
SOLUTION -- I'LL JUST HAVE TO...
STOP TIME!
[ STEAM HISSES ]
[ ENGINE CHUGGING ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
&gt;&gt; OKAY, THE CANTERLOT ARCHIVES
ARE RIGHT OVER THERE.
LET'S MOVE!
[ PITTER! PITTER! PITTER! ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ WHIP! ]
[ WARBLE! WARBLE! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHIP! ]
&gt;&gt; UH, I DON'T THINK WE NEED TO
[ ZIP! ]
SNEAK AROUND, TWILIGHT.
&gt;&gt; UH, I DON'T THINK WE NEED TO
IT'S NOT ILLEGAL TO WALK AROUND
SNEAK AROUND, TWILIGHT.
CANTERLOT.
IT'S NOT ILLEGAL TO WALK AROUND
&gt;&gt; GUARD!
CANTERLOT.
[ SPROING! ]
&gt;&gt; GUARD!
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
[ SPROING! ]
[ WHIRL! ]
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
OH. THAT WAS CLOSE.
[ WHIRL! ]
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW WHY WE HAVE TO
OH. THAT WAS CLOSE.
WEAR THESE THINGS, EITHER.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW WHY WE HAVE TO
&gt;&gt; AREN'T WE WEARING THEM FOR
WEAR THESE THINGS, EITHER.
FUN?
&gt;&gt; AREN'T WE WEARING THEM FOR
&gt;&gt; NO, THERE'S NOTHING FUN ABOUT
FUN?
THIS.
&gt;&gt; NO, THERE'S NOTHING FUN ABOUT
&gt;&gt; OH.
THIS.
ARE YOU SURE?
&gt;&gt; OH.
&gt;&gt; FOCUS, GUYS!
ARE YOU SURE?
THE ONLY WAY TO PREVENT THIS
&gt;&gt; FOCUS, GUYS!
DISASTER IS TO STOP TIME.
THE ONLY WAY TO PREVENT THIS
TIME SPELLS ARE KEPT IN THE
DISASTER IS TO STOP TIME.
STAR SWIRL OF BEARDED WING, THE
TIME SPELLS ARE KEPT IN THE
MOST SECURE SECTION OF THE
STAR SWIRL OF BEARDED WING, THE
ARCHIVES.
MOST SECURE SECTION OF THE
THAT'S WHY WE'RE SNEAKING
ARCHIVES.
AROUND.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE SNEAKING
&gt;&gt; AWESOME!
AROUND.
THAT SOUNDS FUN!
&gt;&gt; AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; NO! IT'S NOT FUN!
THAT SOUNDS FUN!
&gt;&gt; AWWW.
&gt;&gt; NO! IT'S NOT FUN!
[ SLOOP! ]
&gt;&gt; AWWW.
[ ZIP! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
[ ZIP! ]
SNEAKING INTO THE ARCHIVES IS
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
GONNA HELP HER FIND OUT ABOUT
SNEAKING INTO THE ARCHIVES IS
HER BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
GONNA HELP HER FIND OUT ABOUT
[ SLURP! ]
HER BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
&gt;&gt; The coast is clear.
[ SLURP! ]
Now slowly lift me into the
&gt;&gt; The coast is clear.
window so we can --
Now slowly lift me into the
AAH!
window so we can --
[ SLURP! SLURP! ]
AAH!
&gt;&gt; UGH.
[ SLURP! SLURP! ]
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
&gt;&gt; UGH.
[ BOING! BOING! ]
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ BOING! BOING! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
[ SLURP! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ SLURP! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ WHIFFLE! ]
[ SLOOP! ]
[ LIGHT THUD ]
[ WHIFFLE! ]
&gt;&gt; Okay, if my calculations
[ LIGHT THUD ]
are correct, the
&gt;&gt; Okay, if my calculations
Star Swirl the Bearded wing
are correct, the
should be right...here.
Star Swirl the Bearded wing
&gt;&gt; UH...TWILIGHT?
should be right...here.
&gt;&gt; WHAT IS IT, SPIKE?
&gt;&gt; UH...TWILIGHT?
&gt;&gt; ISN'T THIS WHERE WE CAME IN?
&gt;&gt; WHAT IS IT, SPIKE?
&gt;&gt; COOL!
&gt;&gt; ISN'T THIS WHERE WE CAME IN?
CAN WE CLIMB IN THE WINDOW
&gt;&gt; COOL!
AGAIN?
CAN WE CLIMB IN THE WINDOW
THAT WAS SUPER-FUN!
AGAIN?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT WAS SUPER-FUN!
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE RIGHT HERE.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO FIND IT
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE RIGHT HERE.
NOW?
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO FIND IT
&gt;&gt; MAYBE WE SHOULD ASK SOMEPONY
NOW?
IN THE STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED
&gt;&gt; MAYBE WE SHOULD ASK SOMEPONY
WING.
IN THE STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED
&gt;&gt; HUH. HOW'D I MISS THAT?
WING.
LOOK AT ALL THOSE PRICELESS
&gt;&gt; HUH. HOW'D I MISS THAT?
MAGIC SCROLLS.
LOOK AT ALL THOSE PRICELESS
THERE ARE MORE THAN I EVER
MAGIC SCROLLS.
IMAGINED.
THERE ARE MORE THAN I EVER
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT! THE GUARD!
IMAGINED.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT! THE GUARD!
WHAT DO WE DO? WHAT DO WE DO?!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ RATTLE! RATTLE! ]
WHAT DO WE DO? WHAT DO WE DO?!
&gt;&gt; HEY, TWILIGHT!
[ RATTLE! RATTLE! ]
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN A WHILE.
&gt;&gt; HEY, TWILIGHT!
LET ME OPEN THAT FOR YOU.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN A WHILE.
[ TINKLE! ]
LET ME OPEN THAT FOR YOU.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
[ TINKLE! ]
THANKS.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
OH, NO!
THANKS.
[ CLANK! ]
OH, NO!
&gt;&gt; UNGH!
[ CLANK! ]
&gt;&gt; LOOK!
&gt;&gt; UNGH!
I LOOK JUST LIKE
&gt;&gt; LOOK!
FUTURE TWILIGHT.
I LOOK JUST LIKE
THE LAST SIGN HAS COME TRUE!
FUTURE TWILIGHT.
&gt;&gt; AND...THAT'S BAD, RIGHT?
THE LAST SIGN HAS COME TRUE!
&gt;&gt; COME ON!
&gt;&gt; AND...THAT'S BAD, RIGHT?
IT'S ALMOST TUESDAY MORNING.
&gt;&gt; COME ON!
THE DISASTER COULD HAPPEN AT ANY
IT'S ALMOST TUESDAY MORNING.
MOMENT!
&gt;&gt; BUT HOW DO WE FIND THE
TIME-STOPPING SPELL?
THERE MUST BE A MILLION SCROLLS
HERE!
&gt;&gt; I...
DON'T...
KNOW.
[ WHIP! ]
[ POINK! ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT! IT'S OVER!
[ POINK! ]
&gt;&gt; NO!
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT! IT'S OVER!
&gt;&gt; IT'S OFFICIALLY TUESDAY
&gt;&gt; NO!
MORNING.
&gt;&gt; IT'S OFFICIALLY TUESDAY
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
MORNING.
NO!
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
NO!
TUESDAY MORNING...
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
THE DISASTER...
TUESDAY MORNING...
INCOMI-I-I-I-I-I-NG!
THE DISASTER...
[ CHATTER! CHATTER! CHATTER! ]
INCOMI-I-I-I-I-I-NG!
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW, TWILIGHT.
[ CHATTER! CHATTER! CHATTER! ]
I DON'T SEE ANY DISASTERS.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW, TWILIGHT.
IT LOOKS LIKE A PRETTY NICE DAY.
I DON'T SEE ANY DISASTERS.
[ TINKLE! ]
IT LOOKS LIKE A PRETTY NICE DAY.
&gt;&gt; GOOD MORNING, TWILIGHT.
[ TINKLE! ]
LOVE THE NEW HAIRSTYLE.
&gt;&gt; GOOD MORNING, TWILIGHT.
WELL, HAPPY TUESDAY!
LOVE THE NEW HAIRSTYLE.
&gt;&gt; WHY ISN'T ANYPONY SURPRISED
WELL, HAPPY TUESDAY!
TO SEE ME SNEAKING AROUND IN
&gt;&gt; WHY ISN'T ANYPONY SURPRISED
HERE?
TO SEE ME SNEAKING AROUND IN
IS IT POSSIBLE THERE NEVER WAS A
HERE?
DISASTER?
IS IT POSSIBLE THERE NEVER WAS A
THAT I'VE JUST BEEN MAKING
DISASTER?
MYSELF FRANTIC OVER NOTHING?
THAT I'VE JUST BEEN MAKING
&gt;&gt; I DON'T GET IT.
MYSELF FRANTIC OVER NOTHING?
IF FUTURE TWILIGHT WASN'T
&gt;&gt; I DON'T GET IT.
WARNING YOU ABOUT A DISASTER,
IF FUTURE TWILIGHT WASN'T
THEN WHAT WAS SHE TRYING TO TELL
WARNING YOU ABOUT A DISASTER,
YOU?
THEN WHAT WAS SHE TRYING TO TELL
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
BUT I DO KNOW ONE THING --
I DON'T KNOW.
I LOOK RIDICULOUS.
BUT I DO KNOW ONE THING --
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
I LOOK RIDICULOUS.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, YOU DO!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
&gt;&gt; AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE I
&gt;&gt; YEAH, YOU DO!
COULDN'T STOP WORRYING AND LET
&gt;&gt; AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE I
THE FUTURE HANDLE ITSELF.
COULDN'T STOP WORRYING AND LET
WELL, NOT ANYMORE.
THE FUTURE HANDLE ITSELF.
FROM NOW ON, I'M GONNA SOLVE
WELL, NOT ANYMORE.
PROBLEMS AS THEY COME AND STOP
FROM NOW ON, I'M GONNA SOLVE
WORRYING ABOUT EVERY LITTLE
PROBLEMS AS THEY COME AND STOP
THING.
WORRYING ABOUT EVERY LITTLE
&gt;&gt; THAT'S GREAT!
THING.
DOES THAT MEAN THERE WON'T BE
&gt;&gt; THAT'S GREAT!
ANY MORE LATE-NIGHT PACING?
DOES THAT MEAN THERE WON'T BE
&gt;&gt; NO MORE LATE-NIGHT PACING.
ANY MORE LATE-NIGHT PACING?
IF ONLY I HAD LEARNED THIS
&gt;&gt; NO MORE LATE-NIGHT PACING.
LESSON A WEEK AGO, WE WOULDN'T
IF ONLY I HAD LEARNED THIS
HAVE HAD TO GO THROUGH ALL THIS.
LESSON A WEEK AGO, WE WOULDN'T
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT! TWILIGHT!
HAVE HAD TO GO THROUGH ALL THIS.
I FOUND SOMETHING!
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT! TWILIGHT!
[ TINKLE! ]
I FOUND SOMETHING!
IT DOESN'T STOP TIME, BUT IT
[ TINKLE! ]
LETS YOU GO BACK IN TIME.
IT DOESN'T STOP TIME, BUT IT
IT SAYS YOU CAN GO BACK ONCE,
LETS YOU GO BACK IN TIME.
AND IT ONLY LASTS FOR A FEW
IT SAYS YOU CAN GO BACK ONCE,
MOMENTS.
AND IT ONLY LASTS FOR A FEW
DOES THAT HELP?
MOMENTS.
&gt;&gt; PINKIE, YOU'RE A GENIUS!
DOES THAT HELP?
&gt;&gt; WHOO-HOO!
&gt;&gt; PINKIE, YOU'RE A GENIUS!
&gt;&gt; NOW I CAN GO BACK AND TELL
&gt;&gt; WHOO-HOO!
PAST TWILIGHT THAT SHE DOESN'T
&gt;&gt; NOW I CAN GO BACK AND TELL
NEED TO GO BERSERK WITH WORRY
PAST TWILIGHT THAT SHE DOESN'T
ABOUT A DISASTER THAT'S NEVER
NEED TO GO BERSERK WITH WORRY
GONNA COME.
ABOUT A DISASTER THAT'S NEVER
[ TINKLE! ]
GONNA COME.
[ ZAP! ]
[ TINKLE! ]
TWILIGHT, YOU'VE GOT TO LISTEN
[ ZAP! ]
TO ME!
TWILIGHT, YOU'VE GOT TO LISTEN
&gt;&gt; WHO ARE YOU?
TO ME!
I MEAN, YOU'RE ME, BUT I'M ME,
&gt;&gt; WHO ARE YOU?
TOO.
I MEAN, YOU'RE ME, BUT I'M ME,
HOW CAN THERE BE TWO MEs?
TOO.
IT'S NOT SCIENTIFICALLY
HOW CAN THERE BE TWO MEs?
POSSIBLE.
IT'S NOT SCIENTIFICALLY
YOU ARE NOT SCIENTIFICALLY
POSSIBLE.
&gt;&gt; TWILIGHT, PLEASE.
I HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT MESSAGE
FOR YOU FROM THE FUTURE.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE FROM THE FUTURE?!
&gt;&gt; THAT'S RIGHT. NOW LISTEN.
&gt;&gt; WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
THE FUTURE MUST BE AWFUL.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE.
I DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
&gt;&gt; IS THERE SOME SORT OF EPIC
PONY WAR IN THE DISTANT FUTURE
OR SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; ACTUALLY, I'M FROM NEXT
TUESDAY MORNING, BUT THAT'S NOT
IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW.
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T BELIEVE TIME TRAVEL
IS REALLY POSSIBLE.
HOW DID YOU -- I MEAN, I --
FIGURE IT OUT?
&gt;&gt; THE TIME SPELLS ARE IN THE
CANTERLOT ARCHIVES, BUT THAT'S
NOT --
&gt;&gt; REALLY?! WHERE?
I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM.
&gt;&gt; THEY'RE IN THE
STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED WING.
NOW, YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME.
&gt;&gt; IS TIME TRAVEL FUN OR DOES IT
HURT?
I HAVE SO MANY QUESTIONS --
[ MUFFLED SPEAKING ]
&gt;&gt; I HAVE SOMETHING EXTREMELY
IMPORTANT TO TELL YOU ABOUT THE
FUTURE, AND I ONLY HAVE A FEW
SECONDS, SO YOU'VE GOT TO
LISTEN.
WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T...
[ ZAP! ]
...WASTE YOUR TIME WORRYING...
ABOUT...
UGH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I JUST DID THAT!
&gt;&gt; DID YOU TELL HER ABOUT THE
COOL BIRTHDAY PRESENT?
&gt;&gt; REMEMBER LAST WEEK, WHEN
FUTURE TWILIGHT CAME TO WARN ME
ABOUT SOMETHING?
THAT WAS ME TRYING TO WARN
MYSELF NOT TO WORRY SO MUCH.
NOW I'M GONNA SPEND THE NEXT
WEEK FREAKING OUT ABOUT A
DISASTER THAT DOESN'T EVEN
EXIST!
UGH!
&gt;&gt; AW, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S PAST TWILIGHT'S PROBLEM
NOW.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT, PINKIE.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
MY STOMACH...
[ THUD ]
I...I THINK IT'S ALL THAT
ICE CREAM.
I THOUGHT THE STOMACHACHE WOULD
BE FUTURE SPIKE'S PROBLEM.
BUT NOW I AM FUTURE SPIKE.
[ GROANS ]
[ GURGLE! ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
&gt;&gt; COME ON, FUTURE SPIKE.
[ BOING! BOING! ]
[ TINKLE! ]
LET'S GET YOU HOME.
&gt;&gt; ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪