[ GROANS ]
COME ON, TWILIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE FOR
THE NIGHTMARE NIGHT FESTIVAL.
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
HUH?
[ BELLS JINGLE ]
ARE YOU THAT ONE
KOOKY GRANDPA
FROM PONYVILLE
RETIREMENT VILLAGE?
I'M STAR SWIRL
THE BEARDED.
FATHER OF
THE AMNIOMORPHIC SPELL?
DID YOU EVEN READ
THAT BOOK I GAVE YOU
ABOUT OBSCURE
UNICORN HISTORY?
UM...
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
THAT SOUNDS IMPORTANT.
[ ZIP! ]
[ Chanting ]
NIGHTMARE NIGHT!
WHAT A FRIGHT!
GIVE US SOMETHING SWEET TO BITE!
HI, EVERYPONY.
GREAT COSTUMES.
HAPPY NIGHTMARE NIGHT,
GRANNY SMITH.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN ASLEEP
FIVE HOURS AGO.
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ CLANK! ]
PIP-SQUEAK THE PIRATE
AT YOUR SERVICE.
IT'S MY VERY FIRST
NIGHTMARE NIGHT.
SINCE YOU'VE MOVED HERE
FROM TROTTINGHAM?
NO, MY VERY FIRST
NIGHTMARE NIGHT EVER!
[ SQUAWKS ]
ENOUGH CHITCHAT! TIME IS CANDY!
PINKIE PIE, AREN'T YOU
A LITTLE OLD FOR THIS?
TOO OLD FOR FREE CANDY?
AAH!
NEVER!
[ GROANS ]
[ BELLS JINGLING ]
DO YOU LIKE IT?
YEAH!
GREAT COSTUME, TWILIGHT!
OH, YOU MAKE A FANTASTIC
WEIRDO CLOWN.
[ ZIP! ]
A CLOWN?
LOOK AT THE BORDERS
ON THESE ROBES.
THESE ARE
HOOF-STITCHED.
IT'S A GREAT COSTUME.
[ CHUCKLES ] GRANDPA.
[ GROWLS ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
Twilight:
STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED
IS ONLY THE MOST IMPORTANT
CONJURER
OF THE PRECLASSICAL ERA.
YAY!
WHOO!
HE CREATED
MORE THAN 200 SPELLS.
HE EVEN HAS A SHELF IN THE
CANTERLOT LIBRARY OF MAGIC
NAMED AFTER HIM.
MAYBE I SHOULD START UP
A PONY GROUP
TO TEACH PONIES
ABOUT HISTORY.
I BET EVERYPONY WOULD LOVE IT,
DON'T YOU, SPIKE?
MM-HMM.
MMM. I LOVE IT!
[ SIGHS ]
HEY, LOOK.
WE'RE HERE ALREADY.
SHOULD WE GET
SOMETHING TO EAT?
[ BURP! ]
TWILIGHT, TWILIGHT!
LOOK AT OUR HAUL!
[ SQUEALS ]
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?!
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
AND THEN WE WENT
TO CHEERILEE'S HOUSE,
AND WE GOT
A BUNCH MORE GOODIES!
DIDN'T WE, PIP?
SURE DID.
AND THEN WE HAD TO STOP
AND WAIT FOR GRANNY SMITH,
AND THEN --
[ BANG! ]
[ SQUAWKS ]
AAH! AAH!
Rainbow Dash:
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
RAINBOW DASH,
THAT WASN'T VERY NICE.
LIGHTEN UP, OLD-TIMER.
THIS IS THE BEST NIGHT
OF THE YEAR FOR PRANKS.
LOOK WHAT YOU DID
TO SPIKE.
[ COUGHING ]
AW, IT'S ALL
IN GOOD FUN.
OH, OH! THERE'S ANOTHER
GROUP OVER THERE!
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ BELLS JINGLE ]
[ THUNDER CRASHES,
CROWD SCREAMS ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
HAPPY NIGHTMARE NIGHT,
APPLEJACK.
HOWDY, SPIKE.
HEY, TWILIGHT.
NICE COSTUME.
THANKS.
I'M A DRAGON.
SHE MEANS ME, SPIKE.
Applejack:
WITH THAT BEARD,
I RECKON YOU'RE SOME SORT
OF COUNTRY MUSIC SINGER.
[ GRUMBLES ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WHILE Y'ALL ARE HERE,
YOU FEEL LIKE BOBBING
FOR AN APPLE?
[ WATER GURGLING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Mayor:
THANK YOU, EVERYPONY.
AND WELCOME TO
THE NIGHTMARE NIGHT FESTIVAL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
NOW, ALL THE LITTLE PONIES
WHO HAVE BEEN OUT
COLLECTING SWEETS
SHOULD FOLLOW OUR FRIEND ZECORA
TO HEAR THE LEGEND OF...
[ Spooky voice ]
NIGHTMARE MOON!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
HER SPOOKY VOICE
MIGHT WORK BETTER
IF SHE WASN'T DRESSED
LIKE THAT.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ POOF! ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ CROWD GASPING ]
FOLLOW ME, AND VERY SOON
YOU'LL HEAR THE TALE
OF NIGHTMARE MOON.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
LISTEN CLOSE,
MY LITTLE DEARS.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHERE YOU GOT YOUR FEARS...
OF NIGHTMARE NIGHT
SO DARK AND SCARY...
...OF NIGHTMARE MOON
WHO MAKES YOU WARY.
[ ALL GASP ]
EVERY YEAR,
WE PUT ON A DISGUISE
TO SAVE OURSELVES
FROM HER SEARCHING EYES.
AAH!
BUT NIGHTMARE MOON WANTS
JUST ONE THING...
...TO GOBBLE UP PONIES
IN ONE QUICK SWING!
AAH!
[ ZIP! ]
HUNGRILY SHE SOARS THE SKY.
IF SHE SEES NO PONY,
SHE PASSES BY.
SO IF SHE COMES
AND ALL IS CLEAR...
EQUESTRIA IS SAFE ANOTHER YEAR!
[ WHOOSH! ]
Pip-Squeak:
OH, MISS ZECORA,
IF WE WEAR COSTUMES
TO HIDE FROM NIGHTMARE MOON
SO SHE WON'T GOBBLE US UP,
HOW COME WE STILL NEED TO
GIVE HER SOME OF OUR CANDY?
A PERFECT QUESTION,
MY LITTLE FRIEND...
FOR NIGHTMARE MOON
YOU MUST NOT OFFEND.
FILL UP HER BELLY
WITH A TREAT OR TWO
SO SHE WON'T RETURN
TO COME EAT YOU!
AAH! AAH!
EVERYPONY PUT DOWN SOME CANDY!
GET OUT OF HERE!
[ WIND HOWLING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ ALL WHIMPERING ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ GASPS ]
IT'S NIGHTMARE MOON!
RUN!
[ ZIP! ]
AAH! AAH!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
[ SCREAMING ]
AAH! AAH!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
PRINCESS LUNA.
[ BELLS JINGLE ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ TEETH CHATTERING ]
CITIZENS OF PONYVILLE...
WE HAVE GRACED YOUR TINY VILLAGE
WITH OUR PRESENCE
SO THAT YOU MIGHT BEHOLD
THE REAL PRINCESS OF THE NIGHT!
A CREATURE OF NIGHTMARES
NO LONGER,
BUT INSTEAD A PONY WHO DESIRES
YOUR LOVE AND ADMIRATION!
TOGETHER WE SHALL CHANGE
THIS DREADFUL CELEBRATION
INTO A BRIGHT
AND GLORIOUS FEAST!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
DID YOU HEAR THAT,
EVERYPONY?
NIGHTMARE MOON SAYS SHE'S
GONNA FEAST ON US ALL!
AAH! AAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
WHAT?
NO, CHILDREN, NO.
YOU NO LONGER HAVE REASON
TO FEAR US.
SCREAMS OF DELIGHT
IS WHAT YOUR PRINCESS DESIRES,
NOT SCREAMS OF TERROR!
[ WHIMPERS ]
MADAM MAYOR, THY PRINCESS
OF THE NIGHT HATH ARRIVED!
OH!
[ TEETH CHATTERING ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
VERY WELL, THEN.
BE THAT WAY!
WE WON'T EVEN BOTHER WITH
THE TRADITIONAL ROYAL FAREWELL!
I'M GONNA
GO TALK TO HER.
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU CAN'T TALK TO HER!
SHE'S NIGHTMARE MOON!
NO, SHE'S NOT.
I SAW THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY
CHANGE HER BACK TO GOOD.
IT SEEMS LIKE SHE'S HAVING
SOME TROUBLE ADJUSTING
AFTER BEING GONE
FOR 1,000 YEARS.
PRINCESS LUNA?
HI.
MY NAME IS...
STAR SWIRL THE BEARDED.
COMMENDABLE COSTUME.
THOU EVEN GOT
THE BELLS RIGHT.
THANK YOU!
FINALLY!
SOMEPONY WHO GETS
MY COSTUME!
UH, I JUST CAME
TO WELCOME YOU
TO OUR CELEBRATION.
MY ACTUAL NAME IS --
TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
IT WAS THOU WHO UNLEASHED
THE POWERS OF HARMONY UPON US
AND TOOK AWAY
OUR DARK POWERS!
[ WHOOSH! ]
AND THAT WAS
A GOOD THING, RIGHT?
BUT OF COURSE!
WE COULD NOT BE HAPPIER!
IS THAT NOT CLEAR?!
WELL, YOU KIND OF SOUND
LIKE YOU'RE YELLING AT ME.
BUT THIS IS THE TRADITIONAL
ROYAL CANTERLOT VOICE.
IT IS TRADITION TO SPEAK
USING THE ROYAL "WE."
AND TO USE...
[ Loudly ] THIS MUCH VOLUME
WHEN ADDRESSING OUR SUBJECTS!
[ BELLS JINGLE ]
YOU KNOW, THAT MIGHT EXPLAIN
WHY YOUR APPEARANCE
WAS MET WITH...
MIXED RESULTS.
I THINK IF YOU JUST CHANGED
YOUR APPROACH A BIT,
YOU MIGHT BE MET
WITH A WARMER RECEPTION.
CHANGE OUR APPROACH?!
LOWER THE VOLUME?
[ Normal voice ]
OH.
WE HAVE BEEN LOCKED AWAY
FOR 1,000 YEARS.
WE ARE...
NOT SURE WE CAN.
DON'T WORRY, PRINCESS.
FLUTTERSHY CAN GIVE YOU
SOME GREAT POINTERS.
SHE'S DELICATE AND DEMURE,
WITH THE SWEETEST LITTLE VOICE.
Fluttershy:
GO AWAY! NO CANDY HERE!
VISITORS NOT WELCOME
ON NIGHTMARE NIGHT!
UH...
[ CHUCKLES ]
FLUTTERSHY, IT'S ME --
TWILIGHT.
IT IS YOU.
OH, AND NIGHTMARE MOON.
[ GASPS ]
NIGHTMARE MOON?!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SLAM! ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
WAIT RIGHT HERE.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
[ CLATTERING, ANIMAL BLEATS ]
[ PONY WHINNIES ]
FLUTTERSHY [GRUNTS]
YOU REMEMBER PRINCESS LUNA.
CHARMED!
[ ZIP! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
LIKEWISE.
TWILIGHT SPARKLE HAS SPOKEN
OF THE SWEETNESS OF THY VOICE!
WE ASK NOW TEACH US TO SPEAK
AS THOU SPEAKETH!
Okay.
SHALL OUR LESSONS BEGIN?!
SHALL WE MIMIC
THY VOICE?!
Okay.
HOW IS THIS?!
PERFECT.
LESSON OVER.
[ ZIP! ]
A LITTLE QUIETER,
PRINCESS.
HOW IS...
[ Normal voice ] THIS?
BETTER.
RIGHT, FLUTTERSHY?
[ POP! ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
YES.
[ THUD ]
HOW...ABOUT...NOW?
NOW YOU'RE GETTING IT.
AND HOW ABOUT NOW?
YES.
WELL DONE.
[ WHOOSH! ]
AH, THANK THEE,
DEAR FLUTTERSHY.
OUR NORMAL SPEAKING VOICE
SHALL SURELY WIN US THE HEARTS
OF THY FELLOW VILLAGERS!
FLUTTERSHY,
YOU GOT TO HIDE US!
NIGHTMARE MOON IS HERE AND --
[ GASPS ]
SHE'S STOLEN FLUTTERSHY'S VOICE
SO SHE CAN'T SCREAM
WHEN SHE GOBBLES HER UP!
AAH! AAH!
[ ZIP! ]
NAY, CHILDREN!
WAIT!
[ Normal voice ]
I-I MEAN...NAY, CHILDREN.
NO. WAIT.
COME ON, PRINCESS.
TIME FOR PLAN "B."
YAY! YAY!
WHOO-HOO!
[ RECORD SCRATCHES, ALL GASP ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
IT IS OF NO USE,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
THEY HAVE NEVER LIKED US,
AND THEY NEVER SHALL.
MY FRIEND APPLEJACK
IS ONE OF THE MOST
LIKABLE PONIES AROUND.
I'M SURE SHE'LL HAVE
SOME IDEAS.
[ WARBLE! ]
AAH!
OH,
CAREFUL THERE, PARTNER.
UHH!
UH, APPLEJACK?
THE PRINCESS IS LOOKING FOR
A LITTLE ADVICE
ON HOW TO FIT IN
AROUND HERE.
FIT IN?
REALLY?
MM.
I MEAN...
[ CHUCKLES ] THAT'S EASY.
ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS HAVE
THE RIGHT ATTITUDE.
LOOSEN UP A BIT.
BE POSITIVE.
PLAY A FEW GAMES.
HAVE SOME FUN.
FUN?
WHAT IS THIS "FUN"
THOU SPEAKETH OF?
PRAY TELL, WHAT PURPOSE
DO THESE SERVE?
TRY TO LAND
THE S-S-SPIDERS ON THE WEB.
[ WHOOSH ]
[ SQUEAK! ]
YOU CAN DO IT,
PRINCESS!
HA!
YOUR PRINCESS ENJOYS
THIS...FUN.
IN WHAT OTHER WAYS
MAY WE EXPERIENCE IT?
FIRE AWAY, PRINCESS!
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
HA HA!
THE FUN HAS BEEN DOUBLED!
YAY! YAY!
WHOO!
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
BOBBING FOR APPLES?
WE GOT THE BEST APPLES
IN EQUESTRIA HERE, PRINCESS.
I ASK THAT THOU CALL US --
ME...
LUNA, FAIR APPLEJACK.
HEAR ME, VILLAGERS!
ALL OF YOU! CALL ME LUNA!
LUNA!
SHOW ME
TO THESE BOBBING APPLES.
[ WARBLE! ]
WHOA!
[ WHOOSH! ]
HEY, GALS.
ANYPONY SEEN PIP?
WE LOST HIM THE LAST TIME
WE HAD TO RUN -- [ SQUAWKS ]
AAH!
NIGHTMARE MOON
IS GOBBLING PIP-SQUEAK!
EVERYPONY RUN!
[ ZIP! ]
AAH! AAH!
HELP!
MY BACKSIDE HAS BEEN GOBBLED!
'TIS A LIE!
THY BACKSIDE IS WHOLE
AND UNGOBBLED,
THOU UNGRATEFUL WHELP!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
FAIR VILLAGERS,
PLEASE DO NOT BACK AWAY.
LET US JOIN TOGETHER
IN...FUN!
[ SQUEAK! ]
NOT ENOUGH FUN FOR YOU?
WHAT SAY YOU TO THIS?!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SPIDERS CHITTERING ]
AAH!
HUZZAH!
HOW MANY POINTS
DO I RECEIVE?!
[ SCREAMING ]
DO NOT RUN AWAY!
AS YOUR PRINCESS,
WE COMMAND YOU!
[ ZIP! ]
[ CLANK! ]
[ Echoing ]
BE STILL!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
PRINCESS, REMEMBER.
WATCH THE SCREAMING.
NO, TWILIGHT SPARKLE!
WE MUST USE THE TRADITIONAL
ROYAL CANTERLOT VOICE
FOR WHAT
WE ARE ABOUT TO SAY.
SHOULD YOU CHOOSE
TO FEAR YOUR PRINCESS
RATHER THAN LOVE HER
AND DISHONOR HER WITH
THIS INSULTING CELEBRATION,
WE DECREE THAT NIGHTMARE NIGHT
SHALL BE CANCELED -- FOREVER!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
[ SIGHS ]
SHOOT.
WE HAD EVERYTHING
GOING OUR WAY.
LUNA WAS HAPPY.
EVERYPONY IN TOWN WAS HAPPY.
NOW LOOK AT THEM.
[ ALL CRYING ]
[ Crying ] BUT I WANTED TO BE
A ZOMBIE NEXT YEAR.
IT'S NOT OVER YET.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
I'M GOING TO DO
WHAT I DO BEST.
LECTURE HER!
[ BELLS JINGLE ]
PRINCESS?
LEAVE ME BE,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
PRINCESS, I'M SORRY
IT HASN'T WORKED OUT
HOW WE WANTED,
BUT YOU HAVE TO
BELIEVE ME
WHEN I TELL YOU
THAT NIGHTMARE NIGHT
IS ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR
CELEBRATIONS WE HAVE.
YES.
I CAN TELL
BY ALL THE ADORING SHRIEKS
OF THE CHILDREN
AS THEY RUN AWAY.
PRINCESS.
[ ALL CRYING ]
[ CLUCKING ]
[ CLUCKS ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ GULP! ]
[ SQUAWKS ]
NO!
NO SHRIEKING, NO SQUEALING
OR SCREAMING EITHER, OKAY?
[ High-pitched voice ]
OKAY.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT YOU TO SEE,
AND I PROMISE
THAT IT'S SAFE,
BUT YOU REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY CAN'T SHRIEK.
DO YOU PROMISE
NOT TO SHRIEK?
MM-HMM.
[ SQUAWKS ]
PINKIE PIE, YOU REMEMBER
PRINCESS LUNA, RIGHT?
AH, THE RINGLEADER
OF THE FRIGHTENED CHILDREN.
HAS THOU COME
TO MAKE PEACE?
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
NIGHTMARE MOON!
[ SQUAWKS ]
[ ZIP! ]
RAINBOW!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ CLUCKS ]
SHE'S CHANGED, PINKIE.
SHE'S NOT EVIL OR SCARY ANYMORE.
AND SHE DEFINITELY DOESN'T
WANT TO GOBBLE YOU UP.
WELL, DUH.
HUH?
I KNOW THAT.
GEEZ, TWILIGHT.
I'M ALMOST AS BIG AS HER.
HOW'S SHE GONNA
GOBBLE ME UP?
SO WHY DO YOU KEEP RUNNING AWAY
AND SCREAMING?
SOMETIMES IT'S JUST REALLY FUN
TO BE SCARED.
FUN?
PINKIE PIE,
YOU'RE A GENIUS!
NO, I'M NOT. I'M A CHICKEN.
[ SQUAWKS ]
Twilight Sparkle:
PRINCESS LUNA!
I FINALLY FIGURED OUT
WHY YOU'RE HAVING
SO MUCH TROUBLE BEING LIKED.
FORGIVE ME IF I WITHHOLD
MY ENTHUSIASM.
COME WITH ME.
I'LL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING
ON THE WAY.
GOSH, I NEVER THOUGHT
MY VERY FIRST NIGHTMARE NIGHT
WOULD BE MY VERY LAST.
COME, LITTLE PIP.
NOW, DON'T YOU FRET.
NIGHTMARE NIGHT'S
NOT OVER YET.
WE STILL HAVE CANDY
LEFT TO GIVE
SO NIGHTMARE MOON
MIGHT LET US LIVE.
YES.
COME ON, LITTLE PONIES.
WHAT'S NIGHTMARE NIGHT WITHOUT
THE ANNUAL CANDY OFFERING?
[ Spooky voice ]
YOU DON'T WANT NIGHTMARE MOON
TO GOBBLE YOU UP,
DO YOU?
AW, THE RAINBOW WIG
JUST KILLS IT FOR ME.
COME ON, KIDS.
DOESN'T THAT SOUND LIKE FUN?
GOODBYE,
NIGHTMARE NIGHT...
FOREVER.
[ ZAP! ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
Princess Luna:
CITIZENS OF PONYVILLE!
YOU WERE WISE TO BRING
THIS CANDY TO ME!
I AM PLEASED
WITH YOUR OFFERING!
SO PLEASED THAT I MAY JUST
EAT IT INSTEAD OF EATING YOU!
AAH! AAH!
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ SPITS ]
I AM NOT CERTAIN THAT DID
WHAT YOU MEANT FOR IT TO DO,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
JUST WAIT.
FOR WHAT? FOR -- FOR THEM
TO SCREAM SOME MORE?
UH, PRINCESS LUNA,
I KNOW THERE'S NOT GONNA BE
ANY MORE NIGHTMARE NIGHT,
BUT DO YOU SUPPOSE MAYBE
YOU COULD COME BACK NEXT YEAR
AND SCARE US AGAIN
ANYWAY?
CHILD, ART THOU SAYING
THAT THOU...
LIKETH ME TO SCARE YOU?
IT'S REALLY FUN.
SCARY, BUT FUN.
IT IS?
YEAH. NIGHTMARE NIGHT IS
MY FAVORITE NIGHT OF THE YEAR.
WELL, THEN.
WE SHALL HAVE TO BRING...
[ Echoing ]
NIGHTMARE NIGHT BACK!
WHOA!
YOU'RE MY FAVORITE
PRINCESS EVER!
SHE SAID "YES," GUYS!
YAY! YAY!
SEE?
THEY REALLY DO LIKE YOU,
PRINCESS.
CAN IT BE TRUE?
[ Echoing ]
OH, MOST WONDERFUL OF...
[ Normal voice ] I MEAN,
OH, MOST WONDERFUL OF NIGHTS.
Twilight Sparkle:
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
WHEN YOU FIRST SENT ME
TO PONYVILLE,
I DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
I MET SOMEPONY TONIGHT WHO WAS
HAVING THE SAME PROBLEM --
YOUR SISTER PRINCESS LUNA.
SHE TAUGHT ME
THAT ONE OF THE BEST THINGS
YOU CAN DO WITH FRIENDSHIP
IS TO GIVE IT TO OTHERS
AND HELP THEM FIND IT
THEMSELVES.
AND I'M HAPPY TO REPORT
THAT ALL OF PONYVILLE
HAS LEARNED
THAT EVEN IF SOMEPONY SEEMS
A LITTLE INTIMIDATING,
EVEN SCARY, WHEN YOU
OFFER THEM YOUR FRIENDSHIP,
YOU'LL DISCOVER A WHOLE NEW PONY
UNDERNEATH.
AND EVEN IF MY STAR SWIRL
THE BEARDED COSTUME
DIDN'T GO OVER,
THIS STILL TURNED OUT TO BE
THE BEST NIGHTMARE NIGHT EVER.
[ ZAP! ]
AAH!
[ TINK! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪