[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ YAWNS ]
WHO COULD THAT BE?
IT'S STILL DARK.
[ ZOOM! CRASH! ]
COME ON, FLUTTERSHY!
CIDER SEASON'S ABOUT TO START!
[ SHRIEKS ]
OH, WHERE ARE WE?
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
THE RUSH?
DON'T YOU REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
LAST YEAR?
OR THE YEAR BEFORE THAT?
OR PRETTY MUCH ANY CIDER SEASON
EVER?
OH, WELL, UH...
PINKIE PIE.
SHE ALWAYS ENDS UP AHEAD OF US
IN LINE, AND THEN THEY ALWAYS
RUN OUT OF CIDER!
I GUESS I --
WELL, NOT THIS YEAR.
THIS YEAR, I'M GONNA GET THERE
BEFORE SUNRISE SO I CAN DRINK
ALL THE CIDER I WANT AND LAUGH
WHEN SHE DOESN'T GET ANY.
IT'S THE PERFECT PLAN.
[ ZOOM! ]
YOU KNOW, I MIGHT EVEN BUY SOME
CIDER AND HOLD ON TO IT FOR A
WHILE, DRINKING IT DROP BY DROP
IN FRONT OF HER.
[ GASPS ]
GEE, RAINBOW DASH, LOOKS LIKE
A FEW OTHER PONIES HAD THE SAME
IDEA.
[ ZIP! ]
OH, GOSH, PINKIE, I LOVE YOUR
NEW STYLE.
WHO ARE ALL THESE PONIES?
ISN'T THIS GREAT?
I COULDN'T SLEEP LAST NIGHT
'CAUSE I WAS SO EXCITED ABOUT
CIDER SEASON, AND I HAD THIS
BRILLIANT IDEA TO COME DOWN HERE
AND CAMP OUT, SO I TOLD A FEW
OTHERS ABOUT IT, AND THEY ALL
THOUGHT IT WAS A GREAT IDEA,
TOO, AND NOW IT'S JUST A BIG OLD
CIDER PARTY!
WHOO-HOO!
OH, GOSH.
THAT'S A LOT OF PONIES.
HOPE THEY DON'T RUN OUT BEFORE
YOU GET ANY.
[ GROWLS ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
ISN'T THIS EXCITING, SPIKE?
OPENING DAY OF CIDER SEASON.
YEAH.
THAT MEANS IT'S ONLY 30 MORE
DAYS TILL SAPPHIRE SEASON.
ATTENTION, EVERYPONY.
CIDER SEASON IS NOW OFFICIALLY
OPEN!
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
[ GULPS ]
[ FAUCET SPUTTERS ]
[ GROWLS ]
UH, SORRY, EVERYPONY.
THAT'S IT FOR TODAY.
[ CROWD GRUMBLES ]
SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
YOU RAN OUT AGAIN!
YEAH, YOU ALWAYS RUN OUT.
FOR THE RECORD, I DON'T
MIND --
WHY CAN'T YOU MAKE ENOUGH
CIDER FOR ALL OF US?
OR AT LEAST FOR ME.
[ CROWD MURMURS ANGRILY ]
HOLD ON, EVERYPONY.
WE'VE DONE OUR BEST TO IMPROVE
SUPPLY THIS YEAR.
YOU ALWAYS SAY THAT!
AND IT'S ALWAYS TRUE.
BUT APPLE FAMILY CIDER IS MADE
WITH LOVE AND INTEGRITY AND
ONLY THE HIGHEST-QUALITY APPLES
IN EQUESTRIA.
SORRY, BUT THAT RECIPE TAKES
TIME.
[ CROWD MURMURS ANGRILY ]
IF Y'ALL JUST BE PATIENT, WE'LL
HAVE PLENTY MORE TOMORROW.
SHE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
YOU CAN'T RUSH PERFECTION, AND
THIS YEAR'S BATCH WAS
PERFECTION!
UH, PINKIE PIE...
I'LL NEVER FORGET THE CIDER I
JUST DRANK.
IT WAS A MOMENT IN TIME THAT
WILL NEVER EXIST AGAIN.
OH!
[ GROWLS ]
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ CLANKING, SPUTTERING ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
WHAT IN EQUESTRIA IS THAT?
[ Rhythmically ] WELL, LOOKEE
WHAT WE GOT HERE, BROTHER OF
MINE.
IT'S THE SAME IN EVERY
TOWN.
PONIES WITH THIRSTY THROATS, DRY
TONGUES, AND NOT A DROP OF CIDER
TO BE FOUND.
MAYBE THEY'RE NOT AWARE THAT
THERE'S REALLY NO NEED FOR THIS
TEARY DESPAIR.
♪ THAT THE KEY THAT THEY NEED
TO SOLVE THE SAD CIDER SHORTAGE,
YOU AND I WILL SHARE ♪
OOH!
[ GIGGLES ]
Both: ♪ WELL, YOU'VE GOT
OPPORTUNITY IN THIS VERY
COMMUNITY ♪
HE'S FLIM.
HE'S FLAM.
Both: ♪ WE'RE THE WORLD-
FAMOUS FLIM FLAM BROTHERS ♪
♪ TRAVELING SALESPONIES
NONPAREIL ♪
NONPA-WHAT?
[ Rhythmically ] NONPAREIL.
THAT'S EXACTLY THE REASON WHY,
YOU SEE, NOPONY ELSE IN THIS
WHOLE PLACE WILL GIVE YOU SUCH A
CHANCE TO BE WHERE YOU NEED TO
BE.
AND THAT'S A NEW WORLD WITH TONS
OF CIDER FRESH-SQUEEZED AND
READY FOR DRINKING.
♪ MORE CIDER THAN YOU COULD
DRINK IN ALL YOUR DAYS OF
THINKING ♪
I DOUBT THAT.
All: ♪ SO TAKE THIS
OPPORTUNITY IN THIS VERY
COMMUNITY ♪
HE'S FLIM.
HE'S FLAM.
Both: ♪ WE'RE THE WORLD-
FAMOUS FLIM FLAM BROTHERS ♪
♪ TRAVELING SALESPONIES
NONPAREIL ♪
[ Rhythmically ] I SUPPOSE BY
NOW YOU'RE WONDERING ABOUT OUR
PECULIAR MODE OF TRANSPORT.
♪ I'D SAY A MODE OF
LOCOMOTION ♪
AND I SUPPOSE BY NOW YOU'RE
WONDERING, "WHERE IS THIS
PROMISED CIDER?"
♪ ANY HORSE CAN MAKE A CLAIM,
AND ANY PONY CAN DO THE SAME ♪
BUT MY BROTHER AND I HAVE
THE MOST UNIQUE AND SUPERB,
UNSEEN IN ANY TIME IN THIS BIG,
NEW WORLD.
Both: ♪ AND THAT'S
OPPORTUNITY ♪
♪ FOLKS, THE ONE AND ONLY,
THE BIGGEST AND THE BEST ♪
♪ THE UNBELIEVABLE ♪
♪ UNIMPEACHABLE ♪
♪ INDISPENSABLE ♪
♪ I-CAN'T-BELIEVABLE ♪
Both: ♪ FLIM FLAM BROTHERS
SUPER SPEEDY
CIDER SQUEEZY 6000 ♪
WHAT DO YOU SAY, SISTER?
All: ♪ OH, WE GOT OPPORTUNITY
IN THIS VERY COMMUNITY ♪
♪ PLEASE, FLIM, PLEASE FLAM,
HELP US OUT OF THIS JAM
WITH YOUR FLIM FLAM BROTHERS
SUPER SPEEDY
CIDER SQUEEZY 6000 ♪
[ Normal voice ] YOUNG FILLY,
I WOULD BE EVER SO HONORED IF
YOU MIGHT SEE FIT TO LET MY
BROTHER AND I BORROW SOME OF
YOUR DELICIOUS -- AND MIGHT I
ADD SPELL-BINDINGLY FRAGRANT --
APPLES FOR OUR LITTLE
DEMONSTRATION, HERE?
UH, SURE.
I GUESS.
All: ♪ OPPORTUNITY IN OUR
COMMUNITY ♪
♪ READY, FLIM? ♪
♪ READY, FLAM ♪
Both: ♪ LET'S BIG-BANG-ZAM ♪
AND SHOW THESE THIRSTY PONIES
A WORLD OF DELECTABLE CIDER.
All: [ Chanting ] CIDER,
CIDER, CIDER, CIDER, CIDER,
CIDER, CIDER, CIDER...
WATCH CLOSELY, MY FRIENDS.
♪ THE FUN BEGINS ♪
NOW HERE'S WHERE THE MAGIC
HAPPENS RIGHT HERE IN THIS
HEAVING, ROILING, CIDER-PRESS
COILING GUTS OF THE
VERY MACHINE.
THOSE APPLES, PLUCKED FRESH, ARE
RIGHT NOW AS WE SPEAK BEING
TURNED INTO GRADE-A, TOP-NOTCH,
FIVE-STAR,
BLOW-YOUR-HORSESHOES-OFF,
ONE-OF-A-KIND CIDER!
♪ FEEL FREE TO TAKE A SNEAK
PEEK ♪
[ Rhythmically ] NOW, WAIT,
YOU FELLERS.
HOLD IT!
YOU WENT AND OVERSOLD IT.
I GUARANTEE THAT WHAT YOU HAVE
THERE WON'T COMPARE.
FOR THE VERY MOST IMPORTANT
INGREDIENT CAN'T BE ADDED OR
DONE EXPEDIENT.
AND IT'S QUALITY, FRIENDS --
APPLE ACRES QUALITY AND CARE!
[ Rhythmically ] WELL,
GRANNY, I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT
THAT UP, MY DEAR.
I SAY, I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT THAT
UP.
YOU'LL SEE THAT WE ARE VERY
PICKY WHEN IT COMES TO CIDER IF
YOU'LL KINDLY TRY A CUP.
[ Rhythmically ] YES, SIR,
YES, MA'AM, THIS GREAT MACHINE
LETS JUST THE VERY BEST.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY, THEN,
APPLES?
♪ CARE TO STEP INTO THE MODERN
WORLD AND PUT THE SUPER SPEEDY
CIDER SQUEEZY 6000 TO THE
TEST? ♪
WHAT DO YOU THINK, FOLKS?
DO YOU SEE WHAT THE APPLES
CAN'T?
I SEE IT CLEAR AS DAY.
I KNOW SHE DOES.
SO DOES HE!
COME ON, PONYVILLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
All: ♪ WE'RE SAYING YOU'VE
GOT OPPORTUNITY IN THIS VERY
COMMUNITY ♪
♪ HE'S FLIM ♪
♪ HE'S FLAM ♪
♪ WE'RE THE WORLD-
FAMOUS FLIM FLAM BROTHERS, ♪
♪ TRAVELING SALESPONIES
NONPAREIL ♪
Both: YEAH!
YOU GOT A DEAL!
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
NOT SO FAST!
NO WAY NO HOW THAT MACHINE
MATCHES UP WITH THE CARE WE PUT
IN OUR CIDER.
BUT IF IT REALLY DOES WORK,
WE COULD MAKE EVERYPONY IN TOWN
HAPPY.
I JUST DON'T KNOW, Y'ALL.
WE'VE ALWAYS MADE CIDER THE SAME
WAY.
YEP.
HUH?
WE'LL SWEETEN THE DEAL.
YOU SUPPLY THE APPLES...
WE SUPPLY THE SUPER SPEEDY
CIDER SQUEEZY 6000.
Both: THEN WE SPLIT THOSE
SWEET, SWEET PROFITS...
75...
25.
DEAL!
HOLD ON.
WHO GETS THE 75%?
WHY, US, NATURALLY.
AND WE'LL THROW IN THE MAGIC
TO POWER THE MACHINE FOR FREE.
CIDER SALES KEEP OUR BUSINESS
AFLOAT THROUGH THE WINTER.
WE'D LOSE SWEET APPLE ACRES IF
WE AGREE TO THIS.
Both: SO, WHAT WILL IT BE?
NO DEAL.
HMM.
VERY WELL.
IF YOU REFUSE OUR GENEROUS OFFER
TO BE PARTNERS, THEN WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO BE COMPETITORS.
YOU WOULDN'T DARE.
OH, NO?
DON'T YOU WORRY, EVERYPONY.
THERE'LL BE PLENTY OF CIDER FOR
ALL OF YOU.
Once we drive
Sweet Apple Acres out of
business.
[ ALL GASP ]
WHAT?
STILL WORRIED ABOUT FLIM AND
FLAM?
GRANNY SMITH SAYS THEY WERE
JUST BLOWING HOT AIR.
I'M NOT SO SURE.
THEY SOUNDED MIGHTY SERIOUS WHEN
THEY THREATENED TO RUN US OUT OF
BUSINESS.
THAT'S IT!
LAST CUP!
OH, FOR PETE'S SAKE!
[ CROWD GROANS ]
COME ON BACK TOMORROW,
EVERYPONY.
[ CROWD GRUMBLES ]
[ CLANKING, SPUTTERING ]
WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM
HERE?
OH, MY, OH, MY.
OUT OF CIDER AGAIN?
WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
WHO'D LIKE A CUP?
[ EXCITED CHATTER ]
DON'T WORRY, EVERYPONY.
WE'VE GOT THE SUPER SPEEDY
CIDER SQUEEZY 6000 TO MAKE MORE
IN AN INSTANT.
[ WHACK! ]
YOU CAN'T SELL THAT CIDER!
THAT'S MADE FROM APPLE FAMILY
APPLES.
IS THIS SOME KIND OF CRUEL
JOKE?
DON'T WORRY, EVERYPONY.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF APPLES IN
EQUESTRIA.
WE'LL FIND SOME OTHERS AND MAKE
MORE CIDER THAN ALL OF PONYVILLE
CAN DRINK.
[ CROWD GASPS ]
WE'LL MAKE MORE CIDER THAN
YOU COULD EVER IMAGINE.
[ CROWD GASPS ]
NOW, IT AIN'T ABOUT THE
SPEED, YOUNGIN.
IT'S ABOUT QUALITY.
[ CROWD GROANS ]
WHO CARES HOW GOOD THE CIDER
IS IF I NEVER GET TO DRINK ANY?
OH, LOOK AT THESE POOR,
DISSATISFIED PONIES.
PONYVILLE IS
SWEET APPLE CIDER COUNTRY.
OUR CIDER SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
LET'S PUT IT TO THE TEST.
ANYWHERE, ANYTIME.
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
THAT'S ENOUGH, NOW.
WITH OUR MACHINE, WE CAN MAKE
ENOUGH CIDER IN ONE HOUR TO
SATISFY THIS ENTIRE TOWN.
WE'LL DO IT IN 45 MINUTES.
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
EASY, APPLE BLOOM, EASY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
GRANNY SMITH?
CHICKEN?
WHAT DID YOU CALL ME, SONNY?
IF YOU'RE SO CONFIDENT IN
YOUR CIDER, THEN WHAT'S THE
PROBLEM?
TOMORROW MORNING, RIGHT HERE!
BUT I'M AFRAID WE HAVEN'T ANY
APPLES.
YOU CAN USE OUR SOUTH FIELD.
IT WILL BE WORTH IT TO TEACH
Y'ALL A THING OR TWO ABOUT
CIDER-MAKING!
EXCELLENT!
WE HAVE A BET.
WHOEVER PRODUCES THE MOST
BARRELS IN ONE HOUR WINS THE
EXCLUSIVE RIGHT TO SELL CIDER IN
PONYVILLE.
AND AFTER WE BEAT YOU, I
DON'T EVER WANT TO SEE YOU
BAMBAHOOZLERS AROUND HERE AGAIN!
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
UNTIL TOMORROW.
DON'T WORRY, APPLEJACK.
I KNOW YOU'LL WIN TOMORROW.
WE'D BETTER, 'CAUSE IF WE
DON'T, WE'RE GONNA LOSE OUR
FARM.
[ SNIFFING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
APPLEJACK, ARE YOU SURE THIS
IS SUCH A GOOD IDEA?
ME AND THE FAMILY ARE
[GRUNTS] 100% CONFIDENT IN OUR
CIDER-MAKING CAPABILITIES.
AND BESIDES, NOPONY CALLS
GRANNY A CHICKEN.
[ THUMP! ]
ATTENTION, EVERYPONY!
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
THANKS, TWILIGHT.
WE'LL NEED IT.
THE TEAMS HAVE ONE HOUR TO
PRODUCE AS MUCH CIDER AS THEY
CAN.
AFTER WHICH, THE BARRELS WILL BE
COUNTED, AND THE WINNER WILL BE
NAMED THE SOLE CIDER PROVIDER
FOR ALL OF PONYVILLE.
[ CROWD GASPS, MURMURS ]
ARE BOTH TEAMS READY?
[ SNORTS ]
READY!
Both: READY!
THEN LET'S...
GO!
[ SNIFFS ]
UGH. BAD ONE.
GOOD ONE!
[ SNIFFS ]
BAD ONE.
GOOD ONE!
GREAT JOB, Y'ALL.
BAD ONE.
WE'VE ALREADY FILLED AN ENTIRE
GREAT JOB, Y'ALL.
BARREL.
WE'VE ALREADY FILLED AN ENTIRE
I'LL BET YOU THOSE GUYS DON'T
BARREL.
EVEN HAVE --
I'LL BET YOU THOSE GUYS DON'T
[ ALL GASP ]
EVEN HAVE --
[ GULPS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ DING! ]
[ GULPS ]
[ BUZZER ]
[ DING! ]
COME ON, APPLE BLOOM.
FOCUS!
WE GOT TO FORGET THOSE GUYS IF
WE'RE GONNA HAVE A CHANCE OF
WINNING.
SORRY, SIS.
BETTER KEEP UP, GRANNY.
WE'RE FALLING BEHIND.
[ GROANS ]
[ SNIFFS ]
GOOD ONE.
UGH. BAD ONE.
REST WHEN IT'S OVER,
BIG MACINTOSH.
RUN! RUN!
THIS IS JUST DREADFUL.
EVEN AT TOP SPEED, THE APPLES
ARE ONLY MAKING ONE BARREL TO
THE TWINS' THREE.
UM, MS. MAYOR, ARE HONORARY
FAMILY MEMBERS ALLOWED TO HELP
IN THE COMPETITION?
WELL, I'M NOT SURE.
FLIM, FLAM, WOULD YOU OBJECT TO
HONORARY FAMILY MEMBERS HELPING?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
WE DON'T CARE IF THE WHOLE
KINGDOM OF CANTERLOT HELPS.
IT'S A LOST CAUSE.
HMM.
I GUESS IT'S OKAY.
APPLEJACK, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK I'D LOVE TO HAVE THE
REST OF MY FAMILY HELPING OUT.
ALL RIGHT!
OKAY, EVERYPONY.
WE'RE NOT GONNA LET THOSE SMOOTH
TALKERS TAKE OUR FRIENDS' FARM.
YEAH!
FLUTTERSHY, HELP APPLEJACK
WITH THE TREES.
GOT IT.
PINKIE PIE, YOU'RE ON
APPLE-CATCHING DETAIL.
YES, SIR, MA'AM, SIR.
RARITY, YOU'VE GOT A
DISCERNING EYE.
HELP GRANNY SMITH AT THE
QUALITY-CONTROL STATION.
OF COURSE.
RAINBOW DASH, DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN HELP BIG MACINTOSH
PRESS?
IN MY SLEEP.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYPONY.
LET'S SAVE SWEET APPLE ACRES.
ALL RIGHT!
OVER THERE, APPLE BLOOM!
DON'T MISS THEM!
RIGHT BEHIND YOU, PINKIE PIE!
GOOD ONE!
BAD ONE! BAD ONE!
LOVELY.
GOOD ONE!
HORRID! HORRID!
LOVELY.
BASED ON THESE FIGURES, WE'RE
MAKING FIVE BARRELS FOR EVERY
THREE OF THEIRS.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
KEEP IT UP, EVERYPONY!
WE'RE BACK IN THIS.
[ SPUTTERS ]
COME ON, BROTHER, WE'VE GOT TO
PICK UP THE PACE!
RIGHT!
UH, DOUBLE THE POWER!
[ BUZZER ]
WE'VE GOT TO TRY SOMETHING
ELSE!
I'VE GOT IT, BROTHER OF
MINE.
[ DING! DING! ]
WELL, DONE, FLAM.
WE'RE AT TOP PRODUCTIVITY!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
COME ON, RAINBOW DASH.
KEEP GRINDING.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR
QUALITY CONTROL IF WE WANT TO
WIN THIS THING.
[ ZOOM! ]
AAH!
GET BACK, YOU.
ONE BAD APPLE SPOILS THE BUNCH!
APPLEJACK, HELP ME.
THERE'S NO POINT IN WINNING
IF WE CHEAT.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO WORK
HARDER.
COME ON, EVERYPONY.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
DOUBLE TIME!
[ DING! DING! DING! ]
[ DING! DING! ]
TIME'S UP!
[ ALL GROAN ]
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
[ MURMURS ]
I'M PROUD OF YOU, APPLEJACK.
THANKS.
INTEGRITY LIKE THAT WILL
ALWAYS BE REWARDED.
FLIM AND FLAM WIN.
WHAT?
W-W--
WE...LOST?
AWW.
TOO BAD, APPLES.
GUESS YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO
FIND A NEW LINE OF WORK THAT
DOESN'T MATCH YOUR NAMES QUITE
SO PERFECTLY.
NOW, SHOULD WE TEAR DOWN ALL
THESE TACKY OLD BUILDINGS AND
PUT UP NEW ONES, BROTHER?
I DON'T SEE WHY NOT, BROTHER.
AFTER ALL, THIS ISN'T
SWEET APPLE ACRES, ANYMORE.
HOW ABOUT FLIM FLAM FIELDS?
I OUGHT TO PRESS YOU INTO JERK
CIDER!
NO, RAINBOW DASH.
A DEAL'S A DEAL.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
CONGRATULATIONS TO Y'ALL.
THE CIDER BUSINESS IN PONYVILLE
IS YOURS.
COME ON, APPLES.
LET'S GO PACK UP OUR THINGS.
FEAR NOT, EVERYPONY.
THERE'S MORE THAN ENOUGH CIDER
TO GO AROUND.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
GO AHEAD, EVERYPONY.
GO ON, Y'ALL.
IT'S OKAY.
[ CRIES ]
DRINK UP, PONYVILLE!
DOWN THE HATCH.
UGH!
EW!
[ ALL SPUTTER ]
I CAN'T GET THE TASTE OFF MY
TONGUE!
MINE'S GOT ROCKS IN IT.
I WOULDN'T PAY ONE CENT FOR
THIS DREG.
YOU WOULDN'T PAY EVEN ONE
CENT?
All: NO!
[ BOTH MURMUR ]
HOW ABOUT TWO CUPS FOR ONE
CENT?
All: NO!
[ BOTH MURMUR ]
Both: TWO BITS FOR THE
BARREL?
All: NO!
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'VE ENCOUNTERED
A SLIGHT PROBLEM HERE IN
PONYVILLE.
NOPONY WANTS OUR PRODUCT.
NEXT TOWN?
NEXT TOWN.
[ ZIP! ]
LET'S GO, FLIM.
LET'S GO, FLAM.
[ CLANKING, SPUTTERING ]
THEY'RE GONE.
THAT MEANS SWEET APPLE ACRES
IS STILL IN BUSINESS.
PLUS, WE CAN HAVE
HIGH-QUALITY APPLE FAMILY CIDER.
BECAUSE OF THIS SILLY
COMPETITION, WE'VE MADE ENOUGH
OF OUR CIDER FOR THE WHOLE TOWN.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA, I
WANTED TO SHARE MY THOUGHTS
WITH YOU.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
I DIDN'T LEARN ANYTHING!
[ LAUGHS ]
I WAS RIGHT ALL ALONG!
IF YOU TAKE YOUR TIME TO DO
THINGS THE RIGHT WAY, YOUR WORK
WILL SPEAK FOR ITSELF.
SURE, I COULD TELL YOU I
LEARNED SOMETHING ABOUT HOW MY
FRIENDS ARE ALWAYS THERE TO
HELP ME AND I CAN COUNT ON THEM
NO MATTER WHAT, BUT TRUTH IS I
KNEW THAT ALREADY, TOO.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪