[ GASPS ] HERE?
I GET TO STAY HERE?!
TWILIGHT SPARKLE SAID YOU WERE
COMING TO CANTERLOT FOR A VISIT
AND ASKED
IF I MIGHT ACCOMMODATE YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
PRINCESS.
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
NO, REALLY,
THIS IS SO NICE OF YOU.
IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
OH, BUT IT ISN'T NOTHING.
IT'S EVERYTHING!
I-I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY BUT THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
[ ZIP! ]
MWAH!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
THANK YOU! MWAH!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
MWAH, MWAH, MWAH, MWAH, MWAH,
MWAH, MWAH, MWAH!
MWAH!
YOU ARE VERY WEL--
[ ZIP! ]
THANK YOU!
[ PONY GROANS ]
YOUR LUGGAGE, MADEMOISELLE.
I'LL LEAVE YOU
TO GET SETTLED.
[ GROANS ]
YOUR HIGHNESS.
ENJOY YOUR STAY.
THANK YOU!
[ GROANS ]
WHERE WOULD YOU LIKE ME
TO PUT THESE?
[ GROANING ] OHH!
THAT'S PERFECT.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
OPAL, DO YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE
ABOUT CANTERLOT?
[ SIP! ]
AHH. EVERYTHING!
I MAY HAVE BEEN BORN
IN PONYVILLE,
BUT I AM A CANTERLOT PONY
AT HEART.
[ TINKLING ]
NOW, I KNOW THAT WE'RE
HERE TO PICK UP SOME
FABRICS FOR THE SHOP,
BUT TWILIGHT
WAS SUCH A DEAR
TO GET ME THAT SUITE
AT THE CASTLE.
I SIMPLY MUST MAKE HER SOMETHING
TO EXPRESS MY GRATITUDE.
HMM. OOH!
AN OUTFIT FOR HER BIRTHDAY PARTY
THIS WEEKEND!
PERFECT!
DON'T YOU JUST LOVE IT HERE,
OPALESCENCE?
[ SIPPING ]
[ CUP CLATTERS ]
[ SWISH! ]
PLEASE EXCUSE
OUR INTERRUPTION.
I'M JET SET, AND THIS IS
MY WIFE, UPPER CRUST.
WE SAW YOU FROM ACROSS THE CAFé
AND JUST HAD TO FIND OUT...
WHERE DID YOU GET
THAT SIMPLY MARVELOUS CHAPEAU?
[ POINK! ]
OH, THIS OLD THING?
OH, IT'S JUST SOMETHING I --
RARITY!
HEY, RARITY!
[ PLOP! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ SPROING! ]
IT'S ME --
HAYSEED TURNIP TRUCK.
WE MET AT THE BIG HOEDOWN
AT PONYVILLE LAST FALL.
Rarity: OH, YES.
OF COURSE.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD! REAL GOOD!
[ SNAP! THUD! ]
HMM.
YOU'RE FROM PONYVILLE?
WELL, Y-YES, BUT --
SHE SURE IS!
SHE'S A REAL BIG-TIME
FANCY-PANTS DRESSMAKER THERE!
PROBABLY MADE THAT REAL PRETTY
THING SHE'S GOT ON HER HEAD.
I THOUGHT IT LOOKED
A LITTLE COUNTRY.
I TOLD YOU
IT WASN'T SOMETHING
YOU COULD GET HERE
IN CANTERLOT, DEAR.
HMPH!
WELL,
THEY SEEM REAL NICE.
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ TINKLING ]
"LOOKED A LITTLE COUNTRY."
"NOT SOMETHING YOU COULD GET
HERE IN CANTERLOT."
I'LL SHOW YOU SOMETHING WORTHY
OF CANTERLOT!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I HAVE TO GET STARTED
RIGHT AWAY.
THIS NEW DESIGN
IS VERY AMBITIOUS,
AND I'VE ALREADY WRITTEN
TO TWILIGHT
TO LET HER KNOW SHE'LL HAVE
SOMETHING BEYOND FABULOUS
TO WEAR TO HER PARTY.
[ THUD! ]
[ RARITY GASPS ]
FANCY PANTS!
I SAY, THAT'S ONE WAY
TO MAKE AN INTRODUCTION.
OH, GOODNESS!
I AM SO SORRY!
I-I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
I-I'VE JUST GOT
SO MANY BAGS,
AND I WAS TRYING TO GET BACK TO
MY SUITE AT THE CASTLE, AND --
YOU'RE STAYING
AT THE CASTLE?
WELL, THE PRINCESS INVITED ME
TO STAY IN ONE OF THE SUITES.
YOU KNOW THE PRINCESS?
MM! A PONY WITH
EXPENSIVE TASTES, I SEE.
OH, IT'S FOR AN ENSEMBLE
I'M MAKING FOR A FRIEND.
HER BIRTHDAY'S
IN A FEW DAYS.
AGAIN, I-I'M REALLY SORRY
I BUMPED INTO YOU.
Fancy Pants: I'M NOT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU ARE OBVIOUSLY SOMEPONY
WORTH BUMPING INTO.
LISTEN, I HAVE
A V.I.P. BOX RESERVED
AT THE WONDERBOLTS DERBY
THIS AFTERNOON.
WOULD YOU -- WOULD YOU BE
SO KIND AS TO JOIN ME
AND A FEW OF MY COMPANIONS
THERE, HMM?
ME?
BUT OF COURSE,
MY DEAR.
WELL, I-I'M, UH...
SURE.
WE'D LOVE TO SEE YOU THERE,
UH...
RARITY.
[ ZIP! ]
PRO -- SEEING THE DERBY
FROM A V.I.P. BOX
IS A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY.
CON --
GOING TO THE DERBY CUTS INTO
THE AMOUNT OF TIME I HAVE
TO FINISH TWILIGHT'S OUTFIT.
PRO -- FANCY PANTS
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT PONY
IN CANTERLOT.
HIS STAMP OF APPROVAL COULD MEAN
BIG THINGS FOR ME HERE.
CON -- TWILIGHT'S PARTY
MIGHT NOT BE AS SOPHISTICATED
AS THE DERBY,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I SHOULDN'T PUT ALL OF MY ENERGY
INTO CREATING
HER BIRTHDAY ENSEMBLE.
MY PONYVILLE FRIENDS
WILL APPRECIATE MY HARD WORK
MORE THAN ANYPONY.
I HATE TO LET THEM DOWN.
AND I WON'T!
OPAL, I AM GOING TO
THE WONDERBOLTS DERBY
AS A GUEST
OF FANCY PANTS!
[ GIGGLING ]
MM.
[ INDISTINCT CHEERING ]
Rarity: PARDON ME.
EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME.
[ POINK! POINK! ]
RARITY,
JOLLY GOOD TO SEE YOU.
SO GLAD
YOU COULD MAKE IT.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
EVERYPONY,
THIS IS RARITY.
SHE'S STAYING
AT CANTERLOT CASTLE.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ALL MURMURING ]
Announcer:
FILLIES AND GENTLECOLTS,
WELCOME TO
THE WONDERBOLTS DERBY!
THE COMPETITORS
ARE TAKING THEIR PLACES
AT THE STARTING LINE,
AND THE RACE
WILL BEGIN MOMENTARILY.
I'LL BE ROOTING FOR RAPID FIRE,
OF COURSE.
HE'S SURE TO TAKE HOME
THE GRAND PRIZE.
INDEED.
MM-HMM.
Rarity: I DON'T
THINK HE HAS A CHANCE
AGAINST FLEET FOOT.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ FANFARE PLAYING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
AND IT'S FLEET FOOT
BY A NOSE!
WHOO-HOO!
BRAVO, RARITY!
I SAY, HOW DID YOU KNOW
FLEET FOOT WOULD BE VICTORIOUS?
MY FRIEND RAINBOW DASH
TALKS ABOUT HER ALL THE TIME.
SHE SAYS WHAT FLEET FOOT
LACKS IN SIZE,
SHE MAKES UP FOR
IN SPEED.
AND WHO IS
THIS RAINBOW DASH?
UH...
[ GULP! ]
WHY, SHE --
SHE'S T-THE WONDERBOLTS'
TRAINER, OF COURSE.
STAYING
AT CANTERLOT CASTLE,
AND SHE KNOWS THE PEGASUS
TRAINING THE WONDERBOLTS.
I TOLD YOU ALL
THIS WAS AN IMPORTANT PONY.
OH!
LOVELY.
[ ALL MURMURING ]
Fancy Pants:
THREE CHEERS FOR RARITY,
MY NEW FAVORITE
PARTY GUEST!
All:
HIP, HIP, HOORAY!
AND THEN I SAID, "PUH-LEASE,
THAT ISN'T A HAT, DARLING.
"THAT'S A NATURAL DISASTER
THAT SOMEHOW LANDED
ATOP YOUR HEAD!"
[ HAUGHTY LAUGHTER ]
OH, YOU ARE
A DELIGHT, RARITY,
AN ABSOLUTE DELIGHT!
YOU SIMPLY MUST ATTEND
MY ART-GALLERY OPENING
THIS EVENING.
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, I-I'D LOVE TO, BUT --
AND LET'S NOT FORGET MY CHARITY
AUCTION TOMORROW MORNING.
WELL, THAT SOUNDS WONDERFUL,
BUT I --
AND, OF COURSE,
THERE'S A SEAT FOR YOU
AT MY DINNER PARTY
TOMORROW NIGHT.
I'M FLATTERED, REALLY.
IT'S JUST
I HAVE A PROJECT
I REALLY NEED TO
GET STARTED ON, AND --
OH, BUT, RARITY!
I MAY AS WELL CLOSE DOWN
THE WHOLE GALLERY
IF YOU CAN'T ATTEND!
AND MY AUCTION
IS FOR CHARITY, DEAR.
[ Singsong voice ]
FOR CHARITY.
AND MY DINNER PARTY WILL BE
A DISASTER IF YOU DON'T COME.
OF COURSE I'LL BE THERE.
WONDERFUL!
OH, THANK GOODNESS!
DISASTER AVERTED!
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL BE
SPENDING A FEW MORE DAYS
HERE, OPALESCENCE.
TURNS OUT BUMPING
INTO FANCY PANTS LIKE THAT
WAS THE BEST THING
THAT'S EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
OF COURSE,
FINISHING TWILIGHT'S DRESS
IN TIME FOR HER BIRTHDAY PARTY
IS STILL MY TOP PRIORITY.
BUT I CAN'T POSSIBLY DISAPPOINT
THE CANTERLOT ELITE
BY REJECTING THEIR INVITATIONS
NOW, CAN I?
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
♪ I'LL BE
THE TOAST OF THE TOWN ♪
♪ THE GIRL ON THE GO ♪
♪ AND THE TYPE OF PONY ♪
♪ EVERYPONY,
EVERYPONY SHOULD KNOW ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ONE TO WATCH ♪
♪ THE GIRL IN THE FLOW ♪
♪ AND THE TYPE OF PONY ♪
♪ EVERYPONY,
EVERYPONY SHOULD KNOW ♪
♪ BECOMING AS POPULAR
AS POPULAR CAN BE ♪
♪ MAKING MY MARK,
MAKING MY MARK IN HIGH SOCIETY ♪
♪ I'M THE BELLE OF THE BALL ♪
♪ THE STAR OF THE SHOW, YEAH ♪
♪ AND THE TYPE OF PONY ♪
♪ EVERYPONY,
EVERYPONY SHOULD KNOW ♪
♪ SEE HOW THEY HANG ON
EVERY WORD THAT I SPEAK ♪
♪ MY APPROVING GLANCE
IS WHAT THEY ALL SEEK ♪
♪ I'M THE CRèME DE LA CRèME ♪
♪ NOT JUST ANOTHER JANE DOE ♪
♪ I'M THE TYPE OF PONY ♪
♪ EVERYPONY
SHOULD KNO-O-O-W ♪
♪ AT HOME AT THE OPERA ♪
♪ ON A FANCY YACHT ♪
♪ BECOMING THE TALK,
THE TALK OF ALL OF CANTERLOT ♪
♪ I'M THE CRèME DE LA CRèME ♪
♪ NOT JUST ANOTHER JANE DOE ♪
♪ YEAH, I'M THE TYPE OF PONY ♪
♪ EVERYPONY,
EVERYPONY SHOULD KNO-O-O-W ♪
♪ BECAUSE I'M THE TYPE OF PONY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE TYPE OF PONY ♪
♪ EVERYPONY
SHOULD KNO-O-O-O-O-W ♪
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
OH, I HOPE
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN ANYTHING.
ME...TOO.
WE'D BETTER GET GOING.
[ OPAL YOWLS ]
I MUST GET BACK
TO PONYVILLE
WITH ENOUGH TIME TO FINISH
TWILIGHT'S ENSEMBLE.
FOR ME?
"DEAREST RARITY,
YOUR PRESENCE IS REQUESTED
"AT THE CANTERLOT GARDEN PARTY
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
YOURS,
JET SET AND UPPER CRUST."
[ GASPS ]
THE CANTERLOT GARDEN PARTY?!
WHY, NEXT TO
THE GALLOPING GALA,
THAT IS THE PREMIER EVENT
IN CANTERLOT! AAH!
OH.
BUT IF I GO,
I'LL MISS TWILIGHT'S BIRTHDAY.
BUT IF I DON'T GO,
MY NEW REPUTATION IN CANTERLOT
AS A VERY IMPORTANT PONY
MIGHT BE RUINED!
I MIGHT NEVER BE INVITED
TO ANOTHER HIGH-SOCIETY EVENT
AGAIN!
FRIEND'S BIRTHDAY,
VERY IMPORTANT PONY.
[ WHIMPERING ]
IT'S JUST TOO IMPORTANT!
[ SIGHS ]
"MY DEAR TWILIGHT,
"I AM AFRAID
I WON'T BE ABLE TO MAKE IT
"TO YOUR BIRTHDAY PARTY TOMORROW
"BECAUSE...
"BECAUSE POOR OPAL
IS QUITE ILL!
"AND SHE IS IN NO CONDITION
"TO MAKE THE LONG JOURNEY
BACK TO PONYVILLE!
I DO HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
YOUR FRIEND, RARITY."
I SUPPOSE THIS MEANS
YOU DON'T NEED ME
TO BRING DOWN YOUR BAGS?
NO. BUT...
I WILL NEED SOME HELP
UNPACKING THEM.
UNH!
[ OPAL YOWLS ]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TOO MUCH?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
TOO LITTLE.
[ SIGHS ]
GARDEN PARTY, HERE I COME!
SURPRISE! SURPRISE!
[ GASPS ]
[ THUD! ]
SWHOOSH! AND RIGHT BEFORE
SHE HIT THE GROUND,
SHOOM, SHE --
HI, AGAIN!
WHAT DO YOU...?
HOW DID YOU...?
WHY ARE YOU...?
LISTEN TO HER.
SHE'S SO EXCITED TO SEE US,
SHE CAN HARDLY TALK.
WHAT I MEAN TO SAY IS,
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING HERE?
WHEN I GOT YOUR LETTER SAYING
YOU WERE STUCK IN CANTERLOT,
I ASKED PINKIE PIE IF
IT WOULDN'T BE TOO MUCH TROUBLE
TO MOVE MY BIRTHDAY PARTY HERE
SO YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO MISS IT.
BALLOONS
ARE SUPER EASY TO PACK!
[ PFFFFFFFFT! ]
[ PLOP! ]
WOW.
FIRST YOU GET ME A SUITE
AT CANTERLOT CASTLE
AND NOW THIS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY,
TWILIGHT.
HOW ABOUT
YOU START BY SAYING
WHAT YOU'RE DOING
IN THAT FANCY GETUP?
THIS? UH, WELL, I...
I ALWAYS PUT ON
SOMETHING A LITTLE FANCY
WHEN OPAL'S FEELING
UNDER THE WEATHER.
CHEERS HER RIGHT UP.
[ GIGGLES NERVOUSLY ]
[ POINK! POINK! ]
OH, POOR OPAL.
WHERE IS THE SICK DARLING?
OH, UH, SHE'S...
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
[ BLAM! ]
HUH? HUH?
[ TINKLING ]
[ OPAL YOWLS ]
I AM SO SORRY ABOUT THIS.
[ OPAL YOWLING ]
[ TEETH CHATTERING ]
SHE'S RESTING ON THE BED.
[ ZIP! ]
POOR BABY!
[ OPAL YOWLS ]
SHE LOOKS AWFUL.
[ GROWLS ]
IS THAT MY DRESS?
YES.
IT'S SO SIMPLE.
IT'S SO PRACTICAL.
SO ME!
IT'S THE PERFECT DRESS
FOR MY BIRTHDAY PARTY!
[ ZIP! ]
I LOVE IT!
[ SIGHS ]
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW GLAD I AM
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
[ SWISH! ]
Twilight:
WHEN I TOLD THE PRINCESS
THAT I WAS MOVING THE PARTY
TO CANTERLOT,
SHE WAS KIND ENOUGH
TO OFFER US
THE CANTERLOT CASTLE BALLROOM.
[ SLOOP! ]
ISN'T IT FANCY PANTS?
FANCY PANTS?!
[ ZIP! ]
WHERE?!
UH, I MEAN, UH,
WHERE DID YOU FIND THE TIME
TO PUT UP
ALL THESE DECORATIONS?
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
OH, I NEVER LEAVE HOME
WITHOUT MY PARTY CANNON.
[ NOISEMAKER HONKS ]
TA-DA!
I THOUGHT ABOUT HAVING
MY BIRTHDAY OUTSIDE,
BUT THEY'RE HAVING ANOTHER PARTY
ON THE CASTLE GROUNDS TODAY.
[ ZIP! ]
OH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SLOOP! ]
LET'S PARTY!
[ ZIP! ]
[ ROCKABILLY MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
UH...
NO REASON I CAN'T AT LEAST
MAKE AN APPEARANCE.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ]
I'M HERE!
DARLING,
I'M SO GLAD YOU MADE IT.
RARITY,
SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU HERE.
I WOULDN'T HAVE MISSED THIS
FOR THE WORLD.
[ SNIFFS ]
I SAY, WHAT IS THAT SCENT
YOU'RE WEARING?
IT SMELLS LIKE [SNIFFS]
IS THAT CAKE FROSTING?
YES, I ALWAYS DAB
A LITTLE FROSTING BEHIND MY EARS
BEFORE I GO OUT.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
AFTER ALL,
WHO DOESN'T LIKE THE SMELL
OF CAKE FROSTING?
I KNOW I DO.
MM-HMM.
[ SIGHS ]
WELL, ALL THIS TALK ABOUT CAKE
HAS MADE ME HUNGRY.
THINK I'LL GO AND SEE
WHAT'S ON
THE HORS D'OEUVRES TABLE.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
[ ZIP! ]
I MUST SAY...
OH, YES, DARLING.
...YOU LOOK LIKE A...
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ POLITE APPLAUSE ]
[ ROCKABILLY MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ ZIP! ]
...LOOK LIKE THE HEIGHT
OF FASHION.
OH, I REALLY THANK YOU.
OF COURSE, I WOULD EXPECT
NOTHING LESS.
[ TINKLING ]
[ ROCKABILLY MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ GULP! ]
BLAH!
[ ZIP! ]
I THINK I LEFT THE BATH WATER
RUNNING IN MY SUITE.
[ ROCKABILLY MUSIC PLAYING ]
I REALLY SHOULD
GO CHECK ON OPAL.
IS THAT
PRINCESS CELESTIA?!
I need to use
the little fillies' room.
CAN I GET ANYPONY
MORE PUNCH?
I-I HAVE TO DO THE...
THING WITH THE STUFF,
YOU KNOW?
UH, WHAT'S WITH
THE CROQUET MALLET?
[ Muffled ]
WHAT CROQUET MALLET?
DUH!
THE ONE IN YOUR MOUTH.
[ GIGGLES NERVOUSLY ]
OH! THAT CROQUET MALLET.
I -- WELL, I --
YOU KNOW, THE TRUTH IS --
THE TRUTH IS...
WERE YOU AT THAT OTHER PARTY
IN THE GARDEN?
UH, I...I...I...
RARITY,
I'M SURPRISED AT YOU.
TWILIGHT, LET ME EXPLAIN!
I --
I HADN'T REALIZED YOU WERE
SUCH A SAVVY BUSINESSPONY.
YOU MUST UNDERSTAND!
I --
ALL OF THOSE PONIES
LOOK SO POSH,
AND WITH THE GRAND
GALLOPING GALA COMING UP,
I BET YOU COULD TOTALLY
GET SOME OF THEM
TO BUY YOUR DRESSES.
VERY SMART.
WH...WHY, YES!
I-I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO THINK
I WAS BEING RUDE.
SO THAT'S EXACTLY THE REASON
I DIDN'T TELL YOU!
[ Chuckling ]
THE ONE AND ONLY REASON.
[ GIGGLES NERVOUSLY ]
OH, WELL,
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
YOU SHOULD TOTALLY GO OVER THERE
AND MINGLE.
[ POINK! ]
TWILIGHT,
YOU REALLY ARE
THE BEST FRIEND
A PONY COULD EVER ASK FOR.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I EVER THOUGHT
YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
UNDERSTAND WHAT?
NOTHING.
SEE YOU GIRLS LATER!
[ ZIP! ]
HEY, WAIT UP!
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS.
I'M SURE THEY WON'T MIND
IF WE CHECK OUT THE PARTY, TOO.
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
LET'S SHOW THEM HOW TO PARTY
PONYVILLE STYLE!
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
OH, NO!
[ ZIP! ]
[ CANNON WHEELS SQUEAKING ]
[ NOISEMAKER HONKS ]
[ WHIR! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
MMM!
[ PLOP! PLOP! PLOP! PLOP! ]
[ SNAP! PLOP! ]
HOW COME Y'ALL
AREN'T DOING ANY GARDENING?
THIS IS A GARDEN PARTY,
ISN'T IT?
[ TINKLING ]
CAN YOU BELIEVE
WHAT THAT PONY IS WEARING?
Upper Crust:
IT'S JUST SO PLAIN.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ] YEAH.
EXCUSE ME.
MIGHT I ASK WHERE YOU GOT
YOUR ENSEMBLE?
WHY, YES.
YES, YOU MAY.
A VERY, VERY CLOSE FRIEND
OF MINE FROM PONYVILLE
MADE IT FOR ME.
PBHT!
PONYVILLE?
YOU DON'T SAY?
I DO SAY.
HER NAME IS --
FANCY PANTS,
COME WITH ME.
I'D LIKE TO SHOW YOU
THIS, UH, THING
THAT'S OVER THERE,
O-ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE ROOM.
IN A MOMENT, MY DEAR.
THIS LOVELY FILLY
FROM PONYVILLE
WAS JUST ABOUT TO TELL ME
WHO MADE HER CHARMING DRESS.
THAT DRESS?
OH, COME NOW. WHO CARES?
IT'S JUST A PLAIN, OLD --
OH, DON'T BE SO MODEST.
THIS DRESS YOU MADE
IS BEAUTIFUL.
[ ALL GASP, GLASS SHATTERS ]
WE ALL THINK SO.
YOU KNOW
THESE PONIES?
[ ALL MURMURING ]
YES.
YES, I DO KNOW THEM.
THEY MAY NOT BE AS SOPHISTICATED
AS SOME OF YOU CANTERLOT PONIES,
BUT THEY ARE MY BEST FRIENDS.
AND THEY ARE,
WITHOUT A DOUBT,
THE MOST IMPORTANT PONIES
I KNOW.
IMPORTANT PONIES?
THESE RUFFIANS?!
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
I, FOR ONE,
FIND THEM CHARMINGLY RUSTIC.
AND I THINK THE DRESS YOU MADE
FOR YOUR FRIEND IS LOVELY.
[ CHUCKLES ] I DARESAY
EVERY MARE IN CANTERLOT
WILL BE WANTING ONE.
OH, I'D LIKE TO PLACE MY ORDER
RIGHT NOW.
I THINK
YOU SHOULD GET TWO, HMM?
[ ZIP! BONK! ]
UH, YES. NOW, THEN.
HOW ABOUT YOU INTRODUCE ME
TO YOUR FRIENDS?
WITH PLEASURE.
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
"I WANTED TO TELL YOU ABOUT
THE IMPORTANT LESSON I LEARNED
DURING MY VISIT."
NOW, THAT
I WOULD LIKE TO HEAR.
I LEARNED THAT NO MATTER
WHERE YOU GO IN LIFE,
YOU SHOULD NEVER FORGET
THAT YOU ARE THE PRODUCT
OF YOUR HOME
AND YOUR FRIENDS.
AND THAT IS SOMETHING
ALWAYS TO BE PROUD OF,
NO MATTER WHAT.
HM. A VERY VALUABLE LESSON
TO HAVE LEARNED.
Pony:
IT CERTAINLY IS.
BUT MIGHT I ASK THAT
WE HURRY THINGS UP A BIT?!
OH, NO!
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪