Twilight Sparkle:
PRINCESS CELESTIA,
WE CAME AS FAST AS WE COULD.
I NEED YOU TO WIELD THE ELEMENTS
OF HARMONY ONCE AGAIN
AND STOP DISCORD.
THE ELEMENTS --
THEY'RE GONE!
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
EVERYPONY HAS TO PLAY,
OR THE GAME IS OVER AND I WIN.
OUR FRIENDSHIP? OVER?
WHO WERE YOU TALKING TO?
NOPONY.
NOPONY WHATSOEVER.
WHAT?
PINKIE PIE!
ARE WE GLAD TO SEE YOU!
WHY? NEED A GOOD LAUGH?!
Twilight Sparkle:
WHAT IS HAPPENING
TO MY FRIENDS?
LOOKS LIKE WE MIGHT BE DUE
FOR A BIG OL' STORM OF CHAOS.
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
AND WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT?!
OH, YOU PONIES ARE JUST
THE MOST FUN I'VE HAD IN EONS.
WELL, QUIT IT!
YOU BETTER THINK
BEFORE YOU LAUGH
AT THE PINK...IE PIE!
OH, YEAH?
WELL, HA HA.
QUIT IT!
NO. HA HA.
QUIT IT!!
NO.
HA HA-HA-HA HA.
UH, RARITY?
THIS HERE DIAMOND OF YOURS?
TWILIGHT SAID
WE SHOULD SPLIT IT SIX WAYS
SINCE WE, UH,
FOUND IT TOGETHER.
HYAH!
TRY IT, PUNK!
HE'S MINE -- ALL MINE!
HYAH! HYAH!
GIRLS, WHY ARE YOU ALL
ACTING LIKE THIS?
WE NEED TO STICK TOGETHER.
[ CHUCKLES ]
OH, IT'S JUST TOO ENTERTAINING.
STOP IT, DISCORD.
YOU'RE NOT PLAYING FAIR.
I'M NOT PLAYING FAIR?
PERHAPS WE HAVEN'T MET.
I'M DISCORD,
SPIRIT OF CHAOS AND DISHARMONY.
HELLO-O.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO FIND
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY
WHEN YOU TOOK AWAY
THE LABYRINTH
BEFORE WE COULD GET
TO THE END?
OH, WAIT.
DID YOU -- [ LAUGHS ]
HOW FUNNY!
YOU THOUGHT THE ELEMENTS
WERE IN THE LABYRINTH?
TWISTS AND TURNS
ARE MY MASTER PLAN,
THEN FIND THE ELEMENTS
BACK WHERE YOU BEGAN.
I NEVER SAID
THEY WERE IN THE LABYRINTH.
BUT -- BUT --
KEEP TRYING,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE.
[ Mockingly ] MAYBE THE MAGIC
OF FRIENDSHIP CAN HELP YOU.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE SOME CHAOS TO WREAK.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
CHOCOLATE MILK?
I HATE CHOCOLATE MILK!
[ GROANS ]
THINK, TWILIGHT, THINK.
FIND THE ELEMENTS
BACK WHERE YOU BEGAN.
BACK WHERE YOU BEGAN!
DON'T TOUCH MY GEM!
I'M TOUCHING YOUR GEM, RARITY.
HA HA.
WHAT YOU LAUGHING AT?!
UGH, I JUST WANT TO
GO HOME.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HOME --
BACK WHERE YOU BEGAN!
THE ELEMENTS MUST BE IN...
PONYVILLE.
COME ON, GIRLS.
I'M CERTAIN THIS IS WHAT
DISCORD'S RIDDLE REALLY MEANT.
IF WE GET BACK
TO THE LIBRARY,
I HAVE A BOOK THAT I JUST KNOW
CAN GIVE US A CLUE.
AAH!
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ TWEET! TWEET! ]
GOOD BOY, ANGEL.
MAMA'S SO PROUD.
WOW. I CAN SEE
SO MUCH BETTER NOW.
[ SLOOP! SLOOP! ]
WHOA!
[ BONK! BONK! BONK! ]
I MEANT TO DO THAT.
WHA-- OOOH!
WHOA!
DISCORD'S TURNED
OUR DIRT ROADS INTO SOAP!
BEAUTIFUL, ISN'T IT?
THIS IS THE NEW AND IMPROVED
PONYVILLE,
AND THESE ARE ONLY
MY FIRST CHANGES.
THIS MAY LOOK LIKE FUN,
BUT IT'S NOT.
[ SIGHS ]
PICTURE IT --
THE CHAOS CAPITAL OF THE WORLD.
I CAN'T PICTURE ANYTHING.
IT'S TOO DARK.
[ SPLASH! ]
WELL, WAIT A FEW MINUTES
AND YOU'LL SEE IT IN
THE BEAUTIFUL LIGHT OF DAY...
OR NOT.
PONYVILLE --
THE CHAOS CAPITAL OF THE WORLD?
NOT IF I HAVE ANYTHING
TO SAY ABOUT IT.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU WON'T.
[ GIGGLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY, WE'RE HERE.
EVERYONE PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE
JUST GO INSIDE -- PLEASE?
I ABSOLUTELY REFUSE.
WITH PLEASURE.
I HATE LIBRARIES!
[ SIGHS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
PLEASE?
WE GOT TO HURRY.
FORGET IT, TWILIGHT.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE UP TO.
THE SECOND I GO IN,
YOU'LL HAVE
YOUR LITTLE MINION, SPIKE,
COME AND TAKE TOM!
TOM?
WELL, IT'S NOT
GOING TO WORK!
YOU'RE NOT GOING IN
WITHOUT HIM, ARE YOU?
MNH-MNH.
[ GRUNTS ] FINE!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SNORING ]
[ GASPS ]
BRRR!
WHAT YOU DO THAT FOR,
FLUTTERSHY?
'CAUSE YOU JUST LOOKED
SO PEACEFUL.
I, UH -- HUH?
[ CRASH! ]
CAREFUL, TWILIGHT.
YOU'LL RUIN
HIS BEAUTIFUL FINISH.
OH, FOR THE LOVE OF --
TWILIGHT,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY'S EVERYBODY LOOK SO...
GRAY?
DON'T ASK.
I NEED YOU
TO HELP ME FIND SOMETHING.
HEY, TWILIGHT.
WHAT'S SOAKING WET AND CLUELESS?
FLUTTERSHY,
I'VE HAD JUST ABOUT ENOUGH --
YOUR FACE!
[ CLONG! ]
WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO EVERYPONY?
I GUESS YOU JUST BRING OUT
THE WORST IN US, SPIKE.
[ SIGHS ]
NO TIME TO EXPLAIN.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND THE REFERENCE
GUIDE TO THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY
BEFORE SOMEPONY
DOES SOMETHING SHE'LL REGRET.
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY?
OH! I KNOW EXACTLY
WHERE THAT BOOK IS!
FOUND IT!
HA!
FLUTTERSHY...
YOU BETTER GIVE ME
THAT BOOK!
KEEP AWAY!
HEY!
APPLEJACK,
GIVE ME THAT BOOK!
I DON'T HAVE ANY BOOK.
PINKIE!
YOU GUYS!
STOP IT RIGHT NOW!
[ SCREECH! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ TINKLING ]
MINE!
HEY! DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU JUST STOLE?
NO, BUT IF YOU WANT IT,
I WANT IT.
[ GROWLS ]
GIVE ME THAT BOOK!
WHERE IS SHE?
[ RATTLE! ]
WHERE'S RARITY?
BEATS ME.
LIES!
[ BAM! BAM! ]
[ MEOW! ]
[ BAM! CRASH! ]
GET BACK!
ALL OF YOU!
THIS IS MY BOOK,
AND I'M GONNA READ IT!
[ TINKLING ]
[ GASPS ]
THE ELEMENTS!
THEY WERE HERE
ALL ALONG!
THIS IS GREAT!
NOW YOU GUYS
CAN DEFEAT DISCORD
AND PUT EVERYTHING
BACK TO NORMAL.
SEE, GIRLS?
WE DID IT!
WE FOUND
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY --
TOGETHER!
[ YAWNS ]
YOU DON'T
EVEN CARE, DO YOU?
NO. NO.
[ SIGHS ] I NEVER THOUGHT
IT WOULD HAPPEN.
MY FRIENDS...
HAVE TURNED INTO
COMPLETE JERKS!
NECKLACE.
AND...
[ TINKLING ]
BIG CROWN THINGY.
COME ON, EVERYPONY.
LET'S GO.
BUT, TWILIGHT,
AREN'T YOU MISSING SOMEPONY?
NOPE.
WE'VE GOT THE LIAR, THE GRUMP,
THE HOARDER,
AND THE BRUTE.
THAT JUST ABOUT COVERS IT.
WHAT ABOUT RAINBOW DASH?
CONGRATULATIONS, SPIKE.
YOU'RE THE NEW RAINBOW DASH.
NOW LET'S GO!
[ GASPS ] ME?!
B-B-BUT WHAT IF SHE FOUNDS OUT
I'VE BEEN IMPERSONATING HER?
UH, THAT WON'T END WELL.
TOO BAD.
YOU'RE RAINBOW DASH.
NOW LET'S GO DEFEAT DISCORD
SO WE DON'T EVER HAVE TO
TALK TO EACH OTHER AGAIN.
YEAH! YEAH!
WHOO-HOO! WHOO-HOO!
[ GRUNTING ]
MOVE!
[ TINKLING ]
LOOK OUT!
HERE COMES TOM!
[ CRASH! THUD! ]
Discord:
WELL, WELL, WELL.
I SEE YOU FOUND
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY.
HOW TERRIFYING!
DISCORD, I FIGURED OUT
YOUR LAME RIDDLE.
YOU'RE IN FOR IT NOW.
I CERTAINLY AM.
YOU'VE CLEARLY
OUT-DUELED ME,
AND NOW IT'S TIME
TO MEET MY FATE.
I'M PREPARED
TO BE DEFEATED NOW, LADIES.
FIRE WHEN READY.
FORMATION, NOW!
EH. EH.
RAINBOW DASH,
GET OVER HERE.
[ GULPS ]
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET THIS
OVER WITH.
[ WIND HOWLING ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ TINKLING STOPS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MINE'S WORKING.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOURS.
I HATE
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY.
[ SCOFFS ]
GARBAGE.
MINE!
SORRY, TWILIGHT.
I GUESS I BETTER GET BACK
UPSTAIRS
AND CLEAN UP
THE LIBRARY.
GOOD LUCK WITH ALL THIS --
WHOA!
[ RATTLE! ]
OOPS.
SORRY, RAINBOW CRASH.
[ LAUGHS ]
BRAVO, PONIES.
BRAVO.
HARMONY IN EQUESTRIA
IS OFFICIALLY DEAD.
DISCORD RULES,
CELESTIA DROOLS.
[ LAUGHS ]
IT'S YOUR FAULT
IT DIDN'T WORK.
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
ANY OF YOU.
ALL OF YOU!
I'M OUT OF HERE!
I BETTER GO, TOO.
I GOT NEW, BETTER FRIENDS
WAITING FOR ME AT THE FARM.
YEAH, I'M SICK
OF YOU LOSERS.
FINE! LEAVE!
SEE IF I CARE!
I DON'T NEED YOU GUYS,
EITHER.
WITH FRIENDS LIKE YOU,
WHO NEEDS...
ENEMIES?
[ TINKLING ]
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ SCAMPER! SCAMPER! SCAMPER! ]
[ PITTER! PITTER! PITTER! ]
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ WARBLE! ]
[ Laughing ]
OH, MY STOMACH!
[ LAUGHS ] OH!
TWILIGHT, YOU'VE GOT TO SEE
WHAT I JUST DID.
AH-CHOO!
[ THUD! ]
[ Laughing ]
IT'S PRICELESS!
[ LAUGHS ]
COME NOW,
TWILIGHT SPARKLE,
YOU'VE GOT TO GET INTO
THE SPIRIT OF THINGS.
[ SLURP! ]
AFTER ALL,
THIS IS YOUR NEW HOME.
NOT ANYMORE.
YES!
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
PACK YOUR THINGS, SPIKE.
WE'RE LEAVING.
[ GROANS ]
AND DON'T ASK
WHERE WE'RE GOING, 'CAUSE...
I DON'T KNOW YET.
JUST NOT HERE.
[ CLANK! ]
CAN'T...MOVE...
THE PRINCESS...
HAS BEEN SENDING THESE...
SINCE I CAME BACK
UPSTAIRS.
[ BELCHES ]
[ Crying ]
MAKE IT STOP!
THESE ARE ALL THE LETTERS
I'VE WRITTEN TO THE PRINCESS
SINCE I'VE LIVED
IN PONYVILLE.
BUT WHY WOULD SHE
SEND THEM BACK?
[ GROANS ]
[ BELCHES ]
"REAL FRIENDS DON'T CARE
WHAT YOUR COVER IS.
"FRIENDSHIP IS A WONDROUS
AND POWERFUL THING.
"AND LIKE THE PATH
CUT THROUGH THE ORCHARD,
"THERE'LL ALWAYS BE
A WAY THROUGH.
"THE BEST THING TO DO
IS TO STAY TRUE TO YOURSELF.
"EVERYPONY EVERYWHERE
"HAS A SPECIAL MAGICAL
CONNECTION WITH HER FRIENDS,
MAYBE EVEN BEFORE
SHE'S MET THEM."
SPIKE. SPIKE!
IT'S ALL SO CLEAR.
[ GROANS ]
CAN'T YOU SEE?
DISCORD'S TRYING TO DISTRACT US
FROM WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
HE KNOWS HOW POWERFUL
OUR FRIENDSHIPS ARE,
AND HE'S TRYING TO KEEP US
FROM SEEING IT.
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHAT I SAID
THE FIRST DAY WE ARRIVED
IN PONYVILLE?
I TOLD YOU THAT THE FUTURE
OF EQUESTRIA
DIDN'T REST
ON ME MAKING FRIENDS,
BUT THE OPPOSITE
IS TRUE!
THE FRIENDSHIPS I'VE MADE
SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE
ARE WHAT SAVED EQUESTRIA
FROM NIGHTMARE MOON,
AND NOW THEY NEED TO SAVE IT
FROM DISCORD.
[ MOANS ]
YOU'RE RIGHT, SPIKE.
I'VE GOT TO FIGHT
FOR MY FRIENDSHIPS --
FOR THEM, FOR ME,
FOR EQUESTRIA!
[ GROANING ]
OH, UH...
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
STAY HERE AND REST?
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE WHOLE
"FIGHTING FOR FRIENDSHIP" THING
MYSELF.
[ GROANS ]
[ BELCHES ]
[ OINKING ]
[ PANTING ]
AND SO I TRIED TO DEFEAT
DISCORD,
BUT NONE OF
MY SO-CALLED FRIENDS
WOULD LIFT A HOOF
TO HELP ME.
APPLEJACK, I'M HERE TO FIGHT
FOR OUR FRIENDSHIP.
[ PANTING ]
[ SLURPS ]
OH, NOW YOU WANT TO
FIGHT.
WHERE WERE YOU
WHEN I WAS BATTLING DISCORD?
SNAP OUT OF IT.
THIS ISN'T YOU.
YOU'RE NOT A LIAR.
[ TINKLING ]
W-WHAT HAPPENED?
[ RATTLE! ]
TWILIGHT!
OH, I SAW
A VISION OF US
FEUDING AND FIGHTING.
I COULDN'T FACE
THE TRUTH,
SO I STARTED
TELLING LIES.
CAN YOU EVER
FORGIVE ME?
I ALREADY HAVE.
COME ON.
[ TINKLING ]
OH, NO!
TWILIGHT, APPLEJACK,
I JUST HAD THE WORST DREAM.
Rarity: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
GET AWAY FROM MY GEM!
GET AWAY!
[ TINKLING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
LET US NEVER
SPEAK OF THIS AGAIN.
[ LAUGHING ]
I TURNED GRAY!
[ GIGGLES ]
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
HUH?
SHE'S NOT HERE.
WITHOUT RAINBOW DASH,
WE CAN'T USE THE ELEMENTS.
SHE COULD BE ANYWHERE
BY NOW.
WE'RE NEVER
GONNA FIND HER.
YEAH, WE WILL.
'CAUSE SHE'S RIGHT THERE.
RAINBOW DASH!
HEY, GUYS.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING EVERYWHERE
FOR YOU.
THAT'S NICE.
DISCORD'S
STILL ON THE LOOSE.
WE NEED YOU
TO HELP US DEFEAT HIM
WITH YOUR ELEMENT --
LOYALTY.
PBHT!
LOYALTY SCHMOYALTY.
HAVE YOU GUYS
SEEN PONYVILLE?
IT'S A DISASTER!
I'M STAYING HERE IN CLOUDSDALE
WHERE EVERYTHING'S AWESOME.
HOW IN EQUESTRIA
CAN SHE THINK
THAT TINY PATCH OF CLOUDS
IS CLOUDSDALE?
THE SAME WAY HE GOT YOU TO THINK
THAT CHEAP ROCK
WAS A BONA FIDE DIAMOND.
I THOUGHT WE AGREED NEVER
TO SPEAK OF THAT AGAIN.
TIME TO FOR PLAN "B."
[ SNORING ]
[ AIR HISSING ]
OKAY, FLUTTERSHY.
YOU GRAB RAINBOW DASH
AND HOLD HER DOWN.
APPLEJACK WILL LOWER ME DOWN
FROM THIS ROPE
SO I CAN CAST
THE MEMORY SPELL ON HER.
GOT IT.
[ SNORING ]
[ SNORTS ]
UM, I'M JUST WONDERING
IF IT'S OKAY
IF I HOLD YOU DOWN AGAINST
YOUR WILL FOR A LITTLE BIT.
[ GROANS ]
NICE TRY.
PONYVILLE'S YOUR PROBLEM,
NOT MINE.
[ ZOOM! ]
COME ON, FLUTTERSHY.
WE GOT TO CATCH HER.
HYAH!
[ ZIP! ]
APPLEJACK!
AAH!
PINKIE!
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO
SECURE THE ROPE!
OOPS.
RARITY, PINKIE,
HOLD ON!
Y'ALL
ARE SLOWING HER DOWN.
OH, FLUTTERSHY,
WOULD YOU BE A DEAR
AND FLY FASTER, PLEASE?
[ Crying ] I CAN'T.
IF YOU CAN'T CATCH HER,
DISCORD WINS!
THAT BIG, DUMB...
MEANIE!
[ WHOOSH! ]
OKAY, APPLEJACK,
LAST ROPE.
MAKE IT COUNT!
[ WHIFFLE! ]
LET ME GO!
I DON'T NEED YOU GUYS!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
[ TINKLING ]
[ SNORTING ]
W-WHAT HAPPENED?
[ GASPS ]
HOW'S PONYVILLE?
WHERE ARE THE ELEMENTS?!
DID WE STOP DISCORD?
[ ALL CHEERING ]
WELCOME BACK!
[ SCAMPER! SCAMPER! SCAMPER! ]
MAYBE IT'S A LITTLE EARLY
FOR A GROUP HUG.
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ SCAMPER! SCAMPER! SCAMPER! ]
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
CHAOS IS
A WONDERFUL, WONDERFUL THING.
Twilight Sparkle:
NOT AS WONDERFUL
AS FRIENDSHIP.
OH, THIS AGAIN?
[ BOOM! ]
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU COULDN'T BREAK APART
OUR FRIENDSHIP FOR LONG.
OH, APPLEJACK,
DON'T LIE TO ME.
I'M THE ONE
WHO MADE YOU A LIAR.
[ TINKLING ]
WILL YOU EVER LEARN?
Twilight Sparkle: I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT WE'VE LEARNED, DISCORD.
WE'VE LEARNED THAT FRIENDSHIP
ISN'T ALWAYS EASY,
BUT THERE'S NO DOUBT
IT'S WORTH FIGHTING FOR.
[ GROANS ] GAG.
FINE, GO AHEAD.
TRY AND USE YOUR LITTLE
ELEMENTS, FRIENEMIES.
JUST MAKE IT QUICK.
I'M MISSING
SOME EXCELLENT CHAOS HERE.
ALL RIGHT, LADIES.
LET'S SHOW HIM
WHAT FRIENDSHIP CAN DO.
Pinkie Pie:
WAIT WAIT WAIT!
[ GARGLING ]
[ SLURPS ]
[ GROWLS ]
[ TINKLING ]
OH.
WHAT'S THIS?
NO.
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
[ FANFARE ]
[ TINK! ]
Princess Celestia:
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY
TO ONCE AGAIN HONOR THE HEROISM
OF THESE SIX FRIENDS,
WHO STOOD UP
TO THE VILLAIN DISCORD
AND SAVED EQUESTRIA
FROM ETERNAL CHAOS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ TINKLING ]