"PRINCESS CELESTIA CORDIALLY
INVITES YOU TO THE WEDDING OF
PRINCESS MI AMORE CADENZA
AND" [ GASP ]....
MY BROTHER?
TWILY!
OH, I'VE MISSED YOU, KID!
HOW DARE YOU NOT TELL ME
IN PERSON THAT YOU WERE GETTING
MARRIED?
A THREAT HAS BEEN MADE
AGAINST CANTERLOT.
PRINCESS CELESTIA ASKED THAT
I HELP PROVIDE ADDITIONAL
PROTECTION.
BUT I'M STILL PRETTY TICKED
YOU'RE MARRYING SOME PONY I
DON'T EVEN KNOW.
PRINCESS MI AMORE
CADENZA IS CADENCE.
CADENCE IS ONLY THE MOST
AMAZING PONY EVER!
I HOPE I'M NOT INTERRUPTING
ANYTHING IMPORTANT.
CADENCE, IT'S ME TWILIGHT!
UH-HUH.
AND I THINK I SHOULD WEAR IT.
ARE YOU DISAGREEING WITH ME?
[ WINCING ]
SHE'S EVIL!
I SAW HER PUT A SPELL ON
MY BROTHER THAT MADE HIS
EYES GO ALL-
CADENCE HASN'T BEEN CASTING
SPELLS ON ME.
SHE'S BEEN USING HER MAGIC
TO HEAL ME.
IF I WERE, I WOULDN'T SHOW UP TO
THE WEDDING AT ALL.
I JUST LOST A BROTHER.
I'M SORRY.
YOU WILL BE.
[ SOFTLY ] ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
[ UPBEAT ] ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER ♪
♪ WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ♪
♪ ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART ♪
♪ FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ♪
♪ ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ TO HAVE MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALL MY VERY ♪
♪ BEST FRIENDS ♪
HELLO?
IS ANYONE THERE?
[ DISTANT EVIL LAUGHTER ]
WHERE AM I?
THE CAVES BENEATH CANTERLOT.
ONCE HOME TO GREEDY UNICORNS
WHO WANTED TO CLAIM THE GEMS
THAT COULD BE FOUND INSIDE.
AND NOW...YOUR PRISON.
HELP! HELP!
[ CHUCKLING ] IT'S NO USE.
NO ONE CAN HEAR YOU.
AND NO ONE WILL EVER THINK TO
LOOK FOR YOU EITHER.
MOST PONIES HAVE FORGOTTEN THAT
THESE CAVES EVEN EXIST.
WHICH IS WHY THEY ARE THE IDEAL
PLACE TO KEEP THE ONES WHO TRY
TO INTERFERE WITH MY PLANS.
PLANS?
WHAT PLANS?
THE PLANS I HAVE FOR YOUR
BROTHER OF COURSE.
DON'T YOU DARE DO ANYTHING TO
MY BROTHER, YOU-YOU MONSTER!
ONLY WAY TO STOP ME
IS TO CATCH ME.
[ CACKLING ]
OVER HERE!
NOPE.
OVER HERE.
NO! WAIT!
PLEASE. DON'T HURT ME.
TWILIGHT, IT'S ME.
PLEASE. YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
I'VE BEEN IMPRISONED LIKE YOU.
THE CADENCE WHO BROUGHT YOU DOWN
HERE WAS AN IMPOSTER.
LIKELY STORY!
SUNSHINE, SUNSHINE.
LADYBUG'S AWAKE.
CLAP YOUR HOOVES...
both: AND DO A LITTLE SHAKE.
YOU REMEMBER ME.
OF COURSE I DO.
HOW COULD I FORGET THE FILLY I
LOVE TO SIT FOR THE MOST?
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE.
WE HAVE TO STOP HER!
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
[ SOFT PIANO MUSIC ]
♪ THIS DAY IS GOING ♪
♪ TO BE PERFECT ♪
♪ THE KIND OF DAY ♪
♪ OF WHICH I DREAMED ♪
♪ SINCE I WAS SMALL ♪
♪ EVERYPONY WILL GATHER ROUND ♪
♪ SAY I LOOK LOVELY IN MY GOWN ♪
♪ WHAT THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ IS THAT I HAVE FOOLED ♪
♪ THEM ALL ♪
♪ THIS DAY WAS GOING ♪
♪ TO BE PERFECT ♪
♪ THE KIND OF DAY OF WHICH ♪
♪ I DREAMED SINCE I WAS SMALL ♪
♪ BUT INSTEAD OF HAVING CAKE ♪
♪ WITH ALL MY FRIENDS ♪
♪ TO CELEBRATE ♪
♪ MY WEDDING BELLS ♪
♪ THEY MAY NOT RING ♪
♪ FOR ME AT ALL ♪
♪ I COULD CARE LESS ♪
♪ ABOUT THE DRESS ♪
♪ I WON'T PARTAKE IN ANY CAKE ♪
♪ VOWS, WELL, I'LL BE LYING ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY ♪
♪ THAT THROUGH ANY ♪
♪ KIND OF WEATHER ♪
♪ I'LL WANT US TO BE TOGETHER ♪
♪ THE TRUTH IS I DON'T CARE ♪
♪ FOR HIM AT ALL ♪
♪ NO, I DO NOT LOVE THE GROOM ♪
♪ IN MY HEART THERE IS NO ROOM ♪
♪ BUT I STILL WANT HIM ♪
♪ TO BE ALL MINE ♪
♪ WE MUST ESCAPE ♪
♪ BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE ♪
♪ FIND A WAY TO SAVE THE DAY ♪
♪ HOPE, I'LL BE LYING IF I SAY ♪
♪ I DON'T FEAR ♪
♪ THAT I MAY LOSE HIM ♪
♪ TO ONE WHO WANTS TO USE HIM ♪
♪ NOT CARE, LOVE ♪
♪ AND CHERISH HIM EACH DAY ♪
♪ FOR I ALSO LOVE THE GROOM ♪
♪ ALL MY THOUGHTS ♪
♪ HE DOES CONSUME ♪
♪ OH, SHINING ARMOR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE VERY SOON ♪
♪ FINALLY THE MOMENT ♪
♪ HAS ARRIVED ♪
♪ FOR ME TO BE ONE LUCKY BRIDE ♪
♪ OH, THE WEDDING ♪
♪ WE WON'T MAKE ♪
♪ HE'LL END UP MARRYING A FAKE ♪
♪ SHINING ARMOR WILL BE-- ♪
MINE, ALL MINE.
[ EVIL GIGGLING ]
MARES AND GENTLECOLTS,
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY TO
WITNESS THE UNION OF PRINCESS MI
AMORE CADENZA AND SHINING ARMOR.
OH, WE'RE NEVER GOING
TO SAVE HIM.
WE WILL.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIND--
THERE!
all: [ ZOMBIE-LIKE ] YOU'RE
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
PRINCESS CADENCE AND SHINING
ARMOR, IT IS MY GREAT PLEASURE
-TO PRONOUNCE YOU--
- STOP!
[ GUESTS MURMURING ]
UGH! WHY DOES SHE HAVE TO BE
SO POSSESSIVE OF HER BROTHER?
WHY DOES SHE HAVE TO RUIN
MY SPECIAL DAY?
BECAUSE IT'S NOT YOUR SPECIAL
DAY, IT'S MINE!
[ ALL GASP ]
WHAT? BUT HOW DID YOU ESCAPE
MY BRIDESMAIDS?
all: I WANT IT!
CLEVER, BUT YOU'RE
STILL TOO LATE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW CAN THERE BE TWO OF THEM?
SHE'S A CHANGELING.
SHE TAKES THE FORM OF SOME PONY
YOU LOVE AND GAINS POWER BY
FEEDING OFF YOUR LOVE FOR THEM.
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
RIGHT YOU ARE, PRINCESS.
AND AS QUEEN OF THE CHANGELINGS,
IT IS UP TO ME TO FIND FOOD
FOR MY SUBJECTS.
EQUESTRIA HAS MORE LOVE THAN
ANY PLACE I'VE EVER ENCOUNTERED.
MY FELLOW CHANGELINGS WILL BE
ABLE TO DEVOUR SO MUCH OF IT
THAT WE WILL GAIN MORE POWER
THAN WE HAVE EVER DREAMED OF!
THEY'LL NEVER GET THE CHANCE.
SHINING ARMOR'S PROTECTION SPELL
WILL KEEP THEM FROM EVER EVEN
REACHING US.
[ SNICKERING ]
OH, I DOUBT THAT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, DEAR?
MM-HMM.
AH, AH, AH.
DON'T WANNA GO BACK TO THE
CAVES NOW, DO YOU?
EVER SINCE I TOOK YOUR PLACE,
I'VE BEEN FEEDING OFF SHINING
ARMOR'S LOVE FOR YOU.
EVERY MOMENT HE GROWS WEAKER
AND SO DOES HIS SPELL.
EVEN NOW, MY MINIONS ARE
CHIPPING AWAY AT IT.
[ EVIL CACKLING ]
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
HE MAY NOT BE MY HUSBAND,
BUT HE IS UNDER MY TOTAL CONTROL
NOW.
[ BOTH GASP ]
AND, I'M SORRY TO SAY, UNABLE
TO PERFORM HIS DUTIES AS CAPTAIN
OF THE ROYAL GUARD!
NOT MY SHINING ARMOR!
SOON, MY CHANGELING ARMY
WILL BREAK THROUGH.
FIRST, WE TAKE CANTERLOT.
AND THEN ALL OF EQUESTRIA!
NO.
YOU WON'T.
YOU MAY HAVE MADE IT
IMPOSSIBLE FOR SHINING ARMOR
TO PERFORM HIS SPELL, BUT NOW
THAT YOU HAVE SO FOOLISHLY
REVEALED YOUR TRUE SELF,
I CAN PROTECT MY SUBJECTS
FROM YOU!
DON'T!
[ GUESTS GASP ]
PRINCESS CELESTIA!
AH.
SHINING ARMOR'S LOVE FOR YOU
IS EVEN STRONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
CONSUMING IT HAS MADE ME EVEN
MORE POWERFUL THAN CELESTIA!
THE ELEMENTS OF HARMONY.
YOU MUST GET TO THEM AND USE
THEIR POWER TO DEFEAT THE QUEEN.
all: RARITY!
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
YOU CAN RUN BUT YOU CAN'T HIDE!
[ EVIL CACKLING ]
GO, GO!
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO DO THIS THE HARD WAY!
HOW DID YOU--
THEY'RE CHANGELINGS,REMEMBER?
all: THEY'RE CHANGELINGS,
REMEMBER?
DON'T LET THEM DISTRACT YOU.
WE HAVE TO GET THE
ELEMENTS OF HARMONY.
THEY'RE OUR ONLY HOPE.
OKAY, THIS IS JUST
GETTING WEIRD!
REAL ME, REAL ME!
[ GIGGLING ]
DO ME, DO ME!
EH, I'VE SEEN BETTER.
YOU WON'T GET AWAY WITH THIS!
TWILIGHT AND HER FRIENDS WILL--
YOU WERE SAYING?
YOU DO REALIZE THE RECEPTION'S
BEEN CANCELLED, DON'T YOU?
GO! FEED!
[ CHUCKLING ]
IT'S FUNNY, REALLY.
TWILIGHT HERE WAS SUSPICIOUS
OF MY BEHAVIOR ALL ALONG.
TOO BAD THE REST OF YOU WERE
TOO CAUGHT UP IN YOUR WEDDING
PLANNING TO REALIZE THOSE
SUSPICIONS WERE CORRECT.
SORRY, TWI.
WE SHOULD'VE LISTENED TO YOU.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
SHE FOOLED EVERYPONY.
MM, I DID, DIDN'T I?
[ SOFT PIANO MUSIC ]
♪ ♪
♪ THIS DAY HAS BEEN ♪
♪ JUST PERFECT ♪
♪ THE KIND OF DAY ♪
♪ OF WHICH I'VE DREAMED ♪
♪ SINCE I WAS SMALL ♪
♪ EVERYPONY I'LL SOON CONTROL ♪
♪ EVERY STALLION, MARE ♪
♪ AND FOAL ♪
♪ WHO SAYS A GIRL ♪
♪ CAN'T REALLY HAVE IT ALL ♪
[ CHUCKLING ]
QUICK! GO TO HIM WHILE YOU
STILL HAVE THE CHANCE.
WHA-WHERE?
HUH?
IS THE WEDDING OVER?
IT'S ALL OVER!
YOUR SPELL--PERFORM
YOUR SPELL!
[ CACKLING ]
WHAT GOOD WOULD THAT DO?
MY CHANGELINGS
ALREADY ROAM FREE.
NO!
MY POWER IS USELESS NOW.
I DON'T HAVE THE
STRENGTH TO REPEL THEM.
MY LOVE WILL GIVE
YOU STRENGTH.
[ CACKLING ]
WHAT A LOVELY BUT ABSOLUTELY
RIDICULOUS SENTIMENT!
NOOOO!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'M FINE.
YOU HAVE A REAL WEDDING
TO PUT TOGETHER.
[ BIRDS WHISTLING BRIDAL CHORUS]
♪ ♪
SERIOUSLY, THOUGH.
I GET WHY THE QUEEN OF
THE CHANGELINGS WANTED
TO BE WITH YOU.
BUT HOW DID YOU GET SOMEONE AS
AMAZING CADENCE TO MARRY YOU?
I TOLD HER SHE WOULDN'T JUST
BE GAINING A HUSBAND,
SHE'D BE GETTING A PRETTY
GREAT SISTER TOO.
MARES AND GENTLECOLTS,
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY
TO CELEBRATE THE UNION OF THE
REAL PRINCESS MI AMORE CADENZA--
PRINCESS CADENCE IS FINE.
HMM.
THE UNION OF PRINCESS CADENCE
AND SHINING ARMOR.
THE STRENGTH OF THEIR
COMMITMENT IS CLEAR.
THE POWER OF THEIR
LOVE UNDENIABLE.
MAY WE HAVE THE RINGS PLEASE?
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
MARE AND COLT.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
THIS IS YOUR VICTORY AS
MUCH AS THEIRS.
YOU PERSISTED IN THE FACE OF
DOUBT AND YOUR ACTIONS LED TO
YOUR BEING ABLE TO BRING
THE REAL PRINCESS
CADENCE BACK TO US.
LEARNING TO TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS
IS A VALUABLE LESSON TO LEARN.
MWAH.
RAINBOW DASH,
THAT'S YOUR CUE.
BEST...WEDDING...EVER!
HELLO, EVERYPONY.
DID I MISS ANYTHING?
[ SQUEALING ]
LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED!
[ DANCE POP MUSIC ]
♪ LOVE IS IN BLOOM ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL BRIDE ♪
♪ A HANDSOME GROOM ♪
♪ TWO HEARTS BECOMING ONE ♪
♪ A BOND THAT CANNOT BE UNDONE ♪
♪ BECAUSE LOVE IS IN BLOOM ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL BRIDE ♪
♪ A HANDSOME GROOM ♪
♪ I SAID LOVE IS IN BLOOM ♪
♪ YOU'RE STARTING A LIFE ♪
♪ AND MAKING ROOM FOR US ♪
TWILIGHT!
NONE OF THIS WOULD'VE
BEEN POSSIBLE WITHOUT
YOU, LITTLE SIS.
LOVE YA, TWILIGHT.
LOVE YOU TOO, B.B.B.F.F.
READY TO GO?
OH! ALMOST FORGOT.
IT'S MINE!
[ EMBARRASSED LAUGHTER ]
♪ LOVE IS IN BLOOM ♪
NOW THIS WAS A GREAT WEDDING.
OH, YEAH?
JUST WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE WHAT
I HAVE PLANNED FOR THE
BACHELOR PARTY.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]