[ BIRD CHIRPING ]
Rarity: ARE THOSE SWEET
CARROT CUPCAKES I SMELL?
[ GASPS ]
MMM. HOW DIVINE.
NUM, NUM, NUM.
THE AROMA --
SPICED, WARM APPLE CIDER.
[ SNIFFS ]
AHH.
AND THE SMELL OF SMOKE.
SMOKE? SMOKE?!
SMOKE! AAH!
[ CRASH! ]
Sweetie Belle:
RARITY!
GRR!
YOU RUINED THE SURPRISE.
I WAS GONNA SERVE YOU
BREAKFAST IN BED!
[ SIGHS ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ GASPS ]
WOW!
GOOD MORNING, RARITY!
Rarity:
FATHER! UH, MOTHER!
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW
THAT SWEETIE BELLE HERE
COOKED THIS YUMMY-LOOKING
BREAKFAST ALL ON HER OWN.
[ SIZZLING ]
I...FIGURED.
[ SNIFFS ]
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD BURN JUICE.
I'VE BEEN
GIVING HER LESSONS.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF SHE'S GOT A CUTIE MARK
IN FANCY COOKING
BY THE TIME WE GET BACK
FROM OUR VACATION.
VACATION?
IS THAT THIS WEEK?
AS IN STARTING THIS VERY INSTANT
THIS WEEK?
[ POP! ]
MM. LET ME GUESS.
APPLESAUCE?
NOPE. TOAST.
[ POP! ]
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
THE BESTEST TIME
TWO SISTERS
COULD EVER HAVE.
I'M GONNA GO GRAB MY STUFF
FROM DAD'S WAGON.
SO, NOW,
WHEN YOU SAY "A WEEK,"
IS THAT, UM, [CLEARS THROAT]
SEVEN WHOLE DAYS?
AND SIX NIGHTS.
I KNOW!
SUCH A SHORT TIME TO SPEND
WITH YOUR LITTLE SIS.
YOU GONNA EAT THAT?
BUT I'VE GOT
SUCH A LONG TO-DO LIST.
OH, WELL. I SUPPOSE
"SPEND TIME WITH YOUR SISTER"
WILL JUST HAVE TO BE ADDED
TO THE LIST.
[ CRASH! ]
JUST A FEW NECESSITIES.
[ HONK! HONK! ]
NOW, LET'S GET THAT KITCHEN
ALL CLEANED UP.
CLEANED UP?
BUT WE HAVEN'T EVEN EATEN YET.
WELL, NOW, SWEETIE BELLE,
I APPRECIATE THE GESTURE,
BUT WE SIMPLY CAN'T EAT
THIS BREAKFAST.
IT'S BURNT.
IT'S NOT THAT BURNT.
NEVER FEAR, MY DEAR.
I'LL GET A PROPER
BREAKFAST GOING.
[ TINKLING ]
[ RARITY HUMMING ]
CAN I HELP?
OH! UH, OF COURSE.
UH, IN ONE MOMENT,
SWEETIE BELLE.
LET ME
JUST GET THINGS STARTED.
[ TINKLING ]
RARITY! I THOUGHT YOU SAID
I WAS GONNA HELP.
YOU ARE.
YOU CAN...
[ DING! ]
PUT THE GARNISH
ON THE PLATES.
YOU MEAN THIS PARSLEY?
OKAY, NOW, EASY!
IT HAS TO BE JUST RIGHT.
NO NEED TO RUSH.
NO! THAT'S TOO SLOW!
CAREFUL! BACK UP!
LOOKING
FOR PERFECTION HERE.
[ WHIFFLE! THUD! ]
WHOA! WHOA! UGH!
[ DISHES CLATTERING ]
THERE.
NOT BAD.
[ WHOOSH! WHOOSH! WHOOSH! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
[ GASPS ] THERE ARE SOME THINGS
I MUST ATTEND TO.
CAN YOU TAKE THE DIRTY TOWELS
TO THE LAUNDRY ROOM?
[ THUNK! ]
NO PROBLEM.
I'LL MAKE MYSELF USEFUL.
[ BUBBLE! BUBBLE! ]
[ BUBBLE! BUBBLE! BUBBLE! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ BLINK! ]
SWEETIE BELLE!
I TOLD YOU
I'D MAKE MYSELF USEFUL.
SURPRISED?
AM I?
YOU WASHED
MY INCREDIBLY EXPENSIVE,
ONE-OF-A-KIND, DESIGNER,
CROCHETED WOOL SWEATER!
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD
THESE THINGS ARE TO COME BY?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
THE BIG DEAL IS THAT IN THE HEAT
OF THE SUN, WOOL...
[ SQUEAK! ]
...SHRINKS.
OH. SORRY.
[ CREAK! ]
BACK TO WORK.
I MUST CREATE.
[ SPLASH! ]
SORRY?
HAH.
STAY OUT OF TROUBLE, OKAY?
PLEASE?
I JUST WANTED TO DO
SOMETHING NICE FOR MY SISTER.
[ SIGHS ]
I'M SO BORED!
WHEN IS RARITY
GONNA FINISH HER WORK?
[ POINK! ]
STAY OUT OF TROUBLE,
OKAY?
I NEVER GOT IN TROUBLE
FOR DRAWING.
HMM.
THIS NEEDS SOMETHING.
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ ZIP! WHIP! ]
HI, RARITY! I MADE
A SPECIAL DRAWING FOR YOU.
AAAAAAAHH!
OH, NO!
DID YOU USE THESE GEMS?
WELL, YES, BUT I KNOW YOU HAVE
MORE IN YOUR WORK ROOM.
B-B-BUT THESE ARE EXTREMELY RARE
BABY-BLUE SAPPHIRES!
I NEED THEM FOR AN OUTFIT FOR
AN EXTREMELY IMPORTANT CLIENT!
OH. SORRY.
[ SIGHS ]
SWEETIE BELLE, WHAT AM I
GOING TO DO WITH YOU?!
OH! WE CAN PAINT TOGETHER.
WE CAN RIDE BIKES,
PLAY CHESS, SING A SONG,
CATCH FROGS,
PILLOW FIGHT.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT!
OH.
NOW I HAVE TO GO AND FIND
SOME MORE OF THESE GEMS.
I'LL GO WITH YOU
AND HELP.
NO!
NO, THANK YOU.
YOU CAN HELP
BY PICKING UP THESE PAPERS
AND STACKING THEM...
NEATLY.
PUT THE PENS AND PENCILS BACK
EXACTLY WHERE YOU FOUND THEM
AND PLEASE FIND
SOMETHING TO DO
THAT DOESN'T CREATE A LARGE MESS
FOR ME TO CLEAN UP.
[ BLAM! ]
[ SIGHS ]
GEEZ, LOUISE.
CAN'T I DO ANYTHING RIGHT?
[ TING! ]
[ TINKLING ]
SWEETIE BELLE!
I'M BACK.
[ SLOOP! ]
SWEETIE BELLE?
[ GASPS ]
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
SURPRISE!
UHH! EEK! BLEH!
MY INSPIRATION ROOM!
WHAT DID YOU DO?
WHAT DID YOU DO?!
WHEN I SAW THE BIG MESS
IN YOUR ROOM,
I THOUGHT I'D CLEAN IT UP
FOR YOU.
THIS WASN'T A MESS!
IT WAS ORGANIZED CHAOS!
I WAS JUST ABOUT FINISHED
PLANNING MY NEW FASHION LINE.
Y-Y-Y-YOU WENT AND --
AND YOU --
AND YOU PUT EVERYTHING AWAY!
BUT EVERY TIME I MAKE A MESS,
YOU GET UPSET.
BUT THIS WAS MY MESS
IN MY HOUSE!
AND NOW I HAVE TO START
FROM SCRATCH!
BUT, I-I THOUGHT
IT WOULD MAKE YOU HAPPY.
HAPPY?!
HAPPY?! I --
[ GRIND! GRIND! GRIND! ]
[ GULP! ]
I JUST NEED
SOME TIME ALONE.
HMPH!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
HOW'S THAT SLEEPOVER
AT RARITY'S GOING?
[ BLINK! ]
WHY, IT'S SMASHING.
HUH?
I JUST WISH WE COULD DO
SOMETHING SPECIAL TOGETHER
THAT DIDN'T INCLUDE ME
GOOFING ANYTHING UP.
OH,
THE SISTERHOOVES SOCIAL!
APPLEJACK AND I DO IT
EVERY YEAR.
YOU AND RARITY COULD COMPETE
AGAINST OTHER SISTER TEAMS
IN ALL THESE NEAT EVENTS.
[ GASPS ]
THAT SOUNDS LIKE THE PERFECT WAY
FOR US TO HANG OUT!
RARITY WILL THINK
IT'S AN EXCELLENT IDEA.
Rarity:
WHAT A RIDICULOUS IDEA.
A CONTEST
AT SWEET APPLE ACRES?
IT DOESN'T SOUND,
HMM, VERY CLEAN.
SO WHAT?
NOW YOU'RE BACK
TO HATING MESSES?
SWEETIE BELLE!
WATCH YOUR TONE.
I AM STILL
YOUR BIG SISTER.
RIGHT!
AND ANY SISTER WHO CARES ABOUT
HER SISTER GOES.
SWEETIE BELLE, HONESTLY.
PLAYING SILLY LITTLE GAMES
IN THE DIRT IS JUST UNCOUTH --
WITH OR WITHOUT A SISTER.
WELL, THEN, MAYBE --
MAYBE I'LL TRY
THE SISTERHOOVES SOCIAL
WITHOUT A SISTER!
IN FACT, I THINK I'LL TRY
THE REST OF MY LIFE
WITHOUT A SISTER!
[ GASPS ]
OH, I'M THE ONE
WHO'S RUINING YOUR LIFE!
REALLY?!
HAVE YOU LOOKED AROUND
THIS PLACE?
I'M THE ONE WHO WOULD BE
BETTER OFF WITH NO SISTER!
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE FINALLY AGREE ON SOMETHING.
NEITHER OF US
NEEDS A SISTER!
DEAL!
GOODBYE, UN-SISTER!
[ BLAM! ]
HMPH!
Applejack: "UNCOUTH"?
SHE SAID THE SISTERHOOVES SOCIAL
WAS UNCOUTH?!
YEAH, UNCOUTH?!
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! BURP! ]
WAIT? WHAT'S UNCOUTH?
IT'S NOT JUST THE SOCIAL.
SHE THINKS I'M UNCOUTH.
HONEY, RARITY THINKS
EVERYTHING'S UNCOUTH.
[ SLURP! ]
[ Muffled ]
WHAT'S UNCOUTH?
IT MEANS UNCIVIL.
YOU KNOW, BAD-MANNERED?
[ BELCH! ]
EXACTLY!
SWEETIE BELLE,
JUST GIVE RARITY SOME TIME.
SHE'LL COME AROUND.
SISTERS ALWAYS DO.
NOT SISTERS LIKE RARITY.
COME ON, NOW.
APPLE BLOOM AND I GOT
SOME CHORES TO FINISH UP ON.
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP.
YOU SURE YOU WANT ME TO HELP?
I JUST MESS EVERYTHING UP.
OH, COME ON.
THAT'S JUST STINKIN' THINKIN'.
WATCH.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ WHISTLE! PLUNK! ]
[ GIGGLES ]
GOOD CATCH THERE,
APPLE BLOOM. WHOO-HOO!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
[ BONK! SMACK! ]
[ ZIP! ]
THIS IS A CHORE?
SINCE WE CAN'T SELL
THE BRUISED APPLES,
WE GOT TO COLLECT THEM ALL
FOR THE PIGS TO EAT.
[ PLUNK! ]
[ ZOOM! BOING! ]
IT'S A LOT OF WORK,
SO WE MAKE A GAME OF IT.
WANT TO TRY?
UM...OKAY.
[ SMACK! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
OW!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS HARD WORK.
THAT'S WHY
WE DO IT...
Both: TOGETHER!
HMPH. RARITY NEVER WANTS TO
DO CHORES TOGETHER.
Rarity: UNH!
ALL THAT WORK RUINED
THANKS TO SWEETIE BELLE.
[ TINKLING ]
OH, MY. IT'S USUALLY
A BIG MESS IN HERE.
[ GASPS ]
[ TINKLING ]
IDEA!
THIS IS GENIUS!
[ SEWING MACHINE WHIRRING ]
I SHALL CALL IT
"FULL SPECTRUM FASHIONS."
WHY, IF SWEETIE BELLE
HADN'T...
[ BLINK! BLINK! ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
WELL, NO MATTER.
SHE STILL SHOULDN'T HAVE TOUCHED
MY THINGS WITHOUT PERMISSION.
HMPH!
APPLE BLOOM,
YOU'RE UP!
[ ZIP! ]
[ POING! POING! POING! POING! ]
[ BOING! ]
[ SPLASH! SPLASH! SPLASH! ]
[ GURGLE! ]
YOU'RE MAKING
GRAPE JUICE?
RARITY WOULD CALL
THE FASHION POLICE ON ME
IF I GOT GRAPE JUICE
ANYWHERE NEAR
HER PRECIOUS OUTFITS!
WELL, THAT'S SILLY!
[ SPLASH! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
APPLE BLOOM!
PLEASE, APPLEJACK!
SHE DIDN'T ME--
WHOA!
HOW YOU DO LIKE THEM GRAPES,
YOU LITTLE WHIPPERSNAPPER?
[ Laughing ]
THAT TICKLES!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ TINKLING ]
NOW TO GET THESE FABRICS WASHED
FOR MY FABULOUS NEW LINE.
OHH!
MY FAVORITE SWEATER.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT SWEETIE BELLE.
[ YOWL! ]
[ SLURP! PURR! PURR! ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ POP! ]
OH, OPAL-WOPAL.
IT'S AS IF
SWEETIE BELLE KNEW
THE SWEATER
WAS PERFECT FOR YOU.
AND SWEETIE BELLE SHOULD
CONSIDER HERSELF PERFECTLY LUCKY
THAT THIS THOUGHTLESS MISHAP
TURNED OUT ALL RIGHT.
HMPH!
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
APPLE BLOOM!
GOT IT, SIS.
BAA!
BAA!BAA!
WOW! IT'S AS IF
THEY'RE JUST ONE PONY.
YEE-HAW!
WAY TO CORRAL
SOME CRITTERS, SIS.
[ Bleating ] YOU COULD'VE
JUST A-A-ASKED.
[ CREAK! SLAM! ]
RARITY
NEVER HIGH-HOOVES ME.
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
Rarity: PERFECT.
JUST ONE MORE,
AND THIS ENSEMBLE IS FINIS.
GRR!
SWEETIE BELLE!
WHERE'S HER SILLY, LITTLE
ARTS-AND-CRAFTS PROJECT?
[ WARBLE! ]
OH, SWEETIE BELLE!
MY ONE AND ONLY SISTER!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?!
ALL THE TIME
I COULD'VE SPENT WITH YOU
WAS WASTED COMPLAINING
AND WISHING YOU WERE GONE!
[ Crying ] WOE IS ME!
NO!
I MUST GET HER BACK.
I MUST!
AS CELESTIA AS MY WITNESS,
I SHALL NEVER
BE SISTERLESS AGAIN!
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ GASPS ] SWEETIE BELLE!
OH, I HAVE BEEN GALLOPING
ALL OVER LOOKING FOR YOU.
I --
OH, HELLO, UN-SISTER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
BETTER BE CAREFUL.
YOU MIGHT GET SOME DUST ON YOU.
OH, SWEETIE BELLE.
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
I AM NOT BETTER OFF
WITHOUT A SISTER.
I'M NOT BETTER OFF WITHOUT
A SISTER, EITHER.
SPENDING THE DAY
WITH APPLEJACK AND APPLE BLOOM
MADE ME REALIZE THAT.
OH! OH, SWEETIE.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW HAPPY I AM
TO HEAR YOU --
AND THAT'S WHY I'M ADOPTING
APPLEJACK AS MY BIG SISTER!
WHAT?!
[ ZOOM! ]
A SISTER IS SOMEONE
WHO LOVES AND TAKES CARE OF
ANOTHER SISTER.
APPLEJACK'S A REAL SISTER.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
HOLD ON,
SWEETIE BELLE.
DON'T GET AHEAD
OF YOURSELF HERE.
BESIDES...
[ ZIP! ]
SHE'S MY BIG SISTER.
YEAH, UM...
OR MAYBE SHE SHOULD BE
YOUR SISTER
SO SHE COULD TEACH YOU
WHAT A GOOD SISTER
IS SUPPOSED TO BE!
HEH.
UM, ACTUALLY, I --
I-I DON'T NEED LESSONS
ON BEING A GOOD SISTER.
I-I PROMISE!
LISTEN, I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO COOK MY FAVORITE QUICHE.
OR -- OR I'LL SHOW YOU
THE PROPER WAY TO BEAUTIFY
YOUR MANE.
WON'T THAT BE FUN?
HMM?
HMPH!
YOU WANT ME
TO GO HOME WITH YOU
SO WE CAN DO
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO?
UH...YES.
JUST FORGET IT!
WE'RE STILL SISTERS,
RIGHT?
WELL, THAT APOLOGY
WENT SWIMMINGLY.
APPLEJACK, WHY DO YOU
HAVE TO BE SO GOOD
AND MAKE ME LOOK SO BAD?
[ CHUCKLES ]
OH, RARITY.
ONCE AGAIN,
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT YOURSELF.
BEING SISTERS
IS A GIVE AND TAKE.
YOU'VE BEEN DOING
A WHOLE LOT OF TAKING,
BUT YOU HAVEN'T BEEN DOING
A WHOLE LOT OF GIVING.
BUT OF COURSE I GIVE!
I GIVE LESSONS,
REASONABLE DEMANDS.
BUT YOU NEVER GIVE IN.
BEING SISTERS
IS LIKE APPLE PIE.
YOU CAN HAVE
AMAZING APPLES
AND YOU CAN HAVE
A WONDERFULLY CRISPY CRUST,
BUT ONLY TOGETHER CAN YOU HAVE
A PERFECT APPLE PIE.
BUT APART, ALL WE ARE
IS JUST A PILE OF MUSH
AND SOME CRUMBLY,
DRY MESS.
[ GASPS ]
I KNOW WHAT I NEED TO DO!
I JUST HOPE
IT ISN'T TOO LATE.
♪♪
[ SLURP! SLURP! SLURP! SLURP! ]
WELL, I GUESS IT'S A GOOD THING
RARITY ISN'T HERE.
DO I SEE "UNCOUTH" WRITTEN
ALL OVER THIS CONTEST?
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT PIG!
HE SURE IS A CUTIE.
THAT'S THE LAST WORD
RARITY WOULD USE.
[ As Rarity ] OH, MY,
WHAT A REPULSIVE MONSTROSITY.
THIS THING NEEDS
A HEAD-TO-TOE MAKEOVER.
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
IT'S ALMOST TIME!
WELL,
YOU TWO HAVE FUN.
I SURE WISH I HAD A SISTER
TO RUN THE RACE WITH.
[ SLAP! PLUNK! ]
HUH?
YOU DO NOW!
A.B. AND I FIGURED
SINCE WE DO THIS EVERY YEAR...
I'D LET YOU BORROW MY SIS
SO YOU CAN GIVE IT A TRY.
SISTER FOR A DAY.
NO WAY!
ONE DAY.
[ ZIP! ]
[ ZOOM! ]
ONE DAY.
[ FEEDBACK SQUEALS ]
Granny Smith:
IS THIS THING ON?
I DON'T THINK
THIS THING IS ON.
HELLO?!
WHERE'S THE --
EHH? OH.
YOU HAVE TO SAY SO.
CARN-FANGLED MODERN DOO-HICKEY!
[ WHIRL! ]
NOW THE EVENT
Y'ALL HAVE BEEN WAITIN' FER!
THE SISTER SOC--
THE SOCIALHOOVE --
OHH! DAGNABBIT!
YOU KNOW -- THE BIG RACE!
WE HAVE FIVE TEAMS THIS YEAR
FOR THE EVENT,
SO ALL Y'ALL HEAD ON OUT
TO THE FINISH LINE, YOU HEAR?!
EH?
THE START LINE!
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
THAT'S US.
ONE DAY.
GOOD LUCK!
[ ZIP! ]
AND MAY THE BEST SISTERS WIN!
ON YOUR MARK...
...GET SET...
[ POINK! ]
GO-O-O-O!
[ ZIP! ZIP! ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ POING! POING! POING! POING! ]
[ SPLAT! ]
ARE YOU OKAY, APPLEJACK?
[ CRASH! ]
[ WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! WHIP! ]
[ WHIP! WHIP! THUNK! ]
APPLEJACK, HELP!
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! ]
[ ZOOM! ZOOM! ]
[ WHIP! BOING! BOING! ]
[ SPLASH! SPLASH! SPLASH! ]
[ GURGLE! GURGLE! ]
YOU CAN DO IT, SISTER.
[ WHIP! ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ BOING! ]
[ PLUNK! ]
[ SPROING! ]
[ WHISTLE! PONK! ]
[ BONK! ]
[ SPLAT! SPLAT! ]
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ POING! POING! POING! ]
[ ZOOM! WHIRL! ]
[ ALL GROANS ]
[ SLOOP! ZIP! ]
[ THUD! ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, SO CLOSE!
YOU ALMOST WON!
THANK YOU, APPLEJACK.
YOU ARE AMAZING.
I DON'T EVEN CARE
THAT WE DIDN'T WIN.
IT WAS SO MUCH FUN!
HUH?!
[ SLOSH! SLOSH! ]
RARITY?
[ BLINK! ]
[ SLOSH! TWINKLE! ]
WAIT.
WHERE'S APPLEJACK?
[ SLOSH! GASP! ]
I DON'T GET IT.
[ LAUGHS ]
WE SWITCHED PLACES OVER AT
THE VERY FIRST MUD HOLE.
[ SLOSH! SLOSH! SLOSH! ]
SO WE DID
THE WHOLE COMPETITION TOGETHER?
THAT WE DID,
LITTLE SISTER.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR
THE START LINE.
BUT YOU FINISHED
TOGETHER!
Sweetie Belle: YOU MEAN...
YOU WERE ALL IN ON IT?
MM-HMM.
YOU DID THIS FOR ME?
US.
I DID IT FOR US.
YOU SEE?
WE ARE APPLE PIE.
HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
I'LL EXPLAIN LATER.
FOR NOW, I THINK WE DESERVE
A CELEBRATION.
YEAH!
WHERE?
THE SPA, OF COURSE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, RARITY.
OH, GEE WHIZ.
NO, I-I-I'M SERIOUS.
VERY WELL, THEN.
WHAT SHOULD WE WRITE
TO THE PRINCESS?
I'LL START.
"HAVING A SISTER
"IS JUST ABOUT
THE BESTEST THING IN THE WORLD,
BUT IT SURE ISN'T
THE EASIEST."
Rarity: I AGREE THAT BEING
SISTERS IS A WONDERFUL THING.
IT TAKES TEAMWORK.
SOMETIMES,
IT'S ABOUT COMPROMISING.
[ FIRE ALARM BEEPING ]
SOMETIMES, IT'S ABOUT ACCEPTING
EACH OTHERS' DIFFERENCES.
BUT MOSTLY, IT'S ABOUT
HAVING FUN TOGETHER...
EVEN IF IT MEANS GETTING
YOUR HOOVES A LITTLE BIT DIRTY.
A LOT DIRTY!
[ SPLASH! ]
A LITTLE BIT DIRTY.
A LOT DIRTY.
A LITTLE BIT DIRTY!
A LOT --
HOLD IT!
HOW ABOUT A MEDIUM AMOUNT
OF DIRTY?
NOT TOO LITTLE,
NOT TO MUCH.
JUST RIGHT.
DEAL!
[ BIRD CHIRPING ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪