MARZIPAN MASCARPONE MERINGUE
MADNESS!
YOU'VE REALLY OUTDONE
YOURSELVES, MR. AND MRS. CAKE.
THIS IS SURE TO BE THE WINNING
ENTRY AT THIS YEAR'S NATIONAL
DESSERT COMPETITION.
OH, THANK YOU, PINKIE.
AND THANKS FOR TRANSPORTING
IT ALL THE WAY TO CANTERLOT FOR
US.
ABSOLUTELY! IT'S MY HONOR
TO--
UH, BEG YOUR PARDON, BUT
COULD WE MAYBE MOVE THINGS
ALONG?
THIS HERE CAKE IS A MIGHT HEAVY,
RIGHT, BIG MCINTOSH?
[ STRUGGLING ]
YUP.
ALL RIGHTY THEN, BIG MAC.
TO THE TRAIN DEPOT!
THAT'S IT, BIG MAC, NICE AND
SLOW.
THIS IS PRECIOUS CARGO YOU'RE
CARRYING.
YES, IT TOOK MONTHS OF
PLANNING AND TESTING.
I WOULD HATE FOR IT TO...
[ GRUNTING ]
both: FALL!
DON'T WORRY, MR. AND MRS.
CAKE.
RAINBOW DASH! FLUTTERSHY!
A LITTLE PEGA-SSISTANCE!
I'LL GET IT THERE SAFELY,
YOU'LL SEE.
[ NERVOUS LAUGHTER ]
OF COURSE, PINKIE.
WE NEVER DOUBTED YOU.
TWILIGHT, CAN I SEE YOU A
SECOND?
A NICE, PROTECTIVE SPELL AS
EXTRA INSURANCE.
BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY.
AJ? RARITY? ONE LAST THING?
ALL RIGHT, EVERYPONY.
WE'RE IN THE HOMESTRETCH HERE.
[ WHEEZING ]
SEE, MR. AND MRS. CAKE?
I GOT IT HERE WITHOUT A HITCH.
NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS GET
IT...
IN.
[ SOFTLY ] ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
[ UPBEAT] ♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER ♪
♪ WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ♪
♪ ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART ♪
♪ FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ♪
♪ ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ TO HAVE MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALL MY VERY ♪
♪ BEST FRIENDS ♪
[ SIGH ]
THANK YOU ALL FOR HELPING ME GET
THE CAKE SAFELY ON THE DESSERT
CAR.
THANK YOU FOR INVITING US ALL
TO GO WITH YOU TO CANTERLOT
FOR THE NATIONAL DESSERT
COMPETITION.
I'M SURE THE FESTIVITIES
WILL BE JUST LOVELY.
PHOOEY ON THE FESTIVITIES.
I CAN'T WAIT TO TRY ALL
THOSE TASTY TREATS!
WELL, THE TASTIEST TREAT OF
ALL IS SURE TO BE THE CAKES'
MARZIPAN MASCARPONE MERINGUE
MADNESS.
ALL THAT RICH, CREAMY GOODNESS
OF THE MARZIPAN COMBINED WITH
THE TART, TANGINESS OF THE
MASCARPONE BLENDED PERFECTLY
WITH THE SMOOTH, SILKY SWEETNESS
OF THE MERINGUE.
THAT'S WHY I CALL THE MARZIPAN
MASCARPONE MERINGUE MADNESS
THE "MMMM."
all: MMMM.
EXACTLY.
IT'S THE MOST DELICIOUS,
DELECTABLE, DELIGHTFUL, DELOVELY
CAKE IN EQUESTRIA, AND IT'S SURE
TO WIN FIRST PRIZE.
[ FRENCH ACCENT ] THIS IS NOT
SO!
FOR I, GUSTAVE LE GRAND, DO
CHALLENGE YOUR CRUDE CAKE TO A
DUEL OF DELECTABLE DELICACIES
AGAINST MY EXCEPTIONALLY
EXQUISITE ECLAIRS!
THEY WILL UNDOUBTABLY STRIKE
DOWN ALL THE COMPETITION,
WINNING FIRST PRIZE AND CROWNING
ME LE CHAMPION!
NOT A CHANCE, LE GRAND.
DONUT JOE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN PONYVILLE?
PICKING UP THE FINAL,
ALL-IMPORTANT INGREDIENT FOR MY
CONTEST ENTRY.
DONUTOPIA!
AND WITH THESE SUPER SPRINKLES,
MY DONUTS ARE GONNA DUNK ALL THE
OTHER LOUSY DESSERTS, STEAL
FIRST PRIZE, AND MAKE MY DONUT
SHOP FAMOUS...FOREVER!
OH, JOE, YOUR DIPPY DONUTS
COULD NEVER OUTRUN ME.
HELLO.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
I AM MULIA MILD.
BEHOLD MY CHOCOLATE MOOSE
MOUSSE.
IT WILL TRAMPLE ALL YOUR TREATS,
BE GIVEN FIRST PRIZE, AND MAKE
ME THE GREATEST CHEF IN
EQUESTRIA.
MADAME MILD, YOU AND YOUR
MOOSE MOUSSE ARE MISTAKEN.
YOUR FROUFROU ECLAIRS
WILL NEVER DEFEAT MY DONUTS.
THE CAKES' MARZIPAN
MASCARPONE MERINGUE MADNESS
IS GOING TO WIN!
YOUR SIMPLE CAKE COULD NEVER
TAKE MY MOUSSE.
[ TRAIN WHISTLES ]
WELL, IT SURE LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE IN FOR A DELICIOUS
COMPETITION TOMORROW.
MAYBE WE SHOULD ALL SETTLE IN
FOR A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
OH.
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUMBLES ]
[ YAWNING ]
I GOT TO ADMIT I'M PRETTY BEAT.
YEAH, I'M GONNA HIT THE HAY
MYSELF.
WAIT!
DIDN'T YOU HEAR THOSE CHEFS?
WE HAVE TO PROTECT MMMM.
MMMM?
MM-HMM!
I KNOW FOR SUPER SURE THAT MMMM
IS THE BEST DESSERT IN ALL OF
EQUESTRIA.
AND I KNOW THAT THEY KNOW IT
TOO.
SO...?
SO ONE OF THEM IS GONNA
SABOTAGE THE CAKES' CAKE
TONIGHT!
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME STAND GUARD.
PINKIE, YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
YEAH, THOSE CHEFS AREN'T
GONNA DO YOUR CAKE ANY HARM.
BUT THEY ARE!
I JUST KNOW IT.
FINE! IF YOU WANNA STAND
GUARD, GO FOR IT.
WE'RE GOING TO BED.
I'LL SHOW THEM.
I'LL STAY UP ALL NIGHT AND
PROTECT YOU.
NOTHING AND NOPONY WILL STOP ME
FROM KEEPING YOU SAFE.
HUH?
STOP, YOU SABOTEUR!
I HAVE YOU NOW!
WHA?
AHA!
MMMM?
OH, THANK CELESTIA YOU'RE OKAY.
BUT ONE OF THOSE BAKERS IS
MIXING UP SOMETHING BAD, SO I'M
NOT LEAVING YOU AGAIN NO MATTER
WHAT!
HUH? WHO TURNED OUT THE MOON?
DON'T GO NEAR THAT CAKE, THIEF!
STOP, THIEF!
[ CLANG ]
OH! ARE YOU OKAY, THIEF?
[ GROWLING ]
HUMPH!
OVERREACTING MY HOOF!
I KNEW I WAS GONNA HAVE TO KEEP
A CLOSE EYE ON YOU, AND THAT'S
JUST WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
[ SNORING ]
[ ROOSTER CROWS]
HUH? WHA?
[ GASP ] THE CAKE!
OH, MMMM, YOU LOOK MMMMARVELOUS.
WHOA!
I KNOW.
I THINK SOME CONGRATULATIONS ARE
IN ORDER FOR A JOB WELL DONE.
UM, YOU BETTER HOLD OFF ON
GIVING YOURSELF AN AWARD JUST
YET, PINKIE.
LOOK.
LOOK AT WHAT?
HUH?
[ GASP ]
[ SCREAMS ]
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
IT'S THE MARZIPAN MASCARPONE
MERINGUE MADNESS.
IT'S BEEN...MUTILATED!
all: [ GASP ]
NOW WE JUST NEED TO FIND OUT
WHO DONE IT!
YOU MEAN WHO DID IT.
EXACTLY!
WHO DID DONE DOOD IT!
WELL, HAVING READ MANY
MYSTERY NOVELS, I KNOW THAT THE
ONLY WAY TO DISCOVER THE CULPRIT
IS TO INVESTIGATE.
EXACTLY!
AND AS CHIEF DETECTIVE, THAT'S
EXACTLY WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
UH, YOU'RE INVESTIGATING?
YES!
AND TWILIGHT SHALL BE MY LOWLY
ASSISTANT WHO ASKS SILLY
QUESTIONS WITH OBVIOUS ANSWERS.
FINE, PINKIE.
SHOULD WE START LOOKING FOR
CLUES?
PERFECT SILLY QUESTION, MY
DEAR TWILIGHT, BECAUSE THE
OBVIOUS ANSWER IS--
YES?
NO! 'CAUSE I KNOW WHO DID IT!
all: [ GASP ]
PINKIE, HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW?
HOW COULD I POSSIBLY NOT
KNOW?
CLEARLY, THIS DASTARDLY DEED WAS
DONE BY THE BAKER, WHO KNEW
THEIR DESSERT COULD NOT MEASURE
UP TO THE MASTERY OF THE
MARZIPAN MASCARPONE MERINGUE
MADNESS!
I GUESS YOU FEARED YOUR ECLAIRS
LACKED FLAIR...
GUSTAVE!
[ OLD-TIMEY SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC ]
♪ ♪
THUS DESTROYING THE CAKE AND THE
CAKES' CHANCES OF WINNING THE
NATIONAL DESSERT COMPETITION!
BUT IT MAKES NO SENSE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, LOWLY
ASSISTANT?
WELL, FIRST, IF YOU WERE TIED
TO THE TRAIN TRACKS, HOW ARE YOU
NOW HERE?
HUH.
GUESS THAT ISN'T A TOTALLY SILLY
QUESTION.
AND SECOND, THE CAKE HASN'T
BEEN SLICED, IT'S BEEN BITTEN.
JUST LOOK AT THE TEETH MARKS.
HMM, YOU'RE RIGHT, MY FINE
FELLOW.
GUSTAVE LE GRAND IS CLEARLY IN
THE CLEAR, WHICH MEANS THAT MMMM
WAS DESTROYED BY ANOTHER BAKER--
A BAKER WHOSE DONUTS ARE
DO-NOTS!
THAT'S RIGHT, IT WAS JOE...
[ SPY MUSIC ]
♪ ♪
OR AS HE'S KNOWN IN THE SPY
WORLD, MANE, CON MANE.
[ SLURPING ]
[ GIGGLING ]
[ WATCH BEEPING ]
CRUSHING THE CAKES' CHANCES TO
WIN!
PINKIE, THERE IS NO LASER
BEAM SECURITY SYSTEM, AND JOE IS
NOT SLEEK, STEALTHY CON MANE.
HE'S BIG, GRUFF, AND MESSY!
HEY!
ALTHOUGH YOU WOULD LOOK
RATHER DAPPER IN A TUXEDO.
YOU MAY BE RIGHT, LOWLY
ASSISTANT.
MAY BE?
NOW THAT I'M TAKING A CLOSER
LOOK AT THESE DESSERTS, I SEE
THAT ONE SIMPLY CANNOT LOOK ME
IN THE EYE.
PINKIE, THAT MOOSE IS A
MOUSSE.
YES! AND THE MULE BEHIND THE
MOOSE PANICKED WHEN SHE SAW THE
MASTERY OF THE MMMM.
SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT THE
CULPRIT IS...
MULIA MILD!
[ BANG ]
PUTTING AN END TO THE CAKES'
DREAMS OF TAKING FIRST PRIZE.
HUMPH!
I HOPE YOU'RE PROUD OF YOURSELF,
MULIA.
PINKIE, STOP.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
LOOK AT HER.
[ INCOHERENT MUMBLING ]
HUH. I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANK YOU!
BUT I WAS SO SURE THAT IT WAS
ONE OF THE OTHER BITTER BAKERS
THAT DESTROYED THE MMMM.
THAT WAY, THEIR DELICIOUS
DESSERT WOULD REIGN SUPREME.
I MEAN, JUST LOOK AT JOE'S
DONUTOPIA.
IT'S A SPECTACULAR CITY OF
DONUTTY DELIGHT, TOPPED
TEMPTINGLY IN SPRINK-A-LICIOUS
SPRINKLES.
AND GUSTAVE'S ECLAIRS LOOK
INCREDIBLY EDIBLE WITH
GLISTENING GLAZINESS.
BUT THEN THERE'S MULIA MILD'S
MOOSE MOUSSE.
WHY THIS MOUTH-WATERINGLY
MARVELOUS MOOSE MOUSSE TEMPTS
THE TASTE BUDS WITH ITS SILKY
SMOOTH, YUMMY-NUMMY
CHOCOLATINESS.
SO WHY DID THIS CRIMINAL DEVOUR
THE MARZIPAN MASCARPONE MERINGUE
MADNESS WHILE LEAVING THIS TRIO
OF TASTY TREATS UNTOUCHED?
[ SCREAM ]
HUH.
NOW I HAVE NO IDEA WHO DO DONED
IT!
THIS MYSTERY GETS MORE
MYSTERIOUS EVERY MINUTE.
WELL, YOU HAVE TO STOP THE
WILD ACCUSATIONS AND GET TO THE
TRUTH.
EVERYPONY GO BACK TO YOUR CARS
WHILE WE DO A LITTLE
INVESTIGATING.
OKAY, PINKIE, IN ORDER TO REALLY
SOLVE THIS MYSTERY, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO FIND CLUES.
NOW YOU WERE HERE AT THE SCENE
OF THE CRIME ALL NIGHT.
[ GASP ] YOU'RE NOT ACCUSING
ME, ARE YOU?
NO, BUT MAYBE YOU SAW
SOMETHING THAT WILL HELP US.
I SAW A SILHOUETTE IN THE
MOONLIGHT.
GOOD.
LET'S RETRACE YOUR STEPS.
THEN I CHASED THE CULPRIT
DOWN THE TRAIN, TOWARDS THE
CABOOSE.
BUT WHEN I GOT THERE, HE WAS
GONE.
HMM.
AHA!
OUR FIRST CLUE.
I THINK I KNOW WHO DID IT,
PINKIE.
ALREADY?
YES, BUT I NEED MORE EVIDENCE
TO CONFIRM.
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED NEXT.
I HEARD SOMEPONY ELSE IN THE
DESSERT CAR AND CHASED THEM UP
TO THE ENGINE.
BUT WHEN I GOT THERE, ALL I SAW
WAS THE CONDUCTOR SHOVELING
COAL.
THE CONDUCTOR, HUH?
[ GASP ]
BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT, PINKIE?
WELL, I WENT BACK TO THE
DESSERT CAR.
YES?
THE CURTAINS MYSTERIOUSLY
CLOSED ALL ON THEIR OWN.
INTERESTING.
ANYTHING ELSE?
I HEARD HOOFSTEPS, A LOUD
THUD...
AND THEN THEY WERE GONE.
WHEN I OPENED THE CURTAINS,
I SAW THE PORTRAIT BY THE DOOR
WAS ALL CROOKED.
OH, MY, WHAT IS THAT?
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT NEXT, PINKIE?
THAT'S IT.
I WAS HERE GUARDING THE CAKE THE
REST OF THE NIGHT.
I MEAN...
I SLEPT BY THE CAKE THE REST OF
THE NIGHT.
AND WHEN YOU WOKE UP, HALF
THE CAKE WAS GONE?
EXACTLY!
BY JOVE, I THINK I'VE GOT IT!
CALL EVERYPONY BACK.
WE HAVE A CAKE CULPRIT TO CATCH.
WHY ARE WE ALL HERE AGAIN?
[ DOOR CLOSING ]
I BET YOU'RE WONDERING WHY
YOU'RE ALL HERE AGAIN.
SHE'S GOOD!
WE HAVE DISCOVERED THE TRUE
CULPRIT OF THIS CAKE CARNAGE.
BUT HOW?
WELL, YOU SEE, WHEN
COMMITTING A CRIME, IT'S CRUCIAL
THAT ONE NEVER LEAVES BEHIND
CLUES, ESPECIALLY AN OBVIOUS
CLUE LIKE THIS.
all: [ GASP ]
AHA!
A BLUE FEATHER.
I KNEW IT WAS YOU, GUSTAVE LE
GRAND!
PINKIE, GUSTAVE DOESN'T HAVE
BLUE FEATHERS.
NO! 'CAUSE HE'S BEEN DYING
THEM!
NO, PINKIE.
REMEMBER HOW WHEN YOU CHASED THE
SUSPECT TO THE CABOOSE, THEY
SUDDENLY DISAPPEARED?
THAT'S BECAUSE THEY FLEW AWAY.
BUT THE THIEF DID LEAVE A LITTLE
SOMETHING BEHIND, DIDN'T YOU,
RAINBOW DASH?
I-I DON'T EVEN LIKE CAKE!
SO RAINBOW DASH DID IT!
CASE SOLVED!
CASE NOT SOLVED, BECAUSE WHEN
WE WENT TO THE ENGINE, I SAW
THE CONDUCTOR'S HAT.
AND INSIDE THE HAT WAS...
THIS.
SO IT WAS YOU.
THAT PINK HAIR CAME FROM YOUR
RAINBOW COLORED MANE!
I DON'T HAVE PINK IN MY MANE,
PINKIE!
SO YOU'RE WEARING A WIG?
OW! CUT IT OUT!
PINKIE, REMEMBER?
YOU CHASED A PONY TO THE ENGINE
WHERE YOU THOUGHT YOU SAW THE
CONDUCTOR SHOVELING COAL, BUT
THAT WASN'T THE CONDUCTOR AT
ALL.
IT WAS...FLUTTERSHY!
[ GASP] OH, MY.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN,
FLUTTERSHY!
PINKIE!
BUT THEN ANOTHER CLUE CONFOUNDED
MY SUSPICIONS.
YOU WERE GUARDING THE CAKE WHEN
THE CURTAINS MYSTERIOUSLY
CLOSED.
BUT THAT'S NO MYSTERY, THAT'S
MAGIC.
BUT WHEN THE THIEF TRIED TO MAKE
THEIR GREAT ESCAPE...
[ CLANG ]
THEY LEFT A LITTLE ADDITION
TO THE PORTRAIT.
HAS ANYPONY ELSE NOTICED THAT
RARITY IS WEARING HER HAIR
RATHER DIFFERENTLY TODAY?
WHAT?
IS IT A CRIME TO CHANGE ONE'S
STYLE NOW AND AGAIN?
WHY, I THINK IT'S A CRIME NOT
TO.
REALLY?
FINE, I'M GUILTY!
I WEAR FALSE EYELASHES!
OH, AND I TOOK A BIT OF THE
CAKE.
SO DID I.
AW, NUTS! SO DID I.
YOU JUST MADE IT SOUND SO
DELECTABLE.
SO TASTY.
AND BOY, WAS IT!
I ONLY MEANT TO TAKE A LITTLE
LADYLIKE BITE.
BUT IT WAS SO GOOD.
YEAH, I JUST DOVE RIGHT IN!
BUT I'M REALLY, REALLY SORRY.
TERRIBLY SORRY.
SORRY, PINKIE.
THAT'S OKAY.
AT LEAST THIS MYSTERY IS FINALLY
SOLVED.
BUT IT ISN'T.
WE FIGURED OUT WHO ATE THE
MARZIPAN MASCARPONE MERINGUE
MADNESS, BUT WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHO DEVOURED THE OTHER BAKER'S
GOODS.
YOU'RE RIGHT, TWILIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE HAVE TO DO?
WELL, YES, I DO.
DO YOU?
LOOK FOR CLUES!
UH-HUH, UH-HUH, UH-HUH.
WELL, PINKIE, DID YOU FIND
THE DEVOURER OF THE DESSERTS?
I MOST CERTAINLY DID.
IT WAS NONE OTHER THAN...
THE BAKERS!
all: [ GASP ]
FIRST OF ALL, GUSTAVE HAS
MOUSSE IN HIS MOUSTACHE!
AND JOE HAS ECLAIR IN HIS HAIR!
AND MULIA HAS SPRINKLES IN HER
WRINKLES!
WHAT DO YOU SAY, BAKERS?
OH, AND I AM SO SORRY, MULIA.
BUT PINKIE MADE YOUR MOOSE
MOUSSE SOUND--[ SLURP ]-- TRES
MAGNIFIQUE.
AND PINKIE'S DESCRIPTION OF
YOUR ECLAIRS REALLY DID MAKE 'EM
SOUND SCRUMPTIOUS.
AND THE WAY SHE SPOKE OF YOUR
YOUR DONUTOPIA--[ GASP ]--
WAS TOO DELECTABLE TO RESIST.
WELL, EVERYPONY, WE FINALLY
HAVE THE MYSTERY SOLVED.
YES, BUT NOW WE DON'T HAVE
ANY DESSERTS TO ENTER INTO THE
CONTEST.
I THINK WE CAN FIX THAT.
COME ON!
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
TODAY I LEARNED THAT IT'S NOT
GOOD TO JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS.
YOU HAVE TO FIND OUT ALL THE
FACTS BEFORE SAYING SOMEPONY
DID SOMETHING.
IF YOU DON'T, YOU COULD END UP
BLAMING SOMEPONY FOR SOMETHING
THEY NEVER DID.
THIS COULD HURT THEIR FEELINGS,
AND IT COULD MAKE YOU LOOK
REALLY FOOLISH.
SO FROM NOW ON, I WILL ALWAYS
MAKE SURE TO GET ALL THE FACTS.
HOW'S THAT FOR A LESSON,
PRINCESS CELESTIA?
CARE FOR A BITE?
I DON'T MIND IF I DO.
[ ALL GIGGLING ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪