COME ON, FLUTTERSHY.
IT'LL BE FUN.
THERE'S NOTHING FUN ABOUT
DRAGONS.
SCARY, YES.
FUN, NO.
BUT, FLUTTERSHY, THE GREAT
DRAGON MIGRATION HAPPENS ONLY
ONCE IN A GENERATION.
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO PASS UP A
CHANCE LIKE THAT?
NOW THAT YOU PUT IT THAT WAY,
YES!
OH, FLUTTERSHY, WE JUST DON'T
WANT YOU TO MISS OUT.
MISS OUT ON WHAT?
DRAGONS?
BIG, SCARY, FIRE-BREATHING
WELL, YEAH.
DRAGONS?
THANKS, BUT NO THANKS.
WELL, YEAH.
[ GRUNTS ]
THANKS, BUT NO THANKS.
LOOK, FLUTTERSHY, I WATCHED THAT
[ GRUNTS ]
BORING BUTTERFLY MIGRATION WITH
LOOK, FLUTTERSHY, I WATCHED THAT
YOU.
BORING BUTTERFLY MIGRATION WITH
SO NOW IT'S YOUR TURN TO WATCH
YOU.
THE DRAGON MIGRATION WITH ME.
SO NOW IT'S YOUR TURN TO WATCH
YOU OWE ME.
THE DRAGON MIGRATION WITH ME.
I SAID...NO!
YOU OWE ME.
[ YELLS ]
I SAID...NO!
[ GROANS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GASPS ]
OKAY.
[ SCREAMS ]
I GUESS I'LL LET YOU OFF THE
OKAY.
HOOK THIS TIME.
I GUESS I'LL LET YOU OFF THE
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
HOOK THIS TIME.
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER WHAT
FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED ITS
MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART FAITHFUL
AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC MAKES IT ALL
COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL MY VERY
BEST FRIENDS? ♪
I DON'T SEE ANY DRAGONS.
ME NEITHER.
ME NEITHER, NEITHER.
SHOOT.
YOU DON'T THINK WE MISSED
THEM, DO YOU?
NO. I DON'T THINK SO.
WE'RE JUST A LITTLE EARLY.
AND I'M GLAD WE ARE.
THIS WAY, WE CAN WATCH EVERY
MOMENT OF THE MIGRATION WITHOUT
BRINGING ANY UNWANTED ATTENTION
TO OURSELVES.
YOO-HOO!
WELL?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
AM I THE TOAST OF THE TRENCH OR
WHAT?
YOU'LL BE TOAST, ALL RIGHT,
WHEN THE DRAGONS SEE YOU
PARADING AROUND IN THAT GETUP.
YOU LOOK VERY NICE, RARITY,
BUT COULD YOU MAYBE LOOK NICE
DOWN HERE IN THE TRENCH WITH US?
"NICE" IS AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
I LOOK FABULOUS!
WHO SAYS CAMOUFLAGE HAS TO BE
DRAB?
AHOY, MATEYS!
DRAGONS ROAM!
All: OOH!
AAH!
AMAZING.
PBHT. PRETTY LAME MOVE.
IS THAT ALL THEY GOT?
[ DRAGON ROARS ]
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT
MOVE, RAINBOW DASH?
STILL THINK THEY'RE LAME?
UH, NOT SO MUCH.
THE WORD "FIERCE" COMES TO MIND.
AND "FORMIDABLE."
AND "SUPER-DUPER SCARY."
YEAH.
US DRAGONS ARE DEFINITELY A
FORCE TO BE RECKONED WITH.
[ LAUGHS ]
YEAH, RIGHT, SPIKE!
THAT'S ONE OF THE SCARIEST
APRONS I'VE EVER SEEN!
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH WEARING AN
APRON?
YOU WON'T BE LAUGHING WHEN YOU
SPILL BLUEBERRIES ALL OVER YOUR
SCALES, UH, FEATHERS.
THAT'S ONE TOUGH STAIN.
ONE TOUGH STAIN AGAINST ONE
LAME DRAGON.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU LEAVE HIM ALONE,
RAINBOW DASH.
SPIKE'S STYLE IS UNIQUE.
HE DOESN'T HAVE TO LOOK LIKE
OTHER DRAGONS.
OR ACT LIKE THEM.
MY LITTLE SPIKEY-WIKEY IS
PERFECT THE WAY HE IS.
I DON'T ACT LIKE OTHER
DRAGONS?
OH, NOT EVEN CLOSE.
BUT WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO,
SPIKE?
YES.
YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING THOSE
DREADFULLY FIERCE DRAGONS CAN
ONLY DREAM OF.
WHAT'S THAT?
YOUR CUTEST, WITTLE CHUBBY
CHEEKS.
OOH!
CUTE?
DRAGONS AREN'T SUPPOSED TO BE
CUTE!
RIGHT?
OH, SWEETIE, YOU ARE TURNING
THE MOST DELIGHTFUL SHADE OF
RED.
IT IS MOST BECOMING.
[ GROWLS ]
[ BOING! ]
OH, ISN'T HE ADORABLE WHEN HE
WADDLES OFF IN ANGER?
"WADDLE"?! UGH!
WHAT AM I?
WHERE AM I FROM?
WHO AM I SUPPOSED TO BE?
UGH, I DON'T KNOW!
FOR THE LAST TIME, SPIKE, YOU
WERE GIVEN TO ME AS AN EGG.
I DON'T KNOW WHO FOUND YOU OR
WHERE THEY FOUND YOU.
SERIOUSLY?
THAT'S ALL YOU KNOW?
I'M SORRY, SPIKE.
THAT DOESN'T TELL ME ANYTHING
ABOUT WHO I AM.
I NEED ANSWERS!
I FEEL LIKE I'M...I'M LOOKING AT
A COMPLETE STRANGER.
[ GROANS ]
OH, SPIKE.
WHY DON'T WE DO SOME LATE-NIGHT
RESEARCH, SEE WHAT WE CAN FIND
OUT?
REALLY?
YOU'D DO THAT?
OF COURSE.
I'M SURE WE CAN FIND SOMETHING.
[ TINKLE! ]
NOTHING.
NOTHING IN THIS ONE, EITHER.
NOTHING AT ALL ABOUT DRAGONS?
THIS IS GETTING RIDICULOUS!
I KNOW.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE, BUT PONIES
KNOW NEXT TO NOTHING ABOUT
DRAGONS.
APPARENTLY THEY'RE TOO RARE AND
TOO SCARY TO TRY TO TALK TO OR
STUDY.
[ Voice breaking ] I WONDER
IF DRAGONS CRY.
OH, SPIKE.
IT'S OKAY, TWILIGHT.
I'M GONNA DISCOVER WHO I AM IF
IT'S THE LAST THING I DO!
HEY, GUYS!
AAH!
GOOD MORNING!
YOU WANT TO JOIN US FOR
BREAKFAST?
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I'M FAMISHED.
COUNT ME OUT.
I'VE GOT TO GET AN EARLY START.
AN EARLY START?
YES.
I'M GOING ON A QUEST OF
SELF-DISCOVERY.
I NEED TO LEARN WHAT IT MEANS TO
BE A DRAGON.
AND THE ONLY WAY I'M GONNA DO
THAT IS TO JOIN THE DRAGON
MIGRATION!
All: WHAT?!
SPIKE, THAT'S NONSENSE TALK!
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE A DRAGON, BUT
THOSE DRAGONS MEAN BUSINESS.
THEY'RE BIG AND TOUGH AND SCARY.
AND I'M SMALL AND MEEK AND I
LIKE TO WEAR APRONS.
SEE?
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY I NEED TO
SPEND TIME WITH THEM.
ALL I'M SAYING IS THAT YOU
COULD GET HURT.
DARLING, THIS TIME I REALLY
DO HAVE TO AGREE WITH
RAINBOW DASH.
I DON'T WANT THOSE BIG, UGLY,
NASTY DRAGONS TO HURT ONE LITTLE
SCALE ON YOUR CUTESY-WOOTSY
HEAD.
I'M SORRY, BUT I MADE UP MY
MIND.
OH! QUICK! DO SOMETHING!
STOP HIM BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
[ ZIP! ]
[ GRUNTING ]
HEY! GIVE IT BACK!
HOLD IT.
[ TINKLE! ]
WHOA!
AAH!
[ TINKLE! ]
REALLY?
DON'T TELL ME YOU THINK HE
SHOULD GO!
YES, SPIKE.
I COULDN'T ANSWER YOUR
QUESTIONS.
MY BOOKS COULDN'T, EITHER.
I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU WANT TO
LOOK ELSEWHERE.
I TRULY BELIEVE YOU NEED TO GO
ON THIS QUEST.
AND WE HAVE NO RIGHT TO STOP
YOU.
I SUPPOSE NOT.
I STILL SAY YOU'RE NUTTY,
BUT, HEY, I'VE DONE LOTS OF
NUTTY THINGS.
All: WE KNOW.
[ GROANS ]
WELL, THEN, I GUESS THIS IS
GOODBYE, SPIKE.
WE CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR ABOUT IT
WHEN YOU RETURN.
YEAH.
WE HOPE YOUR TRIP --
QUEST.
...YOUR QUEST ANSWERS SOME OF
YOUR PESKY "WHO AM I?"
QUESTIONS.
THANKS, EVERYPONY.
I KNOW IT WILL.
GOODBYE, SPIKEY-WIKEY!
GO GET 'EM, BIG GUY!
WE HAVE FAITH IN YOU!
WE'RE FOLLOWING HIM, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ DRAGON ROARS ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ZIP! ]
[ GULPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CHATTER ]
[ GULPS ]
ALL RIGHT.
[ CHATTER ]
TEENAGE DRAGONS.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, THAT'S MORE MY SPEED -- AND
TEENAGE DRAGONS.
SIZE.
NOW, THAT'S MORE MY SPEED -- AND
[ GRUNTING ]
SIZE.
I'M TELLING YOU, WE'LL NEVER
[ GRUNTING ]
PASS FOR A REAL DRAGON.
I'M TELLING YOU, WE'LL NEVER
OH, PISH POSH!
PASS FOR A REAL DRAGON.
THIS COSTUME IS FABULOUS, ONE OF
OH, PISH POSH!
MY FINER CREATIONS!
THIS COSTUME IS FABULOUS, ONE OF
SHH!
MY FINER CREATIONS!
WE'LL NEVER PASS IF THEY HEAR
SHH!
THREE VOICES COMING OUT OF ONE
WE'LL NEVER PASS IF THEY HEAR
DRAGON.
THREE VOICES COMING OUT OF ONE
NOW, COME ON. LET'S GO.
DRAGON.
[ CHEERING ]
NOW, COME ON. LET'S GO.
UM, EXCUSE ME?
[ CHEERING ]
UH, HI.
UM, EXCUSE ME?
I'M SPIKE.
UH, HI.
YOU SURE YOUR NAME IS SPIKE
I'M SPIKE.
AND NOT SHRIMP?
YOU SURE YOUR NAME IS SPIKE
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND NOT SHRIMP?
NO. IT'S SPIKE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
I-I MEAN, I'M SURE ABOUT THAT.
NO. IT'S SPIKE!
YOU LOOK MORE LIKE PEE-WEE TO
I-I MEAN, I'M SURE ABOUT THAT.
ME.
YOU LOOK MORE LIKE PEE-WEE TO
[ LAUGHTER ]
ME.
HEY, GUYS. COME ON.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SERIOUSLY.
HEY, GUYS. COME ON.
LEAVE HIM ALONE OR HE MIGHT FLY
SERIOUSLY.
AWAY.
LEAVE HIM ALONE OR HE MIGHT FLY
THAT IS, UH, IF HE HAD ANY
AWAY.
WINGS.
THAT IS, UH, IF HE HAD ANY
[ LAUGHTER ]
WINGS.
YOU FLYING ON YOUR MOMMY'S
[ LAUGHTER ]
BACK DURING THE MIGRATION?
YOU FLYING ON YOUR MOMMY'S
NOT EXACTLY.
BACK DURING THE MIGRATION?
NO, NO.
NOT EXACTLY.
CAN'T YOU SEE BABY SPIKE JUST
NO, NO.
HATCHED?
CAN'T YOU SEE BABY SPIKE JUST
I BET HE STILL SUCKS HIS CLAW AT
HATCHED?
NIGHT.
I BET HE STILL SUCKS HIS CLAW AT
NO, I HAVEN'T SUCKED MY CLAW
NIGHT.
IN MONTHS!
NO, I HAVEN'T SUCKED MY CLAW
[ LAUGHTER ]
IN MONTHS!
WELL, IF YOU WEREN'T JUST
[ LAUGHTER ]
HATCHED, HOW COME WE HAVEN'T SEE
WELL, IF YOU WEREN'T JUST
YOU AROUND BEFORE?
HATCHED, HOW COME WE HAVEN'T SEE
OH, WELL, YOU SEE, I LIVE IN
YOU AROUND BEFORE?
PONYVILLE, AND -- AND I'M --
OH, WELL, YOU SEE, I LIVE IN
PONYVILLE?
PONYVILLE, AND -- AND I'M --
[ Laughing ] THAT EXPLAINS IT!
PONYVILLE?
I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
[ Laughing ] THAT EXPLAINS IT!
VAGUELY PONYISH ABOUT YOU.
I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER, I'D
VAGUELY PONYISH ABOUT YOU.
SAY YOU WERE PART PONY.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER, I'D
WHO? ME?
SAY YOU WERE PART PONY.
I'M NOT PART PONY.
WHO? ME?
I'M ALL DRAGON. SEE?
I'M NOT PART PONY.
RAWR!
I'M ALL DRAGON. SEE?
OR MAYBE YOU'RE A PONY IN A
RAWR!
DRAGON COSTUME.
OR MAYBE YOU'RE A PONY IN A
[ LAUGHTER ]
DRAGON COSTUME.
A PONY IN A DRAGON COSTUME!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ LAUGHS ]
A PONY IN A DRAGON COSTUME!
[ NERVOUS CHUCKLE ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ Deep voice ] YEAH. HILARIOUS.
[ NERVOUS CHUCKLE ]
HA!
[ Deep voice ] YEAH. HILARIOUS.
I AM A REAL DRAGON!
HA!
OH, YEAH? PROVE IT.
I AM A REAL DRAGON!
WELL, HOW?
OH, YEAH? PROVE IT.
BY ACTING LIKE ONE.
WELL, HOW?
WHO'S UP FOR A LITTLE BELCHING
BY ACTING LIKE ONE.
CONTEST?
WHO'S UP FOR A LITTLE BELCHING
[ CHEERING ]
CONTEST?
[ BELCHES ]
[ CHEERING ]
[ HICCUPS ]
YOU THINK YOU COULD BEAT
THAT, PEE-WEE?
[ GULPS ]
[ GAGS ]
[ BURPS ]
All: HUH?
"FROM THE DESK OF
PRINCESS CELESTIA.
DEAR SPIKE, PLEASE TELL" --
[ CHUCKLES ] GET THIS, GUYS!
SPIKE'S PEN PAL'S WITH A
NAMBY-PAMBY PONY PRINCESS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ Normal voice ] [ GASPS ]
HOW CAN HE JUST THROW THAT AWAY?
THAT LETTER COULD BE SOMETHING
IMPORTANT.
WE CAN'T WORRY ABOUT THAT
NOW, TWILIGHT.
WE'RE HERE TO HELP SPIKE.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
THAT'S NO REASON TO DISRESPECT
PRINCESS CELESTIA THAT WAY.
MAYBE TAIL WRESTLING IS MORE
YOUR SPEED.
UH...
All: YEAH!
READY? GO!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
THE WINNER!
[ CHEERING ]
GOOD, OLD TAIL WRESTLING.
WE CAN'T LET LITTLE
SPIKEY-WIKEY WRESTLE ONE OF
THEM.
HE'LL GET CLOBBERED!
LET'S GO!
[ Deep voice ] I CHALLENGE SPIKE
TO A TAIL WRESTLE.
WHO'S THIS WEIRDO?
I THINK HE'S CRACKLE'S
COUSIN.
[ ROARS ]
OH. THAT WOULD EXPLAIN IT.
READY? GO!
[ GRUNTS ]
SPIKE'S THE WINNER!
[ CHEERING ]
NICE GOING, LITTLE SPIKE.
MAYBE YOU ARE A DRAGON AFTER
ALL.
YEAH! MAYBE I AM!
RAINBOW DASH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOUR SILLY PLAN ACTUALLY WORKED.
OW.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO'S NEXT?
GETTING A LITTLE COCKY, HUH?
I LIKE THAT.
SO, HOW ABOUT YOU WRESTLE...HIM?
GO!
[ SCREAMS ]
SO, SPIKE, YOU HAVEN'T
EXACTLY PROVEN YOURSELF AS A
DRAGON YET, HAVE YOU?
BUT I GET AN "A" FOR EFFORT?
UM, MAYBE.
LET'S SEE HOW YOU DO IN THIS
NEXT CONTEST.
AAH!
OH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
KING OF THE HOARD!
[ CHEERING ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
THIS IS MY CHANCE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NOT SO FAST!
[ GRUNTING CONTINUES ]
[ BOINK! ]
Both: AAH!
KING OF THE HOAR--
AAH!
OOH!
AH!
OW!
OH!
LOOKS LIKE THIS IS ANOTHER
FAIL FOR YOU, LITTLE SPIKE.
CAN'T WAIT TO WATCH YOU FAIL AT
LAVA CANNONBALL, TOO.
[ GULPS ]
WHOEVER MAKES THE BIGGEST
LAVA SPLASH IS THE ULTIMATE
DRAGON!
GERONIMO!
AH!
[ LAVA BUBBLING ]
[ Normal voice ] SPIKE'S ON
HIS OWN THIS TIME.
[ CHEERING ]
CANNONBALL!
[ CRASH! ]
AAH!
WHAT'S WRONG, SPIKE?
YOU AFRAID THE LAVA WILL HURT
YOUR SOFT PONY HIDE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GULPS ]
AAH!
[ SMACK! ]
All: OOH!
[ SIGHS ]
WAS I...THAT BAD?
NO. DUDE, THAT WAS AWESOME!
NO PONY COULD LIVE THROUGH A
BELLY FLOP LIKE THAT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE ONE TOUGH, LITTLE DRAGON.
WHOA!
AMAZING!
THAT WAS AMAZING!
[ SNORTS ]
SPIKE, BY BELLY-FLOPPING SO
HARD, YOU HAVE PROVEN YOURSELF
WORTHY.
I HEREBY DUB YOU ROOKIE DRAGON.
AND WE'LL NOW PERFORM THE
INITIATION RITUAL.
[ GROWLS, LAUGHS ]
NOW, LET'S PARTY DRAGON-STYLE!
[ CHEERING ]
[ DRAGON ROARS ]
MAN, WAS THAT A GREAT PARTY.
GREAT? HA.
MAYBE BY PONYVILLE STANDARDS.
STICK WITH US, SPIKE.
WE STILL GOT PLENTY TO TEACH YOU
ABOUT BEING A DRAGON.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
THE WAY I FEEL RIGHT NOW, I
COULD HANG OUT WITH YOU GUYS
FOREVER.
All: FOREVER?!
[ SIGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
SPIKEY-WIKEY IS GOING TO STAY
WITH THESE AWFUL DRAGONS
FOREVER?
OH, NO.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
I SHOULD HAVE STOPPED HIM
BACK AT THE LIBRARY WHEN I HAD
THE CHANCE.
NO, RAINBOW DASH.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I ENCOURAGED HIM TO GO.
YOU KNOW, SPIKE, I THINK YOU
JUST MIGHT BE READY FOR A REAL
DRAGON RAID.
[ CHEERING ]
THERE'S A NEST FULL OF PHOENIX
EGGS NEARBY, AND WE'RE GONNA
SWIPE THEM.
AREN'T YOU TOTALLY PSYCHED TO
GO ON THIS RAID?
[ SMACK! ]
OH, YEAH.
I'M EXCITED.
I MEAN, [Deep voice] I-I'M
PSYCHED.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S FLY!
[ Normal voice ] UH, SORRY,
GUYS!
I GUESS I'LL MEET YOU BACK HERE
AT THE CRATER!
AFTER THE RAID'S OVER, WE'LL
TOTALLY HANG THEN!
OH!
OH, NO! THEY TOOK SPIKE!
WE GOT TO GO AFTER THEM!
[ SCREAMS ]
RAINBOW DASH, STOP!
WE CAN'T FLY!
AND YOU'RE RUNNING MY
FABULOUS COSTUME!
I'M SORRY, BUT WE GOT TO HELP
SPIKE!
WELL, WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE
TO HOOF IT.
ALL RIGHT, SPIKE.
SINCE YOU'RE OUR ROOKIE DRAGON,
YOU GET TO LURE THE PARENTS AWAY
FROM THE NEST.
[ NERVOUS CHUCKLE ]
LUCKY ME.
WELL, GO ON, THEN.
HEY, MR. AND MRS. PHOENIX!
I WAS HOPING I COULD HAVE A WORD
WITH YOU!
UM, I'D, UM, LIKE TO ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS, ACTUALLY!
WE HAVEN'T GOT ALL DAY,
SPIKE.
HEY, YOU BIRD-BRAINS, COME
AND GET ME!
[ SQUAWKS ANGRILY ]
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
WHAT THE?
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
THE EGGS HAVE HATCHED.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE TAKE THE HATCHLINGS, OF
COURSE.
[ ALL SQUAWK ]
[ POP! POP! ]
[ POP! POP! POP! ]
[ ROARS ]
[ THUD! ]
PBHT!
GET THEM!
[ SHOUTING ]
[ ALL SQUAWKING ]
[ ROARS ]
HUH?
GET THEM!
[ SQUAWKS ]
AAH!
[ ALL GRUNT ]
UGH! THEY GOT AWAY!
I HATE THAT.
[ THUD! ]
WELL, WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
WHAT HAPPENED?
THEY GOT AWAY!
HEY. YOU STOLE AN EGG?
UH...
WELL, I GUESS THE RAID WASN'T
A TOTAL WASTE AFTER ALL.
[ CHEERING ]
NICE GOING, SPIKE.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR, SPIKE?
SMASH IT!
SMASH THE EGG?
YEAH!
THROW IT ON THE GROUND AS HARD
AS YOU CAN!
All: SMASH IT! SMASH IT!
SMASH IT! SMASH IT! SMASH IT!
NO!
IT'S JUST A DEFENSELESS EGG,
LIKE I WAS!
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU HURT
IT!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I SAID, "NO."
NO ONE SAYS "NO" TO ME.
[ GROWLS ]
NOPONY'S GONNA LAY A CLAW ON
HIM!
THAT'S RIGHT.
FIGHTING'S NOT REALLY MY
THING.
I'M MORE INTO FASHION.
BUT I'LL RIP YOU TO PIECES IF
YOU TOUCH ONE SCALE ON HIS CUTE,
LITTLE HEAD!
[ LAUGHTER ]
OOH, SCARY. [ CHUCKLES ]
SPIKE, ARE THESE NAMBY-PAMBY
PONIES YOUR FRIENDS?
YES, THEY ARE.
AND THEY'RE BETTER FRIENDS THAN
YOU COULD EVER BE.
NOW, IF YOU DON'T BACK OFF,
YOU'LL SEE WHAT US PONIES DO
WHEN CONFRONTED BY A HUGE GROUP
OF JERKY DRAGONS!
OH, YEAH?
[ GROWLS ]
WHAT'S THAT?
RUN AWAY!
[ GROWLS ]
[ TINKLE! ]
[ THUD! ]
AAH!
PHEW. THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
OF COURSE.
WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
YOU'RE MORE THAN FRIENDS.
YOU'RE MY FAMILY.
OOH!
"DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
SEEING THE GREAT DRAGON
MIGRATION MADE ME WONDER WHAT IT
MEANT TO BE A DRAGON.
BUT NOW I REALIZE THAT WHO I AM
IS NOT THE SAME AS WHAT I AM.
I MAY HAVE BEEN BORN A DRAGON,
BUT EQUESTRIA AND MY PONY
FRIENDS HAVE TAUGHT ME HOW TO BE
KIND, LOYAL, AND TRUE.
I'M PROUD TO CALL PONYVILLE MY
HOME AND TO HAVE MY PONY FRIENDS
AS MY FAMILY.
YOURS TRULY, SPIKE."
[ CRACKING ]
[ BIRD CHIRPS ]
AW. [ LAUGHS ]
HEY. WELCOME TO THE FAMILY,
PEE-WEE.
STICK WITH ME.
I'VE GOT PLENTY TO TEACH YOU
ABOUT BEING A PONY.
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪