[ TIMBER WOLVES HOWLING ]
[ BELLS CLANGING ]
[ CLANGING CONTINUES ]
Pony: THE TIMBER WOLVES
ARE A-HOWLING!
THE TIMBER WOLVES
[ HOWLING CONTINUES ]
YEP.
THE ZAP-APPLES ARE COMING!
All: YAY!
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
[ BELLS CLANG ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
HEY, SILLY GOOSE.
QUIT YOUR GAWKING
AND MOVE YOUR CABOOSE.
YEP.
READY, GRANNY.
READY FOR WHAT?
FOR MAKING ZAP-APPLE JAM.
DARN TOOTIN'!
IT'S TIME FOR SOME GOOD,
OLD-FASHIONED
ZAP-APPLE JAMMING.
YES, MA'AM.
I CAN'T WAIT, MA'AM.
WAIT FOR WHAT?
TO MAKE ZAP-APPLE JAM
WITH YOU.
OF COURSE.
NOW, I'VE BEEN DOING THIS EVER
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE PONY.
SO, BE WARNED, PICKLE-PEAR.
THERE'S A WHOLE MESS OF STEPS
IN THIS PROCESS.
AND YOU GOTS TO GET
EACH ONE OF THEM JUST RIGHT,
OR NO ZAP-APPLE JAM.
TAKE THIS.
UH, IS THIS ONE
OF YOUR GAZILLION
SECRET HERBAL INGREDIENTS
FOR THE ZAP-APPLE JAM?
THAT THERE'S A BROOM.
NOW, GET SWEEPING,
PIP-SQUEAK.
NOW, WHILE YOU SWEEP,
I'LL GET TO...
[ MUTTERS ]
OH, PONYFEATHERS.
I'D FORGET MY MANE IF IT WASN'T
ATTACHED TO MY HEAD.
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ SNIFFING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
[ ZAP! ]
THERE'S THE ZAP-APPLE LEAVES,
RIGHT ON SCHEDULE.
♪ A, B, C, D, E, F, G, ♪
♪ H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P ♪
[ LAUGHS ]
WELL, HOW DO YOU DO, THERE,
FILTHY RICH?
HELLO, MRS. SMITH.
DID I HEAR RIGHT --
THAT THERE'S A ZAP-APPLE HARVEST
COMING IN A FEW DAYS?
FOUR DAYS, TO BE EXACT.
EXCELLENT NEWS.
AND, AS USUAL,
I GET YOUR FIRST 100 JARS?
'COURSE, FILTHY.
UH, I PREFER RICH.
OH, AND HOW IS
YOUR PAPPY DOING?
OH, YOU POOR,
POOR THING --
HAVING TO MAKE
ALL THAT ZAP-APPLE JAM
WITH GRANNY SMITH.
[ GAGS ]
ACTUALLY, I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FORWARD
TO MAKING ZAP-APPLE JAM
FOR YEARS.
I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT THE JAM.
I'M TALKING
ABOUT GRANNY SMITH.
YOU MUST BE
SO EMBARRASSED.
[ Muffled ] WHO'S THERE?!
UH...WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU KNOW.
WITH ALL HER SILLY WAYS --
HOW SHE FORGETS THINGS
AND MAKES YOU WEAR
THESE RIDICULOUS COSTUMES.
GRANNY SAID
THAT THE WATER NEEDS --
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE HERE
ON THE FARM AND NOT IN TOWN,
WHERE EVERYPONY
COULD SEE YOU.
DON'T WORRY.
YOUR SECRET IS SAFE WITH ME.
[ ZIP! ]
SILLY WAYS?
[ CLANG! ]
THANK YOU KINDLY, FILTHY!
SHAKE A LEG THERE,
SLOWPOKE.
WE'VE GOT A GAGGLE'S WORTH
OF GOODS TO GATHER
BEFORE THE HARVEST.
COME ON.
♪ GONNA MAKE ZAP-APPLE JAM!
HOOPTY-HOO! ♪
♪ GATHERING MY GOODIES
AND HOOPTY-HOO! ♪
♪ SINGING AND DANCING!
YODELAY-HOO! ♪
♪ BLIPPITY BLUE,
MY DARLING ♪
THEY DON'T MAKE THEM
LIKE THEY USED TO.
[ CLANK! ]
Pony: HEY! YOU BITE IT,
YOU BUY IT.
[ GASP! ]
WHY, HELLO, BEE.
BEATRICE.
BEECHER.
OH, YOU'VE ALL BEEN BUSY
LITTLE BEES, HAVEN'T YOU?
ZZZZ! ZZZZ!
GRANNY.
ISN'T THERE A LESS...SILLY WAY
TO GET THE HONEY?
[ GASP! ]
OH, ISN'T THIS
JUST PRECIOUS?
PLEASE STOP.
AND IT IS PERFECT FOR MAKING
OUR ZAP-APPLE JAM.
SHH! STOP IT, GRANNY!
[ GIGGLING ]
GRANNY, PLEASE!
THOSE PONIES OVER THERE
ARE WATCHING ME.
WHAT? ARE THOSE FILLIES
YOUR FRIENDS?
HELLO,
HALF-PINT'S FRIENDS!
HI, GRANNY SMITH.
HI, HALF-PINT.
[ GIGGLING ]
WHAT DOLLS.
WHY, WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
PONIES DIDN'T COME THAT PURTY.
ARE WE DONE SHOPPING,
GRANNY?
'CAUSE I'D LIKE TO GET BACK
TO THE FARM -- FAST.
ALL DONE, SMELLY-BELLY.
♪ I GOT MY HONEY,
GOOEY-GOO! ♪
♪ GOT MY HONEY,
GOOEY-OO! ♪
YODELAY-OO! ♪
Rich: AND, BY CAPTURING
THE WHOLESALE MARKET,
PURCHASING IN BULK,
AND SLASHING OUR PRICES,
WE UNDERMINED EVERY OTHER
GIFT MARKET IN TOWN.
AND THAT'S HOW RICH'S
BARNYARD BARGAINS
BECAME THE CORNERSTONE
OF RETAIL IN PONYVILLE.
[ SNORING ]
[ CLAPPING ]
WELL, THANK YOU, MR. FILTHY --
I MEAN, MR. RICH.
WHAT A WONDERFUL DAY
OF SHARING.
AND THANK YOU FOR BEING A PART
OF FAMILY APPRECIATION DAY.
NOW, LET'S SEE WHO WILL BE
BRINGING IN A FAMILY MEMBER
FOR NEXT MONDAY'S
FAMILY APPRECIATION DAY.
UM...OH! APPLE BLOOM.
BUT, MISS CHEERILEE, MONDAY
IS ZAP-APPLE HARVEST DAY,
AND APPLEJACK AND BIG MACINTOSH
WILL BE TOO BUSY
TO COME AND SPEAK.
WELL, IS THERE ANYPONY ELSE
IN YOUR FAMILY THAT COULD?
MISS CHEERILEE, APPLE BLOOM'S
GRANNY SMITH
ISN'T WORKING HARVEST.
SHE COULD COME.
OH! BUT, UH, NO,
THAT WOULDN'T --
Cheerilee: THAT'S A SPLENDID
IDEA, DIAMOND TIARA.
APPLE BLOOM, YOU SHALL BRING IN
GRANNY SMITH ON MONDAY.
[ BELL RINGS ]
HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND,
EVERYPONY!
GRANNY SMITH!
COME MONDAY, I'LL BE
THE LAUGHINGSTOCK OF PONYVILLE!
[ CLUNK! ]
[ SIGHS ]
I'M SORRY, APPLE BLOOM.
I ALREADY TOLD YOU
THAT WE JUST CAN'T TAKE
A BREAK FROM HARVEST
TO COME TO YOUR SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW WHAT'LL HAPPEN.
I KNOW.
AFTER THE FIFTH DAY,
THE ZAP-APPLES DISAPPEAR.
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ CAWING ]
LOOK! THE THIRD SIGN!
RIGHT ON TIME!
HOT DIGGITY!
[ ZAP! ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
All: WOW!
ALL RIGHT, YOU LAZY DAISIES!
COOL YOUR CABOOSE!
I'M SORRY, APPLE BLOOM,
BUT DON'T YOU FRET.
GRANNY SMITH'S
GOT NO SHORTAGE
OF ENTERTAINING STORIES
TO TELL.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT.
I'LL BE EMBARRASSED.
SHAMED! DISGRACED!
MORTIFIED! HUMILIATED!
WHAT ARE YOU,
A DICTIONARY?
SNAP OUT OF IT.
WE'RE HERE TO HELP YOU.
AFTER ALL, WE ARE
THE CUTIE MARK CRUSADERS.
WE'LL FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO POSTPONE YOUR PRESENTATION.
[ GROANS ] BUT HOW?
OOH.
ALL THIS WORRY
IS MAKING ME SICK.
[ STOMACH RUMBLES ]
SICK?
THAT'S IT! COME ON.
[ ZIP! ]
FORWARD, HUT!
NOW, LISTEN HERE, TROOPS.
I DON'T COTTON TO ANY WHINING
OR CRYING OR CRACKING
UNDER PRESSURE.
DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR?
[ CRACK! ]
COURT-MARTIALED!
STAY STILL, APPLE BLOOM.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK SICK.
[ SPLAT! ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
AAH! HEY, THIS IS HOT!
WHAT IN THE HAYSEED IS GOING ON
IN THERE, SILLY BILLIES?
OH, GRANNY SMITH.
WE WERE JUST ABOUT
TO COME GET YOU.
APPLE BLOOM'S SICK.
LOOKS LIKE SHE MIGHT HAVE
TO STAY HOME ALL WEEK.
[ MUTTERING ]
PERFECT
AS A PICCADILLY PEAR.
NOW WHAT?
IT'S ALREADY ALMOST SUNDOWN!
TOMORROW IS SUNDAY,
AND I ONLY HAVE ONE MORE DAY
TO FIGURE SOMETHING OUT!
HEY! LOOK!
THAT'S THE FOURTH SIGN!
[ CLUNK! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
THE ZAP-APPLES
HAVE APPEARED!
AND THAT GIVES ME
AN IDEA.
WE CAN'T MOVE FAMILY
APPRECIATION DAY,
SO LET'S MOVE HARVEST DAY
INSTEAD.
Apple Bloom:
THEY DON'T LOOK...QUITE RIPE.
HARVESTING APPLES EARLY
NEVER HURT AN APPLE.
I DON'T KNOW.
ZAP-APPLE TREES AREN'T LIKE
NORMAL APPLE TREES.
THEY'RE MAGIC.
HOW DIFFERENT CAN THEY BE?
[ ZAP! ]
WELL, IF WE CAN'T BUCK 'EM,
LET'S JUST PICK 'EM.
[ BOING! ]
[ CHOMP! ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SPLAT! ]
ANY OTHER BRIGHT IDEAS?
GRANNY SMITH,
IT'S MISS CHEERILEE.
APPLE BLOOM SAID YOU WANTED
TO SPEAK WITH ME?
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
HELLO?
GRANNY SMITH -- OH!
WELL, HELLO, THERE!
HOW DO YOU DO?
UH, HI, GRANNY SMITH.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
OF COURSE IT IS.
WHY WOULDN'T IT BE?
[ SNORES ]
OH, EXCUSE ME.
PICKLES ALWAYS GIVE ME
THE HICCUPS.
I NEED TO TELL YOU
THAT I CAN'T MAKE THE
PRESENTATION ON MONDAY
AFTER ALL.
OH, NO. IS THAT SO?
NO DOUBTS ABOUT IT.
I GOT TO SHEAR THE FLOWERS
AND WATER THE SHEEP.
I MEAN...
I HAVE TO WATER THE FLOWERS
AND SHEAR THE SHEEP.
OH. WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD.
WE CAN RESCHEDULE.
[ BOING! CLUNK! ]
WHAT? HUH? WHERE AM I?
WELL, HOWDY, MISS CHEERILEE.
YOU WINDOW-SHOPPING?
UH, NO.
YOU ASKED ME TO COME HERE
TO TELL ME THAT
YOU WOULDN'T BE MAKING IT
TO FAMILY APPRECIATION DAY.
FIDDLESTICKS!
I WOULDN'T MISS IT
FOR ALL THE TEA IN CANTERLOT.
BUT DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY...
SEE YOU MONDAY!
[ APPLE BLOOM GROANS ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE WOKE UP
FROM HER NAP.
SHE NEVER WAKES UP
I WISH I COULD JUST RUN OFF
AND HIDE.
WELL, YOU CAN'T RUN OFF,
BUT MAYBE SOMEPONY ELSE CAN.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ ZAP! ]
YEEHAW!
THE ZAP-APPLE HARVEST
HAS BEGUN.
[ THUD! ]
AND TOMORROW, WE'LL BE MAKING UP
SOME ZAP-APPLE JAM.
[ KONK! ]
MISS GRANNY SMITH --
TELEGRAM.
[ ZIP! ]
WELL, BUST MY BUTTONS.
UNCLE APPLE STRUDEL WANTS ME
TO PAY HIM A VISIT.
AND YOU CAN JUST MAKE
THE 8:00 A.M. TRAIN.
I ALREADY PACKED YOU A BAG.
WELL,
THAT WAS CONSIDERATE.
BUT DON'T YOU WORRY,
FLIBBERTY GIBBERT.
I'LL BE BACK IN TIME
TO MAKE THAT JAM.
[ SIGHS ]
THAT TRAIN RIDE
TAKES ALL DAY.
I'M SAFE. HA.
Cheerilee: FOR TODAY'S
FAMILY APPRECIATION DAY,
WE ARE PLEASED TO WELCOME
GRANNY SMITH.
UM, APPLE BLOOM.
IS GRANNY SMITH HERE?
OH, I'M SORRY, MISS CHEERILEE,
BUT SHE GOT CALLED OUT OF TOWN
ON ACCOUNT
OF A FAMILY EMERGENCY.
WELL, HOWDY, MY LITTLE PONIES!
HOWDY, Y'ALL.
I'M AS HAPPY AS A PIG
IN A FRESH MUD PILE TO BE HERE.
WH-WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
DID YOU MISS THE TRAIN?
NO, IT CAME.
AND UNCLE APPLE STRUDEL
WAS ON IT.
OH! AH!
NOOGIE-NOOGIE-NOOGIE!
I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR
GRANNY SMITH'S PRESENTATION...
if she can remember
any of it.
[ GIGGLES ]
LONG AGO,
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE PONY,
THINGS WERE VERY DIFFERENT
HERE IN PONYVILLE,
'CAUSE THERE WAS NO PONYVILLE!
THAT'S RIGHT, MY LITTLE PONIES.
ME AND MY FAMILY
WERE PILGRIM PONYFOLK,
BACK WHEN I WAS A LITTLE FILLY.
OH, WE VENTURED FAR AND WIDE,
COLLECTING NEW SEEDS
AND SELLING OLD.
BUT MY PA WAS THE FINEST
SEED-COLLECTOR IN ALL EQUESTRIA.
THEN, ONE DAY, THE SMITH FAMILY
FOUND THEMSELVES
IN THE MOST BRILLIANT,
MOST GRAND, MOST MAGNIFICENT
OF ALL CITIES --
A PLACE CALLED CANTERLOT.
WHY, I'LL BET YOU
HOOVES TO HINDQUARTERS,
I HAD NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
IT BEFORE NOR SINCE.
AND, AS IF THE BEAUTY
OF THAT CITY WASN'T ENOUGH,
SUDDENLY SHE APPEARED --
PRINCESS CELESTIA,
THE MOST REGAL OF ALL HORSES.
WHEN, LO AND BEHOLD,
SHE STOPPED TO LOOK
AT MY PA'S SEED COLLECTION.
THEN, PRINCESS CELESTIA SAW
THAT WE WERE PLUMB TUCKERED
FROM THE HANKERING
TO FIND OUR FOREVER HOME.
SO, BEING THE ROYAL PRINCESS AND
ALL, SHE KNEW EXACTLY THE PLACE
FOR US TO LAY DOWN OUR STAKES.
MY PA GAVE THE PRINCESS
A MIGHTY THANKS.
WE QUICKLY FOUND THAT LAND
NEAR THE EVERFREE FOREST,
AND WE BUILT OUR FIRST HOME.
NEXT, WE PLANTED
OUR FIRST ORCHARD.
BUT AN ORCHARD
DON'T GROW OVERNIGHT,
AND WE WERE GETTING
MIGHTY SHORT ON FOOD.
NOW, MIND YOU, WE WERE CAUTIONED
ABOUT THE FOREST,
AND WE KNEW THAT
IT WAS NOT FIT TO ENTER.
[ TIMBER WOLVES HOWLING ]
BUT I KNEW IF THERE WAS CRITTERS
LIVING THERE,
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING TO EAT.
IT WAS DARK AND MUSTY, AND,
I WON'T LIE, IT WAS SCARY.
BUT EVERY INCH WAS COVERED
IN PLANT LIFE.
AND, BEFORE I KNEW IT,
WASN'T I STANDING IN FRONT OF
THE MOST INCREDIBLE APPLE TREES.
I HAD NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
THAT BORE THIS KIND
OF COLORFUL FRUIT.
I STARTED PICKING APPLES
QUICK AS A WHIP.
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ HOWLING CONTINUES ]
[ TIMBER WOLVES GROWLING ]
I TURNED, AND THERE BEFORE ME
STOOD...THE TIMBER WOLVES.
[ GROWLING ]
I'VE NEVER RUN SO FAST
IN MY LIFE!
[ GROWLING ]
I DID THE ONLY THING
I COULD THINK OF.
[ CLANGING ]
[ GROWLING ]
MY PA AND I PLANTED
THOSE SPECIAL APPLE SEEDS,
AND, BEFORE OUR EYES,
THEY GREW LIKE A WILDFIRE.
WHY, WE HAD FULL-GROWN TREES
FASTER THAN YOU COULD SAY
"LICKETY-SPLIT"!
THEN, EACH YEAR,
I PAID CLOSE ATTENTION
TO THE SIGNS OF THE ZAP-APPLES'
SPECIAL HARVESTING TIMES --
HOW THE WEATHER AFFECTS
THE EVERFREE FOREST,
HOW THE TIMBER WOLVES HOWL
WHEN THE ZAP-APPLES
FIRST START GROWING,
AND HOW THEY ZAPPED AWAY IF YOU
DIDN'T PICK THEM ALL IN ONE DAY!
AND THE FRUITS OF OUR LABOR WERE
THE BEST FRUIT WE EVER TASTED.
SOON ENOUGH, I WAS MIXING UP
BATCHES OF ZAP-APPLE JAM.
JUST LIKE HARVESTING
THE ZAP-APPLES
HAD ITS SPECIAL RULES,
SO DID MAKING ZAP-APPLE JAM.
I LEARNED THAT YOU GOT TO BE
EXTRA FRIENDLY WITH THE BEES.
OTHERWISE, THEIR HONEY
WON'T TASTE RIGHTLY SWEET
TO MIX IN WITH THE ZAP-APPLES.
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT THAT GLASS
JARS NEEDED TALKING TO...
OR THAT ZAP-APPLES
LIKE PINK POLKA DOTS?
BUT MAGIC IS AS MAGIC DOES --
JUST FUNNY THAT WAY.
THEN, PONIES STARTED COMING TO
OUR FARM FROM FAR AND WIDE
JUST TO GET A TASTE
OF MY ZAP-APPLE JAM.
SOME EVEN DECIDED TO STAY --
LIKE STINKIN' RICH,
DIAMOND TIARA'S
GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
MATTER OF FACT,
THE FIRST THING HE EVER SOLD
WAS MY ZAP-APPLE JAM.
AND, BEFORE WE KNEW IT, WE HAD
OURSELVES A NICE LITTLE TOWN,
BUSTLING WITH
ALL KINDS OF PONIES.
AND THAT IS HOW PONYVILLE
WAS FOUNDED.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OH, THANK YOU KINDLY,
LITTLE PONIES.
NOW, NOW, LET'S SETTLE DOWN.
SO, IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU
AND THE ZAP-APPLES,
PONYVILLE
WOULDN'T EVEN EXIST?
DARN TOOTIN', LITTLE FILLY.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR
MY GRANNY SMITH,
YOUR DADDY WOULDN'T HAVE
BARNYARD BARGAINS.
UH-HUH.
YEAH!
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
BUT...
BUT SHE'S JUST
A KOOKY OLD LADY!
[ ALL GASP ]
SHE IS NOT
A KOOKY OLD LADY!
SHE IS THE MOST AMAZING PONY
IN ALL OF PONYVILLE!
I THINK THIS IS THE BEST
ZAP-APPLE JAM I'VE TASTED YET.
MUST BE 'CAUSE YOU HAD SOMETHING
TO DO WITH IT, APPLE BLOOM.
YOU BETCHA!
APPLE BLOOM IS ONE HUMDINGER
OF A ZAP-APPLE JAMMER.
I AM?
SO, I TAKE IT FAMILY
APPRECIATION DAY WENT WELL?
DID IT!
MY GRANNY SMITH
IS SUPER-SPECIAL.
I JUST FORGOT THAT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
AW, DON'T FRET.
I FORGET THINGS ALL THE TIME.
NOW, I'LL GET YOU
[MUTTERS] SOMETHING.
AW.
WHO WANTS TO HELP GRANNY
SING TO THE WATER?
Together: WE DO! WE DO!
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
♪ A, B, C, D, E, F, G ♪
DIAMOND TIARA.
[ GROANS ] BUT, DAD!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪