Rainbow Dash: ATTENTION,
EVERYPONY. ATTENTION!
[ RAPS DESK ]
THE OFFICIAL RAINBOW DASH
FAN CLUB WILL COME TO ORDER.
LET'S GET RIGHT DOWN TO
OUR FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS.
I MOTION THAT RAINBOW DASH
BE DECLARED
THE MOST AWESOME PONY
IN PONYVILLE.
I SECOND THE MOTION!
AND MIGHT I ADD
THAT IF YOU LOOKED UP THE WORD
"AWESOME" IN THE DICTIONARY,
THERE WOULD BE A PICTURE
OF RAINBOW DASH?
YEAH!
[ LAUGHS ]
I OBJECT.
[ ALL GASP ]
I THINK THE WORD "AWESOME"
IS PLAYED OUT.
RAINBOW DASH
DESERVES BETTER.
I MOTION THAT WE DECLARE HER
THE MOST STUPENDOUS PONY.
STUPENDOUS?
IS THAT THE BEST YOU GOT?
I MOTION THAT WE DECLARE HER
WONDERIFIC.
ASTONISHING.
BREATHTAKING.
ASTOUNDING.
BEDAZZLING.
Pony: WHAT ABOUT SUPER-ULTRA
EXTREMAWESOMAZING?
YEAH.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
ALL IN FAVOR OF DECLARING
RAINBOW DASH
THE MOST SUPER-ULTRA EXTRA--
UH, WHATEVER YOU SAID --
PONY IN ALL OF PONYVILLE,
SAY, "AYE."
AYE!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE A DIP
IN THE CLOUDS
TO MAKE A PEGASUS
FEEL SUPER RELAXED.
Pony:
[ Echoing ] HELP! HELP!
HELP! HELP!
LOOKS LIKE MY SKY SWIM
WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
I'M RAINBOW DASH,
AND I'M HERE TO RESCUE YOU.
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
WOW.
WHAT'S WITH THIS CROWD?
UH, THANKS, EVERYPONY.
IT WAS REALLY NO BIG DEAL.
TO ME, IT WAS.
YOU'RE MY HERO,
RAINBOW DASH.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
THAT RAINBOW DASH
SURE IS SOMETHING.
Both: SOMETHING SPECIAL.
[ SCREAMS ]
[ BABY CRYING ]
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
[ SCREECH! ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THE BABY!
[ ALL GASP ]
SHE'S NOT CHEERING FOR
EVERYPONY'S FAVORITE HERO,
RAINBOW DASH!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
THERE JUST AREN'T ENOUGH WORDS
IN THE DICTIONARY
TO DESCRIBE RAINBOW DASH'S
AWESOMENESS.
I CAN THINK
OF A FEW NEW WORDS.
AND I BET "MODEST"
IS NOT ONE OF THEM.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
NO, BUT SHE IS
KIND OF AWESOME.
[ WOOD CRACKING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
Rainbow Dash: NEVER FEAR --
YOUR FRIENDLY NEIGHBORHOOD
RAINBOW DASH IS HERE!
[ PONIES SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMING STOPS ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
WE'D BE LOST WITHOUT YOU!
YOU'RE A HERO,
RAINBOW DASH.
[ Chanting ] RAINBOW DASH!
RAINBOW DASH!
[ Singsong voice ]
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
Crowd: [ Chanting louder ]
RAINBOW DASH! RAINBOW DASH!
RAINBOW DASH!
CALL ME SILLY, BUT I THINK
THIS WHOLE HERO THING
MIGHT BE GOING
TO RAINBOW DASH'S HEAD.
YOU MAY BE RIGHT...
SILLY.
Rainbow Dash:
AND THEN I ZOOMED INTO THE WELL.
I KNEW IT WOULD BE
DARK AND DANGEROUS,
BUT I DIDN'T LET THAT STOP ME.
DANGER'S MY MIDDLE NAME --
RAINBOW DANGER DASH.
THINKING BACK ON IT,
I ACTED PRETTY AWESOMELY HEROIC
THAT DAY.
"...THAT DAY."
AWESOMELY HEROIC THAT DAY
AND AWESOMELY ARROGANT
EVER SINCE.
Both: MM-HMM.
HEY, APPLEJACK,
HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE TO BE IMMORTALIZED
AS MY FRIEND?
IMMORTA-WHAT?
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
[ SCRIBBLING ]
ARE YOU TAKING
YEP. I'VE BEEN HOOF-PICKED
BY RAINBOW DASH HERSELF
TO WRITE HER AUTOBIOGRAPHY.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
UM, AUTOBIOGRAPHIES
ARE SUPPOSED TO BE WRITTEN
BY THE PONY THEY ARE ABOUT.
MAYBE FOR YOUR NORMAL,
RUN-OF-THE-MILL PONIES,
BUT I'M FAR TOO BUSY
SAVING LIVES TO STOP AND WRITE.
THAT'S WHY I HIRED SPIKE
AS MY GHOST WRITER.
[ SCREAMS ]
SPIKE'S A GHOST!
[ ZIP! ]
ANYWAY, SPIKE, HERE,
WRITES DOWN EVERYTHING I SAY,
DON'T YOU, SPIKE?
"...DON'T YOU, SPIKE?"
GOT IT.
THIS WAY, I CAN STAY FOCUSED ON
PERFORMING THOSE ACTS OF BRAVERY
THAT NOPONY ELSE
HAS THE GUTS TO PERFORM.
YEAH. TAKES GUTS.
BUT IT ALSO TAKES BRAINS.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
AND SOMETIMES,
A BIG LUNCH AND A NAP.
BEING A HERO IS SURELY
NOT FOR EVERYPONY,
BUT I'M UP TO THE CHALLENGE.
AH. THERE YOU GO.
SOMEDAY, I WANT TO BE
JUST LIKE YOU.
AIM HIGH, KID, BUT DON'T AIM
FOR THE IMPOSSIBLE.
[ PONY SCREAMS ]
[ CROWD GASPS ]
HELP! HELP!
UH, DON'T YOU THINK
YOU SHOULD GO AND HELP?
YEAH, YEAH.
I'VE GOT A GOOD 10 SECONDS
TO SPARE.
JUST A COUPLE MORE.
Spike:
THE TENSION IS UNBEARABLE.
WILL RAINBOW DASH
MAKE IT ON TIME?
[ THUD ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
Pony: HOLY TURNIPS!
THAT PONY CAME OUT OF NOWHERE!
I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH BRAVERY
IN ALL MY LIFE!
THAT'S RIGHT.
PONYVILLE HAS A NEW HERO --
A MYSTERIOUS MARE THAT HAS DONE
WELL BY OUR FAIR CITY TODAY.
I DUB THIS NEW MASKED HERO
THE MYSTERIOUS MARE DO WELL!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
MARE DO WELL, HUH?
WELL, THAT MARE WOULD DO WELL
TO STAY OUT OF MY WAY.
PONYVILLE'S ONLY GOT ROOM FOR
ONE HERO, AND THAT HERO IS ME.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
NEVER FEAR -- YOUR FRIENDLY
NEIGHBORHOOD RAINBOW --
EXCUSE ME.
UH, DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
SKIP YOUR CATCHPHRASE
AND JUST HURRY UP
AND SAVE US?
UGH. FINE.
PICKY, PICKY.
[ SCREECH! ]
WHOA!
WHOA! AAH!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
MWAH! MWAH! MWAH!
OH, THANK YOU, MARE DO W--
HUH?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
MARE DO WELL
IS STRONGER THAN ME?
WELL, A HERO
IS MORE THAN JUST MUSCLE.
SHE'S GONNA LEARN THAT
THE HARD WAY.
[ MACHINERY WHIRS ]
[ LEVER GRINDS ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
HUH?
NEVER FEAR -- YOUR FRIENDLY
NEIGHBOR-- WHOA!
NEVER FEAR -- AAH!
I'M COMING!
HOLD ON!
[ SCREAMS ]
LOOK!
YAY!
AAH!
LOOK OUT FOR THE --
WATCH OUT FOR FALLING --
AAH!
ON YOUR LEFT.
YOUR OTHER LEFT!
HERE YOU GO.
SAFE AND SOUND.
[ CREAKING ]
OH!
WELL, MARE DO WELL.
OR SHOULD I CALL YOU
MARE DO SLOW?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
PICK UP THE PACE
IF YOU WANT TO COMPETE WITH ME,
'CAUSE I MOVE LIKE LIGHTNING.
ACTUALLY,
SHE SAVED ALL OF US.
WE OWE HER OUR LIVES.
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
[ GROWLS ]
OKAY.
SHE'S STRONG, FAST,
AND SOMEHOW KNOWS WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN AHEAD OF TIME.
I'VE GOT TO STEP UP MY GAME.
[ GASPS ]
IF THE DAM BREAKS,
THE WHOLE TOWN WILL BE FLOODED!
LOOKS LIKE PONYVILLE
NEEDS A HERO.
EASY PEASY.
MY GAME IS OFFICIALLY BACK ON.
IF ONLY SOMEPONY WERE HERE
TO PAT ME ON THE BACK.
GUESS I'LL HAVE TO DO IT MYSELF.
[ RUMBLING ]
AAH! OH!
HELP! HELP!
HELP!
YOU?
HA.
I SUPPOSE YOU WANT ME
TO THANK --
[ TINKLING ]
YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING ME.
[ TINKLING ]
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT --
SHE'S STRONG, SHE'S AGILE,
AND SHE'S MAGIC?
UGGGH!
[ THUD ]
HOW DO I COMPETE WITH THAT?!
WAIT A MINUTE.
I DO HAVE A LEG UP ON HER.
AND THAT LEG IS...
WINGS!
HA!
TAKE THAT, MARE DO WELL.
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
OH, FOR THE LOVE OF PETE.
Applejack:
GOT TO HAND IT TO THE GIRL.
THAT MARE DO WELL SURE CAN PULL
OFF SOME PRETTY HEROIC FEATS.
I MUST SAY, I WAS IMPRESSED
BY THAT SPELL SHE USED
TO FIX THE DAM.
SEEMS LIKE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
WOULD TAKE QUITE
A BIT OF STUDY.
[ GROWLS ]
SHE REALLY CARES
ABOUT EVERYPONY'S SAFETY.
HAVE YOU SEEN HER COSTUME?
IT'S TO DIE FOR.
IF YOU ASK ME,
SHE'S A HERO OF FASHION.
AND SHE'S MODEST
AND HUMBLE.
SHE LETS HER ACTIONS SPEAK
FOR THEMSELVES.
YOU GOT TO ADMIRE THAT.
I DON'T HAVE TO ADMIRE THAT!
I DON'T THINK
SHE'S ALL THAT GREAT!
"SHE'S GREAT."
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
Twilight Sparkle: SOUNDS LIKE
SOMEPONY'S JEALOUS.
WHO, ME?
"RAINBOW DASH IS JEALOUS."
DON'T WRITE THAT, SPIKE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
CORRECTION -- "RAINBOW DASH
IS VERY JEALOUS."
FINE!
LAUGH ALL YOU WANT.
BUT I'LL BE THE ONE LAUGHING
WHEN I PROVE TO YOU ALL
THAT I'M JUST AS GOOD --
NO, THAT I'M A BETTER HERO
THAN MARE DO WELL.
UGH.
NO SIGN OF TROUBLE HERE.
DARN IT.
BUSES AND BABY CARRIAGES ARE
ALWAYS CAREENING DOWN THIS HILL.
WHERE IS AN OUT-OF-CONTROL
VEHICLE WHEN YOU NEED ONE?
[ GROANS ]
THERE ARE ABSOLUTELY
NO FREAK NATURAL DISASTERS
GOING ON ANYWHERE.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
PROVE MYSELF
WHEN EVERYTHING'S
SO NORMAL AND SAFE?
[ GASPS ]
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
GRANNY SMITH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PRETEND
WITH ME.
I CAN SEE THAT YOU'RE IN
WAY OVER YOUR HEAD HERE.
YES.
WHAT'S THAT?
YOU'RE PUTTING ON
A BRAVE FACE.
I GET IT.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
ANYMORE.
I'LL HELP YOU
CROSS THE STREET.
[ GRUNTS ]
ACTUALLY, I CAN CROSS
THE STREET JUST FINE.
[ Strained ] DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE IN EXTREMELY...
CAPABLE...HOOVES.
[ GRUNTS ]
OH!
BACK OFF.
[ PANTS ]
HERE WE ARE.
SAFE AND SOUND.
A GOOD AND HEROIC CITIZEN
DESERVES A LITTLE RECOGNITION,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I DIDN'T WANT TO CROSS
THE STREET IN THE FIRST PLACE!
[ MUTTERING ]
[ GRUNTING IN DISTANCE ]
[ GASPS ]
SOMEPONY'S IN TROUBLE.
UGH!
[ TINKLING ]
YOU'D BETTER LET ME
HANDLE THIS, MA'AM.
FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY, I MUST
ASK YOU TO STAND BACK.
OH, BROTHER.
[ CRACK! CRACK! ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ TINKLING ]
TA-DA!
UH, THANKS.
HOW WOULD YOU DESCRIBE
WHAT I JUST DID?
WOULD YOU SAY
I WAS AMAZING?
AREN'T YOU MILKING THIS
A BIT?
PLEASE JUST ANSWER
THE QUESTION.
WAS I
OR WAS I NOT AMAZING?
OH, YOU'RE AMAZING,
ALL RIGHT.
AN AMAZINGLY --
OH, LOOK!
ANOTHER GREAT FEAT OF HEROISM!
I HAVE JUST SAVED THAT GRASS.
FROM WHAT?
FROM WEEDS --
WEEDS THAT WERE ATTEMPTING
TO EAT THIS LAWN.
LAME.
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
WHATEVER.
OH, WHO AM I KIDDING?
ALL ANYPONY TALKS ABOUT
IS MARE DO WELL THIS
AND MARE DO WELL THAT.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
HOW COULD EVERYPONY FORGET
ABOUT ME SO EASILY?
I MEAN, HAVE I CHANGED?
SAME SLEEK BODY.
SAME FLOWING MANE.
SAME SPECTACULAR HOOVES.
NOPE. I'M STILL AWESOME.
THEY'RE WRONG.
BUT THEN WHY AM I ALL ALONE?
I HATE BEING ALL ALONE.
HEY, RAINBOW DASH!
I KNEW IT!
NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE,
SQUIRT.
ANYPONY CAN MAKE A MISTAKE.
MISTAKE?
WHAT MISTAKE?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
TO INVITE YOU
TO JOIN US.
WE'RE HEADING OFF
TO THE THANK-YOU PARADE
FOR PONYVILLE'S GREATEST HERO,
MARE DO WELL.
NO! NO WAY!
CAN'T YOU SEE
I-I WANT TO BE ALONE?
I LOVE BEING ALONE.
OH, OKAY.
SEE YOU LATER, THEN.
YEAH, RIGHT.
LIKE I'M GONNA THANK HER.
THANK YOU, MARE DO WELL --
WHOEVER YOU ARE --
FOR RUINING EV--
HEY, SQUIRT!
WAIT UP!
[ RAPS PODIUM ]
WELCOME TO PONYVILLE'S FIRST,
BUT SURELY NOT LAST,
THANK-YOU PARADE IN HONOR
OF OUR CITY'S GREATEST HERO,
THE MYSTERIOUS...
MARE DO WELL!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
THE MYSTERIOUS
MARE DO WELL, HUH?
[ ALL GASP ]
SO, WHAT ARE YOU HIDING?
LET'S SEE HOW MYSTERIOUS YOU ARE
WITHOUT THAT MASK.
[ CHOMP! ]
[ MARE DO WELL WHISTLES ]
WHAT THE HAY?
[ WHISTLES ]
[ GROWLS ]
I GOT YOU NOW.
[ CRASH! ]
ALL RIGHT, MISS MYSTERIOUS,
MYSTERY...
...SOLVED!
AAH!
P-P-P-PINKIE?
WHAT D-D-D-- HUH?
TWILIGHT?
APPLEJACK?
THERE WERE THREE OF YOU?
YEP. WE ALL PLAYED MARE DO WELL
AT DIFFERENT TIMES.
I STOPPED THE CARRIAGE BUS
WITH THESE BABIES --
BUCKY McGILLICUDDY
AND KICKS McGEE.
I SAVED THE CONSTRUCTION WORKERS
WITH MY PINKIE SENSE.
[ RATTLING ]
SORRY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
AND I USED MY MAGIC
TO FIX THE DAM.
OOH! OOH!
AND I DID
THE FLY-BY AFTERWARDS.
I MADE THE COSTUMES.
FABULOUS,
IF I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY? DON'T YOU WANT ME
TO BE A HERO?
OF COURSE WE WANT YOU
TO BE A HERO.
BUT A REAL HERO
DOESN'T BRAG.
UH, I GUESS I DID START
TO BRAG A LITTLE.
All: A LITTLE?!
OKAY, A LOT.
CELEBRATING YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENTS
IS NATURAL, BUT...
RUBBING THEM
IN EVERYPONY'S FACE IS NOT.
YEAH.
THE ONLY THING THAT SHOULD BE
RUBBED IN ANYPONY'S FACE
IS CHOCOLATE CAKE.
[ SLURPING ]
I THINK WE'RE GETTING
OFF-TOPIC HERE.
WHAT WE'RE TRYING TO SAY
IS IT'S GREAT TO BE REALLY GOOD
AT SOMETHING,
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT TO ACT
WITH GRACE AND HUMILITY.
OH!
THAT MAKES LOADS MORE SENSE.
YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND I GUESS I SHOULD ALSO ACT
WITH GRACE AND HUMILITY
WHEN OTHERS OUTSHINE ME...
LIKE MARE DO WELL.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
A LETTER TO WRITE
TO PRINCESS CELESTIA.
ALREADY GOT IT COVERED.
AS YOUR GHOST WRITER,
I'VE ALREADY PENNED A LETTER
TO THE PRINCESS.
THAT'S NICE OF YOU, SPIKE,
BUT I REALLY WANT TO WRITE
THIS LETTER MYSELF.
AW, COME ON.
I WROTE
THE WHOLE THING ALREADY.
OKAY.
LET'S HEAR IT.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
"DEAR PRINCESS CEL--"
LOOK OUT!
IT'S A REAL GHOST!
AAH!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ TINKLING ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪