[ TINKLING ]
NO DISTRACTIONS.
TODAY IS TOO IMPORTANT.
[ TINKLING ]
RESHELVING DAY.
"UNDERSTANDING
MEDIEVAL EQUESTRIA"
GOES IN...PONY HISTORY.
"MODERN SPELL CASTING."
THAT'S CLASSICS.
"THE ART OF THE TO-DO LIST."
ACTUALLY, I KIND OF WANT
TO READ THAT AGAIN.
Spike:
[ LAUGHING ]
SPIKE,
WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT?
THIS LITTLE BEAUTY IS
MY BIRTHDAY PRESENT TO MYSELF.
IT'S A FIRE RUBY!
I'VE BEEN AGING IT FOR MONTHS,
AND IT'S ALMOST RIPE!
[ TONE RESONATING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ ZING! ]
[ THUD! CLINK! ]
HEY,
YOU TOOK MY ADVICE!
JUST USE THE WHOLE FLOOR
AS ONE BIG SHELF!
[ GROANS ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ AH-AH-AH-AH ♪
♪ I USED TO WONDER
WHAT FRIENDSHIP COULD BE ♪
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU ALL SHARED
ITS MAGIC WITH ME ♪
♪ BIG ADVENTURE ♪
♪ TONS OF FUN ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HEART
FAITHFUL AND STRONG ♪
♪ SHARING KINDNESS ♪
♪ IT'S AN EASY FEAT ♪
♪ AND MAGIC
MAKES IT ALL COMPLETE ♪
♪ YEAH, MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALL
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS? ♪
HELLO!
ANYPONY HOME?
TWILIGHT?
[ GASPS ]
IS THAT A FIRE RUBY?
OH! THAT MUST BE
AT LEAST 20 CARATS.
NO INCLUSIONS,
PRISTINE FACETS.
AND TOTALLY DELICIOUS.
UH, YOU GUYS DON'T MIND?
OH, UH, OF COURSE.
I-I JUST CAME BY
TO SEE IF YOU HAD ANY BOOKS
ON HISTORICAL FASHION.
DID YOU SAY
"DELICIOUS"?
SURE DID!
NEXT WEEK'S MY BIRTHDAY,
AND THIS IS
MY BIRTHDAY DINNER.
[ TINKLING ]
START WITH THIS ONE.
THANKS, TWILIGHT.
I'VE GOT A FEELING
RUFFLED TAFFETA CAPES
ARE GOING TO MAKE
A HUGE COMEBACK THIS SEASON,
AND I WANT TO BE
AHEAD OF THE GAME.
[ CRUNCH! ]
Rarity: I HOPE IT'S AS TASTY
AS IT IS BEAUTIFUL, SPIKE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
QUITE SO STUNNING BEFORE.
GOSH,
YOU REALLY LIKE IT, HUH?
LIKE IT?
IT'S MAGNIFICENT.
[ SIGHS ]
THEN YOU SHOULD HAVE IT.
THIS BEAUTIFUL GEM
WAS MEANT TO BE WITH YOU.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
THIS IS SO THOUGHTFUL.
OH, MY LITTLE
SPIKEY-WIKEY.
MWAH!
[ SLOOP! THUD! ]
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
WOW, SPIKE.
THAT'S ONE OF THE KINDEST,
MOST GENEROUS THINGS
YOU'VE EVER DONE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN RARITY
SO HAPPY.
I WILL NEVER WASH
THIS CHEEK AGAIN.
[ SIGHS, CHUCKLES ]
[ TINKLING ]
JUST ABOUT FINISHED,
SPIKE?
EVERYPONY
WILL BE HERE SOON.
THERE. PERFECT!
EVERYTHING
LOOKS PERFECT!
NOT QUITE EVERYTHING.
A WASHCLOTH?
I DON'T GET IT.
AH, NO WAY, TWILIGHT!
I SAID I WASN'T GONNA WASH
THE CHEEK THAT RARITY KISSED,
AND I MEANT IT!
[ TINKLING ]
IT'S OVER, SPIKE!
I'M CLEANING THAT CHEEK!
AAH!
AAH! AAH! AAH!
IT'S MINE!
STOP IT!
NEVER!
TWILIGHT!
[ PARTY HORN BLOWS ]
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
[ TINKLING ]
PARTY TIME!
WHOO-HOO!
ARE THOSE...FOR ME?
YOU BET THEY ARE,
BIRTHDAY BOY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SPIKE.
[ THUD! ]
DON'T YOU KNOW YOU GET PRESENTS
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY?
WELL, ACTUALLY, THIS IS
MY FIRST BIRTHDAY IN PONYVILLE.
I USUALLY JUST GET
ONE PRESENT...
FROM TWILIGHT --
A BOOK.
[ TINKLING ]
[ SHEEP BLEATS ]
SPEAKING OF PRESENTS,
THIS IS FROM MY NEW LINE
OF TAFFETA CAPES.
I'M GOING TO MAKE ONE
FOR EACH OF YOU.
WOW! WOW! WOW!
THAT'S GREAT!
I'VE BEEN INSPIRED
BY THE GENEROSITY
OF MY LITTLE SPIKEY-WIKEY,
WHO GAVE ME
THIS BEAUTIFUL FIRE RUBY,
ONE OF THE KINDEST ACTS
I EVER EXPERIENCED.
MM.
APPLEJACK, I CAN'T THANK YOU
ENOUGH FOR THIS GREAT BLANKET.
I REALLY NEEDED A NEW ONE.
COME ON, SPIKE.
YOU ALREADY THANKED ME 15 TIMES.
I'M STARTING TO GET
A LITTLE EMBARRASSED.
I KNOW I KEEP THANKING YOU GUYS,
BUT I'M JUST SO GRATEFUL.
I WISH THIS PARTY
COULD LAST FOREVER.
DUH!
THE PARTY
CAN'T LAST FOREVER,
'CAUSE YOU HAVE TO GO
TO SUGARCUBE CORNER
'CAUSE THE CAKES SAID THEY
HAVE A SPECIAL SURPRISE FOR YOU
'CAUSE
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY!
NO WAY!
[ ZIP! ]
I SAID
THE PARTY COULDN'T LAST FOREVER,
BUT IT DOESN'T NEED
TO END RIGHT NOW!
HI, MR. AND MRS. CAKE!
THERE'S THE DRAGON
OF THE HOUR!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
SPIKE!
THANKS.
WHEN WE FOUND OUT
IT WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY,
WE COULDN'T RESIST TRYING OUT
A NEW RECIPE --
SAPPHIRE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WOW!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
MAN, FIRST I GET
A BUNCH OF GREAT PRESENTS
FROM MY BEST FRIENDS,
AND NOW AN AMAZING
SAPPHIRE CUPCAKE!
OH, WHAT A DAY!
OH!
[ BOING! ]
[ RATTLE! ]
OH, MY GOSH!
I'M SO SORRY, CHEERILEE.
THAT'S OKAY.
WHAT'S GOT YOU SO EXCITED?
[ Muffled ]
PINKIE PIE TOLD ME
I SHOULD
COME SEE THE CAKES
SO THEY COULD GIVE ME A TREAT
'CAUSE IT'S MY BIRTHDAY TODAY.
WELL,
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SPIKE!
I WISH I HAD SOMETHING
TO GIVE YOU.
UH...OH!
HERE YOU GO.
WOW, REALLY?
SURE.
EVERYPONY SHOULD GET FUN GIFTS
ON THEIR BIRTHDAY.
HAVE A GREAT BIRTHDAY,
SPIKE.
I WISH EVERY DAY
WAS MY BIRTHDAY.
PINKIE PIE MENTIONS MY BIRTHDAY
TO THE CAKES,
AND I GET A CUPCAKE.
I MENTION IT TO CHEERILEE,
AND I GET THIS GREAT HAT.
[ SQUEAKING ]
[ SCREECH! ]
HMM, I WONDER.
HEY, THERE,
LICKETY-SPLIT!
THAT'S A PRETTY COOL BALL
YOU GOT THERE.
DID YOU KNOW
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY?
[ CHUCKLES ]
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
HEY, JUNEBUG!
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY!
[ CREAK! CREAK! ]
UH, HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
SPIKE!
WELL, AREN'T YOU GONNA
GIVE ME SOMETHING?
YOU KNOW,
LIKE A BIRTHDAY PRESENT?
UM, I-I DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING.
WELL, HOW ABOUT THOSE FLOWERS?
I'LL TAKE THOSE.
Twilight:
SPIKE!
[ TINKLING ]
UH, SORRY, JUNEBUG.
I THINK SPIKE MIGHT HAVE
GOTTEN A LITTLE CARRIED AWAY.
UH, NO PROBLEM.
UH, HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
SPIKE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE OUT HERE
DEMANDING GIFTS NOW?
WOW. YOU'RE RIGHT,
TWILIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT GOT INTO ME.
THANKS FOR SNAPPING ME
OUT OF IT.
I BETTER GO GIVE CHEERILEE
HER HAT BACK.
NO PROBLEM.
SEE YOU AT HOME LATER?
SOUNDS GOOD!
BYE!
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
WHO ELSE HAS A PRESENT
FOR SPIKEY-WIKEY?
[ HISSES ]
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
WOW. WHAT A ROUGH
NIGHT'S SLEEP, SPIKE.
[ Chuckling ]
I HAD THE WEIRDEST DRE--
Spike:
[ SNORING ]
MM, YEAH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU!
WHERE DID YOU
GET ALL THIS --
[ GASPS ]
[ CLATTER! ]
[ YAWNS ]
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME,
TWILIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW.
THINK BACK TO LAST NIGHT.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
[ CREAK! CREAK! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
SPIKE?
WHAT DID YOU DO
AFTER I SAW YOU?
[ SPLAT! ]
WELL,
I WENT TO TALK TO...
SPIKE!
HUH?
[ THUD! ]
YOU WENT
TO TALK TO WHO?
OH, UM,
I DON'T REMEMBER.
HEY, CAN I HAVE THAT GLOBE?
YOU'RE NOT USING IT, RIGHT?
HUH?
WHAT ABOUT THIS BOOK?
[ TINKLING ]
SPIKE,
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE USUALLY NOT SO...
GRABBY.
[ Deep voice ] MY ARMS AREN'T
USUALLY THIS LONG, EITHER.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
[ SMACK! ]
WELL, NOW.
WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM?
THIS IS SPIKE.
[ SMACK! ]
AND SOMETHING'S
WRONG WITH HIM.
[ SMACK! ]
HE USED TO BE
HALF THIS SIZE,
AND HE KEEPS TRYING TO
TAKE THINGS THAT AREN'T...
[ SMACK! ]
...HIS!
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S JUST HAVE A LOOK-SEE,
SHALL WE?
WITTLE GUY
NOT FEEWING TOO GOOD?
WHO'S THE BRAVE WITTLE BOY,
HUH?
WHO'S THE BRAVE ONE?
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK,
DOCTOR?
WELL, I THINK I KNOW
WHAT THE PROBLEM IS.
HE'S A DRAGON!
THAT'S NOT THE PROBLEM.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN A DRAGON!
OH, WELL,
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN IT.
LISTEN, I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT DRAGONS.
I KNOW ABOUT BABY PONIES.
MAYBE YOU
SHOULD TRY A VET.
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY, THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
HMM. WELL,
I'M FLUMMOXED.
YOU BRING ME A DOG, I'VE GOT IT
DIAGNOSED IN SECONDS.
SNAKE, EVEN FASTER.
BUT TO BE HONEST,
I NEVER SEEN
A REAL, LIVE DRAGON
BEFORE.
[ SNORTS ]
WHO'S A GOOD BOY?
SIT.
[ PANTS ]
THANKS, ANYWAY.
COME ON, SPIKE.
[ SQUEAK! ]
[ SQUEAK! SQUEAK! ]
[ WATCH TICKING ]
[ WHACK! ]
[ SMACK! ]
OOH.
HE IS STARTING TO MATURE.
OF THIS FACT, I AM QUITE SURE.
MATURE?
SO, HE'S JUST GROWING UP?
BUT THAT DOESN'T EXPLAIN
WHY HE KEEPS GRABBING THINGS.
[ TINKLING ]
A DRAGON'S HEART
IS PRONE TO GREED.
A STEADY DIET
TO MAKE GROWTH SPEED.
THEN THE RESULTING
BIGGER SIZE
ONLY MAKES
THEIR HUNGER RISE.
IF THIS TRAIT
SHOULD GO UNCHECKED,
IF SPIKE
CONTINUES TO COLLECT,
MORE GROWTH
WILL CERTAINLY OCCUR.
HE IS GOING TO
TURN INTO A MONSTER.
[ GASPS ]
YOU MEAN, THE MORE THINGS
A DRAGON COLLECTS,
THE BIGGER AND GREEDIER
HE GETS?
BUT HOW DO WE STOP HIM BEFORE
HE'S COMPLETELY OUT OF CONTROL?
[ CLATTERING ]
IF HIS MONSTROUS WAYS
YOU WISH TO IMPEDE,
YOU MUST PREVENT HIM
FROM PRACTICING GREED.
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
Sweetie Belle: GET AWAY
FROM HER, YOU BRUTE!
SPIKE WANT!
YOU'RE NOT
GETTING MY SCOOTER!
[ GRUNTS ]
SPIKE WANT!
Twilight:
HEY, SPIKE!
CHECK OUT
THIS AMAZING BROOM.
SPIKE WANT!
[ HISSES ]
[ GROWLING ]
COME ON, BIG BOY.
LOOK AT
THIS INCREDIBLE BROOM.
[ WHIRL! ]
SPIKE WANT!
[ CRASH! ]
FIGHT ALL YOU WANT.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU OUT.
OH, SPIKE!
I JUST RESHELVED
THIS ROOM.
[ TINKLING ]
[ CRASH! ]
OH, WHAT NOW?!
NOW, WHO IN PONYVILLE
WOULD STEAL MY APPLES?
FOR THAT MATTER,
WHO WOULD STEAL MY LEAVES?
APPLEJACK, HELP!
SPIKE'S RUNNING WILD,
AND I NEED YOU
TO LASSO HIM!
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, THAT'S A GOOD ONE,
TWILIGHT.
SWEET, LITTLE SPIKE
RUNNING WILD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT A LAUGH.
TWILIGHT, GET MY ROPE.
[ ROARS ]
HELP!
HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
DON'T TELL ME!
YOU -- YOU TIED YOURSELVES UP?!
GET US OUT OF HERE
RIGHT NOW!
Fluttershy: AAH!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT SOUNDED LIKE FLUTTERSHY
TO ME.
Twilight:
FLUTTERSHY?
FLUTTERSHY!
Fluttershy:
I'M UP HERE!
WHAT HAPPENED?
I WAS HELPING MY SQUIRREL
FRIENDS WITH A DANCE STEP,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
A GIANT RAMPAGING D-D-DRAGON
STORMED THROUGH.
THAT WAS SPIKE!
SPIKE?!
BUT WHY WOULD SPIKE
STEAL MY CHICKEN COOP?
HE JUST PULLED IT
OUT OF THE GROUND
AND FILLED IT WITH
A BUNCH OF APPLES AND STUFF.
Pinkie Pie: AAH!
THAT SOUNDED
LIKE PINKIE PIE.
COME ON, GIRLS.
BACK!
GET BACK!
[ SPLAT! ]
[ HISSES ]
[ GRUNTING ]
PINKIE PIE,
STOP GIVING HIM CAKE!
I'M NOT GIVING HIM CAKE!
I'M ASSAULTING HIM
WITH CAKE!
Spike:
[ ROARING ]
HOW DARE YOU
TAKE THE CAKE!
[ ROARS ]
[ CREAK! ]
HE'S COMPLETELY
OUT OF CONTROL!
WHO KNOWS
WHERE HE'LL GO NEXT?
[ HUMMING ]
PERHAPS SOME MORE RUFFLE.
AAAH!
[ SIREN WAILS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ROARING ]
AAH!
[ ROARS ]
PUT ME DOWN,
YOU BRUTE!
[ ROARS ]
HOW RUDE.
DON'T WORRY, RARITY!
WE'LL SAVE YOU!
PUT HER DOWN
RIGHT NOW!
I-IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND,
THAT IS.
I MEAN IT,
DRAGON BOY!
WE'LL BE
EVER SO GRATEFUL
IF YOU'D BE SO KIND
AS TO POSSIBLY CONSIDER --
DROP HER, SCALY!
Rarity: HEY!
I AM NOT SOME SORT
OF COMMON FLYSWATTER!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SPLASH! ]
GIRLS!
MY CAPE!
[ ROARS ]
LOOK! THE WONDERBOLTS!
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ROARS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ BUZZ! ]
[ SNORTS ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ CLANG! CLANG! CLANG! ]
[ GROWLS ]
[ ROARS ]
OH, BE QUIET.
YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
TO BE PROUD OF.
STEAL EVERYPONYS' THINGS,
TERRORIZE THE TOWN,
AND USE ME AS A WEAPON
AGAINST ME OWN FRIENDS,
WHICH, AS HORRIBLE AS IT IS,
I CAN ALMOST UNDERSTAND
BECAUSE YOU'RE A DRAGON
AND ALL.
BUT THIS?!
THIS IS A CRIME
AGAINST FASHION!
[ SNORTS ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
OH, NO.
YOU ARE NOT GETTING
THIS GEMSTONE!
[ GRUNTS ]
THIS WAS GIVEN TO ME
BY MY DEAR FRIEND
SPIKEY-WIKEY,
THE KINDEST, SWEETEST,
MOST GENEROUS DRAGON EVER.
AND IT IS TOO PRECIOUS
TO ME TO GIVE
TO A GREEDY, OLD BEAST
LIKE YOU!
Spike: HERE, RARITY.
YOU TAKE IT.
IT WOULD MEAN EVEN MORE
TO SEE YOU HAPPY
THAN TO EAT IT
MYSELF.
I-I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
THIS IS JUST SO...
GENEROUS.
MWAH!
[ RATTLE! ]
OH, WHAT NOW?!
I SUPPOSE YOU'LL BE EATING ME
OR SOMETHING.
[ CREAK! ]
SPIKE?!
YOU'RE
THE RAMPAGING DRAGON?!
[ ZIP! ZIP! ]
[ SCREAMING ]
SOMEPONY DO SOMETHING!
[ HONK! ]
ON IT!
[ YOINK! ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
RARITY, I NEED
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING,
JUST IN CASE
WE DON'T MAKE IT!
I'VE ALWAYS SORT OF
HAD A CRUSH --
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ GASPS ]
WE DID IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
[ CRASH! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
ALL IN A DAY'S WORK.
SPIKE, I JUST HAVE
TO TELL YOU
HOW ABSOLUTELY PROUD
I AM OF YOU.
PROUD OF ME?
YES.
IT WAS YOU
WHO STOPPED...
WELL, YOU, FROM DESTROYING
PONYVILLE.
YOU ARE MY HERO,
SPIKEY-WIKEY.
MWAH!
Spike:
DEAR PRINCESS CELESTIA,
TODAY I LEARNED A GREAT LESSON
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
WELL, YOU MIGHT THINK
THAT IT WOULD FEEL GOOD
TO GET LOTS AND LOTS OF STUFF,
BUT IT DOESN'T FEEL
NEARLY AS GOOD
AS GIVING SOMETHING SPECIAL TO
SOMEPONY YOU REALLY CARE ABOUT.
WELL, I LEARNED THAT IT TRULY IS
BETTER TO GIVE THAN TO RECEIVE,
AND THAT KINDNESS AND GENEROSITY
ARE WHAT LEAD TO
TRUE FRIENDSHIP.
AND THAT'S MORE VALUABLE
THAN ANYTHING IN THE WORLD.
WELL, ALMOST ANYTHING.
[ SMOOCH! ]
♪ MY LITTLE PONY ♪
♪ FRIENDS ♪